<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Guildfest 423 (2017)" id="6##">
  <node id="1" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>A clearing of deep green grass with well-manicured paths provides a perfect setting for a day at the faire.  Tents and wagons are visible in the meadowlands to the west, while an inviting deeply shaded vale lies to the east.</description>
    <position x="480" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bracken arch" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Fairegrounds Meadow" note="candy Barbarians|Glaes Spatula dishes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The fragrance of freshly mown hay is prevalent as the deep green grass of the clearing gives way to the fields where the faire is set up and in full swing.</description>
    <position x="300" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Fairegrounds Meadow" note="candy Moon Mages">
    <description>The hay is flattened for a nice walking surface here, only slightly marred by the wagon tracks of several merchants.  Dew collected in the ruts left by the wagons allows small bathing spots for the occasional bird.</description>
    <position x="200" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ticket gate" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Fairegrounds Meadow" note="candy Paladins">
    <description>The scent of hay is slightly dampened here, as it has been stamped down by the feet of the faire-goers.  A leaning fence festooned with ribbons and garlands provides an elegant boundary to the fields beyond.</description>
    <position x="300" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Fairegrounds, West Field">
    <description>Decorated with colorful pennants and flower garlands, a large branch arch welcomes faire-goers to the west field.  This expansive tract of land is relatively flat, making it easy for merchants to set up their traveling shops in ways that will lure people into purchasing their wares.</description>
    <position x="160" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Fairegrounds, West Field">
    <description>Waves of excited laughter drift over from the east, almost drowning out the mechanical drone of the Faeries' Wheel as it slowly rotates in place.  Periodically as the distant ride grinds to a stop, sounds of screeching metal are followed by nervous shrieks from people who are stuck in the top carriages swinging back and forth through the air.</description>
    <position x="120" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Fairegrounds, West Field">
    <description>Hay strewn paths dissect the broad field, encouraging faire-goers to travel in directions that take them past areas set up by visiting merchants as well as other festival points of interest.  Despite all the traffic, a small patch of pink lady's slipper orchids manages to thrive and scent the air with their sweet perfume.</description>
    <position x="80" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Fairegrounds, West Field">
    <description>Along one side of the path, makeshift stalls stand ready, waiting to safely house the valuable animals of local farmers that will be competing for prizes in the nearby ring.  Across the way, merchants display their wares in an attempt to entice faire-goers into purchasing new treasures from them and away from spending time viewing the well-groomed beasts once they arrive.</description>
    <position x="40" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Fairegrounds, West Field">
    <description>A split rail fence decorated with colored ribbons encircles the main exhibition ring, protecting the animals during shows from any over eager spectators and their excitable children.  In between competitions, workers rake pea gravel covering the ground, leveling it and cleaning up any stinky presents left by the beasts.  The shops of traveling merchants border the area's perimeter attempting to lure in people passing by.</description>
    <position x="0" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Fairegrounds, West Field">
    <description>Created by an underground spring, a small, tranquil pool feeds the brook that runs northerly through the fairegrounds.  Apparently collected from other areas on the property, large, flat rocks look purposely stacked to form a border around the water's edge, making it easier for travelers to water their animals or just grab a quick drink on a hot day.</description>
    <position x="40" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Fairegrounds Meadow" note="candy Bards|brook">
    <description>Sounds of laughter drift across a brook from the northwest, enticing to even the most stoic of faire-goers.  Spanning the brook are several large stones that serve as a way to cross the running water easily.</description>
    <position x="300" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brook" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Fairegrounds Clearing" note="candy Traders">
    <description>A mown grass clearing merges into a scythed hayfield, providing a level surface for the merchant tents and games.  Grasshoppers flick through the cut stalks, dancing to the rhythm of a distant troupe of merry-makers.</description>
    <position x="640" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Fairegrounds, Ring Toss Game" note="Ring Toss Game" color="#00FF00">
    <description>At one corner of the field, a stack of cloth-draped wooden boxes rests atop a sturdy table.  Tiers of glass bottles cover the surface, forming a pyramid.  The barker stands beside the display, juggling wooden rings as he calls out to passers-by, enticing them to try their luck at the ring-toss game.</description>
    <position x="700" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Fairegrounds Clearing" note="candy Commoners">
    <description>A gentle upslope leads from a stream-side willow grove to a rolling meadowland.  The beaten-down grass is strewn with hay, improving traction on the slippery, slanted path.  A cacophony of voices and smells accompany the sound of crunching hay beneath the feet of the revelers.</description>
    <position x="640" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Fairegrounds Clearing" note="candy Rangers">
    <description>Near the brook a small clearing opens to the sky.  The fragrance of damp clover and wild mint mingles with a cornucopia of faire smells drifting through the air.  Shrieks of delight, barking merchants, and the sounds of laughing children travel the distance from the hayfield and speak of some child's mischief or glee.</description>
    <position x="720" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Fairegrounds, Near Some Booths" note="Three Frog Monte" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A series of hastily constructed wooden shacks lean at all angles, supported only by their proximity to each other.  Before them, a barker cries out to passers-by, trying to tempt them into playing his game.</description>
    <position x="760" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="A Shaded Willow Copse">
    <description>A copse of willow trees in this grassy vale provides shelter from the weather for the weary traveler.  Bubbling over smoothly polished rocks, a brook creates a rhythmic rhapsody which harmonizes with the tranquil surroundings.  A boulder with a concave center looks like a nice place to sit alongside the brook.</description>
    <position x="640" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Muddy Streambank" note="candy Clerics">
    <description>A brook fairly bursting from its confines gurgles through the trees.  The banks have been churned into a muddy mess from the meandering faire-goers and from the children weaving around the makeshift gaming tables.  Paper lanterns hang from the branches of the willows just out of reach to provide a soft glow of lighting in the deep shadows.</description>
    <position x="740" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Fairegrounds Path">
    <description>The path slopes gently downward from the west toward a shady vale.  Willow trees cluster to shade the lower grounds, but one large specimen stands out alone at the border of the meadow, providing cool relief and quiet.</description>
    <position x="580" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>An arrangement of intersecting furrows in the once lush sod seem to be working their way easterly towards a stand of graceful willows.  A babbling brook flowing near the large, arching trees keeps them well fed and growing at a steady rate.</description>
    <position x="580" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>The neatly manicured grass is showing signs of wear and tear from the occasional shoppers who happen to stroll by.  Increasing blotches of a brownish yellow hue give the once green sod an appearance similar to that of a threadbare carpet that needs to be replaced.</description>
    <position x="520" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Fairegrounds Clearing" note="candy Warrior Mages">
    <description>This area of the clearing is a bit off the beaten path providing some quiet apart from the clamor of the milling crowds to the south.  The faint sound of an auctioneer's voice floats on the breeze, chanting of treasures for sale and urging prices even higher.</description>
    <position x="480" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas pavilion" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>A series of sandalwood caravans, spangled and beribboned, occupies most of the clearing.  Sounds of a large crowd murmuring in awe drifts from inside.</description>
    <position x="400" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandalwood caravans" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>Looking as if it once was attached to a roughly used farm wagon, a weathered buckboard bench now provides a quiet place where people can stop and take a break from the festival.  With faireground seating at a premium, some attendees seem anxious to look over the recent purchases they made while others just want to rest their tired feet.</description>
    <position x="580" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>Songbirds chirp their lilting melodies from secret spots hidden amongst the wagons and tents set up for the festival.  Occasionally darting out from the shadows, the tiny winged creatures swoop down to snatch a tasty morsel from the ground that was dropped by someone passing by.  After gobbling down their snack, they fly off to find another spot to safely resume singing for their supper.</description>
    <position x="500" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Fairegrounds Clearing">
    <description>Foot traffic increases towards the west, compacting the hay laid to protect the soil from erosion.  The straw forms cushioned paths between each merchant's areas, adding traction and assisting in drainage for those times when the weather refuses to cooperate.</description>
    <position x="440" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="A Cleared Field">
    <description>The mowed hayfield is decorated with ribbons and colorful paper lanterns.  To the north you see another long cleared field that appears to have been marked out with chalk and bright flags.  Large, moss-covered stones cross the brook to lead back to the fairegrounds.</description>
    <position x="160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brook" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="A Cleared Field" note="catapult" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The mowed field has piles of hay stacked all over.  Poles hung with colorful paper lanterns line the edge of the range.  Chalk lines have been put down and marked with numbered flags from one end of the clearing to the other.</description>
    <position x="160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Fairegrounds Entrance" note="Entrance">
    <description>A woven bracken arch festooned with ivy and flowering vines serves as the entrance to the fairegrounds.  People are milling about the entrance hawking their wares while small children run to and fro playing games and singing.  An air of frivolity and joy surrounds everyone present at the occasion.</description>
    <position x="480" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bracken arch" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go north road" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Faeries' Wheel" note="Faeries' Wheel" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The faeries' wheel towers over the faire, definitely one of the tallest structures to be seen.  The view from the top must be spectacular, a good place to see what other attractions await, or to snuggle with your sweetie.</description>
    <position x="180" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carri" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Faeries' Wheel, Carriage">
    <description>Securely fastened in, you lean back, anticipating the trip to the top with some trepidation.  The view promises to be spectacular, and the wheel looks sturdily made, but it is very tall.  The faeries' wheel worker seems quite competent, however, setting you somewhat at ease.</description>
    <position x="170" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="North Road, Farmlands" note="Map40_Langenfirth_to_Therenborough.xml|Therenborough|Langenfirth|North Road|Road|Mistwood Forest">
    <description>Row after row of tidily formed haystacks fill the field to one side of the road.  A fenced-in pasture borders the other side, and the hollow clonk of cowbells resounds as grazing cows occasionally amble over to the fence to peer at the stacks with interest.</description>
    <position x="480" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go field" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="A Cleared Field">
    <description>The mowed field has piles of hay stacked all over.  Poles hung with colorful paper lanterns line the edge of the range.  Chalk lines have been put down and marked with numbered flags from one end of the clearing to the other.</description>
    <position x="160" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="A Cleared Field">
    <description>The mowed field has piles of hay stacked all over.  Poles hung with colorful paper lanterns line the edge of the range.  Chalk lines have been put down and marked with numbered flags from one end of the clearing to the other.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="A Cleared Field">
    <description>The mowed field has piles of hay stacked all over.  Poles hung with colorful paper lanterns line the edge of the range.  Chalk lines have been put down and marked with numbered flags from one end of the clearing to the other.</description>
    <position x="160" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="A Cleared Field">
    <description>The mowed field has piles of hay stacked all over.  Poles hung with colorful paper lanterns line the edge of the range.  Chalk lines have been put down and marked with numbered flags from one end of the clearing to the other.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="A Cleared Field">
    <description>The mowed field has piles of hay stacked all over.  Poles hung with colorful paper lanterns line the edge of the range.  Chalk lines have been put down and marked with numbered flags from one end of the clearing to the other.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Imperial Pavilion, Reception Lounge" note="Imperial Pavilion|alterations|waiting list" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Lavish, burgundy brocades surround the spacious lounge with elegantly draping swags, each trimmed with golden satin tassels.  A trio of gaethzen orbs in filigreed holders dangle from velvet ribbons at the central peak, bathing the room in a soft glow.  Along the far wall are four curtains, beaded in crystals of vibrant emerald, sapphire, amber and ruby, each leading further into the spacious pavilion.  Clusters of plump cushions placed around the area facilitate a more comfortable wait for visiting patrons.</description>
    <position x="460" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas flap" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go emerald curtain" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sapphire curtain" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go amber curtain" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ruby curtain" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Imperial Pavilion, Emerald Parlor" note="Emerald Parlor">
    <description>Swathes of emerald-green satin sweep from corner to corner, the shimmering fabric spiraled with strands of tiny gold beads and iridescent seed pearls.  Placed at the back of the room is an ornately carved workbench of polished mahogany.  Conveniently set near the work area is a pair of brocade upholstered stools.</description>
    <position x="440" y="350" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go emerald curtain" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Imperial Pavilion, Sapphire Parlor" note="Sapphire Parlor">
    <description>Swathes of sapphire-hued satin sweep from corner to corner, the shimmering fabric spiraled with strands of tiny gold beads and iridescent seed pearls.  Placed at the back of the room is an ornately carved workbench of polished teakwood.  Conveniently set near the work area is a pair of brocade upholstered stools.</description>
    <position x="450" y="350" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sapphire curtain" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Imperial Pavilion, Amber Parlor" note="Amber Parlor">
    <description>Swathes of honey-amber satin sweep from corner to corner, the shimmering fabric spiraled with strands of tiny gold beads and iridescent seed pearls.  Placed at the back of the room is an ornately carved workbench of polished maple.  Conveniently set near the work area is a pair of brocade upholstered stools.</description>
    <position x="460" y="350" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go amber curtain" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Imperial Pavilion, Ruby Parlor" note="Ruby Parlor">
    <description>Swathes of ruby-red satin sweep from corner to corner, the shimmering fabric spiraled with strands of tiny gold beads and iridescent seed pearls.  Placed at the back of the room is an ornately carved workbench of polished rosewood.  Conveniently set near the work area is a pair of brocade upholstered stools.</description>
    <position x="470" y="350" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ruby curtain" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Display Room" note="Owirvald Auction Company">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious caravan, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  A pair of glass-topped display tables flank the opal-beaded curtain leading into the main hall.</description>
    <position x="370" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandalwood door" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" note="Auction Floor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="370" y="370" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="380" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="360" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="370" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <label text="Cleared Field">
    <position x="128" y="21" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Entrance">
    <position x="427" y="452" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to North Road">
    <position x="443" y="485" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ring Toss">
    <position x="675" y="164" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Three Frog Monte">
    <position x="764" y="192" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Faeries' Wheel">
    <position x="123" y="345" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="brook">
    <position x="208" y="145" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="catapult">
    <position x="112" y="132" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="West Field">
    <position x="13" y="211" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="alterations">
    <position x="428" y="331" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="auction">
    <position x="350" y="383" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>
