<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Hollow Eve Festival 443 (2022)" id="610">
  <node id="1" name="Andreshlew, South Dock" note="Dolphins|Invitations|Authorization|exit|entrance|south dock|dock|corral" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Overhead, sea plants woven into a mat spread from pillars of coral to provide shade for the visiting land folk.  Small glass and crystal globes hang from the pillars.  Underfoot, the smooth sandstone is decorated with coral, shells, and gold.  Columns and domes rise up from the water surrounding the dock.  Cargo is being brought in by Merelew workers and then stacked on the dock for sorting.</description>
    <description>Overhead, glowing crystal globes shed a soft green-yellow light on the dock.  Tall coral pillars rise from the sandstone to provide anchorage for the awning overhead.  The smooth sandstone of the dock is decorated with coral, shells, and gold.  In the water, glowing points of light give a glimpse of the true Merelew city.  Soft breezes blow through the pillars, and in the darkness, the sound of the sea murmurs unchanged.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go festive gate" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Andreshlew, Dock Extension">
    <description>Signs of hasty construction abound -- from the rough edges of the timbers to the occasional nailhead not sunk completely into the wood.  An awning has been erected on the west side of the extension, helping to shelter visitors from the setting sun while they await entry into the festival.  A small sign is tacked to one of the awning's poles, its painted lettering showing haste with the drips running down the front of the plank.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Andreshlew, Middle Dock">
    <description>Coral pillars rise from the sandstone of the dock to provide anchorage for a woven mat overhead.  The smooth sandstone slabs of the dock are decorated with interlocking circles made from corals, shells, and gold.  Crates soar in neat stacks, each labeled with the names of famous trading houses.  A few bear the seal of the Merelew, indicating that they are being shipped landside.  A group of Halflings moves cargo about.</description>
    <description>Coral pillars seem to twist upward in the soft green-yellow light of the crystal globes.  Underfoot, the dock is decorated with swirling patterns of coral, shell, and gold.  Neatly stacked in rows are boxes and bales of cargo.  Rising on the hill with the lights sparkling like gleaming gems in the night is the Merelew city, while gazing into the water more lights can be seen.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gallaenia" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="The Gallaenia, Fore Deck">
    <description>Deobar railings decorated with carved dolphins separate the polished ebonwood deck from the sea.  Rising from the central cabin is the ship's tall ironwood mast, standing with sails furled.  Access aft is provided by a pair of narrow walkways leading around the cabin, while a locked deobar gate blocks further forward progress.  A lone Halfling crewman works to apply a new coat of oil and wax to the deck.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go merelew docks" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="The Gallaenia, Aft Deck">
    <description>Carved deobar railings decorated with leaping dolphins line the deck.  Overhead an awning provides shelter for the crew to relax under.  The captain, who is sitting in an ebonwood chair inlaid with bits of shell and carved with flowers, watches five of the Halfling crew play a game of cards.  Hanging from the ship's wheel is a wine flask.  Forward access is provided by two walkways that lead around the main cabin.  The sound of waves provides a contrast to the calls of the crewmen.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="The Gallaenia, Main Lounge">
    <description>The silverwood wall panels are covered in fine sea foam-colored silks.  Around the room are couches decorated with carved motifs of shells, and covered in dark blue brocade.  Cedar tables, with chairs of ebonwood inlaid with bits of shell and covered in leather, are available for people to meet take up much of the remaining space.  The silver candleholders are all shaped like deobar trees.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silverwood door" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="The Gallaenia, Purser's Office" note="Bank|Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A large maple desk decorated with carved yaks and inlaid with the seal of the Zoluren Traders' Guild fills the office.  Seated at the desk, the purser is sorting notes into the pigeonholes.  Through the door of the next room can be seen Moon Mages holding open a moongate.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silverwood door" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Andreshlew, Upper Dock">
    <description>Traffic swirls in busy patterns across the dock as merchants, Merelew, and guests all meet here.  To one side sits the Customs Inspector's booth, closed for the festival.  To the north, a large building with onion-shaped domes rises over the city.</description>
    <description>Soft green-yellow light falls across the limestone and coral dock.  Crates, bales, boxes, and assorted cargo stand in quiet rows waiting for the dawn.  A coral booth stands to one side, silent and empty.  To the north, lights glitter and sparkle, while the sound of music drifts on the night breeze.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go guardhouse" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Andreshlew, Guardhouse">
    <description>Amid the warm glow of brass oil dish lamps, several gray-scaled guards in green uniforms inspect dossiers and polish and sharpen their weapons.  Maces and scimitars line the walls, along with multi-colored decorations for heroism.  A few also write reports, inspect cabinets for merchandise, and study a roster on the wall.  A Merelew guard captain looks on quietly, taking in all the activity without comment.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sturdy door" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Andreshlew, West Dock">
    <description>Cargo stands in neat array on the smooth limestone slabs of the dock.  Overhead, an awning made from woven, ornamental rugs stretches between pillars of coral, providing a measure of shelter.  Hovering among the stacks of merchandise, a Merelew merchant in green silks and an Elf in blue brocade bargain over an open box of pearls.</description>
    <description>The cargo stacked in orderly rows makes comfortable nooks and crannies to sit and view the Merelew city sparkling like a jewel in the dark.  Soft green-yellow light comes from crystal globes on the coral pillars.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Andreshlew, Palace Road">
    <description>The sandstone paving contrasts with the patterns of interlocking spirals made from coral, shells, platinum, and gold set into the road.  Low buildings of sandstone, decorated with coral and pearlescent shell panels, alternate with tall coral pillars along the route.  A basalt statue faces a marble statue across the way, the icons mostly ignored as passersby stroll north toward the Palace domes or south to the docks.</description>
    <description>The soft green-yellow light reveals two statues on either side of the road.  Low buildings line the way, a cool ocean breeze sighing around them.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hillside path" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cream-colored building" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood shed" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Andreshlew, Palace Road">
    <description>The sandstone road curves up the hill from the docks towards the Palace, avoiding a large coral garden edged with a low wall.  Both the wall and the road have been decorated with coral, shells, platinum, and gold set in abstract patterns, and coral pillars stand at intervals along the route.  A pair of statues frames the garden, across from a coral bench.</description>
    <description>The road curves up the hill from the docks and goes around a coral garden.  Green-yellow light from the hanging globes illuminates twin statues and pillars along the edge, where a low wall prevents casual visitors from wandering into the garden.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garden gate" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Andreshlew, Palace Road" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The onion-shaped domes of the palace rise over the coral and sandstone archway that stands astride the terminus of the road.  Standing before the archway is a coral tree, shaped like a great deobar.  Under the branches are benches for people to stop and rest.  On both sides are fountains of sandstone decorated with coral.  The sounds of the water gurgling in the fountains and of the wind blowing through the tree can be heard.</description>
    <description>The road ends at a sandstone and coral archway.  Soft green-yellow light shed from crystal globes illuminates a coral tree in the middle of the road.  The relaxing sound of water comes from fountains that edge the roadway.  Underfoot, the sandstone road is inset with square patterns of shell and coral, highlighted with platinum and gold.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandalwood caravans" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden" note="sharks|brine sharks">
    <description>A low gate in the wall allows access to the garden which is lined with paths and neat beds of coral.  Bright red rocks set out the edges of the plantings, their irregular outlines adding a pleasing note of informality to the setting.  Benches along the pathways allow for passersby to stop and admire the garden.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden">
    <description>A trellis supports some delicate coral formations that climb along the walls of the garden.  Nearby, a large stone bench is encrusted with some sort of relative of oysters, but not one normally encountered above the waves.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden">
    <description>Green coral rises from a bed, twisting into a spiral shape that reaches for the heavens.  Lower growths of coral grow in some other beds in this corner of the walled garden.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden">
    <description>Winding paths of crushed sandstone run between the neatly tended coral beds.  Stone benches are scattered about, allowing for the residents to take their rest in the peaceful environs of the garden.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden">
    <description>A lone statue stands in the middle of the garden, its features so worn from the passage of time that it resembles a large rock more than a humanoid figure.  Sculpted coral grows around it, carefully tended and cared for by the hordes of gardeners.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden">
    <description>This corner of the garden is full of twisted corals in a multitude of colors, all of them intertwined into a mass that dominates the area.  A few tendrils have escaped the borders of the garden beds and reach out into the pathways.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Andreshlew, Coral Garden">
    <description>Paths snake between the tidy beds of coral, lined with red rocks and carefully raked clear of debris.  The tall pink spires of coral twist overhead, forming arches and spans.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Andreshlew, East Dock">
    <description>Across the dock all is in disarray, as merchants open crates and boxes, sorting out their cargos.  Busy Merelew carry boxes and bales along the shore, while others haul crates up from the water.  Their task is made more difficult by a couple of still unmended holes in the dock that are covered by sawhorses.</description>
    <description>Neatly stacked crates line the dock, providing convenient access to the road.  Glowing crystal globes shed a soft green-yellow light across the dock, casting the coral into relief.  In the water, lights glitter, and the occasional ripple makes them dance.  A few holes in the dock are blocked off by sawhorses.</description>
    <description>Across the dock all is in disarray, as merchants open crates and boxes, sorting out their cargos.  Busy Merelew carry boxes and bales along the shore, while others haul crates up from the water.  Their task is made more difficult a hole in the dock surrounded by sawhorses.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark alley" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Andreshlew, Dock Walk" note="Peddler" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Crowds of eager visitors to the island file off the sandstone docks, which are decorated with shell and gold.  Some mill about in indecisiveness or awe, while others rush to see the fabled Andreshlew.  Kelp-covered pillars of limestone rise above the docks, thick ropes tied to them mooring visiting ships.  The road cuts a swath through the buildings of coral, leading to the heart of the city.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go octagonal building" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny shack" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go colorful boutique" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Andreshlew, Dock Walk">
    <description>A layer of pastel-shaded ocean shells is embedded in the brown sandstone roadway, creating a colorfully intricate mosaic of marine images.  Land dwellers teem over the roadway, though it shows no signs of wear, and many of them stop by the domed coral shops lining the street.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandstone building" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go overturned shipwreck" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black yurt" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small emporium" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Andreshlew, Dock Walk">
    <description>The rainbow coral blends together with the many pennants and banners of mainlander merchants to create a gaudy display to dazzle the eyes.  The intersection is filled with the noises of buying and selling, as shoppers haggle over prices and hawkers call out all they have to offer.  Blue-scaled Merelew merge with outlanders to create a virtual impasse of people.  Merelew guards bearing tridents and spears guard the merchants and customers.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white pavilion" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crimson tent" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lofty shop" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick building" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Andreshlew, Pearl Road">
    <description>Alongside the sandstone street is a massive pearl-laced oyster filled with bright silk cushions to provide relaxation to the weary.  Opposite the massive oyster, a large sandstone sea turtle statue stands looking passively at passersby.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted shop" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go web-covered wagon" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go web-covered ziggurat" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sturdy tent" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Andreshlew, Pearl Road">
    <description>A wooden structure rises above the street, the seaweed-covered building clearly once part of a ship.  The hulk is rotted away in some places, but has mostly been refitted, and an oak sign proclaims that it is now used as an inn.  The smells of exotic foods fill the air from within.  Carved upon the side of the ship is one word, partially obscured through time: Dolefaren.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elegant shop" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dolefaren" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white building" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow tent" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Andreshlew, Pearl Road">
    <description>Along the side of the road, a rugged coral promontory looks out over the blue depths of the bay.  Ships plow through the water, traveling to and from Andreshlew, as well as navigating to other locations.  On the far horizon can be seen the buildings of a city on the mainland.  Two gaping holes in the roadbed are blocked off by sawhorses.</description>
    <description>Along the side of the road, a rugged coral promontory looks out over the blue depths of the bay.  Ships plow through the water, traveling to and from Andreshlew, as well as navigating to other locations.  On the far horizon can be seen the buildings of a city on the mainland.  A small hole in the roadbed is blocked off by sawhorses.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green-painted hall" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glistening sandcastle" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver tent" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Andreshlew, Lithralia Street">
    <description>Standing at the roadside is a sandstone and coral building, its granite facade carved with images of sea animals like dolphins, gulls, and sharks.  A cinquefoil arch of gold curves over the structure in a graceful sweep.  On the corner stand two gold statues of Merelew, one male and one female, the tips of their webbed hands touching above the roadway to form an arch.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go boxy structure" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cozy shop" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden wagon" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Andreshlew, Lithralia Street">
    <description>A group of Gor'Tog men work at unpacking a sizable stack of wooden crates filled with goods belonging to mainland traders.  The bustling area is filled with garish merchant displays meant to attract customers and loosen moneybelts.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandstone hall" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Andreshlew, Shrine Walk">
    <description>The peristyle courtyard adjoined to the shrine of Andreshlew is filled with sea anemone and bright red and blue coral.  The elaborate pearl colonnade is decorated with pictures of Merelew lore, depicting everything from animals to Eluned herself.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby shrine" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gathering hall" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pink shop" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go snug cottage" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cramped boutique" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white tent" destination="342" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Andreshlew, Shrine Walk">
    <description>A small shop of red coral rests beside a lantern pole, the building covered with a pearl dome in a minaret shape, draped in barnacles and anemone.  A lone column stands in the center of the road, covered in seaweed and providing shelter to the Merelew, unaccustomed to the dryness of the surface.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white-marbled pavilion" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small barn" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go frost-covered shop" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gold temple" destination="340" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Andreshlew, Sinuous Shore Road">
    <description>Along the shore, the road is separated from the ocean by a low wall, which is dotted at intervals by pillars decorated with images of kraken.  A sandstone building topped by a low, onion-shaped dome stands on the northern side of the road, and more domes and towers rise across the water.</description>
    <description>Softly lit by a green-yellow glow, the road winds along the shore, buffered from the ocean by a low wall dotted with pillars.  On the north side of the road stands a sandstone building.  Across and under the water glitters a spectacle of lights.  The lapping of the sea against the wall and the rushing of wind among the coral carry far in the quiet night.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white cottage" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine shop" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flannel tent" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Andreshlew, Sinuous Shore Road">
    <description>On the west side of the road stands a wide building with an open courtyard.  In the courtyard a fountain carved with dolphins is visible.  The dolphin pattern is repeated on the building.  Opposite it a low wall blocks access to the ocean and pillars stand at intervals along it.</description>
    <description>Soft, green-yellow light fills the courtyard of the building on the north side of the road.  Standing sentry at the water's edge, a low wall supported by pillars at intervals, is decorated with a profusion of dolphins sporting about.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide building" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stucco cottage" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood shop" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stucco building" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Andreshlew, Sinuous Shore Road">
    <description>Two walls line the road.  The seaside wall is low and easy to look over but the landside wall is unbroken except for a closed wooden gate.  A pair of guards stands before the gate to turn away non-Merelew.  At intervals along the low wall pillars stand sentinel carved like twining tentacles.</description>
    <description>Walls rise up on both sides of the road.  The seaside wall is low and easy to see over.  In the landside wall a large gate is guarded by two Merelew.  Soft green-yellow light is shed from the globes on top of the pillars standing sentinel along the eastern wall.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white gazebo" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pink pavilion" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clapboard emporium" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rambling shop" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Andreshlew, Sinuous Shore Road">
    <description>The road stretches to a coral and sandstone archway flanked by two towers.  The northern tower is carved with dolphins, the southern with sharks, and the coral of the arch bridging the two is formed into a repeating pattern of flying albatrosses.</description>
    <description>The road stretches through a coral and sandstone archway flanked by two towers.  The northern tower is carved with dolphins, the southern with sharks, and the coral of the arch bridging the two is formed into a repeating pattern of flying albatrosses.  White light gleams from crystal globes on the towers' corners, offsetting the softer green-yellow radiating from the globes on the pillars.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coral archway" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shack" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go colorful bungalow" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entrance" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go yeehar-skin tent" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small shop" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>This end of the lane is shaded by several aquamarine coral trees draped with silken strands of flutter moss.  They frame a small building made entirely from the horned carapace of some giant crustacean.  Its translucent walls shade from cream to scarlet.  A sign spans the round doorway, held in place by the creature's enormous claws.</description>
    <position x="440" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick building" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go whitewashed cottage" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go colorful building" destination="343" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Lobby" note="Gift" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Creamy white marble walls streaked with blue surround the spacious entry hall of Andreshlew's premier artisans' center.  Underfoot, a tile floor surrounds a central mosaic which depicts the creation of the Merelew by Lemicus.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Registrar's Office">
    <description>High arched windows let sunlight stream in, bathing the creamy blue-streaked marble walls in a soft glow.  Standing behind a long marble counter and flanked by enormous filing cabinets, meticulously dressed clerks attend to incoming paperwork.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coralite curtain" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Item Registration" note="Registration" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Creamy white marble walls streaked with blue surround the large office space that is dedicated to the proper documentation of items.  Covered by stacks of forms and feather quills, a large alabaster desk dominates the room.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coralite curtain" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Lounge" note="Alterations|Lounge" color="#00FF00">
    <description>High arched windows let sunlight stream in, bathing the creamy blue-streaked marble walls in a soft glow.  Around the edge of the room close to a long glass table, wooden chairs are arranged in conversational groupings, their polished surface releasing a subtle fragrance of humble beeswax and the sharper tang of lemon.  Heavy mesh curtains in platinum, gold, silver, bronze, and copper lead to different workrooms.</description>
    <description>High arched windows let air in, and candles bathe the creamy blue-streaked marble walls in a soft glow.  Around the edge of the room close to a long glass table, wooden chairs are arranged in conversational groupings, their polished surface releasing a subtle fragrance of humble beeswax and the sharper tang of lemon.  Heavy mesh curtains in platinum, gold, silver, bronze, and copper lead to different workrooms.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platinum curtain" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gold curtain" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver curtain" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze curtain" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go copper curtain" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>Eleven oversized marble statues of heralds line both sides of the lane.  Made of white marble luxuriantly veined with gold, each stands poised with one leg thrust forward, a long-stemmed trumpet at its lips.  Tattered but colorful banners of long-vanished aristocratic houses flap proudly as they hang from the instruments.  Where a twelfth statue once stood is now a huge splinter of metal amidst a pile of marble chips.</description>
    <position x="340" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey building" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white shop" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black hall" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wool tent" destination="224" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Andreshlew, Suporni Tomerszentani">
    <description>A pair of garden beds, sunk deep in murky salt water, outline this twisty lane.  Each contains dozens of spare green spider ferns.  Their delicate, weblike leaves are bedecked with the watery jewels of misted spray.  An occasional snail crawls slowly through the branches, housed in a large shell covered with flowering yellow air blossoms.</description>
    <position x="340" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut wagon" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go enclosed gazebo" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Andreshlew, Suporni Tomerszentani">
    <description>Water-sodden areas to either side of the walkway are occupied by hundreds of cream-colored cowry shells bearing slender brown twigs.  Most are covered with red, trumpet-like blossoms.  An immense tree trunk, once oak, now driftwood, maintains a central spot in the lane.  Carved with arabesqued depictions of Dwarves battling forest-sized monsters, it has been covered with a lattice of copper designed to resemble stitched branches.</description>
    <position x="300" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rustic building" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak wagon" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Andreshlew, Suporni Tomerszentani">
    <description>Saltwater garden patches irrigated from somewhere out of view dot this region.  Each is home to a mixture of blue corals, white and black lotus pads, and delicate tufts of golden seaweave grass.  A couple of Merelew gardeners slosh their webbed feet through the heavy, wet sand, gently pruning and occasionally crooning in high, twittering tones to the life they tend.</description>
    <position x="300" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go aquamarine tent" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go enormous aquarium" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood wagon" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Andreshlew, Suporni Tomerszentani">
    <description>Watery beds of blue, campanular flowers surround a fluted alabaster fountain of heroic proportions.  Depicting some sort of meeting between River Elves and S'Kra Mur, it is carved to size, with nearly a dozen figures encompassed by churning waves and surging sea foam.  The circular base of the fountain is nearly as large and covered by writing in a cursive script.  It is apparently hollow, judging by the round doorway which is propped open.</description>
    <position x="340" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark shanty" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black yurt" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk pavilion" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Andreshlew, Suporni Tomerszentani">
    <description>A swale of sandy turf envelops the meandering lane.  Tussocks of seaweave grass display a wavering golden carpet, bordered by pink coral coaxed and nurtured into various animal shapes.  Dolphins bound, seahorses gallop.  Sea crabs extend rocky pincers forever above their shells.  A school of sculpted flounders loops a fanciful circle around a salmon-colored whale.</description>
    <position x="480" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pebbled path" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large hall" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cozy bungalow" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden chuckwagon" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tapestry tent" destination="248" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>The lane continues between two well-irrigated rows of luxurious purple mintweed.  Bristling like a head of thick Dwarven hair, the plant responds to the ministrations of several Merelew gardeners with a sweetly pungent scent.  In the middle of the area stands a brass gazebo with moss-green jade walls.  The unmistakable sound of clinking coins emerges from within, along with voices raised in occasional argument.</description>
    <position x="400" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black caravan" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rustic cabana" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hide tent" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas booth" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>A squat structure supporting a low, hemispherical cupola occupies the space to the north of the lane, opposite a massive copper bell.  The building is composed of bricks made from compressed shells, mortared with bright yellow amber.</description>
    <position x="200" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go otter den" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large shop" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick building" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elegant emporium" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="271" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan" color="Fuchsia">
    <description>The road slopes through a well-shaded region covered with massive blue and red lichen patches.  Their heavy growths have been carefully trimmed into broad, conical shapes, inset with pale glowstones.  The lichen bushes stir slightly, perpetually undulating from side to side, although no breath of air stirs within the area.  Beneath several specimens lies an eight-sided doorway leading into the earth, outlined in irregular glowstones that slowly shift between darkness and an angry red glare.</description>
    <position x="200" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark caravan" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go half-timbered shop" destination="286" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>A granite rampart rises almost vertically, its few jagged, rocky outcroppings occupied by nests built from salvaged seaweed.  Large grey birds swoop down to grab speckled tortoises as they cross the road, dropping them from on high to crack open their shells.  The splattered remains are carried aloft to hungry chicks that are hidden from sight, but very audible.</description>
    <position x="200" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cavern opening" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black hut" destination="287" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lopsided structure" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany wagon" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go makeshift wagon" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey building" destination="293" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Andreshlew, Saphtinagi" note="Undertaker|Grichye" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This sonorous cavern is lit by a flickering set of pale white globes, each securely held in a brass wall mount shaped like a taloned fist.  Gleaming, uncut sapphires protrude from every rocky surface.  Their gentian lustre invokes a moonless sky, when looking up at midnight is to risk falling into the soothing darkness.  A small crescent-shaped building made of translucent white crystal stands silent and majestic among the sea of gems.</description>
    <position x="200" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go side passage" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Andreshlew, Rubtanagi" note="Wierge" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Granite and iron ore have been chipped away from the walls, revealing imbedded veins of rubies in their natural, uncut state.  They vary in shade from the rose pink of Halfling gardens to the deep red of Elothean vinegar wine, to the magenta interlaced with black known as Teiro's Hate.  An oversized, reinforced brass door, recessed in one wall, is barred and shut beneath a guttering torch.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>Two walls of black granite latticework line the lane above massive blue sandbanks.  From behind the walls stare small, green-skinned children, waving webbed fingers, squealing and giggling.  Occasionally a child throws down a colorful, spinning, silver-winged toy at the heads of passersby, only to have it recoil swiftly into the hands of its owner before it hits.</description>
    <position x="40" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel-banded wagon" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go velvet tent" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick building" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Andreshlew, Falashtan">
    <description>The end of the lane is marked by a pitted, rust-colored obelisk made from some unknown creature's tusk.  An octagonal building stands alongside it, raised on top of eight short, marble columns.  The building is covered with blue floral mosaics imbedded within a golden background, and surmounted by a ribbed octagonal copper minaret that curves on high to a hooked tip.  From that hook depends a swinging bronze plaque.</description>
    <position x="20" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entrance" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go souvenir shop" destination="281" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Andreshlew, Raldtanagi" note="Fortuneteller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Emerald ore sparkles everywhere in this cavern: a dark, rich green that resembles the leaves of an oak at dusk's descent.  A pair of sputtering oil lamps provide dim illumination -- just enough to see a modest lean-to in one corner, built from slabs of quartz.  The structure appears weak enough to collapse with a strong sigh, but sounds of activity from inside prove otherwise.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Andreshlew, Suporni Kavmalitan" note="Drogor Shrine|animal shrine|critter" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A raised circular platform of fossilized bone marks the center of a giant starfish.  Five spacious, symmetrical arms radiate outwards, their surfaces smoothed into walkways.  Far to the north is a golden pavilion.  To the northeast is a blue tower made of several large spheres resting on top of one another.  The northwest arm leads to a smashed seacraft's hull.  A purple spire flying a scarlet flag lies further along the southwest arm, while the southeast one leads to a spiral minaret of black stone.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Vargsavo Utrem">
    <description>Large, twisted trunks and branches of brown coral flank both sides of the walkway.  Artfully covered with green flutter moss, they give the impression of living trees.  Jewel-like beetles fly lazily among the structures, seeking shelter in the myriad holes.  When settled they glance out, blinking surprisingly large, multifaceted sapphire eyes.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden wagon" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garish caravan" destination="296" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk tent" destination="298" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood tavern" destination="299" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crooked shed" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Vargsavo Utrem">
    <description>A giant, windowless spiral minaret of gleaming black brick rises over twenty feet in height.  In the center at its broad base is a reinforced bone archway, pointed with the grinning, bleached skull of a ram.  Within the archway is a recessed darkness unlit by any hint of movement or life.  A staircase snakes along the outside rim up to a flat rooftop.</description>
    <position x="20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch-framed cottage" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go electroweave tent" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pink structure" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron-domed building" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood shack" destination="344" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Bejana Utrem">
    <description>An abandoned handcart sits in the middle of this starfish walkway.  Its clamshell sales counter is empty.  One of its two oaken wheels lies broken off in the street and spinning freely.  A sign sits alongside it, defaced but still readable.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey pavilion" destination="319" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go felt yurt" destination="320" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany caravan" destination="345" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Bejana Utrem">
    <description>The partially decomposed hull of a shipwreck covers much of this area, its prow sunk deep in the porous but unyielding starfish exoskeleton.  Splintered masts and yards lean drunkenly upon the deck.  Flashes of sea breeze send the chipped side rudder and fragments of grey canvas flapping wildly.  An irregular doorway has been cut through the moss-enveloped hull next to a porthole.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go soot-stained building" destination="321" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go multi-colored structure" destination="322" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white pavilion" destination="323" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue shop" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Bejasavo Utrem">
    <description>Blue sandstone warehouses jostle one another on both sides of the starfish walkway.  Each features screened dome windows made of stucco, and decorated with cinquefoil tracery.  Friezes of rosettes run along the top of the walls, and surround the closed jalousies and gates of bolted copper.  One particular warehouse, slightly larger than the others, lies open.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black building" destination="334" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cozy shop" destination="335" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple wagon" destination="336" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go warehouse" destination="346" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Bejasavo Utrem">
    <description>Three enormous blue alexandrite spheres of diminishing size rest on top of one another, forming a bulbous tower.  At close range it displays partially eroded vine and scroll arabesques chiseled into every inch of stone.  A corroded iron banner displaying a seven-rayed star squeaks as it swings on a ceremonial spear attached to the second sphere.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go battered shack" destination="337" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fish-shaped tent" destination="339" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tower" destination="349" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Vargna Utrem">
    <description>The walkway is lined with a plentiful supply of granite chips, covered with glowing yellow algae.  Several sawhorses protect pedestrians from falling into a large gaping hole in the walkway.  Glimmering, golden-winged insects buzz about them, humming softly and exuding a slight scent of myrrh.  Andreshlew traders and officials stop in their rounds to admire them, breathing in the heavy air with evident delight.  Further to the southwest is a purple-domed spire, while a raised platform lies to the northeast.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white cottage" destination="311" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red barn" destination="312" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick store" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Vargna Utrem">
    <description>A curved spire constructed entirely from violet cinnabar dominates this arm of the starfish.  It has been carved into an endless, vermicular relief of stylized claws and dragons' heads.  Mummified arms and hands, swathed in indigo gauze, frame a diamond-shaped doorway.  A single lambent ruby occupies its summit, set in a wattled circular brass frame that resembles an eye.  Wide and round at its base and entryway, the spire swiftly narrows into a single, slender support that reaches for the sky.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go long wagon" destination="314" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="317" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cedar-trimmed bungalow" destination="318" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Beja Utrem">
    <description>A bronze open-air lantern sways gently at the end of a long chain attached to a pole, in this otherwise featureless section of walkway, sea, and expansive sky.  Its oblong dish is filled with an aromatic, cinnamon-colored oil, over which a purple flame dances with abandon.  The pole is made of pink alabaster, carved to resemble three youthful tree trunks entwined into a single column.  The chain is also alabaster, each link carved intact, embracing its neighbors.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elegant shop" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oilcloth tent" destination="333" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Suporni Kavmalitan, Beja Utrem" note="Vine|Catnip" color="Fuchsia">
    <description>At the end of this starfish arm sits a small rectangular pavilion resembling an oversized jewel box.  Its surface is inlaid with turquoise tilework, creating a massive curved eighteen-point star against a rich gold background.  False pillars with entwined vines festoon the corners.  They are covered in heavily dripping clusters of red grapes, made from embedded ruby chips.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="none" move="script hollowevevine" hidden="True" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Andreshlew, Cavern">
    <description>Granite walls rise from the sandy floor of the cavern, the walls slick with seaweed and barnacles.  A few small puddles remain from when the island rose above the waves.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cavern opening" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Andreshlew, Cavern">
    <description>Narrow walls enclose the passage that delves into the granite of the seafloor.  Puddles hold a few scuttling creatures desperate for the ocean to return.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cave opening" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Andreshlew, Cavern">
    <description>Granite layers give way to darker rocks as the passageway drills deeper into the ground, allowing access to caverns and grottos that are normally underwater.  A few bioluminescent plants cling to the walls, shedding a wan light in the area.</description>
    <position x="160" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Andreshlew, Lava Tube">
    <description>A tube that once held lava intersects with the downward passageway, cutting off further delving downward but opening up exploration of the lava tube.</description>
    <position x="140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Andreshlew, Lava Tube">
    <description>Twisting passages interweave in a complex dance of openings and obsidian walls.  Sand has been deposited on the floor, a reminder that this area is usually deep under the ocean.</description>
    <position x="120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Andreshlew, Lava Tube">
    <description>The lava tube ends at a large plug of basalt, the leading edge of a lava flow that solidified in place.  Sand has drifted against the plug, more evidence of the usual undersea nature of these passages.</description>
    <position x="100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Crystal Tunnel, Entrance">
    <description>Just within the entrance, a diffused light filters through the quartz walls to bathe the tunnel in a subdued glow.  The path slopes down from here, bending out of sight after a short distance.  A muted roar of rushing water echoes about the passage.</description>
    <position x="220" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tunnel opening" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Crystal Tunnel, Sloping Passage">
    <description>The slope of the tunnel lessens to a shallow gradient, making it hard to tell if it slopes up or down at this point.  Veins of crystal sparkle against the dark basalt walls, casting faint lights dancing about the dimly lit passage.  A deep roar of rushing water someplace in the distance makes the path vibrate beneath your feet.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Crystal Tunnel, Overlook">
    <description>A narrow ledge overlooks a huge crystalline cavern deep within the island.  Water tumbles noisily through a high opening, falling about fifty feet into a shimmering pool below.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Crystal Tunnel, Moldy Passage">
    <description>Slimy, rope-like roots cling to the walls of the passage to the north, covered by spongy mounds of damp mold.  The passage slopes sharply up, making travel difficult as feet go flying on the slippery surface of the tunnel.  Rushing water echoes about, the sound coming from a path which leads down into the darkness.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Crystal Cavern" note="Races|Tunnel Races|Crystal Tunnel Races|Water Tunnel Races" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This ceiling of this expansive cavern soars twenty feet overhead.  While not as large as the one visible from the ledge, it is no less spectacular.  The light from torches attached to the wall causes multihued sparkles to dance off large crystals and gemstones imbedded in the walls and ceiling.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Underground Caverns, Quiet Lake">
    <description>Water gushes out of an opening in the cave wall overhead, falling about fifty feet into a chilly underground lake.  The cavern sparkles as light plays off the water and the tiny crystals imbedded its walls.  A steep winding pathway leads upward to the north.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Sea Otter Smash, Den" note="Sea Otter Smash|Otter Smash|Otters|Shells" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Colorful chalk murals of sea otters foraging for clams, sea urchins, and other crustaceans cover the craggy walls.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Sea Otter Smash, Sandy Shoal" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Designed to imitate a sandy shoal off of a rocky coast, the walls are painted in blues and greens with wavy white lines to create a backdrop of undulating waves.  The fake marine room features a waterproof flooring covered in sand, and is filled with waist-deep water.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Stupid Terrestrian Tricks, Stands">
    <description>From this small amphitheater the stage is visible in its entirety, as is the registration booth and the waiting area.  Wooden bleachers have been provided for the audience's comfort, and the crowd has taken advantage of them.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go waiting area" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go registration booth" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pebbled path" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Bobbing for Lamprey" note="Bobbing for Lamprey|Lampreys" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Light creeping in from beyond the flap casts streaks of illumination across the room.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go leather flap" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Andreshlew, Dark Alley" color="Lime">
    <description>Poised at the end of an alley, an enormous crimson dragon lies, jaws agape, ready to snap up passersby.  Deep inside the fearsome beast's throat a silver door shimmers, dispelling the illusion and revealing it as the elaborate facade of some festival entertainment.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go east dock" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver door" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Crimson Dragon Gaming, Entry Hall" note="Crimson Dragon Gaming|Bingo">
    <description>Woven garlands of kelp decorated with pristine white waterlilies sharply contrast with the crimson walls of the entryway.  Driftwood arches lead off to the various gaming rooms and a stairway carved of sandstone spirals downward into the gullet of the dragon.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver door" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandstone staircase" destination="350" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Crimson Dragon Gaming, Swordsman's Hall" note="Swordsman's Hall|Deathdragon|Espeda|Reslo|Benane|Bingo 2" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Smoky torches create a faint bluish haze in the air of this long hall.  Coarse benches provide adequate seating for a legion of players.  Assorted weaponry decorates the walls, presumably tools to slay the dragon of gaming lore.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Crimson Dragon Gaming, Lily Room" note="Lily Room|Waerd Kweld|Yerro|Weysu|Nazma|Bingo 1" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Softly glowing gaethzen spheres are suspended from delicate silver chains about the room and highlight a central pond, nearly covered in bright lush waterlilies.  A smooth driftwood table, holding a supply of gaming materials, stands toward one end of the room near the caller.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Seat of Unification, Lobby" note="Factions|Faction Lounge" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A hub of activity, this hexagonal room features each faction equally represented along a wall.  Merelew come and go, briefly stopping to talk with one another before passing through.  Like all transitory spaces, it is marked primarily by clean floors and passably comfortable furniture that appears largely unused.  Festive kelp linen banners hang from the ceiling, which is set with a swirling pattern of blue-hued stones.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coral arch" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go metallic arch" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go living arch" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elaborate arch" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple arch" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go columned exit" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Lounge, Depth Shapers" note="Depth Shapers|Shapers" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Half completed sculptures and murals are arranged around the room, as Merelew dressed in functional work robes mill about.  While the most common medium is flowing shell and coral, stone, tapestry, and the occasional glint of gem or metal are also incorporated into the designs.  Some of the Merelew are busy working on projects, others passionately debating technique or expression.  Visible is a wide range of artistic representation, from the abstract and symbolic to exquisite detail and lifelike forms.  Scattered throughout the room are various imported artworks from the mainland, meticulously cared for and prominently displayed.  Etched into the far wall is an oval line.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coral arch" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Lounge, Trickling Sun" note="Trickling Sun" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Every surface is covered in life, ocean and air breathing represented in equal part. Thick vines cover the walls, tall cylindrical tanks hold schooling fish and stretching kelp, and open basins feature mussel covered rocks regularly misted with brine rising around open pools full of anemone, coral, crab and darting octopus. Several Merelew tend to the room, softly chiding uncooperative flora and fauna and praising new growth. A large stone platform at the center of the room displays a small piece of tomiek sealed in thick lead glass, and on the far wall, a large oval door is secured with thick kelp fiber ropes.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go living arch" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Lounge, Inverted Crucible" note="Inverted Crucible|Crucible" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The air reeks of chemicals, sour acids and bitter bases, the stench of sulfur and the yeasty tang of fermenting kelp. The sound of hammering and roaring fires can be heard echoing deeper into the building. A number of plain tables and benches line the walls, stockpiles of materials carefully sorted along shelves. One wall is clean slate, interrupted by regularly mounted cups holding dense chalk in various colors. The slate is covered in incomplete diagrams, sketched ideas, and mathematical or chemical formulae. On the far wall, a large oval door is secured with thick bands of shimmering steel.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go metallic arch" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Lounge, Red Fan Traders" note="Red Fan Traders|Traders" color="#00FF00">
    <description />
    <position x="240" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elaboratecoral arch" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Lounge, Supplicants of the Tide" note="Supplicants of the Tide" color="#00FF00">
    <description>An expansive limestone dome arcs high overhead, removed sections in a trifold symmetrical pattern forming a large skylight. The acoustics of the room are incredible -- there is no echo, but all sound is amplified. Flawlessly polished sapphire and quartz prisms hang from fine seasilk lines, gently swaying in errant breezes and casting dancing rainbows and spears of light along every surface. At the center of the room sits a softly smiling statue of Aluna, arms outstretched and webbed hands splayed wide. Numerous Merelew in simple robes gaze upward or at the figure in reflection, attending to the questions of guests in muted conversation. On the far wall there is a plain oval door secured with a thick basalt beam. </description>
    <position x="220" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple arch" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Limited Treasures, Lounge" note="Limited Treasures|Gortik" color="Lime">
    <description>Plush white carpet covers the floor from wall to wall, contrasting with the dark polished metal that creates them.  A pair of overstuffed black chairs sit to either side of a long charcoal-hued couch covered in throw pillows.  More pillows of various colors are scattered upon the floor giving customers a choice for seating.  A silversteel door stands across the room from another door ominously curtained with deathfiber.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silversteel door" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Andreshlew's Grand Raffle" note="Raffles" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Like a pebble dropped into a pond, concentric circles of blue and white tile spread forth from the heart of a wide pavilion.  The epicenter of the glistening wave is a white-marbled domed roof covering a small counter.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Andreshlew, Holy Shrine" note="Shrine|Holy Shrine" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Andreshlew's holy shrine, surrounded by its arching peristyle of pearl, contains an elaborate marble altar in the center of a colorful coral garden.  The garden, filled with coral sculptures of animals and rainbow anemone, is broken by paths leading to the altar, upon which is a finely polished gold statue of a Merelew male.</description>
    <position x="210" y="-330" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Andreshlew, Gathering Hall" note="Gathering Hall">
    <description>High overhead large beams support the roof of this airy structure.  Cozy nooks and seating arrangements are scattered about, allowing visitors to the island to relax and unwind before braving the outside once more.  Colorful rugs cover the polished stone flagstones of the floor.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit door" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Gaming Hall, Crown and Anchor Venue" note="Crown and Anchor">
    <description>Pale pink flagstones offset the deeper hued sandstone walls of the Crown and Anchor venue.  Oversized glass-paned storm lanterns hang from the vaulted ceiling and cast bright pools of light, creating a feeling of eternal day.  No windows are present to spoil the illusion of timelessness for the gaming enthusiasts.  Occasional loud cheers or anguished groans escape from behind the thick velvet curtains that seperate the gaming tables from the hall entrance.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go velvet curtain" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coral archway" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Crown and Anchor, High Roller Table" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Reflecting the shape of the table, the room is a little longer than it is wide.  Pale green tapestries line the walls keeping the noise somewhat muted and giving the strong impression of an underwater cavern.  Three sides of the table are open for players and observers to gather around while the fourth is blocked off by portable railings allowing the libik - the table master - plenty of room to oversee the game.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go venue" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Crown and Anchor, Table" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Reflecting the shape of the table, the room is a little longer than it is wide.  Pale green tapestries line the walls keeping the noise somewhat muted and giving the strong impression of an underwater cavern.  Three sides of the table are open for players and observers to gather around while the fourth is blocked off by portable railings allowing the libik - the table master - plenty of room to oversee the game.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go venue" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Crown and Anchor, Table" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Reflecting the shape of the table, the room is a little longer than it is wide.  Pale green tapestries line the walls keeping the noise somewhat muted and giving the strong impression of an underwater cavern.  Three sides of the table are open for players and observers to gather around while the fourth is blocked off by portable railings allowing the libik - the table master - plenty of room to oversee the game.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go venue" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Path">
    <description>Winding along the hillside, the gravel path twists among some coral trees as it works its way upwards towards a grove of kelp and coral.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go winding path" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Path">
    <description>Short strands of seaweed cover the hillside, taking the place of the grass that normally would be there for places that are not underwater most of the time.  Neatly maintained, the gravel path works its way up the hillside towards a grove of kelp and coral.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Path">
    <description>A three-way intersection of the gravel path clings to the hillside.  One way leads further up the hill, another goes to a grove not far away, and the last heads back down towards the city lying below.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go coral grove" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Path">
    <description>Rocky outcrops poke through the hillside, with the path working its way through the increasing numbers of boulders and rocks strewn in its course onwand.  The trail shows signs of poor maintenance, with spots of bare dirt showing through the gravel.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Path">
    <description>The path ends abruptly on the side of the hill, its cessation marked with a few abandoned tools and some piles of crushed rock.  A rotting barricade stands at the end of the path, blocking further passage up the hill.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Grove" note="Cloud Eels|Eels">
    <description>Towering coral pillars support limp kelp fronds while shorter seaweed varieties cover the ground under the tree-analogues.  Small puddles linger in the shade, remnants of the seawater that once covered the island.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hillside path" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Grove">
    <description>Although Andreshlew lacks trees, the massive coral growths fill much the same niche in the ecology.  Normally these towering giants would be surrounded by salt water, but with the raising of the island, they stand proud in the air instead.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Grove">
    <description>Confused seabirds flit through the coral spires, not understanding why their usual waves have been replaced with solid ground.  A few stands of seaweed hang down from the upper reaches of the coral, much like vines would in a terrestrial forest.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Grove">
    <description>Towering spires of coral meet overhead, much like a jungle canopy.  Long strands of kelp dangle from the spans aloft, their wide leaves limp in the unaccustomed air.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Grove">
    <description>Thick growths of coral merge into the hillside, effectively cutting off travel further into the island.  A few larger clumps of seaweed struggle to stay alive while exposed to the surface.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Andreshlew, Hillside Grove">
    <description>Scraggly growths of seaweed cover the exposed seafloor, each clump limp and drooping as they struggle to make it through the time the island is above the waves.  Barnacles cling to the exposed rocks.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Stupid Terrestrian Tricks, Waiting Area" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This temporary, three-sided structure acts as a waiting area for contestants, and as a place for the Mongers' assistants to loiter.  Near a water trough, a number of the stage crew mill about holding clay steins and chatting.  Periodically one slips though the stage door and back out again, nodding to his compatriots.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go amphitheater" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Stupid Terrestrian Tricks, Registration" note="Stupid Terrestrian Tricks|Terrestrian Tricks" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Monger Pyr Od'Lolg sits on a stool behind a narrow countertop lording over the registration list and watching the goings on with a careful eye.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go amphitheater" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Andreshlew, Cave" note="Hunting|undead merelew|decomposing merelew|lobsters|reefs|decapods|deadlight fish">
    <description>Walls eroded from water action, this cavern now stands empty of its creating force for a brief period.  Sand fills the crevices of the floor, while a few stray bits of seaweed lie forlornly about the area.</description>
    <position x="140" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cave opening" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Andreshlew, Cave">
    <description>A few clumps of seaweed cling to the rocky walls, their leaves limply hanging down.  Poking up from the sandy floor is the ribcage of some undersea denizen, its bones encrusted with barnacles and shellfish.</description>
    <position x="120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Andreshlew, Cave">
    <description>Sheer granite walls rise from the sandy floor, polished by water action to an almost unnatural shine.  Nothing clings to the walls as there is no crack or crevice to give purchase.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Andreshlew, Cave">
    <description>The ceiling slopes down to meet the sandy floor, effectively cutting off movement in that direction.  A few bones lie scattered across the floor, although what animal they came from is impossible to determine.</description>
    <position x="100" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Andreshlew, Cave">
    <description>The wide expanse of the cavern spreads out, the gloom hiding the walls from view.  Bits of flotsam litter the sandy floor, deposited there when the waters receded.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Andreshlew, Cave">
    <description>The smell of salt and the sea lingers here, drifting up from the pools of water that remain on the floor after the rising of the island.  A few drifts of sand make the footing on the cavern floor a bit treacherous.</description>
    <position x="120" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Andreshlew, Cave">
    <description>Coral spires reach from floor to ceiling, their sharp, spikey growth inhibiting travel in some directions.  Deep drifts of sand cover the cavern's floor.</description>
    <position x="140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Display Room">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious caravan, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  A pair of glass-topped display tables flank the opal-beaded curtain leading into the main hall.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandalwood door" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" note="Auction Floor 1|Auction 1" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opal-beaded curtain" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" note="Auction Floor 2|Auction 2" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" note="Auction Floor 3|Auction 3" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Owirvald Auction Company, Auction Floor" note="Auction Floor 4|Auction 4" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Rich sandalwood covers the interior walls of this spacious hall, its high-polished sheen reflecting the light from the various brass lanterns hung about the room.  Rows of leather-padded benches face the podium, offering a comfortable place to sit.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Tunnel Races, Waiting Pool">
    <description>This large wading pool appears to be fed by an underground stream.  The water is warm, possibly fed by hot springs.  Even in the shallow pool, the current is quite brisk, moving toward an opening in the north wall, where a metal gate is placed across the stream.  Apparently the starting gate is just one more room north.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Tunnel Races, Starting Gate">
    <description>You find yourself bobbing up and down in mid-stream, with others surrounding you doing the same.  You tread water, holding your position against the currents, as you wait for the starting signal.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="The Great Sea Battle, Ticket Booth" note="Great Sea Battle|The Great Sea Battle|Sea Battle" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Cool, humid air fills the area and droplets drape over everything in the area, living and inanimate.  Water pools in sunken areas showing all the places the ground is not exactly level.  A Merelew female stands in a booth to one side, her unblinking gaze sweeping the crowd for potential riders.  A brightly painted sign hangs above her head proclaiming, Tickets for sale!  People of all ages are gathered near another sign that contains further information on the ride.</description>
    <position x="0" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="The Great Sea Battle, Line" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Coral barristers mark out the queue as it snakes around in a repeating pattern of rows.  It is an extremely efficient use of the space but in a busy day the wait could be a few anlaen long.  The floor here is wet from riders getting off soaked then running around to go on it again.  A quick glance up and over the line of people waiting shows the loading platform for the boats.</description>
    <position x="0" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Minaret, Roof">
    <description>A one-room hut of thin white bone squats on top of the brick roof.  Torchlight flickers through a series of lancet windows.  A horseshoe archway frames an entrance, outlined along its length by writing engraved in flowing gold foil calligraphy.</description>
    <position x="40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Platinum Workroom" note="Platinum Workroom">
    <description>Bright sunlight and the scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide additional light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded platinum legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded platinum legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>The scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide bright light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded platinum legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded platinum legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platinum curtain" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Gold Workroom" note="Gold Workroom">
    <description>Bright sunlight and the scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide additional light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded gold legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded gold legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>The scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide bright light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded gold legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded gold legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gold curtain" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Silver Workroom" note="Silver Workroom">
    <description>Bright sunlight and the scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide additional light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded silver legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded silver legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>The scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide bright light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded silver legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded silver legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver curtain" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Bronze Workroom" note="Bronze Workroom">
    <description>Bright sunlight and the scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide additional light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded bronze legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded bronze legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>The scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide bright light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded bronze legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded bronze legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze curtain" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Saidakyp of Andreshlew, Copper Workroom" note="Copper Workroom">
    <description>Bright sunlight and the scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide additional light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded copper legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded copper legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>The scent of the ocean drifts in through high arched windows in the wall of the workroom, while gaethzen orbs hang in each corner to provide bright light.  Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded copper legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <description>Placed to the side of the room, a large marble table with gilded copper legs provides ample working space.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go copper curtain" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Don't Spill The Tea, Gazebo" note="Don't Spill The Tea|Tea" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Freshly painted beams create a spacious octagonal enclosure, leaving plenty of room between tea tables draped with pistachio cloths and high-backed chairs tied with peach bows.  Porcelain tea settings and three-tiered stands offer decadent fare to the patrons.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go egress" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Limited Treasures, Sales Floor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Polished to a gleam, dark metal covers the walls, ceiling, and floor save for a spot in the very center of the room where a silversteel stand sits upon a white velvet rug trimmed in silver.  A steel candle-covered chandelier is suspended exactly above it, the lights glimmering across all the metal surfaces.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silversteel door" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Two Doors Down, Salesroom" note="Two Doors Down" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pale cream walls are trimmed with matching painted baseboards and crown molding, giving a subtle warmth to the shop.  That radiance is enhanced by the oil lamps hanging from the ceiling.  The expensive merchandise is displayed on hinged mounts, allowing purchasers to examine each offering on both sides.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted hatch" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Capture the Bag, Shop" note="Capture the Bag" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Planks of weathered driftwood line the walls although there are a number of gaps between the slabs.  Everything has a ramshackle look except for the merchandise offered on the driftwood displays covering the bare earth floor.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood door" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Sumptuous Silks, Main Showroom" note="Sumptuous Silks" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The walls of this octagonal room are covered with eight panels of thick rice paper, held in place by bamboo frames.  Thousands of folds made into each piece of paper create a hazy visual effect in the masterful paintings of sunset upon the Lake of Tears, rendered in vivid watercolors.  A dramatic marbled gaethzen orb hangs overhead, reflected by the polished metal of the dome above.  Mannequins are arranged neatly around the area.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel doorway" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk-draped doorway" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Sumptuous Silks, Bamboo Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Long strips of bamboo cover the walls and frame the doorway in and out of this room.  Layers of reed and cork mats line the floor here, in an apparent effort to create a quiet atmosphere.  Arranged neatly around the room are some dragonwood mannequins with a marble pedestal in the center and a lacquered rack standing along one wall.  A dramatic marbled gaethzen orb hangs overhead, the pale glow illuminating everything with soft light.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk-draped doorway" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="ArtSea Gifts and Souvenirs, Main Room" note="ArtSea Gifts" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Although as tiny inside as it appeared from the outside, this diminutive shop is bursting with merchandise.  Shelves line the walls and racks are stuffed into every corner.  Hooks hanging from the ceiling allow for even the narrow aisleways to display wares for the discriminating tourist.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny door" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Hot Tropics, Sunkissed Sands" note="Hot Tropics" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sunlight streams through the avodire-framed windows and open doorway of this spacious room, highlighting the colorful shells arranged in an intricate swirl across the tall walls.  A tufted rug is stretched over the mottled yellow wooden floorboards.  Colorful sundresses and sarongs hang on metal racks arranged around the room.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go avodire-framed door" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Hot Tropics, Shifting Seas" color="#FF0000">
    <description>White cumulus clouds painted along the top of the bright sky-blue walls shimmer under the warm candlelight like fluffy tufts of cotton caught on an errant sea breeze.  The pale yellow ayabere floors are polished to a high shine to best display the wood's natural mottling.  Various wares are displayed atop a trio of tables in the middle of the room.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Salvage Finds of the Reshal Sea, Shop Floor" note="Salvage Finds" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Fashioned from an upturned ironwood galley once wrecked along the sea floor, the vessel has been repurposed into a freestanding structure using reclaimed oaken driftwood nailed to the hull.  Gaethzen lamps dangle from closed portholes, swaying freely.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open hatch" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="The Naked Sheep, Woolly Wears" note="Naked Sheep" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Fluffy and soft, swaths of thick cream-colored fleece coat every side of the cozy room.  The theme continues along the floor in the form of a puffy black carpet that stretches underneath several trunks and chests full of goods for sale.  Warm but not stifling, the air holds a faint musty scent from all the fabric, which the merchant has apparently tried to smother with dozens of freshly potted flowers placed in the room's corners.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black door" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="The Naked Sheep, Fuzzy Fluff" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Puffy as a cloud, the fleece along the walls retains its natural beige hue, arranged in swaths that drape casually along the slanting sides of the homely nook.  The woolly black carpet extends into this section of the tent as well, lining the floor beneath a collection of opened boxes.  Stationed in one corner is a brass sheep sculpture with a look of embarrassment on its face, the surface of its skin cleanly smooth to mimic its strikingly shorn real life counterparts.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="A Second Round, Tent" note="Second Round" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dingy canvas walls encircle a floor of uneven pine planks.  A few spots of mold or mildew spread across the fabric, adding a note of mustiness to the still air.  A few battered tables hold the merchandise which is heaped up with no sign of organization.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Tighten Up!, Salesfloor" note="Tighten Up" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Bare whitewashed walls accentuate the wild colors and patterns of the merchandise displayed on shelves and counters.  A few free-standing racks in the center of the room hold more wares for the milling customers to peruse and purchase.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tall door" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Clothes By Any Other Flame, Showroom" note="Clothes by Any Other Flame|Any Other Flame" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The canvas walls are painted a brilliant red, similar to the shade of a leaping flame.  The wooden racks and shelves that hold the merchandise are colored in the same hue, while the floor is planks of broad pine.  Helpful salespeople circulate through the crowds, answering questions and making sales.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Trees Four Walls, Showroom" note="Trees Four Walls" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Large mockups of walls hang from the rafters, allowing the patrons to view the various offerings from a variety of distances.  The deep pile carpet on the floor muffles most sounds, helping to foster the mood of quiet contemplation amongst the shoppers.  The saleshelp unobtrusively circulates and are ready to answer questions or place orders.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tall door" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Inkspressions, Written Wonders" note="Inkspressions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pale green walls stenciled with twining ivy enclose this spacious room, and a deep blue rug covers the majority of its goldenoak floor.  Gaethzen lanterns hang from the ceiling to illuminate the tables and stands displaying wares for sale.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slender door" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="A Walk on the Wild Side, Salesroom" note="Walk on the Wild Side" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Random splashes of variegated colors cover the paneled walls, brightening the room with vivid hues.  Simple shoe racks made from polished woods are stationed about the room, allowing easy inspection of the wares.  More shoes are displayed on a pine shoe tree positioned in the middle of the wooden flooring.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted door" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Arachnomancy, Advent" note="Arachnomancy" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Surprisingly roomy, this wagon is the most spacious of the three, providing ample room for dramatic demonstrations.  Spidersilk tapestries drape the wooden walls, concealing the patina of age.  Doorways to the east and west provide access to the adjacent wagons.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wagon door" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Arachnomancy, Incantation" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A constellation of tiny gaethzen spiders provides just enough light to see, while heavy spidersilk carpets muffle the footsteps of customers and onlookers.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Arachnomancy, Departure" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spiders dangle from the ceiling, perhaps providing a little too much illumination.  The walls are shrouded by thick sheets of spidersilk, each of which is crawling with thousands of tiny spiders.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Accents for the Arachnophile, Jewels and Accessories" note="Accents for the Arachnophile|Arachnophile" color="#FF0000">
    <description>At first glance, this room appears to be nothing more than the den of a giant, demented spider.  The wan light of a single gaethzen lantern dangling from a chain in the ceiling illuminates somber metal walls festooned with a drapery of webbing.  Thick curtains of the silky white strands droop low from the ceiling, making it difficult to navigate without becoming entangled.  Fortunately, the webs are only slightly sticky and refuse to cling excessively to those brave enough to enter.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go web-covered doorway" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Accents for the Arachnophile, Clothe and Carry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>At first glance, this room appears to be nothing more than the den of a giant, demented spider.  The wan light of a single gaethzen lantern dangling from a chain in the ceiling illuminates somber metal walls festooned with a drapery of webbing.  Thick curtains of the silky white strands droop low from the ceiling, making it difficult to navigate without becoming entangled.  Fortunately, the webs are only slightly sticky and refuse to cling excessively to those brave enough to enter.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Accents for the Arachnophile, Offense and Defense" color="#FF0000">
    <description>At first glance, this room appears to be nothing more than the den of a giant, demented spider.  The wan light of a single gaethzen lantern dangling from a chain in the ceiling illuminates somber metal walls festooned with a drapery of webbing.  Thick curtains of the silky white strands droop low from the ceiling, making it difficult to navigate without becoming entangled.  Fortunately, the webs are only slightly sticky and refuse to cling excessively to those brave enough to enter.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Accents for the Arachnophile, Hearth and Home" color="#FF0000">
    <description>At first glance, this room appears to be nothing more than the den of a giant, demented spider.  The wan light of a single gaethzen lantern dangling from a chain in the ceiling illuminates somber metal walls festooned with a drapery of webbing.  Thick curtains of the silky white strands droop low from the ceiling, making it difficult to navigate without becoming entangled.  Fortunately, the webs are only slightly sticky and refuse to cling excessively to those brave enough to enter.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="To The Hammer Born, Salesfloor" note="To The Hammer Born|Hammer" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Racks and stands displaying the merchandise are scattered across the plain plank floor.  The hide walls of the tent occasionally move slightly in the breeze, but little else disturbs the customers as they browse the selection of weapons on offer.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Everlasting Beauty, Foyer" note="Everlasting Beauty" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Clean and inviting, this spacious beauty shop reflects a magical merging of nature's beauty and versatility.  Durian wood flooring and smooth peach walls encompass the vast room.  The large mirror affixed to the wall allows the shoppers a place to admire their beauty.  A sizeable handmade tapestry on one wall depicts a colorful forest.  Goldwood furniture pieces fill the room displaying a wide variety of cosmetics and supplies.  An intricately carved door leads outside while a small arch leads to another room.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small arch" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go apricot door" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Everlasting Beauty, Parlor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Clean and inviting, this spacious beauty shop reflects a magical merging of nature's beauty and versatility.  Durian wood flooring and amber walls encompass the vast room.  The large mirror affixed to the wall allows the shoppers a place to admire their beauty.  Goldwood furniture pieces fill the room displaying a wide variety of hair and beauty supplies.  A small arch leads back to the main room.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small arch" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="The Dolefaren, Common Room" note="Dolefaren|Inn" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The dim interior of the ship is lit by scattered brass lanterns hanging along the walls.  A Merelew woman with green hair and silver scales serves the delicacies of her people to the restaurant's guests at several wood tables.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Affair of the Art, Salesfloor" note="Affair of the Art" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the colors provided by the merchandise, the room is an unrelieved white - white walls, white floors, white ceilings, and white counter.  Large empty spaces between the artworks allow for each piece to be properly appreciated without distractions from other works.  Gaethzen globes provide a steady and safe lighting for all the wares.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Fit to be Tied, Shop" note="Fit to be Tied" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the canvas walls and the wooden racks, this narrow space is lacking in decoration.  The only color comes from the brilliant shades of the merchandise on the racks scattered about.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Tool as a Cucumber, Forging Supplies" note="Tool as a Cucumber|Cucumber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sea green silk walls enclose the room, which is floored in wide planks painted a matching shade of green.  Cream-colored rugs cover the floor upon which scattered racks, tables, and shelves stand displaying the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green-painted door" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Tool as a Cucumber, Engineering Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Forest green silk walls enclose the room, which is floored in wide planks painted a matching shade of green.  Alabaster-colored rugs cover the floor upon which scattered racks, tables, and shelves stand displaying the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Tool as a Cucumber, Dyes" note="Dyes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Multi-colored silk walls enclose the room, which is floored in wide oaken planks.  Various colored bins are scattered around the room, showing the multitude of dyes available for purchase.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Tool as a Cucumber, Enchanting Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Jade green silk walls enclose the room, which is floored in wide planks painted a matching shade of green.  Bone-colored rugs cover the floor upon which scattered racks, tables, and shelves stand displaying the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Tool as a Cucumber, Alchemy Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Olive green silk walls enclose the room, which is floored in wide planks painted a matching shade of green.  Ivory-colored rugs cover the floor upon which scattered racks, tables, and shelves stand displaying the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Tool as a Cucumber, Outfitting Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Moss green silk walls enclose the room, which is floored in wide planks painted a matching shade of green.  Snow-colored rugs cover the floor upon which scattered racks, tables, and shelves stand displaying the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Siegery Shop, Soldiers" note="Siegery Shop|Soldiers" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Detailed maps of Ilithi's different roads and towns are painted on the walls.  The largest map depicts the city of Shard and the deep blue of the lake around it.  Two long tables of polished wood fill the floor space, while a thick black rug spreads from corner to corner.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandy arch" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Siegery Shop, Castles and Cases" note="Castles and Cases" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rendered in precise detail upon the walls are maps of Therengia's cities and towns.  Stately Therenborough takes up a whole wall, complete with an inner view of The Keep's hallways and rooms.  A trio of black tables rest upon a matching rug.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Tower of Terror, Shop" note="Tower of Terror" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sturdy racks and stands holding the merchandise are scattered around the shopfloor.  Careful lighting throws spotlights on the various items and draws attention to the exquisite craftsmanship on display.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Familiar Treats, Inside" note="Familiar Treats" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Blocks of glittering sand create a boxy room with an inviting, open space.  Starglass sconces have been strategically positioned to highlight sales displays spaced around the room.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open doorway" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="In The Snow, Outerwear" note="In The Snow" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain white wainscotting runs along the walls, dividing the white plastered top from the blue painted bottom.  Oak planks provide the floor which has a number of racks painted in various shades of blue scattered across it.  Iron sconces hold gaethzen spheres which illuminate the room and the merchandise displayed on the racks.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted door" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Gift Me Up, Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A multitude of shelves and racks hold a variety of merchandise and goods for sale.  The whole shop is stuffed with items and the floor is piled with baskets and bins of overflow items.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wagon door" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="The Pink Pirate's Plunder and Pillage Palace, Anteroom" note="Pink Pirate's Plunder" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Done in many shades of pink, the room is a riot of shades and tones, with the walls painted a dark rose shade that clashes with the brilliant petal pink of the floors.  Standing in the middle of the room is a mannequin dressed in an outrageous outfit composed of piratical garb in a range of hues, but all of them variations of one color - pink.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pink door" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="The Pink Pirate's Plunder and Pillage Palace, Weapons etc." color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pine planks painted a pulsating shade of pink cover the walls and the floor is painted the palest of rosy hues.  Standing throughout the room are a few stands and weapon racks displaying the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="The Pink Pirate's Plunder and Pillage Palace, Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Racks and shelves cover the walls and floors, displaying a variety of garb and garments.  Stands and counters display accessories for purchase.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Granny's Knot Spot, Cozy Shop" note="Granny's Knot Spot" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A rocking chair sits next to the fireplace, a basket of knitting beside it on the floor.  The whitewashed stone walls hold wooden shelves while some wooden racks and stands are scattered about the floor.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sturdy door" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Unique-corn, Salesfloor" note="Unique-corn|Unique corn|Unicorn" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Oak shelving lines the walls, displaying the varied wares of the shop.  Globes filled with gaethzen dangle from the ceiling, providing illumination for the customers.  Clerks bustle about refreshing the merchandise supply and answering shoppers' questions.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Bought The Farm, Front Room" note="Bought The Farm" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Broad planks cover the walls, their surfaces and edges only roughly finished.  Bits of straw are strewn across the floor, escapees from the bales used to display some of the shop's wares.  More planks are cobbled together with some poles to form a rickety shelf that displays further merchandise.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go barn door" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="A Quick Bite, Salesroom" note="Quick Bite" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Something keeps this room perpetually chilly, almost the temperature of an icehouse on a summer day.  Gleaming metal walls contrast with the warmth of the hand-polished wooden racks displaying the shop's wares.  A butcher block counter stands in one corner.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Glam and Gritty, Anteroom" note="Glam and Gritty" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Elegant ebony cabinets display wares behind slightly grimy glass doors.  The polished wood of the floors shines through the occasional patch of scuffing that really could use some cleaning.  A brass and glass chandelier hangs from the ceiling, its perfection only slightly marred by a small spiderweb run between two of the candleholders.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebony door" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Glam and Gritty, Main Floor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The dark ebony floors contrast with the pale, almost white, wood of the birch paneling on the walls.  Matching ebony shelves are set slightly askew on the walls, almost as if the builders were in too much of a hurry to actually make sure they were level.  A few dust bunnies lurk in the corners, having escaped the lackluster cleaning of the salesforce.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Glam and Gritty, Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tucked into a corner are a couple of brooms, the dust and cobwebs covering them a mute testimony to how little use they see.  A few scuffed storage boxes litter the floor, the lids leaning against them while they spill packing straw around the floor.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Wally's World of Walls, Salesfloor" note="Wally's World of Walls" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain pine planks form the interior walls of this minimalist showroom.  The deliberate lack of decoration throughout the room is designed to emphasize the exotic woods and flamboyant patterns of the merchandise samples displayed throught the store.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Sleepwalkers, Salesroom" note="Sleepwalkers" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Soft flannel drapes and plush cushions surround the area, inviting patrons to curl up for a nap after putting on their new purchases.  Piles of folded pajamas in assorted patterns and colors mound over a large, padded table, while two baskets nearby are full of fluffy foot coverings.  A padded shelf hangs on the wall, opposite the curtain.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flannel curtain" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Hero To Go, Supplies" note="Hero to Go" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Maps, sketches and paintings from all over Elanthia cover the plastered walls.  One wall is entirely taken up by a mural of an erupting volcano while a large model of a mechanical dragon hangs from the ceiling.  Opposite the mural, a gilded frame displays pressed phofe flower specimens next to a very large sign.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit door" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Hero To Go, Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Unlike the first room of the shop, this one is bare of anything but merchandise and the displays for the merchandise.  Plastered walls hold some shelves and hooks, while the floor is crowded with racks and stands for wares.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Natural Beauty, Sales Floor" note="Natural Beauty" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Thick tapestries depicting a dense, wild forest surrounding a picturesque glade cover the walls, each blending seamlessly into the next.  The tall ceiling painted to resemble a cloudless summer sky features a gaethzen sun positioned directly in the center.  Polished driftwood furniture set up around the room displays a wide variety of garments available for sale.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ayabere door" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood arch" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Natural Beauty, Special Occasions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth metal walls painted to resemble a nighttime garden seem to almost disappear beneath the layered colors.  Swirled blues and purples adorn the blackened ceiling, fading down to brush the tops of the foliage with their velvety embrace.  Tiny, glowing pieces of gaethzen dot the mural, from fireflies amongst the flowers to stars laboriously placed to recreate constellations, providing a diffuse but adequate source of light by which to examine the shop's surfaces.  A stylish aybere jewelry case and polished driftwood counter display a wide range of goods for sale.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood arch" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Altered Reactions" note="Altered Reactions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The aroma of analgesic ointments and smelling salts waft all around you, testament to the 'research' that occurs under this enterprise.  Hanging curtains separate the room into private testing chambers, though the sounds of hands clapping against faces and the elicited response are muted by cleverly arrayed wall coverings.  A series of locked doors line one wall, and attendants rush about soothing bruised faces and egos.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go teak doorway" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Killer Pinks, Fatally Aggressive" note="Killer Pinks" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coralite lanterns dangle freely from petalette cords strung across the high ceiling and cast a pinkish-gold light across the glossy black floor.  The ricepaper walls are vertically striped in shades of mauve and cream, each lined with coralite hooks bearing various bows and crossbows.  Narrow tables shoved into the corners display additional weapons available for purchase.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elegant archway" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Killer Pinks, Define Outcomes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Lengths of peachy-pink spun glitter cover the room's walls, their metallic threads shimmering beautifully beneath the soft light cast by an ornate coralite chandelier hanging from the center of the room.  Freestanding mannequins are artfully arranged across the bright pink floor to highlight their wares.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Shimmers of Silver" note="Shimmers of Silver" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Despite the rather small confines of this long, narrow hall, careful attention has been given to the expensive-looking decorations.  The white walls prominently showcase several small glass windows that look into elegant sculptures of colored glass, and bright lighting in the ceiling of their small cabinets shines onto the the works of art.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="A Knight at the Club, Entry" note="Knight at the Club" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A few benches along the walls provide seating for those who need a break from shopping.  Warm light from the hanging brass chandelier spreads throughout the entry, making the polished oak floors gleam.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="A Knight at the Club, Outerwear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Spread out around the room are wooden racks and stands displaying a wide variety of outerwear.  Rushing salesclerks move about, answering questions and restocking clothing.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="A Knight at the Club, Legwear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Piles of clothing are stacked up on shelves and counters, ready for purchase by customers.  Smiling clerks answer questions and help the buyers with their other requirements.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="A Knight at the Club, Doublets and Shirts" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Garments hang from the racks and stands around the room, their colorful fabrics and trims dazzling to the eye.  Cheerful salespeople roam about, ready to answer questions or get a different item from the stockroom.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="A Knight at the Club, Jewelry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Glass cases and cabinets along the walls offer up jewelry and other adornments for perusal and purchase.  Several armed guards stand in the corners, their gimlet eyes keeping the customers under watch to prevent theft.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="A Knight at the Club, Accessories" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A long walnut counter displays accessories and other extras for purchase.  A few bins and baskets on the floor provide extra display space for further items.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="A Knight at the Club, Gowns and Robes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Long racks of robes and gowns line the walls, their wooden poles almost groaning under the weight of the merchandise.  The quiet murmur of voices fills the air as customers debate their purchases.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Carpin Capers, Main Room" note="Carpin Capers" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Colorful walls in all the shades of the rainbow hold a few shelves with merchandise.  Hanging from the rafters are a number of bells made of different metals and finishes.  Several lanterns also hang from the rafters, providing illumination for the entire room.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go colorful door" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="The Future is Now, Armillary Sphere" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Contained within the gargantuan iron sphere that forms this chamber are dozens of massive brass rings connected to a globe via a thick central axis.  Ceaselessly, the rings twirl and spin about in silent harmony, no two plotting the same course.  Prominently featured upon each is a limelight which collectively casts a multihued kaleidoscope of illumination about the room.  A particularly wide ring slowly plots a course that offers customers a relatively safe path between the entrance and exit of the shop proper.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entrance" destination="348" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Hashal's Haven" note="Hashal's Haven" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Surprisingly roomy and well appointed, the interior of the tent is draped in lavish tapestries embroidered with elaborate arabesques in shimmering gold thread.  Gilded lanterns illuminate the many fine wares, while a burly S'Kra guard keeps a watchful eye on patrons.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Tick Tock, Sales Floor" note="Tick Tock" color="#FF0000">
    <description>From behind a counter, a clerk carefully cleans fingerprints and other smudges from the wares proudly displayed throughout the small room.  A shadesatin-lined tray of fancy clockwork devices is set on a counter between a black bust and some alerce pegs showcasing similar mechanical creations.  Metal keys matching the various gadgets hang from some aldamdin hooks.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Which Craft, Sitting Room" note="Which Craft" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A crooked brick fireplace stands against a stone-textured wall, cold and bare except for an empty cauldron inside.  The area in front of the fireplace is dominated by a large, dusty floral-patterned sofa and an area rug, covered in ruddy stains.  Light flickers from a twisted iron chandelier above, hanging precariously from a nearly broken chain.  Everything is draped with a fine veil of cobwebs, with the exception of the goods for sale.</description>
    <position x="480" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit door" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Which Craft, Kitchen" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A large, sooty brick oven dominates the majority of the east wall, lit from the inside with a white-hot glow.  A rough iron counter stands in the middle of the room, covered with pits and ruddy stains.</description>
    <position x="500" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Which Craft, Experimentation Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A large marble platform, draped in chains and ruddy stains, stands in the middle of the room.  Locks of all shapes and sizes cover the walls, while a spiral chain chandelier hangs overhead.</description>
    <position x="500" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Which Craft, Conservatory" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The west wall is treated to resemble a glass, overlooking a mural of a graveyard with a full moon above.  A spiral vine decorated with several vials of multicolored liquid hangs overhead.</description>
    <position x="460" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Which Craft, Bed Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A false window painted with a full moon against a backdrop of silvery stars takes up the majority of one wall.  The area in front of the window is dominated by a large, lumpy bed with spiral-carved ivy posts.  Opposite the bed stands a slender wardrobe, wrapped in chains.</description>
    <position x="460" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Whimsies" note="Whimsies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>As customers enter this brightly lit shop, ribbons and bells sway, and jingle as the door opens and closes.   Along its fine oak walls is fanciful coralite furniture piled with goods for sale.</description>
    <position x="420" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plank door" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Wrath of the Storm, Salesroom" note="Wrath of the STorm" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dark grey banners hang on the indigo walls, portraying choppy seas tossing about a hapless ship.  The floor is painted a slate-blue, the same shade as a storm-tossed sea.  Gaethzen orbs dimly light the small room, casting an eerie and muted glow throughout the cramped space.</description>
    <position x="320" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey door" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Floors for Thought, Main Salesfloor" note="Floors for Thought" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Metal racks with rollout shelves line the walls, each shelf displaying a different sample of floor covering for perusal.  Windows high in the walls provide lighting during daylight hours, with hanging gaethzen globes available during evening hours.</description>
    <position x="360" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Floors for Thought, Refined Tastes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>In contrast to the main salesfloor, the racks in this room are crafted from the finest tropical hardwoods.  The flooring in the room is plain ash planking, but of such a fine finish that it is like walking on satin.  Leaded glass clerestory windows allow in clear sunlight to aid the patrons in their selections.</description>
    <position x="380" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="The Haunted House, Front Hall" note="Haunted House" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dark red candles burn in small braziers on either side of the arched doorway, the myriad of rugs spread across the floor awash with the eerie light.  Several chests line the sides of the small room, watchful eyes painted above them on the completely black walls.  Shadows run deep in every corner, relentlessly assaulting the imagination with images of childhood monsters.</description>
    <position x="340" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="The Haunted House, Study" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Standing in a battle-ready position with both hands gripped on their swords, a row of empty plate armor lines the northern wall, which is hung with moth-eaten purple drapes.  On the southern side of the room, a skeletal horse with a fleshless knight mounted on its back is poised toward the armor, making the only path to the wares pass directly in the line of fire of both sides.  Thin floorboards have been painted a dull grey, doing little to hide the extensive wear and tear.</description>
    <position x="360" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="The Haunted House, Bedroom" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Very little light filters through boarded-up windows, covered in webs thick with the dried corpses of black widow spiders.  Antique at best and sinister at worst, the furniture lining the room is neatly laid out, though much of it is difficult to make out in the dim light.  Treacherous holes in the floor have been precariously patched over with thin boards, offering little safety.</description>
    <position x="320" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="The Haunted House, Kennel" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several cages are dimly visible in the poorly lit room, their doors tightly bolted.  Shining eyes blink out from the darkness, some natural and some seeming otherworldly, glowing red and standing out in the darkness.  A low brazier burns in the corner of the room, doing little to chase away the oppressive shadows.</description>
    <position x="300" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="The Haunted House, Attic" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The cramped room resembles a large crawlspace underneath a peaked roof, with the sharply slanted ceiling intersecting the floor on the eastern side.  Muted light filters in through a frosted window, illuminating dust motes floating through the air.  Cobwebs clutter every corner of the small room and drape over dreary pieces of furniture.</description>
    <position x="320" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Sheepish Shep's Ship-shape Sheep Ship Shop, Sales" note="Sheepish Shep's Ship-shape Sheep Ship Shop Sheesh" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The plush wool tent walls are woven from undyed wool, giving the fabric a mottled look as the different shades of white and cream yarn were combined in the weaving process.  A few paintings of nautical themes grace the walls while wooden shelves display the extremely eclectic stock of the shop.</description>
    <position x="320" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Tea For Tamsine, Entrance" note="Tea for Tamsine|Tamsine" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The entrance to this well-lit shop is framed in soft curtains of petalette, the shimmery rose-hued fabric complements the ivory and gold floral pattern that covers the walls.  A small table rests next to the small hearth burning brightly in the center of the room, while a gilded drink cart sits in the corner.</description>
    <position x="340" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Tea For Tamsine, Tea Time" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The faintest whiff of oranges and black tea drifts in to the brightly lit room, the pleasant smell matching the room's interior.  Polished cherry floorboards look clean enough to eat off of, not that the proprietor would recommend doing so.  A broad black walnut kitchen counter takes up one wall, while a pair of lacquered tables sit in the far corner.</description>
    <position x="360" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Tea For Tamsine, Kitchy Kitchens" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The majority of the floor is covered by a grey and white chevron-striped rug, but along the edges of the room it's possible to make out the polished cherry boards gleaming below.  An assortment of kitchen furniture is placed around the brightly lit room, each set to show off the fine craftsmanship that went into its creation.</description>
    <position x="320" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="The Musiceum, Orchestral Manoeuvres" note="Musiceum" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dark sable velvet drapery has been hung from ceiling to wall, swathing the room in near blackness.  The darkness is staved off completely by several gaethzen globes hung by near invisible wire that have been carefully positioned over the display cases to allow the wares for sale to be seen clearly.  Nestled between the swathes of cloth, cases and instrument tools have been hung on pegboards to show them off to their best advantage.</description>
    <position x="360" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gold door" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="The Musiceum, Amber Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set up in an octagonal shape, this room has been fitted with amber panels throughout.  Behind each panel, light has been set up to allow the amber to glow like a warm fire as well as highlighting the tiny bubbles and animals trapped within.  Ornate gold hardware secures each panel to the next, blending almost seamlessly with the tawny-hue of the paneling.  Three gaethzen globes suspend above the empty room, while a large hanging sign has been strung up to rest immediately below the middle globe.</description>
    <position x="380" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Haute Dogs and Fat Cats, Salesroom" note="Haute Dogs and Fat Cats|Hot Dogs|Fat Cats" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The canvas walls are covered with murals of dogs jumping and playing while cats slumber on windowsills and chairs.  Brightly painted shelves and counters display the products for sale while the sales staff circulates to answer questions and make sales.</description>
    <position x="320" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flap" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Focus on the Past, Relic Room" note="Focus on the Past" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several soil-stained packing crates stacked along the back encroach towards the interior at random intervals, detracting from the otherwise orderly desk where recent finds are cataloged.  Various shelves and bookcases occupy much of the remaining space, holding artifacts marked and tagged from previous expeditions.  A slight mustiness lingers in the air, infusing the room with the dampness imagined held within the tomb or temple where these artifacts originated.</description>
    <position x="300" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rustic doorway" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Too Much of a Good Sling, Salesroom" note="Too Much of a Good Sling|Slings" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Canvas tent walls enclose a bare spot of ground, with little beyond some baskets and bins scattered about to show that this is a shop selling merchandise.  A lantern hangs from the tent pole and provides some illumination throughout the cramped space.</description>
    <position x="280" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas flap" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="The Other Siegery Shop" note="Other Siegery Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Elaborate tapestries hang from the four walls in colorful banners.  Each is decorated with an army marching over fields and meadows, ready to clash with an opposing army on the opposite banner.  Incandescent lights hang from the ceiling, illuminating numerous tables filled with miniature figures and a lone shelf with sets for sale.</description>
    <position x="280" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="The Other Siegery Shop, Team Gear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Elaborate tapestries hang from the four walls in colorful banners.  Each is decorated with an army marching over fields and meadows, ready to clash with an opposing army on the opposite banner.  Incandescent lights hang from the ceiling, illuminating the various sales surfaces.</description>
    <position x="280" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Fishy's Pants Mart, Pants Department of Pants" note="Fishy's Pants Mart" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Scorch marks festoon the inside walls of this tent as if someone had run amok with a torch, or perhaps there were several small explosions.  A mild sulfurous odor hangs in the air with an underlying hint of old fish.  All this combined with the bright colors of the displays, however, might lead one to suspect that the proprietor is not a reserved or, indeed, stable individual.</description>
    <position x="320" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Fishy's Pants Mart, Pants Department of Not-Pants" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This side room is a bit shabby and unadorned, as if it were an afterthought.  The tent walls show less obvious damage than those in the main section, although the general aroma is similar.  Stray fragments of fabric litter the floor here and there.</description>
    <position x="340" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="235" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Bathed in Splendor, Submerged" note="Bathed in Splendor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Enclosed within water-filled glass walls, the shop is surrounded by a school of brightly colored tetras and a trio of tiny marbled-shell turtles as they dart through clusters of blue-green waterferns that rise from a bed of silvery sand.</description>
    <position x="280" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass archway" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Stitched by the Sea, Sewing Room" note="Stitched by the Sea" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Decorated with delicate strings of gaethzen seashells that criss-cross a vaulted ceiling, the spacious room is filled with light that streams in from large stained glass windows depicting panoramic seascapes at each corner.  The comfortable sewing space has a variety of counters and a large bobbin cabinet pushed up against the walls to leave the center of the room easy to navigate.</description>
    <position x="300" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood door" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="All Gallows Eve, Salesfloor" note="All Gallows Eve" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The dark, almost dreary, room is lit by a few skull-shaped sconces on the dark brown walls.  The main counter is shaped like a gallows, with a noose hanging over the locked cash box.  Carrying the morbid theme further, most of the merchandise is displayed on several coffin-shaped racks, stands, displayes, and shelves scattered throughout the room.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark door" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Natural Selections, On Your Guard" note="Natural Selections" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Skulls of strange creatures and beasts hang overhead from pieces of sinew, each one free of any remnants of their previous owners.  Various furs are splayed along the floor, cushioning the footfalls of visitors into the room.  Painted upon the walls are depictions of conquests and adventures within the wilds of the lands.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit flap" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Natural Selections, Fang and Claw" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Furs are littered about the floor, hiding only portions of the metal floor.  Overhead, an oil lantern brightens the area and provides light for a tapestry that covers the wall.  Adjacent to the tapestry is a small, well cared for tree planted in a ceramic pot.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Natural Selections, Below the Belt" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Figurines depicting various scenes of violence sit on a small end table beside the metal wall.  Attached to a metal bolt is a lantern that puts the products for sale under bright light.  Several skins have been placed on the ground, cushioning customers' feet from the bare metal flooring.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Katy Gore The Door, Sales Area" note="Katy Gore The Door" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Deep shadows linger in the corners where the fitful lighting does not quite reach.  Racks spread around the room display the doors for sale.</description>
    <position x="340" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go yurt flap" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="The Emperor's New Robes, Outlet" note="Emperor's New Robes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Lofty tentpoles hold up the striped roof which soars overhead.  Multi-hued bands of silk run vertically along the walls, making the interior a riot of color even without the kaleidoscopic hues of the merchandise.  Racks and stands display the wares on offer while salesclerks bustle about.</description>
    <position x="320" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pavilion flap" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Only The Holy, Salesfloor" note="Only The Holy" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Frescos depicting the Immortals cover the wall, each depicted with their symbols and animals.  The exposed roof beams have been carved into a running frieze of holy symbols, leaving no surface undecorated.  In contrast to the roof beams, the racks and shelves displaying the merchandise are of plain wood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large door" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Jynli's Cattery HE Wing, Main Room" note="Jynli's Cattery" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Large spacious cages line the walls, each outfitted with a comfortable bed and a scratching post as well as full water and food bowls.  Behind the mesh, each cage displays one of the exotic cats that Jynli is known for.  The pets are mostly sleeping, but a few stare boldly out at the customers wandering around.</description>
    <position x="500" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cat-shaped door" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Pita Pan, Mainroom" note="Pita Pan" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain walls enclose a mostly bare room with just a counter for the salesclerks and a large table displaying the wares.  A few lamps provide subdued lighting in line with the minimalist feel of the shop's fixtures.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="All The King's Men, Entrance" note="All The King's Men" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Opulent tapestries ring the walls of the spacious vestibule, while thick plush rugs blanket the gleaming wooden floors.  Low benches of polished deobar wood flank the entry flap.  One lone table stands in the middle of the carpeted floor, a branching candelabra positioned carefully on a pristine white tablecloth.</description>
    <position x="480" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="All The King's Men, Shirts" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Silken gauze curtains dyed in jewel-tones partition the interior of the tent into smaller sections.  Surrounding this section are delicate drapes in pale blue-greens the color of aquamarines.  Gleaming white ash racks and tables hold brilliantly colored wares.</description>
    <position x="480" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="All The King's Men, Pants" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Opulent rugs of thick wool completely cover the ground, allowing patrons to browse in comfort.  Folded pants are stacked on the aromatic cedarwood tables and counters.  Wispy curtains of translucent emerald-green silk screen the area from the rest of the tent.</description>
    <position x="480" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="All The King's Men, Shoes" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Burnished lunat wood stands and racks stand in the center of a midnight blue wool rug covering the matching plank floor.  Shoes and boots in a myriad of styles grace the polished surfaces.  Wispy draperies dyed a deep sapphire blue section the area off from the rest of the tent.</description>
    <position x="500" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="All The King's Men, Cloaks" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Intricately figured cocobolo wood racks and wardrobes display a profusion of brilliantly colored wares.  Amber-colored sheer silken drapes delineate the section of the tent devoted to cloaks and other outerwear.  Deep yellow wool pile carpets muffle all sounds of movement.</description>
    <position x="480" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="All The King's Men, Doublets" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Fine-grained teak shelves and stands set out the luxurious offerings on sale.  Wispy fabric drapes the shade of watermelon tourmaline help to section off this area from the rest of the commodious tent.  Flooring of dark teak covers the floor, its surface almost totally concealed beneath the fuchsia-colored plush carpets.</description>
    <position x="460" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="All The King's Men, Hats" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plush pile carpets dyed in swirls of white and light purple cover the floor, hiding the waxed wood from view.  Thin amethyst-colored silken curtains isolate the space from the remainder of the tent.  Hats are piled in profusion on polished rowan wood tables and stands.</description>
    <position x="460" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="The Finer Things, Front Room" note="Finer Things" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The room is lavishly floored with durian buffed to a brilliant sheen while a perfume bottle chandelier hangs from above illuminating the opulent coral walls with a warm glow.  A shelf of brushed platinum faces an intricately carved chest, each carefully placed to subtly catch the light upon their showcased wares.  Taking the central focal point of the room is a glass counter wrapped in strands of seashells and adorned with purposely placed jars of brightly glowing gaethzen.</description>
    <position x="400" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="The Finer Things, Back Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The opulence of the shop is carried into this room, but with a more casual setting.  Sun bleached coral walls are draped in pastel-tinted whisperlayne interwoven with soft glowing lights that help to highlight the salt-stained durian floors.  Reclaimed wood and expensive fabrics combine to create the chests and whitewashed shelves used to display the wares in the cozy area.</description>
    <position x="420" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="The Finer Things, Corner" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The lush, ocean-blue carpeting of the small room serves the dual purposes of muffling the sounds of heavy foot traffic and providing a more cushioned place to sit or stand.  Lavish piles of sea-shell patterned pillows are stacked with an eye to detail and the customers' comfort in mind.  Potted palm trees strung with softly glowing sungold lanterns stand in each corner of the room, giving off just enough light to create a relaxed ambience.</description>
    <position x="380" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Field Fashion, Not-Really-Skirts" note="Field Fashion" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Palm fronds cover the walls, providing partial cover from the elements.  The raised floor is sanded teak planks which support a variety of racks and stands for the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="400" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go screened door" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Field Fashion, Things That Are Still Not Skirts" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tucked into the back of the cabana is this airy room with large open screened windows.  A few shelves and racks showcase the items for sale.</description>
    <position x="420" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Field Fashion, Long Things That Might Trip You" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Instead of palm frond walls, the room is enclosed with louvered panels that help to keep the elements out without impeding air flow.  The merchandise is displayed on counters and tables.</description>
    <position x="380" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="In Gore Pouch, Inside Tent" note="In Gore Pouch" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Shelves and racks run along the hide walls of the tent, set there to display the merchandise without impeding the flow of customers.  A few clerks circulate through the crowds as they restock the wares and answer questions about the stock.  Gleaming gaethzen spheres hang from the tent poles and illuminate the corners with bright light.</description>
    <position x="380" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Urn Back Time, Front Room" note="Urn Back Time" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A framework of oak poles holds up the canvas sides, which are decorated with painted designs in red and black depicting people in flowing clothes marching in procession.  A few lanterns hanging from the roofpoles provide lighting for the shop's wares displayed on the wooden shelves and racks about the area.</description>
    <position x="430" y="65" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas flap" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Urn Back Time, Back Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A framework of oak poles holds up the canvas sides, which are decorated with painted designs in red and black depicting people in long robes parading through a city street.  A few lanterns hanging from the roofpoles provide lighting for the shop's wares displayed on the wooden shelves and racks about the area.</description>
    <position x="430" y="85" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Sew It Seems, Entrance" note="Sew It Seems" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Cheerful yellow walls provide a welcoming entrance to this inviting shop.  Various seating options are available to allow the patrons to rest between buying sprees.</description>
    <position x="240" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Sew It Seems, Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Racks of pants in various shades, grouped by color onto correspondingly painted displays, fill the central area of this room.  Shelves, likewise arranged by color, are set along the walls and sell shirts in a wide array of colors.</description>
    <position x="240" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Sew It Seems, Footwear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several racks of boots are grouped next to plain benches where patrons can try on their prospective purchases.  Each rack is painted in colors to match the merchandise on offer for that display.</description>
    <position x="220" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Sew It Seems, Adventuring Gear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The entire room is filled with stands overflowing with backpacks, rucksacks, and knapsacks.  Each stand is a different color, and the items on display for each stand are various shades of the stand's color.  Busy clerks keep the merchandise stocked.</description>
    <position x="220" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Sew It Seems, Outerwear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Scattered about the room are differently colored cloak racks, each carrying an assortment of outerwear in matching shades.  Sales clerks bustle about keeping the displays stocked.</description>
    <position x="260" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="265" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Fabric Fantasies, Salesroom" note="Fabric Fantasies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Lengths of assorted colorful and luxurious fabrics cover the room's dingy walls, allowing customers closer inspection of the exquisite goods sold at this location.  Large gaethzen spheres dangle from the ceiling, washing the area in bright light, which causes metallic threads and gem flecks in certain displayed textiles to sparkle like crystals on a summer's day.  Pale beige carpeting covers the floor, hiding the building's metal partitions from hurried shoppers.</description>
    <position x="180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Looty Booty, Entrance" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain birch walls circumscribe the room, lacking any embellishment or adornment.  A square doorway leads further into the shop, while a simple chain dangling from the ceiling holds a gaethzen sphere that illuminates the sparse alcove.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go square doorway" destination="351" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Things That Go Bump in the Fight, Control Room" note="Things That Go Bump in the Fight|Bump in the Fight" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set up in the middle of the floor are a number of utilitarian shelves and racks made of wood.  A few small cubicles are set up along the canvas tent walls so that patrons can try on the merchandise.  The scent of oiled canvas and freshly cut wood still drifts on the air in the confined space.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas flap" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Entry" note="Sputkin's Splendors" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Decoration is sparse in the entryway.  A cramped passage leads northward between stacks of empty crates, whose contents are presumably on display elsewhere.</description>
    <position x="60" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="273" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Nexus" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This chamber is the most spacious in the wagon, providing ample room for a crowd to attend a sermon.  A high white marble altar rises majestically in the middle of the room, flanked by tall silver candlesticks which cast a nimbus of warm light across its pale surface.  Shallow alcoves surround the chamber, branching off in all directions.</description>
    <position x="60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oaken ladder" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Small Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Soft black velvet tapestries drape the walls of this alcove, bathed in the light of a single candle held from an ornate platinum floor sconce.</description>
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Small Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Deep blue watersilk tapestries cascade down the walls, shimmering in the light of an ornate silver lantern suspended from the ceiling.  The play of color and light against the fabric gives the cramped alcove a spurious illusion of spaciousness.</description>
    <position x="40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Small Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This small alcove has been draped in pearlescent white silken tapestries.  Several large candles held in delicate white-gold floor sconces bathe the area in a gentle glow, causing the tapestries to shimmer beneath the soft caress of the flickering candlelight.</description>
    <position x="40" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Small Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A bizarre mix of gaudiness and subtlety, festive banners adorn one side of this small alcove while plain white cotton tapestries mask the other wall.  A simple iron lantern sways from the ceiling, bathing the area in its glow.</description>
    <position x="80" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Sputkin's Splendors, Cramped Loft" note="Sputkin's Scrolls|Sputkin's Loft|Scrolls" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Not a single cobweb mars this small loft, allowing a feeling of comfort to permeate throughout.  A single candle rises from a golden floor sconce, casting playfully dancing shadows on the walls.</description>
    <position x="60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Farhana's Island Exquisites, Sales Room" note="Farhana's Island Exquisites" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Arched walls are hung with ivory gauze layered over pale rose silk, softening the light of the room and rippling with every breeze.  Tall seagrass baskets filled with honeysuckle blossoms and curls of sandalwood and cinnamon bark are tucked in the corners, lending a light and spicy fragrance to the air.  Big cushions covered with raw silk and edged with tiny golden bells are scattered near the merchandise racks, inviting shoppers to linger and choose.</description>
    <position x="40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Kilt From Scratch, Shop" note="Kilt From Scratch" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Although the mortar between the bricks is a bit crumbly, the walls are stout and solid.  Counters and shelves display the products for sale, while the busy salespeople bustle about helping customers and replenishing merchandise.</description>
    <position x="60" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Jousting Grounds, Lances and Roses Souvenir Shop" note="Jousting Grounds|Lances and Roses" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dolls, ribands and other souvenirs are laid out in neat groups atop the display tables in the shop.  Sales clerks work quickly to maintain the order as items are snatched up by prize-hungry spectators attending the competitions.</description>
    <position x="20" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sturdy door" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Artistry of Flesh" note="Artistry of Flesh" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The room is low and cell-like, an excess of gaethzen orbs hanging from the ceiling filling the small space with a harsh, sterile light.  The only piece of furniture is a large reclining chair bearing a range of gadgets both mundane and alien.  Samples of flash cover the far wall, the only break from the dull grey wood.  A thin young Kaldaran man, presumably the artist, stands rigidly out of the way with a flat expression.</description>
    <position x="220" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go darkened door" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Artistry of Flesh, Side Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen orbs hang from the ceiling and fill this small room with harsh white light, illuminating the sterile space and its lack of decorations.  A small table pushed up against the back wall is covered in a mound of crumpled papers and mangled trinkets, remnants from an unknown project.  Nestled amongst unwanted items is a small catalog.</description>
    <position x="240" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Dying to Shop, Front of Tent" note="Dying to Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Black canvas walls have a few openings that allow air and light to come into this large tent.  Fresh grass mats cover the ground while various displays hold the merchandise for sale.  A large white banner hangs between the tentpoles.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="285" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="Dying to Shop, Back of Tent" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Black canvas walls have a few openings that allow air and light to come into this large tent.  Fresh grass mats cover the ground while various displays hold the merchandise for sale.  A large white banner hangs overhead.</description>
    <position x="160" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="Knotty Pirate, Entry" note="Knotty Pirate" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain oak paneling covers the walls with rich, yellow-brown wood while the floors are narrower planks of the same wood.  Occupying the central space of the entry is a tall mannequin, dressed in a flamboyant outfit.</description>
    <position x="180" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Dark Dalliance, Chamber" note="Dark Dalliance" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A hint of perfume upon the air greets all who enter this merchant.  The area is mostly dark, with just a hint of candlelight dancing against the stark obsidian walls.  Merchandise rests upon dark furniture lining each side while a massive throne offers seating at the back.</description>
    <position x="180" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched door" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="The Ghostly Galleria of Spiritual Souvenirs" note="Ghostly Galleria" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The unmistakable salty tang of the sea hangs heavily in the air.  The small room sits at a slight angle, as a bulky crate would lean with a heavy load stacked atop it.  The ceiling on one side is higher than the other.  Despite the structure's physical condition, a fresh coat of white paint covers the walls, and a royal purple rug -- still curled at its edges -- sits in the center.</description>
    <position x="220" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crooked opening" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Nigeyi's, Purveyor of Fine Footwear" note="Nigeyi's|Footwear|Fine Footwear" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Various displays, each catering to the different tastes of Nigeyi's customers, line the room.  Suspended from the ceiling are wagon wheels upon which lit candles brighten the room and cast dancing shadows whenever the door opens.  A worn stool and cobbler's form sit in the corner beneath a rack holding a neat assortment of tools.</description>
    <position x="220" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Nigeyi's, Selections" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tapered candles fill the center of the small room with bright light, throwing dusky shadows against a small sign hanging from a wagon wheel in the corner.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="291" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Nigeyi's Resale" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Deliberately darker than the other rooms, items consigned to this space have been rehabilitated, but no one has appeared to pay for the service.  Long abandoned by their owners, they accumulate dust as Nigeyi attempts to recoup his labor and expenses.</description>
    <position x="240" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Makeshift Killing Supplies Annex, Shop" note="Makeshift Killing Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Crafted of rough wooden boards cobbled together with rusted nails, this wagon looks as though it's ready to fall apart.  Wares are displayed in the center of the room, where they are slightly less likely to be attacked by the termites that infest the mobile shop.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wagon door" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="293" name="Soulful Trinkets" note="Soulful Trinkets" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Lamps are placed around the room haphazardly, offering just enough light to clearly view the merchandise for sale here.  White cloth covers the dark metal walls in an attempt to further brighten the area.  Three racks are strategically placed around the room, their colors signifying the sort of aspects the wares on them represent.</description>
    <position x="220" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Ritual Addiction, Ceremony" note="Ritual Addiction" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth leather walls of overlaid straps with silver studs rise up around a dark haon floor.  Dim sconces cast irregular shadows across the room, revealing a collection of haphazardly arranged tables.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="295" name="Ritual Addiction, Strife" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth leather walls of overlaid straps with silver studs rise up around a dark haon floor.  Dim sconces cast irregular shadows across the room, revealing a collection of haphazardly arranged tables.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Reinventing the Wheel, Entry" note="Reinventing the Wheel" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The aromas of hay and wood are very strong in the small entryway.  Rough cedar planks, comprising the shop's floor, creak beneath the movements of customers.  Two small bales of hay have been used to anchor a large wagon wheel on its end across from the entrance.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="297" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted door" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Reinventing the Wheel, West Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Two circular display boards, painted to resemble wagon wheels, have been mounted upon the walls.  Various images of available merchandise have been placed within the spokes of each display.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="296" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Galleria of Garters" note="Galleria of Garters|Garters" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Elegant gold lanterns glow softly from their perches high above the sales floor.  Bolts of vibrant silk drape from the corner posts and airily drift towards the floor.  Adjacent to the fabric walls reside pieces of richly polished mahogany furniture which double as displays.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="The Lost Tavern" note="Lost Tavern" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dark and gloomy, the atmosphere reflects the abandoned appearance of the area.  Four dingy, vine-covered walls hide faded messages, once legible and now covered in dust and unreadable, while unlit torches are attached to the rounded wooden beams that support the tall roof of this forgotten building.  Small windows covered with dust and grim line the wall above a vine-covered display case.  Scattered around the large room are tables covered with various bottles in a variety of sizes.  A small bar stands next to the dilapidated door.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood door" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="In The Hollow" note="In The Hollow" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A cold draft wafts through the room at regular intervals, its source undetermined.  Each passing breeze causes the hooks hanging from the rafters to sway, making the ribbons and papers decorating the pinatas they hold flutter with eerie sounds.  A small table set to one side contains additional beribboned items.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rickety door" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Delicate Creations" note="Delicate Creations" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pale blooms of fragrant flowers are interspersed throughout this small shop.  The oak-paneled walls are softened by crystal sconces and ivory tapestries.  Simply clad clerks appear ready to help customers with fine clothing hung on racks and set out on tables.</description>
    <position x="0" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Conductive Contraptions, Sales Floor" note="Conductive Contraptions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A lamp of caged lightning churns with a harsh white illumination, and the air is heavily charged, smelling faintly of ozone.  Crates of inventory overflowing with wool packing material line the back wall, and several sconces burn with crackling fires to dry the air.  Shelves bearing dishes of ground charcoal line the perimeter of the room.</description>
    <position x="20" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go electroweave flap" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Tastelessly Tacky, Vestibule" note="Tastelessly Tacky" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Crystals encrusted on the walls glitter in the warm glow of the candelabra resting on the white harpsichord positioned in the center of the room.  Next to the instrument is a mannequin dressed in a dazzlingly white ensemble.  A pure white wool rug, its plush pile thick and luxurious, covers the ground.</description>
    <position x="60" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go purple door" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Tastelessly Tacky, Pointy Things" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plum-colored watered silk covers the upper walls over a wainscotting of cherrywood.  Matching planks form the floor which peeks out beneath the numerous sheepskins scattered about as carpets.  Wildly painted weapon stands and armor racks display the wares for sale.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Tastelessly Tacky, Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pink painted walls enclose a wooden floor stained purple.  A bright blue table stands in the middle of the room, displaying various clothing items for sale, with an orange and purple painted chest next to it.</description>
    <position x="80" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Tastelessly Tacky, Containers" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Fake leopard-print wallpaper covers the walls, clashing with the zebra-skin rugs on the black and white checked wooden floor.  A counter, covered with red dyed fur, holds containers for sale.</description>
    <position x="40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Tieheq with the Thirteen, Vestibule" note="Tieheq with the Thirteen" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Overlapping panels of starlight velvet drape from the ceiling, loosely defining the circular shop.  Dominating the center of the chamber is a pure white marble monument of Misiumos.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="310" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron-framed door" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Tieheq with the Thirteen, Vestments" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Overlapping panels of starlight velvet drape from the ceiling, loosely defining the circular shop.  Dominating the center of the chamber is a pure white marble monument of Misiumos.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Tieheq with the Thirteen, Iconography" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Overlapping panels of starlight velvet drape from the ceiling, loosely defining the circular shop.  Dominating the center of the chamber is a pure white marble monument of Misiumos.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Tieheq with the Thirteen, Accouterments" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Overlapping panels of starlight velvet drape from the ceiling, loosely defining the circular shop.  Dominating the center of the chamber is a pure white marble monument of Misiumos.</description>
    <position x="0" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Halberdashery, Main Room" note="Halberdashery|Halberds" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Whitewashed walls enclose the simply furnished shop.  A plain pine counter in one corner is matched by the wooden weapon racks displaying the goods for sale.  Overhead some gaethzen spheres provide illumination.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Down on the Farm, Salesroom" note="Down on the Farm" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Small pens and paddocks are set up on the floor, each one filled with tiny animals munching on fodder.  The space overloads the senses with the sounds and smells of a barnyard as the attendents rush around trying to simultaneously help the customers and care for the pets on offer.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go barn door" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Rite of Cravat, Salesfloor" note="Rite of Cravat|Cravats" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sturdy brickwork forms the walls around the shop, the bright red of the masonry contrasting with the pale color of the mortar.  Elegant brass sconces hold beeswax candles that illuminate the area with a bright clear light.  Polished wood shelves hold the merchandise while the cheerful clerks stand ready to assist in any way.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="314" name="Svenblum's Annex, Inner Child" note="Svenblum's Annex" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The soothing scent of cedar fills the room while oil lanterns fill the area with brightness.  In the center of the room is a black walnut burl that appears to be a makeshift workstation.  Various shaping tools, knives, and wood shavings clutter the burl.  Flanking it are some wooden benches with items for sale.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="315" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wagon door" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="315" name="Svenblum's Annex, Play Corner" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This corner of the wagon appears to have been designed with a child in mind.  Some wooden shelves filled with woodcarvings line the walls while a small reed basket nests in multi-colored throw pillows.  A small teak burl sits in the middle of the area with an unpainted doll house resting on top.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="316" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="314" />
  </node>
  <node id="316" name="Svenblum's Annex, Cubbyhole" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The main embellishment in this shadowy corner of the workroom is a standing silverwillow burl.  An overhead lantern provides just enough light to view the various wooden shelves on the walls.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="315" />
  </node>
  <node id="317" name="Dress for Success, Salesfloor" note="dress for Success" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sturdy walls of cut grey limestone are topped by large wooden beams supporting the roof.  A few lanterns hang from the roofbeams, illuminating the spacious room and the mannequins displaying the shop's merchandise.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="318" name="Raw Silk, Shopfloor" note="Raw Silk" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tall stands and racks scattered around the shop exhibit the product while keeping the delicate fabrics off the floor.  The bustle of the clerks as they circulate about mingles with the chatter of the patrons to create a constant background noise.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cedar door" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="319" name="Stabbaticals, Sales Floor" note="Stabbaticals" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Billowy white banners are draped along the walls, framing the wooden pegs and hooks affixed at even intervals around the room.  A trio of tables rests upon a dark blue rug stretched over the polished oak floor.  Running along the back wall is an intricate mural of a battlefield strewn with broken weaponry and fallen bodies.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey door" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="320" name="Divine Design, Shop" note="Divine Design" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Felt panels are placed over a framework of slender rods that rise in a dome.  Appliques of the many symbols of the gods cover the walls, while the floor is made up of finely polished oak planks laid in a circular pattern radiating from the center.  Wooden shelves hold the merchandise on offer.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go felt flap" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="321" name="Home for the Fireplace, Showroom" note="Home for the Fireplace" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Exhibited back to back in the center of the room are a number of displays of the various fireplaces available in the shop.  More are set against the paneled walls.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go soot-stained door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="322" name="Creature Story, Sales" note="Creature Story" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted in garish colors spanning all the walls is a mural depicting hundreds of creatures from Elanthia -- from arbelogs to zombies.  Centered in the middle of the oak floor are a number of wooden stands, each one made from a different wood.  The stands display a variety of merchandise, tastefully arranged on velvet-padded arms extending from the stands.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go multi-colored door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="323" name="Wedding Belles, Foyer" note="Wedding Belles" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A sense of lightness and elegance pervades the room, helped by the richness of the ivory silk-covered walls.  Silver sconces jut out from the walls, holding candles out from polished reflectors.  A small side table against one wall holds some refreshments, and white chairs stand against the two flanking walls.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="324" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="324" name="Wedding Bells, With This Ring" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Subtle but bright lighting ensures that the clientele of this shop can properly appreciate the exquisite merchandise on offering.  Pale birch paneling along the walls adds to the general feeling of light and warmth.  Three display cases - trimmed in teak, ebony, and cherry - hold pride of place in the center of the salesfloor.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="325" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="323" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="327" />
  </node>
  <node id="325" name="Wedding Bells, Dapper Designs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Deeply padded leather armchairs provide spots for lounging and resting before further shopping.  Dark wood paneling of various woods run vertically along the walls to the white plasterwork of the ceiling.  Large chandeliers dangle from the ceiling, illuminating the tables placed in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="324" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="326" />
  </node>
  <node id="326" name="Wedding Bells, Bridal Suite" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Instead of wood, the walls are covered in an off-white silk with a subtle shifting pattern of moire watermarks.  A tri-fold mirror stands in one corner while mannequins garbed in luscious fabrics display the shop's bridal wares.  Delicate lamps scattered throughout the area provide copious illumination of the designs and details.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="325" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="327" />
  </node>
  <node id="327" name="Wedding Belles, Artful Accouterments" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Lit chandeliers provide light now that night has descended, illuminating the cream-colored walls and pale pine floor planking.  Mannequins stand in various poses in one corner.  Large floor to ceiling mirrors allow for the trying on of the merchandise before purchasing.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="326" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="328" name="Lute The Room, Mainroom" note="Lute The Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Exotic woods and odd metals are heaped in and on containers throughout this cramped shop.  A workbench, littered with tools, testifies that each instrument is handcrafted with care.  A table stands near the door, displaying what's available for purchase.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="329" name="Scentsations, Sweet Senses" note="Scentsations" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pure white walls enclose the airy confines of the sales floor.  Faint scents waft through the area, a bouquet of mingled aromas that blends into an overall impression of pleasure and delight.  Across one wall stands a counter, its plain ash wood unrelieved by any ornamentation.</description>
    <position x="-90" y="-110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="330" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black door" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="330" name="Scentsations, Functionally Fragrant" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Heavy, almost overpowering scents dominate the room, each one warring with the other for preeminence.  Besides a tall white counter, there is little in the room to distract from the overwhelming cacophony of scents that pervades the area.  Spread across the display are the numerous bottles and vials of the shop's merchandise.</description>
    <position x="-70" y="-130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="331" name="Scentsations, Seasonal Scents" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Thin black stripes alternate with wide white planks in the floor, set diagonally to the walls which are an austure white without any decoration.  Hints of wintergreen, pumpkins, roses, and strawberries drift through the air, each new scent bringing memories of seasons long past.  A long white counter stands in the center of the room, featuring the exquisite wares of the shop.</description>
    <position x="-90" y="-150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="330" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="332" />
  </node>
  <node id="332" name="Scentsations, Once and Floral" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tiles on the floor form a stylized floral design in black and white with the same blossom theme repeated on the carved baseboards and crown moulding of the whitewashed walls.  A plain birch counter stands against a wall, showing the shop's wares without any distractions from the furnishings.</description>
    <position x="-110" y="-130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="331" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="329" />
  </node>
  <node id="333" name="Row Row Row Your Coat, Shop" note="Row Row Row Your Coat|Row Your Coat" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Oilcloth walls devoid of decoration enclose the shop, the peaked roof upheld by long wooden poles.  Simple stands and shelves are dispersed around the room, each strategically placed under a lantern hanging from the tentpoles.  Clerks circulate throughout, always ready to answer a question or make a sale.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oilcloth flap" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="334" name="The Scorpion Shop, Salesroom" note="Scorpion Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Finely polished ebony walls enclose the room, the narrow planking fitted so expertly together that is almost impossible to tell where the joints are.  A deep grey carpet covers most of the flooring, an abstract pattern of lighter and darker areas the only variation in the rug.  Bare metal shelves and racks display the shop's merchandise.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black door" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="335" name="Sofa So Good, Salesroom" note="Sofa So Good" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Spacious in extent, the room is floored with broad oak planking sanded smooth and then lacquered to protect the surface.  Vertical oak paneling covers the otherwise undecorated walls.  Sofas, divans, and other seating are displayed throughout the store, ready for purchase.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="336" name="Skin Art by Jaecinda" note="Skin Art|Jaecinda" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The simple wagon lacks any significant decoration.  The walls are bare wood, and large windows provide ample natural lighting while an ink-stained rug, likely once cream colored, covers most of the floor.  A lone workspace exists for Jaecinda to do her work.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opened doorway" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="337" name="The Fighting is on the Wall, Salesfloor" note="Fighting is on the Wall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Scuffed and scarred, the oak planks of the floor show the signs of heavy use.  Wooden weapons hang on the walls, each one battered from heavy use before being retired to serve as decorations.  A few stands and shelves display the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go battered door" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="338" name="Now And Trader, Salesfloor" note="Now And Trader" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Frames on the walls display drawings of the various customization options available, each one labeled with the basic information on the stock.  Brightly polished brass lanterns hang from the ceiling, illuminating the plastered walls and well-swept floors.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go circular hatch" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="339" name="The Contented Sole, Salesfloor" note="Contended Sole" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Giant appliqued fish are affixed to the canvas walls, cut from colorful felt and decorated with googly eyes.  Paper lanterns shaped like various fish species hang from the tent poles, giving light to the room.  Shelves and racks crowd the salesfloor, each one stuffed with a wide selection of footwear.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="340" name="See the Light, Kermorian Divinity" note="See the Light" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Aurulent curtains are draped along the walls of lifesculpted coral, lending a majestic air to the space, while luxurious rugs muffle the sounds of footsteps and of conversations.  Thirteen gilded lanterns provide ample illumination.</description>
    <position x="165" y="-315" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="340" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gold door" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="341" name="See the Light, Foreign Powers" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sanguine swathes accentuate the walls of lifesculpted coral, lending bursts of color to the space, while exotic rugs muffle the sounds of footsteps and of conversations.  Several flickering torches illuminate the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="155" y="-325" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="340" />
  </node>
  <node id="342" name="Excess Baggage, Salesroom" note="Excess Baggage" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Panels of ethereal white fabric are draped across the ceiling and allowed to fall in waves to the floor, creating a bright, neutral backdrop for the displayed merchandise.  Woven rugs hide the last bit of ground from the existing space as well as muffle the hurried footsteps of busy shoppers.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="343" name="Eluned's Dreams in Flesh" note="Eluned's Dreams in Flesh" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The mother-of-pearl walls are a pristine white, reflecting light in iridescent swirls.  Cabinets are stocked with dyes of every imaginable color and shade.  Comfortable looking benches and stools are spaced about the room.  Small tables are setup in the corners of the shop.</description>
    <position x="460" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go round doorway" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="344" name="Red Fan Siegery Suppliers, Basalt Isle Room" note="Red Fan Siegery" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Inside this poorly-constructed shack, a Merelew shopkeeper stands over a number of tiny figurines, idly carving on one and not particularly paying attention to you.  A single gaethzen lamp swings idly from the ceiling, casting shadows across the room.</description>
    <position x="0" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood door" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="345" name="Rizadi's Outfitters, Sales Floor" note="Rizadi's Outfitters" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Brass lanterns hang in each corner, spreading a warm glow over the well-tended merchandise and handsomely framed provincial maps that dot the varnished honey-pine walls.  Rows of pewter, brass and copper hooks hang over the iron-banded oak chest that stands near a curtained alcove.  An elaborate globe, inlaid with precious gemstones, rests on the centrally located polished walnut counter.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="346" name="Piralpa Tridents, Coral Showroom" note="Piralpa Tridents|Tridents" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sculpted in bas-relief, images of fish with childlike faces adorn the coral walls, their glassy gem eyes following any motion in the room due to tricks of light and shadow.  The monotony of the rough walls is broken not only by these cheerful masques but by a series of thick colored bands, adding a rainbow of seafoam greens, ocean blues and pastel pinks to the otherwise pale coral room.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="347" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandstone arch" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="347" name="Piralpa Tridents, Shell Showroom" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Shells from a variety of sea creatures turn the floor into a sparkling mosaic of iridescent color, a strong contrast to the dull beige shade of the walls.  From the pale ceiling hang a few twisted ribbons of dried seaweed, suspending decorative bits of coral and stone to be reflected in the glossy and buffed surface of the floor.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="346" />
  </node>
  <node id="348" name="The Future is Now, Workshop" note="Future is Now|The Future is Now" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The once spacious workshop is cramped by mechanical flights of fantasy.  Many are little more than carefully annotated blueprints, scattered springs and stray gears, while others proudly proclaim their completion with scribbled price tags.  Some merchandise lies in tangles and piles of clutter, while others sprawl across the workbench, a side table, the assorted shelving and even the walls.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go egress" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="349" name="Gosling's Exotic Fish" note="Gosling's Exotic Fish" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Colorful fish dart amidst the greenery in a large tank along the far wall of the shop.  Above the tank, water trickles from tier to tier down a roughly carved blue sandstone waterfall, finally tumbling into the tank.  Light reflecting off the surface of the water sends flickering patterns dancing around the room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brass door" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="350" name="Crimson Dragon Gaming, Sea Chamber" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Crystal columns form a semicircle about a wall of glass that stretches along one side of the room and looks directly into the sea beneath the island.  Schools of tiny phosphorescent fish dance and dart within the columns, creating shifting patterns of light throughout the chamber.  The caller stands before the backdrop of ocean life that thrives a few feet away.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandstone staircase" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="351" name="Looty Booty, Salesfloor" note="Looty Booty|Booty" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Glass-fronted wooden cabinets line the walls, their black velvet-covered shelves displaying the exquisite wares to a well-heeled clientele.  The pale woods of the paneling and floor provide a sharp contrast to the plush ebony-hued shelving.  Genteel salespeople unobtrusively wait to help the patrons with their selections.</description>
    <position x="160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go square doorway" destination="270" />
  </node>
  <label text="Docks">
    <position x="80" y="-77" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bank">
    <position x="125" y="-77" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="GIFT">
    <position x="345" y="-230" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Raffles">
    <position x="120" y="-320" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Alterations">
    <position x="311" y="-300" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Item">
    <position x="260" y="-230" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Registration">
    <position x="260" y="-220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Faction">
    <position x="245" y="-260" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Auction">
    <position x="129" y="-173" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Limited">
    <position x="90" y="-250" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Treasures">
    <position x="80" y="-240" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Shrine">
    <position x="190" y="-320" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dolefaren">
    <position x="40" y="-380" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crown and Anchor">
    <position x="190" y="-420" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Sea Otter Smash">
    <position x="210" y="165" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bobbing">
    <position x="440" y="-117" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="for Lamprey">
    <position x="440" y="-105" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crimson Dragon">
    <position x="153" y="-120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Stupid">
    <position x="460" y="-80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Terrestrian">
    <position x="450" y="-70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tricks">
    <position x="460" y="-60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crystal">
    <position x="235" y="-70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tunnel">
    <position x="235" y="-60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Races">
    <position x="237" y="-50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Great Sea Battle">
    <position x="-50" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Don't">
    <position x="365" y="-120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Tea">
    <position x="365" y="-100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Drogor Shrine">
    <position x="-145" y="-50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Touch Vine (teleport down)">
    <position x="-130" y="-220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="(pull) Fortuneteller">
    <position x="130" y="-60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Rothov's area">
    <position x="250" y="123" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Grichye">
    <position x="150" y="-10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wierge">
    <position x="150" y="-30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pishuna">
    <position x="50" y="-210" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Elven peddler">
    <position x="220" y="-178" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zentham">
    <position x="140" y="-150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Brine Sharks">
    <position x="-3" y="-241" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cloud Eels">
    <position x="-50" y="-135" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="* Various Mobs">
    <position x="80" y="0" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Various Mobs:">
    <position x="-140" y="120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="* decomposing Merelew">
    <position x="-150" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="* Torbisan decapods">
    <position x="-150" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="* deeplight fish">
    <position x="-150" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="* rockclaw lobsters">
    <position x="-150" y="160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="* ambulatory coral reef">
    <position x="-150" y="170" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="NPCs:">
    <position x="-150" y="-385" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wierge: Custom login/logouts">
    <position x="-150" y="-370" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Grichye: Custom depart messages">
    <position x="-150" y="-355" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Rothov: Weapon enchantments (wanders)">
    <position x="-150" y="-340" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Elven peddler: Gift wrapping">
    <position x="-150" y="-325" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pishuna: Chocolates">
    <position x="-150" y="-310" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zentham: Counterfeit Ecospheres">
    <position x="-150" y="-295" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crafting Tasks (NPCs wander):">
    <position x="310" y="-405" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zasele: Outfitting">
    <position x="320" y="-390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bradyn: Engineering">
    <position x="320" y="-375" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Poltu: Smithing">
    <position x="320" y="-360" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Spill">
    <position x="365" y="-110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="(DANGER)">
    <position x="78" y="-228" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Lounges">
    <position x="245" y="-250" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bingo">
    <position x="210" y="-90" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>
