<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Aesthene's Close 449 (2024)" id="501">
  <node id="1" name="Aesthene's Close, Central Vault" note="raffle" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Interspersed with painted almagarus flower tiles, glittering cobblestone flooring stretches across the cavernous hold.  A barrel vaulted ceiling adds more height to the already spacious chamber, its simple sloped arch curving between the stacked stone walls.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Aesthene's Close, Southern Vault" note="Southern Vault|south" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Interspersed with painted horeb root tiles, glittering cobblestone flooring stretches across the cavernous hold.  A barrel vaulted ceiling adds more height to the already spacious chamber, its simple sloped arch curving between the stacked stone walls.</description>
    <position x="160" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Aesthene's Close, Western Vault" note="Western Vault|west" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Interspersed with painted Elvish urn tiles, glittering cobblestone flooring stretches across the cavernous hold.  A barrel vaulted ceiling adds more height to the already spacious chamber, its simple sloped arch curving between the stacked stone walls.</description>
    <position x="120" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Aesthene's Close, Eastern Vault" note="Eastern Vault|east" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Interspersed with painted tamarind tree tiles, glittering cobblestone flooring stretches across the cavernous hold.  A barrel vaulted ceiling adds more height to the already spacious chamber, its simple sloped arch curving between the stacked stone walls.</description>
    <position x="200" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Aesthene's Close, Northern Vault" note="Northern Vault|north" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Interspersed with painted dirdel flower tiles, glittering cobblestone flooring stretches across the cavernous hold.  A barrel vaulted ceiling adds more height to the already spacious chamber, its simple sloped arch curving between the stacked stone walls.</description>
    <position x="160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Aesthene's Close, The Vaults">
    <description>Continuing to spiral in a slight incline, the gilded deobar planks are flanked by stacked stone walls.  Thin streamers of glittery silk hang from gaethzen sconces in graceful twists and loops.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Aesthene's Close, The Vaults">
    <description>Enclosed by stacked stone walls, gilded deobar planks form a graceful spiraling ramp with a gentle incline.  Thin streamers of glittery silk hang from gaethzen sconces in festive swoops and swags.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Aesthene's Close, Crystal Chamber" note="portal" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>The narrow, sloping sides of the vaulted ceiling create a mirror-like effect that amplifies the vivid colors that saturate the room's curved walls.  Constantly shifting in their prismatic dance, brilliant rainbows emerge from a massive, glittering crystal that is suspended in mid-air at the very center of the room.  Multiple open corridors branch away from the circular room, but an undulating, kaleidoscopic ward blocks access to all passageways except for the one to the north.  An ornately gilded ramp, located directly beneath the crystal, leads downwards into another area.</description>
    <position x="160" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go colorful portal" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go prismatic portal" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Aesthene's Close, Corridor">
    <description>Overlain with decorative wood slats, the stacked stone walls form a narrow passageway to traverse through.  Tiny glittering tiles are pieced together into a colorful mosaic floor, depicting a pattern of swirling orlog faces.  Flanked by gaethzen sconces, jewel-toned brocade tapestries bring a touch of softness to the long corridor.</description>
    <position x="160" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock1|one" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting rainbow hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock8|eight" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting violet hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock7|seven" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting indigo hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock6|six" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting blue hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock5|five" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting green hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock4|four" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting yellow hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock3|three" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting orange hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Aesthene's Close, Chronoscape" note="lock2|two" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shifting red hues pulse overhead, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern amidst the shattered shards of a dark fathomless ceiling.  Fractured orlogs are jumbled together and form a floor of wreckage that drifts aimlessly above a bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Foyer" color="White">
    <description>Subdued lighting illuminates the tasteful wooden paneling of the room while a bevy of overstuffed furniture provides comfortable seating for those contemplating weighty choices.  Thick plush carpets in a myriad of hues cover the floor, almost totally obscuring the pale wooden planks of the flooring.  Around the walls, a number of colored archways contain magical portals that, when open, allow access to the prize rooms beyond.  A large set of double doors allows access to rooms devoted to dispenser activities while a round opening leads to the area devoted to workshops for alterations.</description>
    <position x="180" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go return portal" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green portal" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue portal" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Green Suite, Olive Hall" color="White">
    <description>Coats of olive paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green portal" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Green Suite, Sea-Green Hall" note="Sea-Green Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of pale sea-green paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <position x="260" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Green Suite, Avocado Chamber" note="Avocado Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the rich avocado-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="260" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Green Suite, Malachite Niche" note="Malachite Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the rich malachite-hued plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="240" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Green Suite, Pickle-Green Cubicle" note="Pickle-Green Cubicle|crafting" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the pickle-hued walls, the room is bare of adornment.  Simple gaethzen globes hanging from the ceiling provide light.  The lack of ornamentation focuses attention on the prizes on display.</description>
    <position x="280" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Green Suite, Grass-Green Hall" note="Grass-Green Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of vibrant grass-green paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <position x="280" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Green Suite, Sage Chamber" note="Sage Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the muted sage-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="280" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Green Suite, Chartreuse Niche" note="Chartreuse Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the eye-searing chartreuse plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="260" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Green Suite, Moss Cubicle" note="Moss Cubicle" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the moss-colored walls, the room is bare of adornment.  Simple gaethzen globes hanging from the ceiling provide light.  The lack of ornamentation focuses attention on the prizes on display.</description>
    <position x="300" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Green Suite, Viridian Hall" note="Viridian Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of deep viridian paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <position x="320" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Green Suite, Emerald Chamber" note="Emerald Chamber|heroic|tattoos" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the brilliant emerald-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="320" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Green Suite, Pear Niche" note="Pear Niche|moon mage" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the pale pear-green plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="300" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Green Suite, Pine-Green Cubicle" note="Pine-Green Cubicle|foci" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the pine-colored walls, the room is bare of adornment.  Simple gaethzen globes hanging from the ceiling provide light.  The lack of ornamentation focuses attention on the prizes on display.</description>
    <position x="340" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Green Suite, Lime Hall" note="Lime Hall|armor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of bright lime-green paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving an upbeat feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <position x="340" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Green Suite, Pistachio Chamber" note="Pistachio Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the pastel pistachio-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="340" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Green Suite, Verdigris Niche" note="Verdigris Niche|weapons" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the verdigris-colored plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="320" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Blue Suite, Royal-Blue Hall" note="Royal-Blue Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a deep royal-blue hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue portal" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Blue Suite, Ocean-Blue Hall" note="Ocean-Blue Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a pale ocean-blue hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="200" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Blue Suite, Turquoise Hall" note="Turquoise Hall|f2p" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a bright turquoise hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="220" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Dispenser Hall" note="Dispenser Hall|raffle" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Centered in the middle of the floor, a luxurious carpet covers the polished wooden floor underneath a cut-crystal chandelier.  Oak paneling covers the walls while pale ecru plaster coats the spaces between the coffered ceiling.  A few leather armchairs provide seating for those needing time to contemplate their choices.</description>
    <position x="200" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="The Strand, Sandy Path" note="Map1_Crossing.xml" color="White">
    <description>Following the roadside along the Oxenwaithe's bank, you are struck by the quiet beauty of the place.  Taking pause to breathe in the crisp, clean air, you reflect on your surroundings.  Sand, sparkling as if mixed with diamond dust, pours into deep blue undulating waters.  A lush copse of trees spreads to the north, while to the southeast, a series of delightful small buildings is set back from the river's edge.</description>
    <position x="120" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
  </node>
  <label text="Exit Portal">
    <position x="90" y="-10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Raffles">
    <position x="180" y="-20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Time Locks">
    <position x="130" y="-70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Northern Vault">
    <position x="170" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Southern Vault">
    <position x="120" y="250" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Eastern Vault">
    <position x="210" y="190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Western Vault">
    <position x="30" y="190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="weapons">
    <position x="324" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="armor">
    <position x="344" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="foci">
    <position x="344" y="-10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="moon">
    <position x="300" y="-30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="mage">
    <position x="300" y="-20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="tattoos">
    <position x="324" y="10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="crafting">
    <position x="250" y="-20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="f2p">
    <position x="196" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>