<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Mer'Kresh" id="107">
  <node id="1" name="Carillon, Garden" note="Premium Portal|Portal" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>A barrier of hostas and ferns set between the flagstones and a fountain is wide enough to block visitors tempted to leave the path but narrow enough that with a favorable breeze someone could toss a few crackers into the water.  Speckled carp swim lazily in the fountain, some weave among the lily pad stems and some nudge against the curved bowl as if looking for a crumb of bread.  A thicket of forsythia grows between the path and the carillon.</description>
    <position x="40" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meeting portal" destination="315" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>Curving from the south, the flagstone path continues its tour around the Carillon, still visible as it rises above the trees lining the inner side of the path.  A small herd of metal oxen grazes among stands of ornamental grass.  Garlands, each woven of vines, bits of paper, and flowers have been placed around the necks of the sculpture.</description>
    <position x="40" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>Soft cooing floats from a dovecote sitting on the outer side of the path, and periodically a curious bird pokes its head out to gaze at the passersby.  Light glints off the breeze-rippled surface of a shallow reflecting pool.  At the end across from the dovecote is a bronze statue of a woman kneeling as she sets a toy ship into the pool.  The carillon is visible to the southwest.</description>
    <position x="40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>Several black basalt slabs surrounding a sphere sculpted from lava sit near the inner edge of the path.  A flame flickers from atop the ball, an eternal reminder of the fire warming the heart of M'Riss.  A curved bench rests on the outer edge of the flagstones, providing a clear view of the carillon rising in the distance behind the garden's stone sentinels.</description>
    <position x="20" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>Tree roots burrowing under the path have caused several of the flagstones to buckle.  A tulip and iris border fails to brighten the drab-colored mosaic set outside the path.  Untrellised, straggling wysteria dot the area between the path and the carillon, their slender switches lashing in even the slightest breeze as though a gale were blowing through them.</description>
    <position x="0" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>Bamboo chimes dangle from the branches of a grove of rosewood trees that separates the path from the carillon.  Lilies ring the trunks of the rosewoods and between them, a vibrant carpet of crocus paints a sea of color.  On the opposite side of the path, a bed of tiny, multi-hued shells holds a large bronze chime and a statue of a sitting jackal.  Dull basalt stepping stones skirt the shells and disappear into a stand of mimosa.</description>
    <position x="0" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stepping stones" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>A small footbridge spanning an ornamental brook interrupts the winding flow of the flagstone path.  Roses mingling with honeysuckle climb the bridge's posts and stretch across its handrails.  Tangled vines grow along the banks of the stream and knee-high shrub parterres filled with flowers border the path.  As the path curves, the carillon can be seen rising to the north east.</description>
    <position x="0" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go footbridge" destination="347" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Carillon, Garden">
    <description>Each of the dark flagstones paving the Carillon path has been carefully shaped for fit and appearance, which, along with the meticulous care of the plants, lends a formal grace to the gardens.  A low border of phlox edges the pathway as it continues north toward the Carillon.  Bright hued flowers to the east and west beckon visitors with their color and aroma.</description>
    <position x="20" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sculpted archway" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Carillon, Entrance" note="Carillon">
    <description>Night fails to darken the sparkle of the quartz flecks of the Carillon's sandy granite exterior, and a glow from within lights the stained glass windows.  Only the bells, normally visible through the arches beneath the roof during the day, are hidden in shadow.</description>
    <description>Towering above the city, the Carillon tolls the sailor's watch and serves as a look-out for those who wait for a mariner's return.  Centered on the innermost disk, this slender obelisk is home to those who seek comfort and counsel.  Flecks of quartz in the sandy granite exterior sparkle in the light, and stained glass windows, like a jeweled belt, encircle the building midway to the top.  Atop, bells hang in the open arches supporting the roof.</description>
    <position x="20" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carved archway" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Carillon, Main Hall">
    <description>Light from the glow of burning votive candles banked around the room rises upwards to illuminate the massive stained glass windows set high in the carillon.  Thick, angular lines form a complex, intersecting pattern which nearly spans the length and breadth of the pale marble floor.  A staircase zig-zags upward above the doorway toward the belltower.</description>
    <description>Beams of jewel-toned light shine down from the stained glass windows, drowning the glow of burning votive candles banked around the room.  Thick, angular lines form a complex, intersecting pattern on the marble floor and colors streaming from the windows cast puddles of color.  A staircase zig-zags upward above the doorway toward the belltower.</description>
    <position x="20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carved archway" hidden="True" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Carillon, Stairs">
    <description>A slender handrail and low ledge on the outside of the narrow stairs are all that prevent someone from plummeting to the marble floor below.  A gilded framed landscape adds a splash of color to the sand-toned wall.  There is a small landing at the top of the staircase, just wide enough to turn to climb the next flight.</description>
    <position x="20" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Carillon, Stairs">
    <description>A slender handrail and low ledge on the outer edge of the narrow stairs are all that prevent someone from plummeting to the marble floor below.  More steep than the last flight, the stairs cling precariously to the carillon wall.  There is a small landing at the top of the staircase, just wide enough to turn to climb to the next flight.  From this height, the lines on the floor resolve clearly into a mariner's compass.</description>
    <position x="20" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Carillon, Stairs">
    <description>A slender handrail and low ledge on the outside of the narrow stairs are all that prevent someone from plummeting to the marble floor below.  There is a small landing at the top of the steep staircase, just wide enough to turn to climb to the next flight.  Midway, one of the treads has become loose and wobbly.</description>
    <position x="20" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Carillon, Stairs">
    <description>A slender handrail and low ledge on the outer edge of the narrow stairs are all that prevent someone from plummeting to the marble floor below.  The angle of the staircase pitches more sharply between the landings than the previous flight.  A tapestry, the linen frayed and wool faded with time, hangs on the stairwell wall.</description>
    <position x="20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Carillon, Stairs">
    <description>A slender handrail and low ledge on the outside of the narrow stairs are all that prevent someone from plummeting to the marble floor below.  At this point the staircase is nearly vertical as it scales the inside of the tapering tower.  At the summit of the ladder-like stairs is a small landing leading to a door.</description>
    <position x="20" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small door" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Lavishly detailed carvings grace the archway leading to the Carillon and its gardens.  The normal throng of people has thinned to a few evening strollers, intent upon the city's pleasures instead of its business.</description>
    <description>Lavishly detailed carvings grace the archway leading to the sole haven from the city's press of people -- the Carillon and its gardens.  Here on the cobbled street, throngs of people intent upon their business shoulder past, yet some glance wistfully towards the arch and up toward the magnificent bell tower.</description>
    <position x="20" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Tendrils of spider vines cascade from the rooftop garden and down the front of a tall building dominating its neighbors.  Trailing greenery nearly obscures the arched windows and polished basalt facade.  Perhaps discouraged by the pointy-eared mastiff patrolling the small fenced yard, few people choose to visit this dark edifice.</description>
    <position x="20" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze gate" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Front Yard">
    <description>High above, a colorful awning peeks out from the edge of the rooftop between hanging strings of spider vines that cascade down the manor's walls.  At regular intervals along the upper ledges, stone gargoyles leer downward with mouths gaping open, some of their number wrapped in cloaks of vines.  Far closer to the ground, an ironwood door allows entry into the building.</description>
    <position x="20" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze gate" hidden="True" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Side Yard">
    <description>Brown and red bricks set into the basalt of the manor outline each of the arched windows and emphasize the building's rich opulence.  Spider vines struggle across some of the sills, winding down toward the ground from their source on the rooftop.  Additional victims of the strangling vines are the gargoyles of varied design that stare from the heights into the gurgling canal.</description>
    <position x="20" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spider vine" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Gaps between the buildings provide a glimpse of the canal water slapping against the foundation of the middle ring.  While all the stores enjoy a brisk business, the clear focus belongs to a shop sporting a startlingly purple door inlaid with quartz chunks.  The road's arc serves as a buffer between the Warrior Mage guild to the northeast, and Caress-of-the-Moons Manor to the west.</description>
    <position x="120" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Mer'Kresh, Dajere Bridge">
    <description>The outer and inner canals meet in a clash of currents at the Dajere Bridge.  Stone pelicans stand atop the side railings while their living models roost between.  The roadways are mostly untraveled this time of day, and few barge captains will risk the tricky turn from one canal into the other during darkness.</description>
    <description>The outer and inner canals meet in a clash of currents at the Dajere Bridge.  Stone pelicans stand atop the side railings while their living models wheel freely among the bridge's stone pilings.  Largely unnoticed by people scurrying on the roadways above, barges laden with cargo negotiate the tricky turn from one canal into the other.</description>
    <position x="140" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Mer'Kresh, Dajere Bridge">
    <description>Unlike the other bridges, Dajere Bridge is unique in the way it crosses the canals.  Except for where it connects with both Gull Circle and Shell Circle, the bridge is free-standing, supported only by scalloped basalt columns rising from the canals.  Enough space is left between the pilings to allow barges and gondolas free passage beneath the bridge, as well as plenty of room for the daring seagull or pelican to swoop after a meal.</description>
    <position x="160" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Mer'Kresh, Dajere Bridge" note="Dajere Bridge">
    <description>High above the waters of the canal, stone pelicans march in neat rows along the top of the railings.  A few gaze upward at the sky, as though wishing to rejoin their living companions, while others gaze longingly at the canal.  Many are marred, scratched by carts from uncaring delivery folk or rocks from vandalistic children.</description>
    <position x="180" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Mer'Kresh, Dajere Bridge">
    <description>The roofs of warehouses along the wharves are visible just over the intervening lines of homes and shops.  Nestled in the seedier section of town, the wharf warehouses are filled with goods from smaller docks along the canal, which in turn are fed by the barges that cautiously manuever across the water.  If one were to stay here for several hours, the entire process of loading and unloading could be easily seen from this section of the bridge.</description>
    <position x="200" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Mer'Kresh, Dajere Bridge">
    <description>A parade of sculpted pelicans marches down the side railings of Dajere Bridge, repeated symbols of the bridge's namesake.  Though this is the closest bridge to the wharves and the arriving ships from other lands, many townsfolk and travelers prefer to walk a fair distance northwards to make use of Tamris Bridge, choosing a stroll through the seedier section of Mer'Kresh to the perils of construction on southern Gull Circle.</description>
    <position x="240" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb construction barricade" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Four minarets jut from the corners of a single-storied white marble building.  Although no fence protects the structure, the surrounding buildings seem to shrink away from the acrid scent of naphtha mingled with incense and salt water.  Continuing its broad curve, the road's southwest sweep angles toward the Dajere Bridge.</description>
    <position x="160" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white building" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Banners touting the current special exhibits flutter between the Mer'Kresh Museum's carved granite columns.  A fountain set at the top of the entrance sends a stream of water down a shallow channel cut in the middle of the stairway.  Students and visitors have deserted the museum steps, but the gulls remain -- roosting or splashing in the fountain, vigilant for food in a generous or careless hand.</description>
    <description>Banners touting the current special exhibits flutter between the Mer'Kresh Museum's carved granite columns.  A fountain set at the top of the entrance sends a stream of water down a shallow channel cut in the middle of the stairway.  Students comparing lecture notes crowd the broad steps, and small children harass the gulls begging an honest meal from anyone eating.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Pelts, strings of teeth, and various animal parts hang from the entrance awning to a cramped-looking store.  Squeezed between taller neighbors, high narrow windows in the building's upper stories emphasize the structure's slender facade.  A faint chant from the north mixes with the clip-clop of dray animals hauling goods through the city.</description>
    <position x="100" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go store" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Clutter fills the front window of a small shop -- old clothing, tarnished armor, once-treasures now unwanted or perhaps stolen.  Shoppers pause to look in the windows, and occasionally someone ducks into the door with a bundle underarm, later emerging packageless.  The cobbled street continues to curve north, a worn red course separating the Carillon wall from the line of tightly packed buildings opposite.</description>
    <position x="100" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pawn shop" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>The soft light glowing from the library's windows is disturbed by people moving among the bookshelves, and casts flickering shadows on the Carillon garden wall.  Two stone dolphins flanking the broad library steps shelter a brood of sleeping pigeons.</description>
    <description>Recent patches of soft grey stucco mottle the Carillon garden wall.  Nearby, threads of people weave into knots, then unravel, as quick words of business or perhaps simple greetings are exchanged.  Two stone dolphins flank the broad library steps where they watch over lounging drunks and patrons pursuing diversion.</description>
    <position x="60" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go library steps" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" note="South Barricade" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Except for a handful of simple tools such as shovels and hammers, there are few signs of a construction in progress.  The cobblestones are in place, and the edges of the street are lined with stone guardrails.  Only the lack of buildings betrays what work is needed, but meanwhile the empty spaces reveal an unobstructed view of the ocean.</description>
    <position x="220" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb construction barricade" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Soldiers of the construction world, wheelbarrows line the edge of the road in tight rows.  Most of them wear the grey and white scars that a load full of stones would leave behind, while others are marked by reddish flakes of rust from exposure to the salty sea air.  For now, the burden they've carried is gone, and rest they will until they are called upon again.</description>
    <position x="200" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A covering of dirt and pebbles partly masks the cobblestones.  Aside from a good sweeping, this section of the construction area looks in complete readiness to be opened.  Westwards, the gaping maws of open pits and unfinished street surfaces tells a different story, while southwards only the eternal rising and falling of the ocean's waves awaits.</description>
    <position x="180" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Planks and temporary fences become border guards as Gull Circle curves along its path.  Each of the guardians vigilantly watch over one of several open gaps in the street, protecting both the workers from a fall and the pits from unwelcome additions to their contents.  A clearly defined line cuts across the road where the cobblestones stop and the underlying ridge stones are revealed.</description>
    <position x="160" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The sounds of waves crashing down upon the stones on either side of the road is as regular as a heartbeat, pounding out a steady and noisy rhythm that drowns even the sounds of the ever present sea winds.  Though they can not be heard clearly, the winds make their presence known by whipping at whatever loose objects they find.  Far to the south of this nearby combination of sky and surf, the hazy line of the horizon lay.</description>
    <position x="80" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The backs of the buildings and homes of Pearl Circle look across the canal at the construction in progress along Gull Circle.  Many of the structures are reinforced with stone and wood, and few have low windows despite the fact that a thief would have to risk drowning to manage a break-in.  Odd marks along the walls appear to be some form of damage, but a closer examination -- difficult to do from here -- would be necessary to be sure.</description>
    <position x="20" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A fair distance to the northwest, the arching form of Zirelga Bridge rises easily from behind the nearby stacks of brick and stone that litter the unfinished street.  One end of the bridge disappears behind the buildings across the canal while the other abruptly stops as it juts out over Gull Circle.  Duplicating the function of the bridge in a small scale, a thick wooden board stretches across one of the pits that are so common along this section of the road.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden board" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Looking more like a letter in Gamgweth than a street, the road splits into two halves that straddle a rubble- and water-filled pit.  The walls of the pit reveal the layered construction of Mer'Kresh: the cobblestones rest on a bed of crushed stone that in turn overlays a mass of rubble and broken rock.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden board" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The remains of a seagull lie dead-center in the road, torn to shreds by some predator.  Around the kill, the stones are jagged and cracked, as through something massive collided into them from above.  Wide and open, the sky is unobstructed by buildings or other structures, lending no credence to the concept that the murderer of the gull came from on high.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The foul stench of uncovered garbage rises from a wide hole in the surface of the road, overwhelming the salty sea breeze.  A circle of gull feathers surrounds the refuse-filled pit, left behind when their previous owners swooped in for a quick meal.  Along one side, a wooden plank has been fastened down to keep the hole from swallowing runaway wheelbarrows.</description>
    <position x="-281" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb bridge support" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Mer'Kresh, Zirelga Bridge" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A dented wheelbarrow lies beneath the unfinished lip of Zirelga Bridge, its handles cracked and its contents long gone.  At this stage of construction, the bridge is little more than a glorified dumping ramp, used by workers to unload their hauls of garbage.  A stone block, halfway up the support of the bridge, channels the dumped rubbish to one side.  From there, the debris is carried off to fill in holes along the road.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone block" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The swirling and foaming waters of the ocean churn against the black basalt exposed from beneath the road as a sudden transition takes place.  The rock and wooden framework of a construction in progress yields to the intermittent placement of dark stones rising from the sea.  The rectangular walls are representatives of the first stages of ring-building, and are designed to be platforms to support both workers and the later layers of stones.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Here, the road is nothing more than the top of several closely packed stone walls.  Shiny from the sea waters washing over them, the largest of the walls flank either side of where the finished road will be, and the spaces between will eventually be filled with rubble, rock and garbage.  The western most wall is severed from this section of the road by a water-filled channel, so any travel to the north must take place across the surface of the eastern one.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A huge bulge curves out of the wall, filled with gently rocking sea water.  The dark pool of water gurgles with every thrust of the waves, but the walls of its confinement keep it mainly separate from the freedom of the wide ocean.  One large stone, reinforced with wooden supports, sits directly across from the bulge on the other side of the channel that guts the middle of the road.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Beyond the mirrored twin of this road atop the walls, the ocean heaves, white-caps dancing atop its shifting surface.  Swept away by the tides, bits of driftwood bob in the currents, occasionally rapping against the sides of the stones in the walls before being pulled away and back into Eluned's caress.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Jagged basalt clamors in the surf around the bases of the stone walls, wet and sharp.  Northwards, room to walk is virtually non-existent, replaced by the chaotic piles of the black stones.  Above the rocky clutter, a wooden walkway allows workers to continue with their tasks in relative safety.  Here and south, only the flat tops of the water barrier is available to stand upon.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="276" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden steps" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A temporary pier of scaffolding mounts the walls and tapering dikes to provide workers with sure footing.  Hanging from one of the support beams, a bucket sways in the wind, its contents clattering as it moves.  Just beneath the planking of the makeshift walkway, the explosive sound of the ocean washing over the jumbled stones shakes the wood, and sends the bucket into yet another shifting motion.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="212" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden steps" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Most of the pilings and posts that support the wooden walkway lean askew, pushed off kilter by the movement of the heavy and keen-edged boulders underneath.  The boards, glossy and green from the constant dampness, shudder under the slightest weight or the most gentle push of the wind.  Whenever a particularly potent wave slams into the barrier, some unseen part of the walkway growls angrily as it shakes and repositions itself.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="148" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Abruptly stopping over a mound of pointed basalt, the walkway lacks any safety features such as guardrails or warning signs.  One heavy black stone in particular is a favorite spot for the waves to dash, if only because its great size presents such a good target.  Just poking from the surface of the waves, another series of black basalt curves in mimicry, shielding this one from the worst of the ocean's assault.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="104" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black stone" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Only slightly more stable than its twin to the west, this heap of rock and rubble is at least saved from the most dramatic of swells flooding over both.  All manner of rough stonework is half-buried in the mounds, from cracked sculptures and friezes to the remnants of support columns and paving stones.  Some are glaringly apparent, the white of pitted marble contrasting sharply with the dark basalt.  Others are more subtle, like the mostly-covered face of the statue gazing from the shattered rocks.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden walkway" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The wet, black stones underfoot shift menacingly in the tide, every so often uttering a muffled plop as one of their number slides into the sea.  Thick pilings struggle to keep the pile of stones from vanishing completely under the onslaught of the ocean's power, but their barnacle-encrusted forms betray the weakened state that their time in the water has brought.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Mer'Kresh, Southern Canal Gate" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Solidly mortared and built from heavy blocks of basalt, the base for the planned canal gate is closer to completion than the surrounding ring, and stands out from the surrounding pile of rough and loose rock.  Ebbing waves slicken the stones on top of the base with spray and foam.  Caught only by the most violent splashes, a brilliant red banner flutters from atop a wooden pole.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb metal gate" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Sandalwood incense overlays the ever-present scent of seawater.  Like the chanting, it drifts from a marble building set behind a wrought iron fence.  Centered upon a neatly clipped swath of green, the Cleric's Guild sits apart, as if the other buildings defer to its holiness.  Still clinging to the Carillon wall, the road curves northwest, toward the more secular sections of the city.</description>
    <position x="100" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cleric guild" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Stately and austere, the Courthouse dominates the northeast corner of Ship Circle.  Alone among the lands of Elanthia, Mer'Kresh disdains brutal forms of justice -- no jails, no stocks, nor flogging pillars are present to coerce citizens to obey the law.  Soft chanting fills the night's breeze, serenading the occasional passerby or strolling couple.</description>
    <description>Stately and austere, the Courthouse dominates the northeast corner of Ship Circle.  Alone among the lands of Elanthia, Mer'Kresh disdains brutal forms of justice -- no jails, no stocks, nor flogging pillars are present to coerce citizens to obey the law.  Soft chanting fills the lulls in the chatter of passersby as they scurry towards the Town Hall or head in the direction of the Cleric's Guild.</description>
    <position x="40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go courthouse" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Even at night, the volume of citizens coming and going distinguishes the unassuming entrance to the Town Hall.  Opposite, the Carillon wall bordering the road is obscured by tendrils of ivy that have escaped the garden and spilled over the city side of the wall.  The cobbled road's gentle circular bend arcs toward the Trader's Guild and Courthouse.</description>
    <description>Set within a row of tall brown buildings, only the volume of citizens coming and going distinguishes the unassuming entrance to the Town Hall.  Opposite, the Carillon wall bordering the road is obscured by tendrils of ivy that have escaped the garden and spilled over the city side of the wall.  The cobbled road's gentle circular bend arcs toward the Trader's Guild and Courthouse.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town hall" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Night quiets the boasting and mock jeers that usually accompany the drivers waiting outside the Traders' Guild for their next assignment.  A few traders add to the low buzz of noise as they check their caravans in preparation for the next journey.  Light flickering from iron lanterns provides just enough illumination for the guild servants to sweep the day's debris from the road.</description>
    <description>Boasts and mock jeers accompany the goodnatured swaggering of drivers waiting outside the Traders' Guild for their next assignment.  Some traders add spirited voices to the noise, yelling wagers on pack animals or commenting acidly about the quality of the drivers -- others clutch their contracts, grimly silent while preparing for the next journey.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>The road bends sharply, angling northeast towards the Traders' Guild, south past Tillithern's Emporium and continuing toward the Bank.  Birds nesting on the ledges and under the eaves of the tall buildings coo lullabies to their chicks.</description>
    <description>The road bends sharply, angling northeast towards the Traders' Guild, south past Tillithern's Emporium and continuing toward the Bank.  Birds nest on the ledges and under the eaves of the tall buildings.  Screeching, they launch themselves into the air intent upon their own business, an avian imitation of the people below.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="248" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>People stream through the doors of a domed building, hopeful that haste will prevent them from being victimized by the unsavory individuals loitering outside.  Even at night, groups of hawkers yell themselves hoarse with extravagant claims about their merchandise and shifty-looking characters try to dodge the guard's watchful eyes by melting into the shadows.  Although a garbage can sits near the building's entrance, most people just throw their trash into the street.</description>
    <description>People stream through the doors of a domed building, hopeful that haste will prevent them from being victimized by the unsavory individuals loitering outside.  Hawkers yell themselves hoarse with extravagant claims about their merchandise and shifty-looking characters try to dodge the guard's watchful eyes by melting into the shadows.  Although a garbage can sits near the building's entrance, most people just throw their trash into the street.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go domed building" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>Bright red curtains embroidered with silver stars flutter from an open shop window.  Tubs planted with violet phlox rest on a stoop, and the brick face of a building complements the brick of the Carillon's garden wall opposite.  The cobbled road bends sharply to form a bowl that mixes the noises from the bank and boisterous singing from the southeast into a softer nighttime melody, missing only the daytime's high notes from swearing drivers and the counterpoint of pedestrian shouts.</description>
    <description>Bright red curtains embroidered with silver stars flutter from an open shop window.  Tubs planted with violet phlox rest on a stoop, and the brick face of a building complements the brick of the Carillon's garden wall opposite.  The cobbled road bends sharply to form a bowl that mixes the noise from the bank, swearing from drivers and shouts from pedestrians with boisterous singing from the southeast.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Mer'Kresh, Ship Circle">
    <description>The cacophony of pipes, strums, and thumped drums accompanied by voices raised in enthusiastic song tumbling from a one of the vibrantly painted buildings lining the cobbled roadway isn't stilled by the night or concern for anyone's peaceful sleep.  Wrought iron bars cover the upper windows of the building, seemingly more to keep people from falling out than to discourage intruders.  Further east, the ivy-covered wall enclosing the Carillon's garden meets the bell tower's arched entrance.</description>
    <description>A cacophony of pipes, strums, and thumped drums accompanied by voices raised in enthusiastic song tumble from a one of the vibrantly painted buildings lining the cobbled roadway.  Wrought iron bars cover the upper windows of the building, seemingly more to keep people from falling out than to discourage intruders.  Further east, the ivy-covered wall enclosing the Carillon's garden meets the bell tower's arched entrance.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>The air is perpetually warm, unnaturally heated by the flames from makeshift grills sitting behind buildings leading to one of the few open areas in the city.  Covered pots sitting near the fiery coals soak up some of the heat, and several men with mugs of steaming cocoa sit around discussing politics.  Businesses line the street, one store's window displaying leather armor beaded with cowrie shells.  In another shop, weapons gleam from a rack cleverly built into the casement.</description>
    <description>The air is perpetually warm, unnaturally heated by the flames from makeshift grills sitting behind buildings leading to one of the few open areas in the city.  Covered pots sitting near the fiery coals soak up some of the heat, and several children with long sticks take turns toasting gooey treats.  Businesses line the street, one store's window displaying leather armor beaded with cowrie shells.  In another shop, weapons gleam from a rack cleverly built into the casement.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oilcloth lean-to" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shop" destination="330" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lean" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Mer'Kresh, Undogoz Alley" note="Undogoz Alley">
    <description>Precious few alleys trail between the buildings of Mer'Kresh, and those that do manage to squeeze in an existence are often filled to capacity with all manner of odds and ends, crates and shipping goods, or simple refuse.  This alley, however, proves the exception, as its owners have kept the cramped area free of obstruction, leaving a clear path that runs directly back towards a small square overlooking the canal.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="316" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Stores and homes vie for space on the curving cobbled street.  Colorful paper decorations strung in the window of one shop flutter in the same breeze as laundry hanging from a window two stories above.  Sporadic rings from hammer striking metal pierce the night air from the south -- the weaponsmith has his apprentices working late again to fill their orders for merchandise.</description>
    <description>Stores and homes vie for space on the curving cobbled street.  Colorful paper decorations strung in the window of one shop flutter in the same breeze as laundry hanging from a window two stories above.  Sporadic rings from hammer striking metal sound from the south, blending with the laughter of children playing tag on the sidewalk.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Mer'Kresh, Nelyn Bridge">
    <description>A sculpted seal rookery rests atop the pedestals marking the entrance of the Nelyn Bridge.  Modest buildings adorned with flowerboxes squeeze against the bridge's abutments, and tiny stalls hung with merchandise line the bridge's cobbled surface, completely hiding the canal coursing so near.  Only the smell of salt, fish and damp hint at the water's presence.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Niches filled with sculptures of armored champions set one building apart from its plain-faced neighbors.  From it, a clatter of weapons practice echoes through the street and mingles with the plaintive braying of dray animals penned nearby.  Southwest, the towers of Nelyn Bridge are visible over the rooftops.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone arch" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Mer'Kresh, Sahra Bridge">
    <description>Massive paved arches bounding from ring to ring span the canals.  The bridge's carved basalt arcs mimic the stone dolphins sculpted along the outer walls.  One of the five bridges welding the circular city together, the Sahra Bridge's broad structure curves upward to allow gondolas passage beneath.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Conveniently wedged between the Tamris and Sahra bridges, the carousel provides supplemental storage to the tiny Rissan homes, as well as a place for nomadic adventurers to unburden themselves.  Across the cobbled street, unsavory-looking individuals clutching portfolios stuffed with papers mill around the back entrance to the Courthouse.</description>
    <position x="40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carousel" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Mer'Kresh, Tamris Bridge">
    <description>Stone convoys of brisk ships sail atop the arched walls of the Tamris Bridge.  Gulls and pelicans roost together peacefully on the bowsprits and gunnels of the sculpted vessels.  Dim globes of light surrounding the iron lanterns edging the walkway cast a soft glow along the street.  Every so often, the sound of footsteps echo from an unseen pedestrian as someone makes their way in the darkness.  Past the bridge's entrance, the cobbled street continues its northwest curve toward the Carousel.</description>
    <description>Stone convoys of brisk ships sail atop the arched walls of the Tamris Bridge.  Gulls twist in the air above the sculpted vessels, eager to dislodge the placid pelicans perched on the bowsprits and gunnels.  Below, tradesmen and shoppers, the idle and the adventurous, mingle on the streets heedless of the competition above them.  Past the bridge's entrance, the cobbled street continues its northwest curve toward the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>The road wends northwest past tightly clustered shops and offices.  A lopsided sign, the target of a variety of thrown weapons (including tomatoes), hangs bedraggled above an equally shabby doorway.  Across the cobbled street, several colossal statues sculpted in a severe, muscular style carry a domed roof upon their shoulders.  Doors set between the legs of the statues would dwarf even a Gor'Tog passing into the building.</description>
    <position x="160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Street cleaners leisurely sweep up the scraps of paper littering the cobbled road and small lawn outside an elegant building.  The frenzied activity of the day's business, shouting clerks and gossiping traders, has paused for the evening.  Only the scratch of brooms on pavement and echo of footsteps from an occasional pedestrian break the night's quiet.</description>
    <description>Harried-looking clerks waving scraps of paper shout excitedly as they rush between an elegant building and a group of mages poised next to their moon beams.  Amid the noise of the clerks and jumbled street sounds of the Zirelga Bridge to the northwest, knots of traders exchange news about crop conditions and gossip about the latest political rumors.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Mer'Kresh, Zirelga Bridge">
    <description>People trickle over the bridge in dim light cast by the flickering iron lanterns, and the canal's waters stream beneath.  Arched walkways flank the bridge's pavement, separated from the roadway by a low railing perfect for sitting on and watching the activity on the canal below.  Ornate starfish mosaics, the symbol of Tamris and Sahra's eldest daughter, Zirelga, decorates the arches and abutments.</description>
    <description>People stream over the bridge and the canal's waters stream beneath.  Arched walkways flank the bridge's pavement, separated from the roadway by a low railing perfect for sitting on and watching the activity on the canal below.  Ornate starfish mosaics, the symbol of Tamris and Sahra's eldest daughter, Zirelga, decorates the arches and abutments.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Mer'Kresh, Shell Circle">
    <description>Narrower in this section, the cobbled road bends southeast to meet the Zirelga Bridge.  A mash of vibrantly colored, closely packed buildings sacrifices space for cheerfulness.  People funnel through the street, careful to give reverent berth to a tall sculpture set on the walkway in front of one modest shop.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The darkened arch of Dajere Bridge rises from behind the buildings to the south and west as it spans the inner canals on a journey towards the center of town.  Though the buildings do not squeeze as tightly together here as they do to the north, the lack of illumination and oily cobblestones maintain the claustrophobic feel that pervades so much of the city.</description>
    <description>The density of buildings lessens towards the south, but enough are present to block sight of the base of Dajere Bridge as it arches over one of the canals.  Glimpses of trade ships and houseboats floating on Torbis Sanhalas peek through the alleys between shops and warehouses, while gulls wheel through the air, descending to the street long enough to make a meal of a discarded bit of food.</description>
    <position x="260" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The backsides of warehouses butt against the street as it curves towards the north and south.  Many days have come and gone since they were constructed, but their cracking bodies still can safely hold a horde of supplies from prying eyes.  Slogans and ads cover the streetside buildings from the ground to an arm's length above the height of the average Elf.  Few areas are spared, and both homes and commercial buildings wear the plastered advertisements.</description>
    <position x="280" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>A row of low shrubbery cordons off a yard in front of a large three-story home.  The building is as old and grey as the rest of the structures around this part of Mer'Kresh, but is hardly in disrepair.  Something unseen speaks of charming grandeur, like a whisper just out of earshot drifting on a breeze.  A small stone fountain trickles contentedly in the yard, adding another touch of elegance to the scene.</description>
    <position x="300" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Gull Circle, Deeper's Tavern">
    <description>An odd little building of cypress on a stone foundation stands north of the road.  From its windows, small and low to the ground, come laughter, song, and a warm, soft light.  Of all its oddities, the most striking is its entryway, through yawning, bleached jaws that once armed an enormous shark.  The gaping maw is hung with a net curtain, and over this fierce yet intriguing entrance hangs a sign.</description>
    <position x="320" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shark jaws" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Mer'Kresh, Wharfs">
    <description>The walls of yellowed warehouses and storage buildings form a man-made canyon, straight passage through made difficult by the seemingly random placement of stacks of crates.  Near the rooftops, narrow open windows squint from under the eaves, revealing several warehouses to be filled to the top with goods.</description>
    <position x="300" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Wharf End, Mer'Kresh" note="Jolas" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Through the gaps in the heavy wood planks, one can easily see the waters of Torbis Sanhalas lapping noisily at the pilings.  Although most of the surface of the wharf is covered by a wide assortment of boxes, barrels and shipping goods, there is little that would stop a dropped coin or trinket from vanishing through the slats and sinking into a watery grave.</description>
    <position x="320" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>In the darkness, the huddled forms of shabby buildings and run-down shops join into one solid block of black.  Somewhere fairly close, the sounds of sloshing water sneaks out to the street, barely perceptible when the wind jostles through the canyon of structures along the street.  Squares of colored paper flicker with the breeze, half-covering a faded diorama along the face of one of the larger buildings.</description>
    <description>Shabby buildings and run-down shops huddle closely together, the wooden planks of each of the structures' walls barely a hand's length apart.  In many cases, the buildings actually touch, leaning on one another for support or physically sharing a wall.  Half-covered by sales posters, a faded diorama runs the length of the otherwise bare face of a seedy-looking apartment building.</description>
    <position x="320" y="265" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go apartment building" destination="326" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Small bits of paper and debris swirl in the breeze, rustling softly against the sides of the faded buildings.  Many of the windows of the structures here are cracked or broken, taking on almost sinister characteristics within the night's embrace.  The cry of gulls that is so common during the daylight hours is missing, and a few white feathers drifting casually on the street become a reminder of their visits.</description>
    <description>Several seagulls strut and flit along the ground, snatching scraps of garbage and discarded food before hopping off to devour their meals.  The gulls are considerably braver here than elsewhere in Mer'Kresh, though this may owe as much to the abundance of loose trash as it does to any courage the birds can muster.  The flaking paint and broken windows of some of the buildings here echo the street's condition.</description>
    <position x="320" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The pungent scent of garbage floats out to the street from a nearby alley.  A banner, suspended between the two apartment buildings that flank the alley, shudders in the same evening breezes that drive the odor streetward.  Even though a torch lights a set of descending steps at the far end of the sidestreet, the glow offers little relief from the dark shadows that gloom the alley walls.</description>
    <description>Squeezed snugly in an alley between two apartment buildings is a descending series of stone steps.  Makeshift handrails flank the steps and a banner flaps from above the alley's entrance.  Someone has kept the narrow side street swept clean of most debris, but the nostril-flaring scent of rubbish still wafts through the air.  On the other end of the alley, the tops of gondolas can be seen bobbing on the canal waters.</description>
    <position x="320" y="115" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The scent of honeysuckle mingles with the smell of salt and fish with every breeze off of the bay.  An iron fence, veiled in shadowy vegetation, hides sight of the base of a belltower on the other side.  Torches flicker from the tower's belfry, illuminating a bell hanging silent within its stone embrace.</description>
    <description>Thick strands of honeysuckle dangle teasingly over the top of an iron fence, blocking all but scant glimpses of a stone building on the other side.  A bell tower rises proudly from the building, dwarfing the fence and the surrounding structures.  Attached firmly to one of the brick supports for the fence is a brass-plated plaque.</description>
    <position x="320" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The darkened silhouette of a large hammer creaks back and forth on top of an odd building.  Shades have been pulled across the windows from within, but a cheerful crowned face painted on one of the outside pane smiles to those braving the nighttime chill.  The words King's Hardware and Fine Goods are barely visible in the shadows above the door.</description>
    <description>An over-scaled wooden hammer nods in the wind from atop an oddly-angled building nearby.  Displayed in the windows of the shop are a wide assortment of tools and construction goods, and the painted image of fat crowned face gleefully peers out into the street.  Tacked above the door, a sign proclaims King's Hardware and Fine Goods in bright, flowing colors.</description>
    <position x="280" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The wagons and carts that narrow the street's passage are in turn oppressed by the shadows of nightfall.  The occasional flapping of cloth banners dangling in breezes above the alleys snaps out defiantly.  Every so often, the echo of shuffling footsteps patters in the darkness before being swallowed again in the still of the night.</description>
    <description>The backsides of stalls and wagons press in against the road, forcing it to narrow slightly in passing.  Bright and festive banners flutter madly in the breeze while colorful signs beckon passerby with promises of exotic wares at affordable prices.  The cry of an auctioneer echoes out from somewhere down one of the alleys that cut between the wagon carts.</description>
    <position x="260" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>An orange glow flickers from behind the closed windows of a slumping inn, the shutters allowing just splinters of light to escape and dance on the cobblestone street.  The quiet murmur of speech sneaks out of the inn, only to be dissolved by the gentle rushing of a seabreeze.  Along the roof, white shapes betray the location of several sleeping seagulls, resting silently through the night.</description>
    <description>The face of a large three-story inn stares longingly over the street and out across Torbis Sanhalas, its sagging doors and window frames becoming tired eyes and a saddened mouth.  Though this section of Mer'Kresh is comparatively young, enough years have passed to grey the inn's wooden frame.  Despite the toll time and the salt winds have taken, the inn has been maintained in a usable state.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Mer'Kresh, Tamris Bridge">
    <description>A half-ring of red bricks partially encircles an abrupt drop-off where the Tamris bridge once crossed the canal.  It also marks a change in the surrounding buildings as the festively painted shades of the north yield to the darker and more mundane colors of the south.  Rubble, sent flying as the bridge was destroyed, has been gathered into neat piles for use by work crews.  The massive stone fountain has been lovingly repaired and no longer spills its precious fresh water into the canal.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>A fuzzy halo of light edges from behind a large caravan barn, originating from the general direction of the Carillion at the center of town.  The deep shadow of a canal cuts immediately behind the barn, partially shielded by a livestock fence.  No livestock noises echo out from the pen, and aside from the usual nighttime cries of revelers and the creaks of supply wagons, all remains still.</description>
    <description>Standing just in front of one of the canals is a large caravan barn, the usual sounds of livestock and traders absent.  Though the structure appears to be upkept regularly, it suffers from disuse.  Ideally located close to the ferry to the mainland, no indication of why the barn lacks business can be seen.  An empty animal pen rests behind, its wooden fences partially blocking the lip of the canal and keeping creatures from falling into the waters.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Well placed torches crackle beside an arch created from two entangled trees, illuminating it for display.  The dancing shadows of the tree limbs waver across the cobblestone surface of the road, stumble across the wooden planks of a pier jutting into the bay, and then fall into the waters.  Several small rowboats rest against the dock, covered during the evening and early morning hours, and visible from here only as white shapes bobbing upon the surface of the waves.</description>
    <description>Two small, carefully cultivated trees arc overhead, entwining each other's branches to form a living arch.  Their trunks descend into identical ceramic pots set firmly into the street.  Beyond the trees, a pier stretches out into the bay, harboring rowboats and fishing junks as a mother goose might shelter goslings.  On either side of the living arch, festive dwellings and shops cluster tightly, as if jostling for attention.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Spawning from windows and torches along the street, shuddering lights sneak across the dark walls of the buildings, illuminating the pastel shades normally hidden within the night.  With few exceptions, such as one faded green building in particular, the dwellings and businesses embrace the respite from the shadows.  Those that do not, sulk and withdraw within the darkness formed from their own eaves and unlit windows.</description>
    <description>The pastel hues that many of the homes and businesses have been painted reflect equally bright in the water of the canal that separates Gull Circle from Pearl Circle.  While the shades are not as brilliant as those used on structures lining Pearl Circle, there still remains a festive degree of tones.  With the exception of a few faded buildings, such as the dull green dwelling nearby, the colors are easily representative of flowering plants or speckled sea shells.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>A clear dome of windows nests atop a rounded pink building, twinkling gently from the sources of torch and gaethzen that litter the city.  The pink shade of the building glares out at the street even while veiled in shadow, as the waters of Torbis Sanhalas indifferently steal glances at passers-by.</description>
    <description>The glint of light sparkles from the glass dome atop a rounded pink building, only slightly less brilliant when clouds cover the sky.  Aside from the light catching dome and the bright pink shade painted on its walls, the building has been constructed with function in mind, and shows minimal adornment.  The waters of Torbis Sanhalas glare from behind this obstruction, desperate to catch a glance of the city streets.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pink building" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Stark against the nightfall, a pale crescent-shaped building hides behind a white fence that lines the street.  Even with the surrounding darkness, the bright shades of flowering plants peaking through the fence match those colors painted on the nearby buildings.  The basalt street, even darker in evening hours, becomes a dance floor for the twisting shadows and square spotlights shining upon it from still active windows.</description>
    <description>Behind a towering white fence sulks a pale crescent-shaped building resting atop a series of terraces.  Richly colored plants of various species crowd the sculptured steppes, some fronds and leaves poking through the gaps in the fence to tickle the paving stones.  Though the street itself is basalt colored, a wild assortment of shades is provided by the brightly painted facades of the nearby buildings.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white-washed arch" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Mer'Kresh, Sahra Bridge" note="North Barricade">
    <description>The rising and falling humps that line the sides of Sahra Bridge prove to be the stone forms of dolphins, decoratively added to the cresting arch of the bridge.  As the bridge curves down to the street, the sideguards flare in either direction, each capped with an iron brazier set into their ends.  A seashell mosaic spirals between, the normally bright shades of blue and green dusty from traveling wagons.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb construction barricade" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Mer'Kresh, Sahra Bridge">
    <description>Mimicking the rising and falling of a serpent cresting in the water, Sahra Bridge arches as it spans the canals.  Dark stains dot the cobblestones, left behind by the steady flow of traffic heading to and from the outer ring.  The water below heaves and sloshes, leaving foamy bubbles where it splashes against the rocks lining the ring.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Mer'Kresh, Sahra Bridge" note="Sahra Bridge">
    <description>People, animals, and caravans flood the crossroads of the Sahra Bridge and Tuilis Clemois.  The caravan dray animals shy from the noise, while their drivers alternate shouting encouragement and curses.  Small knots of children stalk the trundling wagons, intent on snatching a plump turnip or a juicy esturi fruit while the driver isn't watching.</description>
    <description>Animated by the flickering street lamps, the stone dolphins set atop the bridge's edge leap from shadow to wavering shadow.  A crew of street sweepers work to clean the day's trash -- esturi fruit rinds, dung and debris fallen (or perhaps flung) from the wagons that clogged the crossroads of the Sahra Bridge and Tuilis Clemois earlier in the day.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Mer'Kresh, Sahra Bridge">
    <description>Certainly the lowest of the bridges, Sahra Bridge curves just high enough to allow the gondolas on the water to squeeze beneath.  Sometimes a larger gondola will come amazingly close to scraping along the bridge's underside, and the cautious looks on the pilots prove that a collision isn't out of the question.  Lining the edges of the bridge and carved with surprising detail, basalt dolphins leap and frolic in the stone water, frozen eternally in their joyous dance.</description>
    <position x="20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Mer'Kresh, Tamris Bridge">
    <description>Even at the highest point of Tamris Bridge, several buildings on the skyline rise yet higher.  The belltower in the Carillion is obviously one, rising higher than any other building in town.  Half the size of the Carillion's, a less dominating belltower near the edge of town on Gull Circle stretches skyward.  From this vantage point, it is clear that structures in Mer'Kresh have a tendency to be built upwards since open space is so rare.</description>
    <description>The constant gurgling of the canal several feet below is echoed oddly along the ruins of the bridge.  No longer a viable egress from the center of the city, there are some who forget, and with their heads turned away from the devastation and their lips uttering regretful sighs, turn back the way they came.  Far away, the shores of M'Riss can be seen clearly, but access to Gull Circle-- and the ferry to the main island -- is impossible from here due to the great rift that splits the bridge in two.</description>
    <position x="160" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Mer'Kresh, Tamris Bridge" note="Tamris Bridge">
    <description>Even at the highest point of Tamris Bridge, several buildings on the skyline rise yet higher.  The belltower in the Carillion is obviously one, rising higher than any other building in town.  Half the size of the Carillion's, a less dominating belltower near the edge of town on Gull Circle stretches skyward.  From this vantage point, it is clear that structures in Mer'Kresh have a tendency to be built upwards since open space is so rare.</description>
    <position x="140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Mer'Kresh, Tamris Bridge">
    <description>Tamris Bridge slopes up, arching over the innermost canal of Mer'Kresh before crossing Pearl Circle.  Among the three tallest of the bridges, this one is as ornate as its fellows and decorated with a recurring theme of ships, sails unfurled in bas-relief.  Across the rooftops and in the bay, the ships' real life counterparts drift across the sloshing waves of Torbis Sanhalas, on journeys to places unknown.</description>
    <position x="120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Mer'Kresh, Nelyn Bridge">
    <description>By gazing directly along the canal as it curves, one can make out the humped forms of Sahra Bridge to the northeast and Zirelga Bridge to the south.  Though by far the shortest of the five bridges of Mer'Kresh, Nelyn Bridge is only the second lowest, and still arches higher above the waters of the canal than Sahra Bridge.  The roots of all the overpasses are hidden, tucked away behind shops, stalls and homes.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Mer'Kresh, Nelyn Bridge" note="Nelyn Bridge">
    <description>Directly across from the sea's entrance through the outer ring, two sculpted seal rookeries resting atop the pedestals of the Nelyn Bridge stare over the incoming ships and onward toward the open ocean.  Chairs and benches are sprinkled near the water's edge, both in placement and literally, as the spray from the waves washes over the area.  With few buildings to block the canals, the scent of salt and seaweed overwhelms the usual city smells.</description>
    <description>In the evening's quiet, the waves sing a lullaby as they splash against the middle ring's foundation and surge through the sea's entrance in the outer ring.  High above, on the pedestals of the Nelyn Bridge, two sculpted seal rookeries gaze toward the open ocean, as if drawn by the barks of their living cousins skimming through the surf.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Intriguing bottles of unguents, ointments, and salves are jammed on one shop's display shelving, along with bundles of dried herbs and potted plants.  An odd scent -- not quite something burning, not quite something rotting, and not quite something fresh -- curdles the air near the shop.  One of the more pricey bundles of dried herbs hanging in the window looks suspiciously like a clump of weeds growing between the cobbles near the gutter.</description>
    <description>The streetlamp's glow reflects off the jewel-toned bottles collected in one of the shop windows.  One of the more pricey bundles of dried herbs hanging in the window looks suspiciously like a clump of weeds growing between the cobbles near the gutter.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go whitewashed shop" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Mannequins posing in one shop window are skillfully draped with silks and cottons, linens and threaded spidersilk.  Strands of beads and elegant lace medallions adorn the lengths of fabric, each perfectly placed to enhance both fabric and ornament.  Wide terracotta planters, each containing a rosewood sapling, are evenly spaced at the edge of the walkway.  Curving toward the northeast, the road continues its great arc between the rows of buildings.</description>
    <description>The evening breeze rustles the rosewood saplings carefully nurtured in wide terracotta planters set at the edge of the walkway.  The stores are dark, but even the night can't dull the sparkle of beads against silk in one shop window.  A clink of glasses, an occasional laugh, and the murmur of soft music drift from the northeast.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Flat and black, the basalt foundations for future shops and homes fill either side of the road, their edges lined with wood guiderails.  The dark grey streaks of ash and lime mortar between the stones creates the illusion that the surfaces are cracked deeply, when in fact the specially made mortar keeps a tight grip on the individual stones.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb construction barricade" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Though the road is completed, no structures stand but for one run-down shack huddled quietly off to the side.  A constant sloshing from the canal behind the shack replaces the sounds of workers and townsfolk, and only the occasional cry of a hungry seagull breaks through the noisy water's gurgle.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southeast" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Unobstructed by buildings or people, the coast of M'Riss lies serenely across the bay, Torbis Sanhalas.  Beyond the ash-colored sands of the beaches, Undogoz Mountain towers over the woodlands of the main island, a perpetual haze clouding details due to the distance.  Much closer, a series of broken and shattered fences run a circle around one of the finished basalt foundations along the street.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" note="Super Celpeze" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Thin patches of ashen dirt cover some sections of the road's flagstones, lending the area an unkempt appearance.  The assortment of tools and construction supplies remaining after the workers were done doesn't add to the concept of tidiness.  A stack of leftover bricks sits to one side of the main causeway, no longer needed now that this section of Gull Circle is nearing completion.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="311" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Mer'Kresh, Northern Canal Gate" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The most prominent feature of the end of the road is the massive bronze-wrapped tower that will, once finished, hold the northern half of the canal gate in place.  Practically a work of art, the tower stretches high overhead, holding several colorful banners aloft.  Taut ropes run from the midsection, the top, and a point inbetween, down to several metal loops along the ground.  A pile of jagged rocks, discarded from the construction of the road, lean against the ring from inside the canal.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb jagged rocks" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Reception Area">
    <description>Squares of thick glass, stacked in place of windows, distort every simple motion outside into a flailing and pulsing mimicry of light and shadow.  Copying this in static form, blue and grey stripes dive up and down the contour of the walls, only splitting apart once the ceiling ascends into the domed central hall.  The design is a potent sight, and may explain the vacancy behind the receptionist's desk.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Main Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Near the domed roof high above, a circle of windows floods the hospital with natural, healing light during the day and gives a relaxing view of the dark sky during night.  A curved bench offers those tired or ill souls a place to rest and enjoy the sky that lies beyond those lofty windows.  Apartment doors along the walls show that some resident students make their homes here, near enough to be called upon at a moment's notice in an emergency.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone steps" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Waiting Room">
    <description>A cushioned sofa rests under a dazzling painted landscape that graces the walls.  The vivid colors flow up from the floor in bold dashes and streaks, encircling the sofa as if each of the brushstrokes were moths flying about an open flame.  A simple red shelf is treated in similar fashion by the design, yet the artistic swirls on the wall give it a wider berth than they do the neighboring sofa.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white-striped door" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Healing Room" note="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital|Healer|Yolesi" color="#00BF80">
    <description>A single gaethzen sphere serves as the area's only light source, sending soft bird-like shadows spinning slowly around the room as it twirls gently.  Directly below it, a padded wood and steel table awaits to serve the wounded, as do the white sheets hanging in the corner await to provide cover to those beyond help.  Near them, a sealed cabinet mounted on the wall faces those sitting on the table.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white-striped door" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Mer'Kresh, The Galley Dock">
    <description>The gentle thumping of rowboats and fishing junks bouncing casually against the stone columns of the dock fills the air with a disjointed rhythm.  Tight coils of heavy rope wrap the lower sections in a vain attempt to cushion the sounds of the drifting boats.  Two trees lean into one another in the opposite direction, creating a living arch leading to the street.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Mer'Kresh, The Galley Dock" note="Galley Dock|First Land Herald|Herald|newspaper|news stand" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>The stone dock, a happy union of usefulness and beauty, rises from the water on fluted columns softened by layers of moss.  Its carved stanchions and bright lampposts define an area both comfortable for waiting passengers and spacious for cargo.</description>
    <description>The stone dock, a happy union of usefulness and beauty, rises from the water on fluted columns softened by layers of moss.  Its carved stanchions and painted posts define an area both comfortable for waiting passengers and spacious for cargo.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go galley" destination="285" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go galle" destination="286" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>A fringe of boots and shoes swings from the entrance awning of a prosperous-looking shop.  The scent of tanned leather mixed with dye wafts through the door, beckoning the fashion-conscious to enter if the window display fails.  The din from the Nelyn Bridge rises from the north.</description>
    <description>The shop awnings have been furled for the evening, but the flickering streetlamps cast enough light to admire the wares in the various shop display windows.</description>
    <position x="-291" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Drawn by a puddle fed from a leaking cistern, a flock of strutting gulls drink and bathe in the water.  Pecking at each other and menacing the passersby with their shrill cries, the gulls compete for choice spots at the makeshift pool.  Every so often, a shopkeeper will charge out of his store and beat at the gulls with a broom, while yelling "Wifwif, irin madaricama asacimian!  Wifwif!"</description>
    <description>The steady drip from a leaky cistern fills a pothole in the street.  Several gulls roost upon a ledge, resting soundly after an exciting day of dodging shopkeepers' brooms.</description>
    <position x="-291" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>The soft glow of lamplight shines down on the myriad of toys displayed in a nearby shop window.  An occasional shadowy figure is silhouetted against the drawn curtains of an above-store apartment.</description>
    <description>Toys, fanciful and alluring, draw both adults and children to the display window of a shop snuggly occupying the lower level of a vividly colored building.  The upper stories are filled with apartments, each having a tiny balcony wrapped around an oversized window.  The road curves gently north, bending toward the Nelyn Bridge.</description>
    <position x="-292" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Close-set buildings line both edges of Pearl Circle.  Although they hide the view of the canals, the scent of fish and salt is a reminder the ocean is never far.  A golden-lettered sign hangs over the door of one building.  Rocking chairs with thick cushions dot the porch floor and baskets of deep purple fuschias swing from the eaves.  Further down the street, closer to the theater district, a blend of bright costumes, wigs and props fill a store window.</description>
    <position x="-292" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Curving gently, the road passes through a melange of shops and businesses that cater to the entertainers who perform at the theater.  A nearby restaurant's elaborately painted window portrays a group of revelers with frothing mugs raised.  If the picture fails to entice, a discrete placard on the door assures diners that the food is cheap and filling.  A shop window displays clothing designed for dancers.  Above the store, bold black letters on the window announce, Willert Snerk, Agent.</description>
    <position x="-292" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Reflected lamplight floods the face of the theater, striking the building's bright paint and gilded columns to transform the dull daytime landmark into a palace.  Jewel-eyed bronze dolphins leap among sprays of water surging from the fountain in front of the theater.  Noisy crowds fill the street, some clamoring at the ticket booth and entering the theater in a steady stream, others content to watch the street performers and spend coppers on food, drink and baubles at the pushcarts.</description>
    <description>Stripped of the night's magic, the heart of the entertainment district seems drab in the day's light.  The pushcarts are cloaked in canvas and awaiting dusk.  The theater's main doors are shut and thick curtains drawn across the windows -- even the fountain's watery hiss is silent.  A few tradesmen and hopeful actors slip in through a side door at one end of the theater.  At the other end of the building, the ticket booth does a brisk business, and a barker touts the delights of the evening to come.</description>
    <position x="-292" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>The shops and houses are drawn closer together in the western quarter than in the ring's southern quadrant, and in places obscure the view of the canals altogether.  From the northwest, a theater barker's enticements to the passing crowds compete with the southeasterly noise of the bridge's traffic.  A shuttered tavern, a favorite with entertainers and late-hour audiences crouches at the edge of the theater district.</description>
    <description>The shops and houses are drawn closer together in the western quarter than in the ring's southern quadrant, and in places obscure the view of the canals altogether.  From the northwest, shouts and music mixed with applause overwhelms the southeasterly noise of the sporadic evening traffic surrounding the bridge.  A tavern, aglow with lanterns and windows flung wide, invites entertainers and late-hour audiences to continue their celebrations after the show.</description>
    <position x="-292" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shuttered tavern" destination="317" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark tunnel" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle" note="Sttiejal">
    <description>Small, umbrella-shaded tables on the sidewalk in front of a cafe offer refuge from the swift current of people swirling along the cobbled road toward the Sahra Bridge.  Terracotta pots, each as wide as a grown man's armspan, are home to graceful rosewood saplings.  Two small pozreman -- one for luck, the other for prosperity -- are nestled together beneath a moss hut near the base of one sapling.</description>
    <description>The umbrellas may be folded and fastened for the evening, but the flickering candles set on each table invite guests to pause for a nightcap before retiring.  Lanterns sit upon each corner of the terracotta sapling pots lining the walkway.  One of the planters is home to two small pozreman as well as a graceful rosewood sapling.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>The canal's rippling water shimmers in the lamplight.  The steady, gentle bumping of gondolas against their slips gives a steady beat to the music of the tide and night.  Lulled by the quiet, a group of pelicans roost atop the gondola mooring posts and slip pilings.</description>
    <description>The cobbled road widens as it curves past a gondola landing.  Tall blue and purple striped poles topped with golden streamers and set with large metal rings are moored near the slips.  The frayed remains of rope used to tie off the gondolas hang off one ring.  The only barriers to Shell Circle and Gull Circle are the salty stretches of water and the massive terracotta planters marking the entrance steps to each gondola slip.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Staggered gaps between the colorful buildings give plenty of room to gaze at the canals and the slow moving barges hauling cargo.  The area boasts few shops -- residences surrounded by patches of lawn dominate.  Above, ropes strung between the upper stories flap with laundry and birds.</description>
    <description>The few shops in the area are shuttered for the night.  Above, slivers of light slip from between the drawn curtains, and shadows of movement hint at the lives of those within.  A line of crows sleep on laundry ropes strung between the upper stories.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>The road continues its broad arc, stretching away from the residences and curving east toward the Tamris Bridge.  A mob of familiars clogs the walkway outside a metal grillwork door.  They scratch themselves and chase their tails, some sleep or lounge, while others stare malevolently at anyone approaching too near.</description>
    <description>The road continues its broad arc, stretching away from the residences and curving east toward the Tamris Bridge.  Streetlamps give a soft glow to the night, and cast murky shapes in the alleys between the buildings.  Wood shavings and cambrinth flakes litter the area near a metal grillwork door.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Mer'Kresh, Tamris Bridge">
    <description>Four sets of evenly spaced stone pillars support the arched masonry carrying the bed of the Tamris Bridge high overhead.  The area between the columns far exceeds the squat tunnel of the Zirelga Bridge, allowing the pedestrians and wagons to maneuver with ease.  Centered beneath the vaulted ceiling, an octagonal mosaic of tiny, brilliantly hued tiles depicts Eluned cradling a three-masted ship.</description>
    <position x="240" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Although closed for the day and the front of the store dark, behind the counter the bakery still bustles with work.  Faces and clothing smudged with flour, the baker's apprentices prepare dough and shape loaves.  Leaning against the back wall, racks of cloth-covered bread rise and await their turn in the oven.</description>
    <description>The road arcs slowly, as if to pause and revel in the thick scent of baking bread.  Loaves -- round, long, and braided -- fill the bakery's window.  Samples slathered with creamy butter sit beneath heavy glass-domed plates.  The gulls have learned they cannot get to the bread themselves, but wait patiently for their expected handout, and, wings flapping angrily, will shrilly pursue anyone not giving them their due share.</description>
    <position x="280" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bakery" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>The dim lamplight can't rescue the pink awnings and aqua shutters, or the white-walled buildings with their window boxes full of red blossoms from the drab cloak of night.  Soft evening sounds rustle the area and only the brine from the canals retains its daytime tang.  The road bends unevenly through the area, meandering restfully from the bakery toward the ring's end.</description>
    <description>A kaleidoscope of sensations, the smell of brine, white-walled buildings, voices caroling, the aroma of yeast and grain, the twang of a lute string, pink awnings and aqua shutters, the press of the crowd, the clop and creak of wagons, and red blossoms in the window boxes dance into a whirlpool of smell, color and sound.  Even the road's curve wavers as it sweeps through the area, as if not quite able to maintain its steady cobbled stream in the cacophony.</description>
    <position x="280" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>With nightfall, the gems are removed from the shop window and in their place, elegant ruby and sapphire velvet cloths are artfully arranged over the display setting.  The glow from the wrought iron lanterns hung high on curved posts illuminate the boldly painted buildings, sending splashes of vivid pinks, yellows, oranges and blues against the night's darkness.</description>
    <description>The flashy gemstones in the jewelry shop window mimic the gaudy tones of the surrounding homes and shops.  Vivid oranges and yellows, eye-searing greens, and bright blues and pinks splash the buildings, awnings, and shutters.  Like a raucous flock of wild parrots perched along the roadside, the boldly painted colors fuse harmoniously in the tropical landscape.</description>
    <position x="280" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Elegant for this section of the city, the High Tide Inn's imported brick, intricate wrought iron gate, carved rosewood columns, and expansive lawn are a startling contrast to the vibrant tropical hues of the surrounding buildings.  The cobbled road curves gracefully in its course between the walkways and terracotta planters.  A jutting brick cobble has forced one planter to be placed slightly out of line with the others.</description>
    <position x="280" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Oil lanterns hanging from ornate wrought iron poles cast a faint illumination over the miniature trees, sculpted shrubbery, and carefully nurtured lawns fronting the homes and shops lining the cobbled street.  The shops are shut tight for the evening: doors locked and window curtains drawn, even the stoop mats welcoming visitors have been removed until the next day's business.</description>
    <description>Miniature trees and sculpted shrubbery thrive in the carefully nurtured lawns that front the homes and shops lining the cobbled street.  Windowsills are bright with blossoms and shop displays are skillfully arranged to lure customers.  As with nearly every Rissan shop, no sign is needed to proclaim the owner or his service: everyone knows everybody else's business in this isolated society.</description>
    <position x="280" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Empty tin pails reflecting the streetlamp's glow are clustered near the florist's garland-swagged door, and a scattering of bruised and broken blossoms litter the walkway.  Few buildings crowd this stretch of road, so near the ring's end.  Greenhouses dot the area, taking advantage of the relative desertion.  Their simplistic easy-to-disassemble design suggests that the florist may be borrowing space to which he isn't entitled.</description>
    <description>Few buildings crowd this stretch of road, so near the ring's end.  The florist has taken advantage of the relative desertion by planting the open areas with blooms.  His greenhouses dot the area, and the simplistic easy-to-disassemble design suggests that he may be borrowing space to which he isn't entitled.  Clustered near the florist's garland-swagged door, tin pails of freshly cut roses, bellflowers, and columbine sweeten the air.</description>
    <position x="280" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garland-swagged door" destination="350" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Set at Nuscilremi's feet, a jumble of votive candles flickering in a driftwood shelter casts a dim glow in the night.  Barge lamps reflected from the canal soften the jagged basalt chunks forming the ring's foundation, and the decay of the few shacks nearer the florist's stolen patches of ground is less evident.</description>
    <description>Weeds slowly engulf the street, thrusting up between the cobbles and loosening them, until finally all that remains of the road meeting the ring's basalt foundation is a path of bramble and rubble.  A few decaying shacks, once vivid purples, pinks and oranges, line the far end of the area near the florist's stolen patches of ground.  A life-sized statue representing Nuscilremi, wedged tightly between the stone chunks of the ring's bed, greets the barges as they pass through the canal gate.</description>
    <position x="280" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Iden Araba, Southwest" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The Zirelga Bridge looms near.  A bevy of gulls hover in the air, squawking and competing with each other for the scraps flung from the roadway above.  The current slows slightly as it flows toward the southwest, checked by the bridge's massive footings.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb bridge support" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Iden Araba, South" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The blue-green water sweeps past the middle ring's gondola landing and scrapes against the basalt blocks forming the outer ring's foundation.  Sheltered in the crevices between the stone slabs, pink anemonies hopeful of a meal wave their tentacles in the quickly moving southeasterly current.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Iden Araba, South" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The drag of water on rock slows the current as it curves eastward toward the Dajere Bridge.  A dark brown patch marking the remains of a canal barge lies nestled in the seagrass growing on the bottom of the waterway.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging eastward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Iden Araba, South" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Mirroring the blue-green water, sprawling colonies of tiny blue-shelled snails stain the damp foundation rocks.  Sprigs of green growing atop the rough ring edges flutter in breeze.  The current flows eastward toward the Dajere Bridge.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging eastward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="20" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Iden Araba, Southeast" color="#0000FF">
    <description>As it rushes against the footings of the Dajere Bridge, the current splits, part veering into the inner canal, part continuing the circular trip through the outer canal.  The water surging through the area is perpetually turbulent as the bridge footings and inner canal's point repel and rechannel the frothing waves.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="140" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Iden Araba, Southeast" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The footings of the Dajere Bridge split the current, sending little eddies of water spinning toward the northeast.  Puddles of foam careen among the twisting whirls of water like dancers pirouetting from partner to partner.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="200" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Iden Araba, East" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Streaks of white brine mark the tides on the steep basalt pillars that form the ring foundations.  Long slender strands of green slime floats atop the water, pulled along by the current.</description>
    <description />
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="300" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Iden Araba, East" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Delectable scents from the back of an inn waft over the canal: roasting meat mingles with baking bread and the tang of salt.  A squall of gulls swarm near the inn, while on the other side of the canal, a group of pelicans perches on the mooring poles of the outer ring's gondola landing.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging northward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="300" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Iden Araba, East" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Cries of hawkers selling their goods cut through the slosh of water and squawk of birds which normally defines the canal's voice.  Small buoys, painted with the colors of their owners, mark the position of lobster traps.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging northward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="300" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Iden Araba, Northeast" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The Tamris bridge looms nearby, its sculpted ships clearly visible as they sail across the arching sides.  Several fishermen have cast their lines over the bridge's side, but, more interested in gossip and coffee, pay little attention to the floats bobbing in the water.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="240" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Iden Araba, Northeast" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Blunted by the Tamris bridge's thick footings, the current is slowed as it continues its journey through the canal.  Whirls of foamy water spin forward languidly, picking up particles of debris and greenish brown scum torn from the ring foundations.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Iden Araba, North" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Noise from the normal life of the city echoes across the canal.  The shallow-walled channel formed by the basalt foundations gathers the sound, echos it and reflects the noise off the water, magnifying its intensity.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Iden Araba, North" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Crude drawings and crooked-lettered puns scrawled on the bridge's footings emerge through the dark grey paint intended to obscure these rude artistic efforts.  The current flows westward toward the sea's entrance to the canal.</description>
    <description>The water slapping against the bridge footings echos in the confined space beneath it.  A lighter patch of dark marks the mouth of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Iden Araba, North" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The canal churns with confusion as the westward current shears against the waves pushing through the sea entrance of the outer ring.  White froth scuttles across the water's ebb and swell before slapping against the jagged basalt foundation.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging westward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Iden Araba, Northwest" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Waves rolling in through the sea entrance rake the heavy abutment of the Nelyn Bridge.  The angle of the marching waves sets the canal's flow spinning widdershins to the southwest.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging to the southwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Iden Araba, Northwest" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Waves crashing off the jagged foundations of the sea entrance send towering sprays of foam into the air and rippling across the canal's surface.  The force of the incoming waves push the canal waters swiftly to the southwest.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb metal gate" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Iden Araba, West" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Dark patches of seagrass growing on the canal bed bend and sway in the current.  The canal's strong pull flows southwest past the desolate outer ring and the lively pinks and oranges of the buildings squating on the eyen tayac.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Iden Araba, West" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Swept by the strong southward current, clumps of grey moss cling precariously to the smooth, finished foundation wall of the middle ring.  Colonies of tiny blue snails coat both canal walls like textured, sky-speckled paint.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging southward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Iden Araba, West" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Cries from the middle ring, perhaps the theater barker hawking tickets or a flock of dissatisfied gulls, float across the water.  The current swirls southward, dragging strings of foam with it.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging southward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Iden Araba, Southwest" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The canal's waters flow past the gulls diving for scraps thrown off the roadway above, then duck beneath the starfish sculpted on the Zirelga bridge's arches high overhead.  The current rolls between the massive stone footings toward the southeast.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Unless hidden behind the miscellaneous construction tools or stacks of cobblestones, there are no laborers working on the ring.  The deep gouges scarring the edge of the road may have something to do with this, as they are obviously not the result of any shovel or hammer.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Eyen Araba, Southeast" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Stringy swags of moss hang from underside of the Dajere Bridge.  A tangle of debris is pushed against the bridge's footing, pinned in place by the inward rushing current.</description>
    <description>The water slapping against the bridge footings echos in the confined space beneath it.  A lighter patch of dark marks the mouth of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="140" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Eyen Araba, South" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The current quickens as the water is pulled by the water surging through the canal gates further northeast.  Overhead, gulls swoop from the Dajere Bridge, dive at the water below, then return to their perches.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging eastward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="100" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Eyen Araba, South" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Streaks of white brine stain the foundation's surface.  Moving sluggishly, the water can't quite clean the reeking pools of refuse that collect in the crevices of the rock footings.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging eastward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="20" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Eyen Araba, East" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Wakes from passing barges and gondolas churn the canal's surface.  The current, propelled by the influx of water from the outer canal, surges toward the northeast.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="260" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Eyen Araba, East" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The gondola slips moored at the museum deflect the strong current toward the eyen tayac -- the inner ring.  Crashing against the city's jagged basalt roots, the current dissipates as lurches northward.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging northward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="260" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Eyen Araba, East" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Sudsy white flecks float northward in the current.  They coalesce, forming patches of bubbly film, only to be dashed against the jagged foundation rocks and rendered once again into small foamy blotches.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging northward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="260" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Eyen Araba, Northeast" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Whirling eddies of water spin around the footings of the Tamris Bridge.  The slap of water on rock kicks up a frothy spray.</description>
    <description>The water slapping against the bridge footings echos in the confined space beneath it.  A lighter patch of dark marks the mouth of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="220" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Eyen Araba, North" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Barely visible, a bed of purplish-green seaspike grows in uneven patches on the bottom of the canal.  Their pointy fronds ripple in the current.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the northwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Eyen Araba, North" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Cobri Esheceni! is scrawled across on the bridge's footing above the high tide mark -- possibly a reference to the many caravans that use the roadway above, but is more likely commentary about the denizens of Town Hall which sits across from the bridge's entrance.</description>
    <description>The water slapping against the bridge footings echos in the confined space beneath it.  A lighter patch of dark marks the mouth of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Eyen Araba, North" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The swift southwest current funnels against the steep foundation of the Tuilis Clemois and central platform.  A slick layer of algae coats the underpinnings of the ring:  what looks like an easy climb is a treacherous reality.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging westward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Eyen Araba, Northwest" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Half-raveled and rotted, a fishing net hangs from a twisted bit of metal wedged into the stone masonry of the Nelyn Bridge.  The bottom of the net flops onto a small rock shelf near one of the bridge's footings.</description>
    <description>The water slapping against the bridge footings echos in the confined space beneath it.  A lighter patch of dark marks the mouth of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Eyen Araba, West" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Bearing south, the current rushes between the central platform -- what the Rissans call mercen dirailur -- and the inner ring.  Bright spots of paper, origami ships, bob in the water.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southwest, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Eyen Araba, West" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The current swirls past the western gondola landing on the central platform and, slowed by the bulk of the slips, wends toward the Zirelga Bridge.  Rivulets of slimy moss coat the walls containing the canal.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging southward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-274" y="179" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Eyen Araba, West" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The aroma of roasting meat and bread baking from the restaurants in the theater district overlays the pungent odor of salt and decaying waste.  Moving lazily, the current flows southward.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging southward, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Eyen Araba, Southwest" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A splotchy layer of moss and pearlescent blue shellfish coats the bridge footings between high and low tide.  Fresh striations in the rock mark where someone has harvested some of the clinging mussels.</description>
    <description>The water slapping against the bridge footings echos in the confined space beneath it.  A lighter patch of dark marks the mouth of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Eyen Araba, South" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Slowed by the gondola landing, the torpid water struggles eastward.  A small pile of driftwood floats against one of the gondola slips.</description>
    <description>Light from the city's buildings reflects off the rippling water, but doesn't cast enough illumination to navigate.  Only the current, tugging toward the southeast, hints at where you are.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Crescent Gardens, Memorial Arch">
    <description>A set of stone steps rises upwards into the terraced lawns, flanked by the waving stalks of cultivated orchids and lilies.  Opposite, a white-washed arch leads out to the street, twisted rose vines entangling themselves lovingly within the gaps of the arch's trelliswork.  Even at such a short distance, the sounds of the busy road begin to fade, absorbed by the flora as a sponge absorbs water.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white-washed arch" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone steps" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Crescent Gardens, Terraced Lawn" note="Crescent Gardens">
    <description>Brilliant orchids dance along the edges of raised terraces, performers on natural stages that would make many a landscaper proud.  Each morning, the tiny flowers unfold to catch any breeze and sway in their dance, while each night they fold slowly and graciously for slumber.  The scene is repeated on many of the planted terraces about the lawn by a multitude of different plants, some brightly colored, others simply green.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone steps" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Crescent Gardens, Terraced Lawn">
    <description>The potent scent of brine mingles with fragrant orchids in an exotic combination, whipped by the coastal winds that swirl up from the waters of Torbis Sanhalas Bay and over the terraced slopes of the lawn.  Adding to the white of the heady flowers are silk memorial ribbons, tied at intermittent heights in the trees and shrubs and shuddering slightly in the sea breezes.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Crescent Gardens, Patio Entrance">
    <description>The curving walls of a one-story building embrace the lawns, the building itself closely surrounded by the lush gardens.  A few audacious vines crawl upwards, reaching vainly for the eaves.  Centered in the side of the concave structure is a mahogany door, adorned with a solemn assortment of white ribbons and a few bows.  Above the door a wreath hangs, the visible symbol of a loss.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Crescent Gardens, Terraced Lawn">
    <description>Pale and unobtrusive, a portrait of a demurely smiling Elven woman nestles snugly against the walls of foliage.  At the foot of the stand it rests upon, flowers lie, and fluttering in the trees all around are white ribbons.  A glimpse of pink winks from behind the painting -- not a flower, but the side of Torbis Sanhalas Hospital next door.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Mer'Kresh Empathic Gathering Hall, Front Passage">
    <description>Simplistic in design and function, the foyer serves as both a reception area and main hall, curving off in either direction.  At the apex of the curve, a multi-paneled door resides in the wall, etched with an unusual pattern and guarded by a birch-topped desk.  A white banner stretches over the door, and small bows and wreaths hang from the ceiling rafters.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Mer'Kresh Empathic Gathering Hall, Study Area">
    <description>Shelves line all but one of the walls, each filled with books, memorabilia, and assorted odds and ends.  A large picture window takes up the space of the remaining wall, revealing a sharp slope cluttered with orchids and day-lilies, some of which droop as if in mourning against the backdrop of the bay's waters.  The shore of M'Riss lies far beyond, details lost to distance.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Mer'Kresh Empathic Gathering Hall, Student Walk">
    <description>A double row of bricks runs down the base of the corridor, butting tight against the exposed support timbers.  Diagrams and pictorial sequences of healing in process do a poor job hiding the unfinished walls, the parchment curling up in the miniscule breezes set into motion by passing students.  Abruptly, the papers and the hall stop, the rough timbers replaced with the smooth handrails of an open-air walkway leading to a pink structure next door.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open-air walkway" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Open Air Walkway">
    <description>Two ship's masts stretch between the hospital and the crescent-shaped Empath's hall, lodged firmly in the walls of each.  A sturdy walkway connects the two buildings with the mast's firm support as the pink walls of the hospital stare beneath at the slope dropping away from the Empath's hall.  Those areas of the horizon that aren't blocked by the dual structures exposes Mer'Kresh in all its splendor as well as the far shores of M'Riss.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Balcony">
    <description>If only for show, a thin wooden arch marks the point at which the balcony cuts into a tight angle and then changes into an open-air walkway.  The far side of the walkway collides into one wall of a pale crescent-shaped building.  A simple wooden plaque gazes across as a few dried rose petals swirl in the air beneath it.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open-air walkway" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Balcony">
    <description>The balcony curves around the street-facing side of the hospital, hugging tight to its arching pink surface, while the large windows that surround the hospital's domed top loom overhead, too high to reveal a sight of the interior.  Mer'Kresh is not difficult to see, as this lofty vantage turns the streets and roads into ripples on the surface of a puddle, radiating outwards from the Carillion at the center of town.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Torbis Sanhalas Hospital, Bay Overlook">
    <description>Far across the waters lies the coast, dotted with buildings and dwellings along the Ring Road.  Angling towards that shore is the aqueduct, a marvel of engineering that provides fresh water for the city.  A glance eastwards bestows a more natural scene of the far-off lands of M'Riss, while below, the waters of the bay for which the hospital is named lap against the stony rocks of the shore.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone steps" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Mer'Kresh, Zirelga Bridge">
    <description>The cobblestones on the bridge are all painted gaily in brilliant shades of pink and orange and create a starfish arrangement, marred only be the streaks from wheelbarrows and carts.  Respite from the crowds of the inner rings is found here since few people venture too far across Zirelga Bridge on a regular basis, preferring to use only the northeastern tip to circumvent the thickest of gatherings.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Mer'Kresh, Zirelga Bridge" note="Zirelga Bridge">
    <description>One wall of a tavern on Pearl Circle leans snugly against the supports of the bridge, but its mottled blue roof tiles are out of reach to all but the seagulls.  Here, at the highest point in the arch of the bridge, the skyline opens wide to reveal all the intricacies of the architecture of Mer'Kresh and the way it weaves into one panoramic scene of city life.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Mer'Kresh, Zirelga Bridge">
    <description>The bridge stops suddenly, jutting out and above the unfinished surface of Gull Circle.  The overpowering scent of garbage and refuse drifts from below, while a wooden sign on the bridge's railing directs workers to be cautious in their tasks.  White feathers along the edge reveal the attraction the smell has had for seagulls, even though none currently dine on the scraps that swirl in the breeze.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone block" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>A squat, dark tunnel bored through the footings of the massive Zirelga Bridge connects the southern quadrant of Pearl Circle to the western quarter.  Barely big enough to allow two merchant wagons to pass side by side, those afoot must take care to avoid being crushed.  Oil lamps held high by heavy metal sconces illuminate the moss growing on the ceiling, and the trickle of moisture that perpetually dampens the walls.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go southeast arch" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go northwest arch" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>The arc of the road sweeps west toward a cluster of buildings shouldering against the Zirelga Bridge.  Narrow wrought iron balconies and window boxes bright with flowers adorn the shopkeepers' homes built above their businesses.  In a bay window of one shop, a succession of young women models clothing.  They pose and turn, then smile at the crowds gathered to watch, enticing their audience to buy.</description>
    <description>The arc of the road sweeps west toward a cluster of buildings shouldering against the Zirelga Bridge.  Narrow wrought iron balconies and window boxes bright with flowers adorn the shopkeepers' homes built above their businesses.  The bay window of one shop, usually the stage for young women to display clothing, is dark with the curtains partially drawn.  A chink of candle light from one corner of the shop casts wavering shadows upon the mannequins clad in the fashions for tomorrow's models.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark tunnel" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Trays of chocolates and strands of spun sugar are prominently displayed in one of the shop windows.  A group of noisy children lean against the panes, their fingers and noses smudging the glass as they peer longingly at the sweets and plan their purchases.  The cobbled road curves west toward the Zirelga Bridge and away from the sparsely populated southern quadrant of Pearl Circle.</description>
    <description>Waxed paper covers the trays of chocolates, dishes of gumdrops and bowls of marzipan prominently displayed in one of the shop windows.  A dim light filtering from the back of the store reveals the shopkeeper inside, busily scraping fudge on a marble tabletop in preparation of the next day's business.  The cobbled road curves west toward the Zirelga Bridge and away from the sparsely populated southern quadrant of Pearl Circle.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shop" destination="352" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle" note="gondola">
    <description>A shabby gondola landing spans the width of the ring.  Tacked above a small shack, a sign proclaims "Rent Here" in paint so badly flaked as to be nearly illegible.  Northward, a set of wobbly steps creaks down to the gondolas docked in the inner canal.  Across the street, a stairway southward descends to a half-sunken dock where boats tie up in the outer canal.</description>
    <description>The dim light from the street torches flicker off the canal waves.  A shabby gondola landing spanning the width of the ring draws a fair business from couples desiring a romantic evening boat ride.  Rent Here proclaims a sign, with paint so badly flaked as to be nearly illegible.  Northward, a set of wobbly steps creaks down to the gondolas docked in the inner canal.  Across the street, a stairway southward descends to a half-sunken dock where boats tie up in the outer canal.</description>
    <description>A shabby gondola landing spans the width of the ring.  Tacked above a small shack, a sign proclaims Rent Here in paint so badly flaked as to be nearly illegible.  Northward, a set of wobbly steps creaks down to the gondolas docked in the inner canal.  Across the street, a stairway southward descends to a half-sunken dock where boats tie up in the outer canal.</description>
    <position x="0" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Tufts of wiry brown grass push up through the cobbles, and flowering weeds edging the roadside gutters wave in the gentle breeze flowing from the outer canal.  Rubble litters one side of the road, debris from a section of buildings torn down to make way for fresh construction.  Across the street, sparkling new paint and crisp curtains adorn MAMAS, the local assay shop.</description>
    <description>Tufts of wiry brown grass push up through the cobbles, and flowering weeds edging the roadside gutters wave in the gentle breeze flowing from the outer canal.  Several shadowy figures pick through the rubble littering one side of the road, no doubt salvaging items left in the pile created when some buildings were torn down to make way for fresh construction.  Across the street, sparkling new paint and crisp curtains adorn MAMAS, the local assay shop.</description>
    <position x="20" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go assay shop" destination="263" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Fewer buildings jam the roadway as the cracked cobbles curve toward the end of the circle where the middle and inner canals meet.  The yards grow from tiny to small, and some homes have little lawns carpeted with neatly trimmed grass.  An old store, shaded by faded blue and green striped awnings at the windows, sags toward a young oak tree whose roots have found purchase deep in the alluvial soil beneath the city.</description>
    <position x="40" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go old store" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Night has silenced the raucous squawking, barks, growls and braying that normally screeches forth from the pet shop.  The parrots in the store window have their heads tucked beneath their vibrantly plumed wings, and the small furry animals are curled into slumbering balls.  Northeast toward the end of the ring, where few people travel or care, the cobbles gradually become loose and rutted.</description>
    <description>Raucous squawking accompanied by various barks, growls and braying screech forth from a small wooden building.  The store window is full of vibrantly plumed parrots clinging to their perches as they bob their heads in time to the noise, and small furry animals peep out of their cages at passersby.  East toward the end of the ring, where few people travel or care, the cobbles gradually become loose and rutted.</description>
    <position x="80" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pet door" destination="265" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Mer'Kresh, Pearl Circle">
    <description>Piles of cracked basalt mark one tip of Pearl Circle's foundation.  The Dajere Bridge deflects the waves in the channel toward the edges of the circle and sends the water sloshing forcefully against the ring's dark stone bed.  Several benches and picnic tables set near the water offer a panoramic view of the inner platform, the bridge, and the turbulent water where the canals meet.  Savory aromas waft from a modest wooden building nearby.</description>
    <description>Shadows from the street torches streak the nearby Dajere Bridge and canals.  The waves striking the ring's stone foundation seem loud without the normal noises of day, and the night breeze off the canal is brisk with cold and brine.  Savory aromas waft from a modest wooden building nearby.</description>
    <position x="120" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Carillon, Bell Tower" note="Bell Tower|shrine" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Eight bronze bells are suspended from the carillon's rafters.  Each bell is a different size, and each plays a different scale note.  A series of arched openings cut through the walls allow the sea breeze to flow in and the toll of the bells to ring out.</description>
    <position x="20" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small door" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Lobby" note="Harti Clemois Bank|Bank">
    <description>The bank lobby has been roofed over and is open to customers, although the walls still show some scorching where the painters have not yet finished.  Scaffolding and building supplies lie here and there.  The staircase to the second floor, uncarpeted as yet, has been repaired and the polished wooden handrail replaced.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb large staircase" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Main Hallway">
    <description>Stately guardians, two potted fiddlehead ferns of enormous size flank the staircase leading to the lobby below.  Obviously, some extraordinary measures were taken to promote the growth of these two decorations, be it magic or alchemical, perhaps for the purpose of drawing attention from the doors beyond.  An ash door peeks out from the behind the fern to the north and down the hall towards its ornate looking opposite.  The hall itself opens to a domed courtyard filled with a multitude of plants.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb large staircase" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ash door" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Courtyard">
    <description>A dazzling array of multicolored plants with large, floppy leaves decorates every niche and recess of the walls.  Most of the plants have been set into heavy looking ceramic pots and all show signs of good maintenance.  A deep red carpet stretches across the floor, marking pathways through the flora and along the gently inclined stairs leading upwards.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Courtyard">
    <description>There is a definitive lack of the larger indoor plants that make up the decor in other parts of the bank's courtyard.  Where they might have been, large statues of crouching gargoyles sit.  Despite the tell-tale worn spots in the center of the red carpet, little business takes place here beneath the eyes of the grotesque stone forms.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Courtyard">
    <description>The timid beige hues of the walls peek out from behind the brilliant splash of the red and green foliage of the potted plants.  Pushed against one of the polished stone walls is a wooden bench padded with red velvet.  The indentations in the seat confirm that many a trader and bank employee have rested here, stopping to gaze upwards at the soft glow of daylight from the domed ceiling above.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Conference Room 'X'">
    <description>Unadorned tapestries hang from a handful of thick bronze wall mounts encircling the room, doing little but adding to the already present gloom.  The tapestries have been arranged in such a way that they emphasize the solid oak table set centrally.  Without a skylight or window to shed any illumination upon the table, items upon it take on a similar murky quality.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Teller's Window" note="Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A pretty Elf sits behind the teller's window, dabbing occasionally at the rose petal makeup daintly applied to her cheeks.  Every so often she looks towards the exit and past the velvet ropes that file customers to her booth and sighs.  A soft light flows in from the courtyard outside, as well as from the skylight above, keeping the area cheerfully lit for the benefit of easy transactions.</description>
    <description>A tired-looking Halfling sits behind the teller's window, grumbling as he occasionally drops a handful of coins.  Every so often he begins to nod off in front of a customer, snapping awake only after a few seconds elapse.  The dark sky stares down through the skylight above, lending no helpful light to the fumbling teller.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Moneychanger" note="Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Appearing to be little more than an afterthought in the construction of the bank, the coin exchanger's room is manned by a stooped, elderly Human.  He constantly kneads something at his chest as he sits behind the safety of the steel bars that seperate him from his customers.  The black metal and ironwood craftwork of the booth is in direct opposition to the softer hues and flowing architecture of the beige stonework elsewhere in the bank.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Harti Clemois Bank, Conference Room 'B'">
    <description>More cramped than cozy, this conference room has seen a fair amount of use.  The carpet has lost its color in an arching trail from the ash door to the chair at the head of the glossy black table, and the walls are brown from years of cigar-smoking inhabitants.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ash door" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Origami Shop" note="Origami Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Burlap bags filled with old rags cast a sharp scent throughout the shop.  Several fine mesh screens lean against a large square tub filled with thick, grey liquid.  Colorfully glazed jars, brushes, and sheets of raw paper are neatly arranged on the work table in the center of the room.  Above, finished paper is hanging to dry on rough cord strung from wall to wall.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" hidden="True" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Mer'Kresh, Santazel's Lean-To" note="Santazel's Lean-To|Repair Metal|Repair Leather|Repair Tools|Diwitt" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Splits of leather, replacement hilts and blades, rivets and metal scraps are jumbled together in crates.  A box of broken shields, armor and weapons sits in one relatively clean corner.  Two barrels with a plank of wood across them serve as a makeshift counter.  In the back of the small lean-to, a scruffy-looking Elf with tobacco-stained teeth and fingers works at his trade.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Paladins' Guild, Entrance" note="Paladin">
    <description>Tall and stately, the entrance to the guild proper looms just ahead.  Giant slabs of quarried stone support a gabled entrance which frames a door of immense proportions.  From this vantage point, both the hushed tones of conversation and the clanging of metal on metal can be heard.</description>
    <description>Tall and stately, the entrance to the guild proper looms just ahead.  Giant slabs of quarried stone support a gabled entrance which frames a door of immense proportions.  As long shadows cast their quiet presence on the arched porticos, a sense of peace and tranquility settles over the darkened building.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone arch" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go immense door" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Paladins' Guild, Grand Hall" note="Paladin">
    <description>A magnificent room of great breadth and height is set off by smooth alabaster walls and tall arched windows that suffuse the hall with sunlight.  A huge stone fireplace commands the entire north wall with several large chairs placed strategically to take advantage of the warmth of the roaring fire.  Footfalls are subdued by several skin throws on the cold stone floor.</description>
    <description>A magnificent room of great breadth and height is set off by smooth alabaster walls and tall arched windows that suffuse the hall with moonlight.  A huge stone fireplace commands the entire north wall with several large chairs placed strategically to take advantage of the warmth of the roaring fire.  Footfalls are subdued by several skin throws on the cold stone floor.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go immense door" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched passageway" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone steps" destination="212" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Paladins' Guild, Armory">
    <description>A beautifully carved display case fills most of one side of this narrow room.  Razor-sharp blades atop the case glint with reflected light, emphasizing their flawless condition.  Shields of all types hang closely together along the opposite wall, many bearing the crest of the Paladin guild or the D'Sel family.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Paladins' Guild, Portico">
    <description>In contrast with the otherwise stark architecture, the portico is softened by latticework and silvery vines.  An open window offers a glimpse of fresh cut flowers and the unmistakable smell of roasting meat.  A dirt path leads toward the east and the training fields.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched passageway" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dirt path" destination="211" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Paladins' Guild, Courtyard">
    <description>Cobbled stones are precisely set into a swirling pattern around a central garden.  A large iron gate separates the courtyard from a shaded portico that leads back toward the living quarters.  Sounds of music, laughter and the clinking of metal on metal accompanies the bustle of activity outside this otherwise peaceful enclave.</description>
    <description>Cobbled stones are precisely set into a swirling pattern around a central garden.  A large iron gate separates the courtyard from a shaded portico that leads back toward the living quarters.  Sounds of soft music, and quiet laughter punctuate this otherwise peaceful enclave.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cobblestone steps" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Paladins' Guild, Hallway">
    <description>At the top of the steps, the noise from the courtyard lessens and can only faintly be heard.  The cobblestone steps end at marble flooring.  A large ornamental rug, which almost encompasses the entire hall, lies in the middle of the floor.  This passageway does not have the look of a room with heavy traffic as dust has built up on several of the surfaces.  Several benches and chairs are scattered throughout the hall as if it were a waiting area.  A lone door sits in the far northwest corner.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cobblestone steps" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Paladins' Guild, Training Field" note="Training Field">
    <description>High wooden walls surround the expansive training field.  On the opposite side of the field, a massive gate that opens to the street is barred with an equally massive wooden beam.  Several younger paladins attend their training sessions here, eager eyes focused on one grizzled tutor as he demonstrates combat stances with grace and agility.</description>
    <description>High wooden walls cast oppressive shadows across the vast training field.  Darkened by nightfall, the short clipped grasses gather fresh dew and prepare for the dawn of a new day.  The clinking of metal on metal is now just a memory invading many a young squire's dream.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dirt path" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Paladins' Guild, Lady Avant's Office" note="GL Paladin|Avant|RS Paladin" color="#FF8000">
    <description>A long room, appointed with dark hardwood mouldings and a beautiful woven carpet, the office exudes a quiet sensibilty.  A massive cherrywood desk commands the far end of the room, the long walk agonizing to any young squire summoned to speak with the Guild Mistress.  In each corner of the office, a large iron stand supports a fat, scented candle nestled among silver ivy vines.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone steps" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Mer'Kresh, The Carousel" note="Carousel|Vault">
    <description>Exotic tapestries of every possible description drape the wall ringing the Carousel's core.  A circular roof supports a vast framework of iron and timbers rising to the building's apex.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights within the structure form the strikingly complex and beautiful mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="0" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="351" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go registration desk" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark arch" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gleaming arch" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go polished arch" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platinum arch" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Booth">
    <description>A polished steel lever protrudes from the eastern wall of the small, ebony-panelled room, flanking a steel door to the north.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gleaming arch" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Booth">
    <description>A polished steel lever protrudes from the eastern wall of the small, ebony-panelled room, flanking a steel door to the north.</description>
    <position x="20" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark arch" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Chamber">
    <description>A sturdy vault, set in the back wall, stands ready for your use.  The floor is covered by a soft thick carpet of deep red, and the walls are paneled in polished gold pine.  Looking at the back wall, you notice a tiny gap between it and the rest of the room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Booth">
    <description>A polished steel lever protrudes from the eastern wall of the small, ebony-panelled room, flanking a steel door to the north.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white arch" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Booth">
    <description>A polished steel lever protrudes from the eastern wall of the small, ebony-panelled room, flanking a steel door to the north.</description>
    <position x="20" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platinum arch" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="none" move="door" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Desk" note="Lost and Found" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A long wooden desk spans the width of the western wall.  Brass lanterns hang from the ceiling, and the floor behind the desk is covered in spotless red tile.</description>
    <position x="0" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Chamber">
    <description>A sturdy vault, set in the back wall, stands ready for your use.  The floor is covered by a soft thick carpet of deep red, and the walls are paneled in polished gold pine.  Looking at the back wall, you notice a tiny gap between it and the rest of the room.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Chamber">
    <description>A sturdy vault, set in the back wall, stands ready for your use.  The floor is covered by a soft thick carpet of deep red, and the walls are paneled in polished gold pine.  Looking at the back wall, you notice a tiny gap between it and the rest of the room.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Chamber">
    <description>A sturdy vault, set in the back wall, stands ready for your use.  The floor is covered by a soft thick carpet of deep red, and the walls are paneled in polished gold pine.  Looking at the back wall, you notice a tiny gap between it and the rest of the room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Globe Arena, Entryway">
    <description>A stone relief of a young barbarian dressed in fur-lined leather straddles the door.  Several raging polar bears circle the young lad, their snarls etched with meticulous care.  Behind, a tremendous fortress rises from a snowy plain and blocks some of the mountains that line the horizon.</description>
    <position x="160" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" hidden="True" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden stairs" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Globe Arena, Barbarian's Hall" note="GL Barbarian|Tusfaov|RS Barbarian" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Two large basalt statues lean forward from the wall, flanking a simple oak podium.  Both of the stone forms are identical, and each statue's face is curled in a cross between a snarl and a grin that bears rows of flat, square teeth.  Nestled on the wall between the two is a portrait of a young barbarian holding a gleaming broadsword aloft in triumph.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Globe Arena, Side Hall">
    <description>Textured stone lines the walls between the massive columns supporting the roof.  A fresco of a straining barbarian, struggling to drag a giant-sized catapult across the burning sands of a desert, stretches across the wall.  On one side of the barbarian, a horde of jeering Gorbesh soldiers screams.  On the other side, a small group of wounded warriors cluster, pinned down by Gorbesh arrows while they await the heroic barbarian's salvation.</description>
    <position x="200" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="224" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Globe Arena, South Hall">
    <description>Along the southern wall, a remarkable frieze depicts an exploding volcano flinging blazing orbs into the bay.  Several boats are lashed together in the water, just out of reach of most of the fiery lava chunks, and a wall of stoic-looking barbarians, with weapons drawn, deflect those few projectiles that threaten the vessels.  Clearly, some liberties were taken by the sculptor.</description>
    <position x="180" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cypress door" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Globe Arena, The Pit" note="Globe Arena">
    <description>Four large statues bear the weight of the domed ceiling upon their shoulders, each at the corner of an area cleared of obstructions.  A thick length of rope encircles the area, affixed tightly to the floor to cordon off a sparring section, and to mark a boundary for contests of skill.  Clearly known as The Pit for esoteric reasons, there is actually nothing here that resembles a pit or sunken area.</description>
    <position x="180" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Globe Arena, Upper Hallway">
    <description>More a landing than a true hallway, there is little in this tiny alcove at the top of the stairs except a reed mat on the floor and heavy cypress door.  Even the whitewashed walls are bare of everything but a few fingerprints.</description>
    <position x="140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cypress door" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden stairs" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Globe Arena, Roaring Room" note="Darts">
    <description>Deep swaths of quilted white fabric covering the ceiling and walls give the impression of huge pillows stuck to the interior surfaces.  Underfoot, a thick brown carpet muffles the sound of movement.  Even the window is made of several layers of glass set into the frame.  Amidst this stark decor, a lone table huddles near the door.</description>
    <position x="140" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cypress door" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Globe Arena, Courtyard">
    <description>White sand embedded with chunks of black volcanic rock covers the ground like soot-streaked snow.  Raised beds of esturi fruit bound one side of the courtyard, and figs grow in the bed opposite.  An obsidian fountain sits in the center of the area erupting not with a geyser of water, but one of flame.</description>
    <position x="180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cypress door" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bamboo hut" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bamboo arch" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Globe Arena, Library">
    <description>Slate stepping stones are harmoniously laid to create a winding path through the neatly raked sand floor.  Reed mats offer a place to sit and study -- or lie and snooze.  Books are neatly arranged on a bookcase resting atop a large, flat-surfaced rock serving as a desk.</description>
    <position x="180" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Globe Arena, Guest Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Twists of morning glory cling to the bamboo arch, nearly obscuring it in a green shadow, and a stone threshold separates the courtyard's sand from the neatly clipped common yard where these homes rest.  Each bamboo hut's exterior is nearly identical to its neighbor, giving a serene and ordered look to the small neighborhood.</description>
    <position x="200" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bamboo arch" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Under the Aether Dome" note="Warrior Mage|GL Warrior Mage|Margathe|RS Warrior Mage" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Thick cut-looped carpets cover the floor and a circle of cushions scattered around the water pipe provide a place to talk and watch the aquarium fish.  A tile walkway edges the walls, allowing passage through the area without leaving boot-dirt on the rugs.  One corner holds the guild leader's desk and a set of bookshelves.  The great dome of the guild looms overhead, its interior decorated with a flowery lattice-work in gold leaf and azure.</description>
    <position x="220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak doors" hidden="True" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Hall of Air" note="Air">
    <description>Several knotted hangings, each worked in the shape of an animal, are tacked to the walls.  Cushions and crumbs surround a low rosewood table that matches the corner bookshelf.  The hardwood floor is uncarpeted and unremarkable, except for a splattering of green paint near the stair.</description>
    <position x="240" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Hall of Earth" note="Earth">
    <description>Triangular raised planting beds are set in a rough triskele with smooth ocean pebbles and crushed shell providing a walkway through the garden.  A potting table rests against one wall, with a large wheelbarrow of loam parked next to it.  Skylights in the dome above ensure enough light for healthy plants.  The aroma of floral and herbal fragrances has banished the scent of brimstone and naphtha, leaving this as the only room in the guild that doesn't smell of something burning.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Hall of Water" note="Water">
    <description>Dark tiled walkways surround a shallow octagonal pool with a fountain set in its center.  The pool's blue and green tiles create an intricate, repetitive geometric mosaic that gives the impression of looking through a kaleidoscope.  The fountain's water trickles into the pool with a lulling patter.  A cypress bench rests against one wall, with a cluster of potted palms on either side.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Hall of Fire" note="Fire">
    <description>Tattered bits of burned carpet have been pulled together to cover the floor at one end of the hall.  Scorched chairs and singed tables are clustered near the carpet.  The other end of the hall is starkly empty, the walls burned and gouged and the floor coated with ash.</description>
    <position x="200" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Tower of Air" note="Tower of Air">
    <description>Airy and open, the landing's archways give a clear southeasterly view beyond the inner canal to the break in the middle ring and the Dajere Bridge.  An occasional murmur from people passing below rises up the stairwell to mix with the sounds of the canal and Screeee! of the gulls.  Each quadrant of the dome's ceiling is painted with a view of the sky.</description>
    <position x="240" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Tower of Fire" note="Tower of Fire">
    <description>Airy and open, the landing's archways give a clear view over the city toward the carillon, and of the northern end of the Dajere Bridge.  Smoke and noise drift up from below, accompanied by the smell of naptha, brimstone, and incense.  Every so often, the conversations of people below can be heard over the racket and rumpus downstairs.  Despite regular cleanings, the dome overhead is covered with a sooty film that obscures the decoration.</description>
    <position x="140" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open archway" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Tower of Earth" note="Tower of Earth">
    <description>Airy and open, the landing's archways give a clear northwesterly view over the city and toward the carillon.  The smell of cultivated earth and growing plants wafts up from below, and partially obscures the ever-present scent of something burning.  The dome was designed with skylights to provide plenty of sun for the plants.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="235" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Warrior Mage Guild, Tower of Water" note="Tower of Water">
    <description>Airy and open, the landing's archways give a clear northeasterly view beyond the inner canal to the colorful homes and businesses nestled on the middle ring.  The sound of splashing water rising from the fountain mingles with the slosh of the canal to drown out any conversation from the lower room.  The dome is painted in blues and greens, its geometric motif a mirror of the pattern in the pool below.</description>
    <position x="240" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open archway" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Ship Circle, Scupper's Furrier" note="Scupper's Furrier|Bundles" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Neat as a pin, Scupper's Furrier Shop still bears the disquieting scent of uncured hides and pelts.  An attempt has been made to mask it, not quite successfully, with large bowls of potpourri placed here and there.  Scupper busies himself about the place, moving stock from one pile to another.</description>
    <position x="80" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Oweede's Place" note="Oweede's Place|Pawn" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The air is thick with motes of dust dancing in the dim light and the scent of lemon polish nearly masks the smell of musk.  Heavy oak shelves lining the walls from floor to ceiling bow under the weight of countless items of undeterminable value.  A stack of crates holding hundreds of used cards and wedding invitations rests against the end of a scarred counter.  In one corner, a canvas sack full of dull jelly beans lies against a box overflowing with used shapers.</description>
    <position x="80" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Library, Foyer">
    <description>Two sculptures, each resting upon a slender pedestal, flank the archway leading into the main reading room.  A mural depicting M'Riss flows across the walls.  Each wave, each gull, each pinnacle of rock is so exacting in detail that the mind expects to hear the crash of water rumbling beneath the cry of gulls and the smell of salt tickling the nostrils.</description>
    <position x="100" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Library, First Floor" note="Library">
    <description>A book balcony juts overhead from the rosewood paneled walls.  Wheeled wooden ladders attached to a brass track lining the top of the bookshelves stand ready to lend height to patrons too short to reach the top of the stacks -- where all the most interesting books hide.  A woolen area rug overlays the hardwood floor, muffling scooting chairs as well as footsteps.  Oblong study tables and the librarian's desk are centered in the room, beneath a multi-tiered chandelier hanging from the high ceiling.</description>
    <position x="100" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Library, Lounge" note="Flinder">
    <description>The lounge is replete with amenities for patrons taking a break from their reading, or who have just stopped by to chat and socialize. A scattering of leather chairs, low tables topped by lamps radiating a cozy glow through delicate milk-glass globes, and a bar stocked with coffee and lemon water offers refreshment.  An ornate marble fireplace mantled in carved rosewood and surmounted by an oval mirror is laid with wood and fragrant cuttings, ready for use should the weather turn cold.</description>
    <position x="100" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Library, Balcony">
    <description>A rosewood balustrade prevents plunging off the wide balcony and interrupting the studies of the patrons below.  Unlike the serious reference works on the first floor, these bookshelves are tight with leather volumes containing fanciful tales of adventure.  Oversized armchairs accented with needlework pillows offer cozy retreats to while away an afternoon.  A multi-tiered chandelier hanging from the high ceiling hovers just above eye level.</description>
    <position x="80" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Perobler's Orlogs, The Vestibule">
    <description>A small vestibule lit by ornate bronze lamps occupies the space between an ascending flight of stairs and the street door.  All the furnishings, from the polished lamps to the soft carpet underfoot, set a tone of quiet (and expensive) good taste.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go street door" hidden="True" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="Perobler's Orlogs, The Lobby">
    <description>At a large landing at the top of the stairs, several gleaming oak chairs face each other across a dark blue carpet with deep pile.  In the far wall, paneled double doors stand open, in limed oak matching the chairs.  To the right of the doors is a window with a dark blue drape, and to the left is a smaller door that says Repairs.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go smaller door" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Trintah's Herbal Remedies, Front Salesroom" note="Trintah's Herbal Remedies">
    <description>Twinkling sounds from a cowrie shell door chime hung above the entrance welcome visitors to this bustling shop.  Display shelves lining a large window are packed with an assortment of curious bottles, jars, and boxes containing healing remedies collected from several provinces that have been arranged between a collection of potted plants.  Small bundles of exotic herbs hang from the ceiling, thickening the air with their earthy perfume while partially concealing a set of stairs leading to the attic.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go driftwood door" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety stairs" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Trintah's Herbal Remedies, Side Salesroom" note="herbs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Faded whitewashed walls, painted with images of healing regents, serve as advertising for some of the items sold here.  An earthy, herbal scent wafts through the air, growing stronger near an iron cauldron hung above a copper brazier, which slowly simmers with one of Trintah's latest experiments.  Flashes of color dash around the room like elusive pixies as light from bronze lanterns bounces off strings of colored sea glass, collected from local beaches and hung to create a decorative beaded curtain.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beaded curtain" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Trintah's Herbal Remedies, Salon">
    <description>Offered by the owner, this cozy salon may be a ploy to keep people spending coins in her shop.  The smell of freshly baked bread mingled with medicinal liquors wafts from a sideboard against the wall, masking the odd scent permeating the building while encouraging customers to linger and socialize.  Groupings of small tables, covered in colorful linens and surrounded by comfortable chairs, are strategically placed about the room to draw attention to a dolphin triskele mosaic set into the tiled floor.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="Trintah's Herbal Remedies, Behind the Beaded Curtain">
    <description>Upon first glance, the curtain leads to a narrow hall that appears to be no more then a well-stocked closet.  Rows of shelves line the walls, deceiving the eye, as it opens to a private room.  Padded walls covered in red velvet combine with plush carpets to soundproof this area, making it perfect for clandestine meetings.  Ornate racks hung behind elegant cases display items not available to the general public.  Incense wafts from a round mahogany table, surrounded by chairs, at the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beaded curtain" destination="251" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="Trintah's Herbal Remedies, Attic" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Ventilation grates provide a slight breeze that assists in drying bundled herbs hung from the rafters but do nothing to relieve the oppressive heat.  The air is thick with a strange odor, not floral and not spice but definitely unpleasant.  Large storage barrels stacked alongside wooden crates provide seating for the weary.  Light from a lantern outside a small window falls on one of these containers, marked with a skull and crossbones, fueling rumors that not all of Trintah's concoctions are for healing.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety stairs" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="Saja's Boarding House, Common Room" note="Saja's Boarding House|Boarding House" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Saja's Common Room is near-continual chaos.  A hurried clerk at the back checks travelers in and out while throwing drinks across the counter that serves as both bar and desk.  A harried waitress rushes in and out of the kitchen, delivering food to patrons at trestle tables in the main room.  A second waitress delivers food through an arch, then delivers coffee to a battered oak booth.  Steep twisting stairs at the back lead to the balcony above.</description>
    <description>Saja's Common Room is near-continual chaos.  A harried clerk at the back checks travelers in and out while throwing drinks across the counter that serves as both bar and desk.  A harried waitress rushes in and out of the kitchen, delivering food to patrons at trestle tables in the main room.  A second waitress delivers food through an arch, then delivers drinks to a battered oak booth.  Steep twisting stairs at the back lead to the balcony above.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak arch" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak booth" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb twisting stairs" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="Saja's Boarding House, Dining Room">
    <description>The stone wall separating this room from the common room keeps the noise down to a dull roar, making it a preferred location for intimate or discrete conversation over dinner.  The oak benches here are smoother than their counterparts in the common room, and the trestle table has a tablecloth.  Even so, the real attraction is being at Saja's but out of the common room.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak arch" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="Saja's Boarding House, Battered Booth">
    <description>This battered oak booth is a favorite haunt of bards and students and home to near continuous discussion.  The topics tend toward wine, women and song, but even when they're intellectual, they're never less than heated.  Be it coffee by day or ale by night, the semi-permanent residents of this booth drink too much.  The trestle tables and oaken benches are battered beyond belief, but the history is such Saja would never dare replace them.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Saja's Boarding House, Common Room Balcony">
    <description>Steep, narrow stairs connect the common room to this open landing.  Doors to the various rooms in the inn open off the balcony while a sturdy railing prevents inebriated patrons from falling to the common room below.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb twisting stairs" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Saja's Boarding House, East Hall" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The one relatively quiet place in Saja's, this hallway provides access to the private rooms of Saja's long-term tenants and some of the better funded students.  Stout stone walls and smooth oaken floorboards along this hall exhibit little of the spontaneous carving so typical of the more public areas of the inn.</description>
    <position x="-306" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Saja's Boarding House, Oak Room" note="Oak Room">
    <description>A large feather bed in a battered oak frame dominates a room so small one must almost sit on the bed to close the door.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Saja's Boarding House, Deobar Room" note="Deobar Room">
    <description>Two bunk beds are squeezed into this tiny room, creating space for four students to sleep.  A rough chest provides the only storage for clothing.  The lack of space compels the residents to spend most of their waking hours in the booth downstairs and only use this room for sleeping.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Saja's Boarding House, Pine Room" note="Pine Room">
    <description>A heavy oak-framed bed takes up most of this tiny room.  A nightstand is the remaining decor of significance.  The door latches, though, and the room is dry. The walls are solid and the sheets are clean.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="The Assay Shop, Main Office" note="Assay Shop|Geprofa|MAMAS" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The Assay Office has an exceptionally orderly look to it, as if great care is taken to put, stack, stow or store everything in exactly the right place.  An assay clerk with a feather duster in hand stands behind a polished wooden counter bearing three graduated scales.</description>
    <position x="20" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Barber Shop" note="Barber Shop|Kriley" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Metal bars angled like a tiny scaffold, a wrought-iron seat, and a headrest form a chair bolted to the middle of the floor.  Vials, brushes, and razors clutter a shelf beneath a wall mirror placed to show patrons the barber's handiwork.  An orange cat alternates lounging on the window seat and teasing the parrot perched at the far end of the room.  Scattered between beast and bird, a dusting of fur, feathers, seed husks and hair clippings softens the rugged floor.</description>
    <position x="40" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Pearl Circle, Pet Shop" note="Pet Shop|pets|Woodhut" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Cracked seed husks are splayed across the floor, and the scent of birdcages and dogs permeates the air.  The shop display windows are smudged from wet noses pressing against them from within, while small handprints from without further cloud the panes.  A scrappy-looking parrot stares balefully from his perch.  Stains on the walls and counters mark the bird's favorite flightpaths.  An elderly lady with orange-tinted hair scurries about the shop, while her assistant tends to the counter.</description>
    <position x="80" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Mer'Kresh, Courthouse Entryway" note="Courthouse">
    <description>Low steps, each the entire width of the room, climb at evenly spaced intervals to the large door at the far end.  A long, narrow, black carpet lines the center of the room from one door to the other, hugging the steps closely.</description>
    <position x="60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ornate door" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Mer'Kresh, Courthouse Guardroom" note="Guardroom">
    <description>Several long-suffering guards stand on the other side of a large table, arms crossed, frowning and nodding at the supplicants across from them.  Occasionally a guard will turn around and pick up an item of some sort and hand it to the person across from him, but more often than not, the people leave empty-handed.  The unwilling are forcefully escorted out of the room.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Mer'Kresh, Court of Law and Justice" note="Court of Law and Justice">
    <description>High arches in the eight cardinal directions meet in the center to support a large, circular skylight.  Behind a curved desk on the far side of the round room sit the judges, stern-looking men and women with a reputation for rapidly deciding the fate of the accused.</description>
    <position x="60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ornate door" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Clerics' Guild, Foyer" note="Cleric">
    <description>Heavy double doors open onto a large, rectangular foyer.  Two stories high, the entryway to the Cleric's Guild is dimly lit by several wall-mounted lanterns.  Two thick, fluted pedestals guard each side of the chapel's double door to the east.  Low padded benches line each wall between the pedestals and the doorway to the guildmaster's office on the north wall, and the meeting room on the south wall.</description>
    <description>Heavy double doors open onto a large, rectangular foyer.  Two stories high, the entryway to the Cleric's Guild is well lit through tall, narrow windows high on the walls.  Two thick, fluted pedestals guard each side of the chapel's double door to the east.  Low padded benches line each wall between the pedestals and the doorway to the guildmaster's office on the north wall, and the meeting room on the south wall.</description>
    <position x="120" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ornate door" hidden="True" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Clerics' Guild, Guildmaster's Office" note="GL Cleric|Eydtha|Authun|RS Cleric" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Neat bookshelves behind a large desk hold Eydtha's private library.  The office is brightly lit by a hanging lamp in each corner.  A thick, dark blue carpet covers the stone floor, and two padded, straight-backed chairs sit in the corners nearest the door.  The large desk holds neatly stacked papers and a small statue of a dolphin.</description>
    <description>Neat bookshelves behind a large desk hold Eydtha's private library.  The office is brightly lit through two tall windows on the east and west walls.  A thick, dark blue carpet covers the stone floor, and two padded, straight-backed chairs sit in the corners nearest the door.  The large desk holds neatly stacked papers and a small statue of a dolphin.</description>
    <position x="120" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Clerics' Guild, Meeting Room">
    <description>The windowless meeting room holds a long, narrow table surrounded by chairs, as well as several smaller tables.  Several people sit at a corner table discussing a private matter.  Benches line the walls underneath three large tapestries depicting various gods.</description>
    <position x="120" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Clerics' Guild, Chapel" note="Shrine4-15|Chapel" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Tall windows high on the north and south walls allow plenty of light into the chapel.  A plainly carved altar sits under two beautiful stained-glass windows in the east wall.  Thick red carpets hug the walls, leaving the center of the stone floor bare.  Each corner holds two floor-standing braziers for the ritual burning of sacred writings.</description>
    <position x="140" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="273" name="Alydendael, Front Gardens">
    <description>Thick growths of honeysuckle mingle with clumps of red and blue bellflowers to cover the iron fence and block out much of the noise of the street beyond.  Though the plants drape seemingly randomly over the fence, a guiding hand has been at work here.  The grass has been trimmed closely along the sides of a gravel path and bands of flowering plants curve alongside all the way to the walls of a sturdy stone building across from an iron gate.</description>
    <description>A dark mass of plants clings tenaciously to the iron fence that surrounds the garden.  Even at night, the bright colors of flowers stand out against the shadows, obviously tended on a regular basis.  A paltry few torches dimly light a gravel path as it angles its way up the sloped surface of a stone building.  The flicker of light is brighter on the roof of that building and contrastingly darker where the path runs down to the iron gate that leads to the street.</description>
    <position x="320" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Alydendael, Elevated Walkway">
    <description>New cornerstones have been mortared into place around the top of a downward arching ramp made of similar new stones.  At one point, this walkway was nothing more than a simple roof, now worked over with fresh beams of polished acanth for sturdy footing.  A tower pokes up from the far end of the walkway, holding aloft a large bell that peeks out of windows near the top.  Below, on either side of the building on which the walkway rests, sit well-tended and thick gardens.</description>
    <description>Lines of lit torches flank the sides of the walkway, their glare a bit too bright to make sense of the odd shadows that dance in the gardens below.  Perhaps the motion in those gardens is nothing more than an illusion created by the flicker of lights here, but the dark and elegant spire that stretches upwards at the other end of the walkway is hardly false.  Only when a torch shimmers just right does the outline of the shade reveal itself to be a bell tower.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Alydendael, Tower Arch">
    <description>Exposed to the elements, the base of the tower is little more than a covered section of the building's rooftop walkway.  A sturdy arch stretches over a ramp descending to the back gardens, and an identical one arcs over the walkway itself, but the main support for the tower above are the solid pillars stoically bearing its weight along the northern and western sides.  From behind one of the pillars, a tight tendril of ivy wraps its way upwards from the gardens and vanishes from sight.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron-edged stairs" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Alydendael, Waterfront Gardens" note="Alydendael">
    <description>A carefully manicured gap parts the growths of bellflowers and honeysuckle that drape over the back fence, revealing the lapping waves of the bay beyond the fence's iron bars.  A tossed stone would have to travel no further than an arm's distance past the fence before it'd be flying over nothing but the water's surface.  The shores of M'Riss from this distance are far out of reach of any tossed thing, however, and can be seen as only a bold tree-lined ridge far away.</description>
    <description>The murky waves of the bay splash just beyond an empty space in the plants hanging from the back fence, merely an arm's throw away.  Further away is the dark smudge of M'Riss's shore that blocks the horizon, lit only by the tiny twinkling lights of traders moving along the Ring Road.  A brighter spark of light flickers into being as a ship on the bay floats past, coming into view as it passes through the gap in the shadowy bellflowers on the fence.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth door" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Alydendael, Belltower" note="Belltower">
    <description>Rising from the lower floor in a gentle curve along the wall, a set of iron-edged stairs ends just before a small arched window.  An ivy vine tapers to an end just beyond the window, growing from some indeterminate place below and clinging to the beige stonework.  Crafted from the same stone as the walls, a table rests heavily below the window, safely enough away from the vine therein.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron-edged stairs" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Alydendael, Oceanview Bell" note="Oceanview Bell">
    <description>A huge bronze bell hangs suspended from a roughly hewn frame in front of the arched windows.  Though the bell fills the top of the tower, it fails to block the expansive view of Mer'Kresh and the bay.  Far to the northwest, Undogoz Mountain is but a blue mound on the horizon, while much closer, the rooftops of Mer'Kresh lay as would a child's toppled toy blocks.  Concentric rings of canals force the building blocks into circles.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Estate Holders Club, Hallway">
    <description>The walls are made of neatly arranged stone blocks.  In place of windows, triangular azure and emerald banners dangle from thick acanth rods that criss-cross the ceiling.  A few of the banners attempt to hide a section of the western wall where the older stones give way to a recently filled-in arch.</description>
    <position x="300" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth door" destination="276" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Estate Holders Club, Lounge" note="Estate Holders Club">
    <description>A white marble statue of a woman carved with flowing robes stretches her arms upwards, coming within a fingerspan's width of the ceiling.  Within her hands, she grasps a solitary gaethzen globe that spreads a smooth glow across the room.  Crouched in the dim shadow of that statue is a beaten leather couch, built in a gentle curve so that it fits neatly into one of the corners.  Before the couch a fluffy bearskin rug sprawls.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="281" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Estate Holders Club, Alydendael Branch Bank" note="Premium Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Definitely cramped and pressed for space, the bank has been left devoid of most adornments.  Since a large group of people would fill the room quickly, everything has been designed with speed and efficiency in mind and with few distractions to make customers linger.  Still, a great deal of effort has been put into keeping the floors and stone walls spotless.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Estate Holders Club, Alydendael Branch Exchange" note="Premium Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The exchange booth was once obviously nothing more than a simple storeroom, as is testified above by the exposed undersides of the raw roof beams.  From the beams hangs a colorful banner, probably set there to distract customers from spotting clues about the booth's previous use.  A recent addition is the set of strong iron bars that cage off the actual booth and the sturdy reinforced door leading therein.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="281" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Perobler's Orlogs, The Showroom" note="Perobler's Orlogs|Orlogs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The light gleams off polished glass in the showroom of Bergen Perobler, Elanthia's foremost chronometrician, where the wares of this inventive and artistic genius are displayed.  The buzzes, hums, chirps, cuckoos, chimes, and ticks of his astonishing creations are a background to every conversation.  A competent-looking guard by the exit doors keeps a wary eye on the customers and merchandise alike.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Perobler's Orlogs, The Repair Closet" note="Knobby" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This tiny, almost bare room -- the workroom of Knobby Snaggle, Perobler's repairdwarf -- has only a small counter with a high stool behind it.  What light there is comes from a small window in the rear wall, on which hang a handsome sign and a framed certificate.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small door" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="The Galley Sanegazat" note="Map107a_Belarritaco_Bay.xml">
    <description>The galley, like its twin, carries passengers and cargo, but it can easily become a war galley.  Brackets for catapults and a reinforced prow for mounting a ram show its military use, part of the reason why the rowers are trained and willing volunteers for this hard service.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-140" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="The Galley Cercorim" note="Map107a_Belarritaco_Bay.xml">
    <description>Passengers and cargo crowd the deck of the sleek, black galley.  Below, visible through the large opening amidships, sit the tanned and muscular rowers, one shift at the oars while the other rests.  The exhorter sits in the stern behind his drum, ready to speed or slacken the rhythm as needed.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-140" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Deeper's Tavern, The Common Room" note="Deeper's Tavern">
    <description>A few steps lead down to a hot, brightly lit room packed with sailors in every state of consciousness from keen-eyed alertness to drunken collapse.  Somewhere in the crowd, a reedy concertina accompanies one or another of several songs being sung in cheery disregard for each other.  Behind the mahogany bar, the owner Deeper presides over the tumult, disappearing into the throng from time to time with an armload of mugs.  Above the bar hangs a hand-written menu.</description>
    <position x="340" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="Deeper's Tavern, The Mainmast">
    <description>A yard-thick, floor-to-ceiling wooden pillar dominates this corner of the tavern.  The mast, as the regular patrons call it, rises like a tree trunk through the center of a circular table.  Here the boastful and the optimistic gather to test their strength of arm.</description>
    <position x="320" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Deeper's Tavern, Behind the Bar">
    <description>Kegs empty and full, mugs for the filling, and the tools of the trade (including a solid-looking bungstarter) line this long, narrow space between the bar and a rear wall hung with trophies of the sea.  At the end farthest from the entrance is an open trapdoor.</description>
    <position x="340" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="287" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open trapdoor" destination="291" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Deeper's Tavern, Rancois' Table" note="Rancois' Table">
    <description>This secluded corner of the tavern contains the favorite table of Rancois Sendaque, the most famous part-time poet in Mer'Kresh.  Many of the song scrolls he sells are his original work, and well known among the discriminating (and the stingy).</description>
    <position x="360" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Deeper's Tavern, The Cellar">
    <description>The dim lantern-light reveals a room filled from the floor to the low ceiling with the supplies and furnishings of the tavern.  Here stand broken tables and benches awaiting repair, boxes of crockery mugs, framed paintings that appear to have been used as weapons, and even a stuffed marlin that has seen better days.  Stacked kegs of rum hide one wall completely, and a large wine rack filled with bottles stands a little ways out from another wall.  Stairs lead up to the tavern's main room.</description>
    <position x="360" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Mer'Kresh Town Hall, Grand Foyer" note="Town Hall">
    <description>A multitude of torches illuminates the high arch of the Grand Foyer, light glinting from stained glass windows in the ceiling.  White marble columns anchor the majestic arch to the grey marble floor.  Great oaken doors along the north wall lead to government offices and the formally lit Council Arch leads south to the Grand Hall.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go council arch" destination="293" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arcade door" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office door" destination="296" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office entrance" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="293" name="Mer'Kresh, Grand Hall of the Council" note="Council">
    <description>The Grand Hall of the Council is extremely formal.  If the Rissan oak beams and white marble walls could speak, they would tell tales about the founding of Rissan tradition.  A huge oak council table dominates the hall.  Council chairs surround the table at precise locations.  The council president's chair looms like a throne above one end of the council table, adding to the sense of awe the room inspires.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go council arch" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Housing Arcade, New Homes Office" note="Homes" color="#00FF00">
    <description>At the far end of a spacious room with a polished oak floor sits a large, ornately carved desk and a high-backed oak chair with a velvet cushion.  On either side behind the desk are floor-to-ceiling stained glass windows.  A brightly colored rug is draped over the desk.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="295" />
  </node>
  <node id="295" name="Housing Arcade, Transfer Office" note="Home Transfer Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This little room, barely bigger than a closet, is crowded even more by crates, boxes, racks, and bookcases overflowing with scrolls and papers.  In front of a tiny window is a folding desk and stool.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Mer'Kresh Town Hall, Debts and Fees" note="Debt" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A massive oak counter topped with a fence of steel bars dominates the Mer'Kresh Office of Debts and Fees.  A smiling clerk behind the counter does his cheerful best to help Rissans who have problems with debts or with the city bureaucracy.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Mer'Kresh City Hall, Office of Citizens" note="Citizenship" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Several candles cast a warm glow on the polished rosewood counter spanning the back third of the room.  An elderly clerk stands behind the counter, ready to serve people seeking citizenship.  Plainly framed documents interspersed with banners and flags hang from the walls, and historical mementos are housed in a case near the entrance.  A large bronze plaque is affixed to the wall near the case.  Amid the mishmash of artifacts, and perhaps an artifact himself, sits an old man whittling.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Rooftop Garden">
    <description>Stone troughs along the edges of the rooftop serve a dual purpose as homes for flowering plants and as guard rails to keep sky-watching mages from stumbling off into the gardens two stories below.  Spider vines arc over the ledges and flow downward, unafraid of the height.  To the west, the roof of the commodities building stares into the sky in poor imitation of the scholars that use this manor.</description>
    <position x="0" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="299" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spider vine" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Rooftop Garden" note="Telescope">
    <description>Heavy growths of plants and vines drape down the side of the building, wrapping themselves lovingly around the stone gargoyle statues protruding from the ledges.  A blank spot some distance below hints that one of the gargoyles may have lost its mortared hold on the wall and plummeted into the canal.  Poking out over the edge of the rooftop, and uncaring of the canal's rushing waters, is a polished blackwood telescope set neatly onto a raised pedestal at the southern end of the roof.</description>
    <position x="0" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Upper Hall">
    <description>Dark wood paneling runs the length of the upper hall, split by contrasting trim nearly halfway up the wall.  A carved sandalwood door breaks the monotony of the paneling along the southern wall.  Tacked to the center of the door is a curled note, pierced through the middle by a bent nail.  At the far end of the hall, a spiral staircase rises through a covered opening in the roof, while opposite, a set of wide steps descends to the lower floor.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="298" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide steps" destination="301" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Hall" note="Besoge|Grazhir|Ways|Astral Plane" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>An unusual copper and bronze sculpture consisting of crescent moon shapes bobs silently at the base of some wide steps.  Surrounding the metal moons on all sides, the walls are covered with a painted depiction of Moon Mages in various stages of stargazing.  The three moons -- Xibar, Katamba and Yavash -- smile down upon the watching mages from their locations high in the painted sky.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide steps" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Caress-of-the-Moons Manor, Foyer">
    <description>Directly opposite from an ironwood door is a massive portrait of a hunting expedition, though this is far from the only indication of the manor owner's inclinations.  The walls are decorated with an inordinate number of trophies, ranging from snowbeast heads to bearskins and leucro tails.  A snarling boar's head stares down the hall from its perch high above the glazed marble floors.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Carillon, Garden Shrine" note="Favors|Depart" color="#800080">
    <description>Two simple altars, one of rosewood and the other of stone, nestle within the stand of close-set mimosa.  Fluttering slowly to the ground, feathery blossoms settle to the earth like a carpet of pink snow.  Overhead, soft murmurs whisper through the leaves, perhaps the counsel of the gods, perhaps the entreaties of the dead.  Dull basalt stepping stones lead out of the grove.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stepping stones" hidden="True" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Mer'Kresh Ovens" note="Ovens|Bakery" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The warm aroma of baking invites adventurers into this tidy shop.  Fresh bread is displayed on a counter next to a table full of tarts.  A sturdy stair squeezed into one corner shares the back wall with a great stone oven.  The baker and her helpers scuttle about behind the counter, mixing batter, kneading bread, tending the oven, and generally scattering flour everywhere.</description>
    <description>The warm aroma of baking invites adventurers into this tidy shop.  Freshly baked bread is displayed on a counter next to a table full of tarts.  A great stone oven along the back wall dwarfs a sturdy stair squeezed into one corner.  The night crew is busy behind the counter, mixing batter, kneading bread, tending the oven, and preparing bread for tomorrow's Mer'Kresh.</description>
    <position x="260" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy stair" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Mer'Kresh Ovens, Apartments" note="Apartments" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The rich aroma of baking bread drifts along the hall from the bakery below followed by an occasional dusting of flour.  Warmth radiates from a huge stone chimney next to some stairs on the back wall.  The plain oak floor and sturdy oak walls suggest solid, but unspectacular apartments.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy stair" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="JAIL" note="JAIL">
    <description />
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Marbled granite boulders have been used to create a retaining wall that shores up the land along one side of the road.  Stones once carefully stacked by size and secured with mortar form a solid mass that should stand the test of time despite its rundown appearance.  Along the top, wires running between wooden fence pickets have been added to discourage the local children from exploring.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Weatherworn pallets of flagstone sit waiting for workers to return and lay them out as pavement on the sections of unfinished road.  Weeds grow in scraggly patches around the stacked stone, managing to spread despite the hardened soil.  Broken and discarded masonry tools litter the area, suggesting it has been some time since a cleanup crew has been by.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="314" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="313" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>In preparation for paving with flagstones and mortar, this section of the road's gravel base has been covered with a bed of sand carted in from the island's shoreline.  Having been left too long, the once packed and graded surface is now covered in uneven ruts.  A collection of rakes has been tossed into a haphazard pile that passing seagulls have liberally decorated with excrement as they've flown by.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="314" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="313" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="312" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>The trail of gravel runs alongside the waterway then swerves off towards a section of open land.  Rolling waves can be heard slapping at the footings of the Nelyn Bridge located a short distance away, filling the air with the salty scent of the water in the nearby canal.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="313" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="312" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="311" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Veering off, this section of road still needs a lot of work.  The flagstones stop abruptly as the land drops down into a shallow path, dug to create a route through the ashen soil.  Chunky gravel lines the ditch's base and is topped by another layer of rocks the size of peas in an attempt to provide good drainage under the flat stone surface when it is completed in the future.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="310" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Crunching underfoot, the hard-packed soil is covered in chunks of broken mortar and its dusty residue, carpeting the land in construction debris.  A broken-down wooden wagon stands tilted at an angle, its cargo of granite blocks slowly shifting to one side of the bed as time goes by.  Several planks, piled haphazardly nearby, are starting to show signs of rot from the island weather combined with the occasional damp mist that travels over from the canal.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="310" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Surviving despite the poor soil conditions, a tall oak was left standing to provide some shade from summer's heat to the otherwise stark lot.  A makeshift bench, built from a stack of black basalt slabs, sits close to the tree's gnarled trunk.  Judging by the trash left scattered around, workers took full advantage of the slight comfort offered to eat and watch the entertaining scenery of gondolas gliding by in the canal or fishermen struggling with their catch at the water's edge.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="314" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="312" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="314" name="Mer'Kresh, Gull Circle">
    <description>Granite markers subdivide this large lot into smaller sections, mapping out a strip of plots suited in size for future shops.  The ground limestone once used to connect them has now mostly worn away, leaving only a slight shadow on the hard, ashen soil to show the builder's original intentions.  In one corner, a black basalt foundation remains unfinished, waiting for mortar to secure the back wall in place.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="313" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="315" name="Fang Cove, Fate's Fortune Lane" note="Map150_Fang_Cove.xml">
    <description>A towering marble archway opens a gap in the wall to the north and separates the ongoing construction and somewhat more refined completed structures of Fate's Fortune Lane from the crude structures and makeshift walkway along the beach.  The entrance to a squat, wide bungalow sits in opposition to the arch, and the sheltering cliffs of Fang's Peak rise up from behind it.  To either side of the arch, cobblestones of different shapes and sizes have been laid out to form the wide Fate's Fortune Lane.</description>
    <position x="60" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit portal" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="316" name="Mer'Kresh, Undogoz Square" note="Undogoz Square">
    <description>Cobblestones line this small square, which is dominated by the large, stone building housing the Mer'Kresh Crafting Society.  A parade of sturdy wagons going in and out of the nearby alley is a common sight as artisans haul their hand-made goods off for sale at the local markets.  Wooden benches line the edge of the canal, offering a scenic spot for workers to rest and enjoy some fresh air.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go building" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="317" name="Lanternside Inn, Front Desk">
    <description>A long desk enhanced with pieces of shell and driftwood rests in front of a series of shelves lined along the back wall.  Timidly, envelopes and scrolls poke out from their current homes upon the shelves, awaiting delivery to some employee or resting traveler.  A small bell dangles above the desk, patient for a tap from the next person to check into the inn, while a hutch fastened with a bronze padlock waits calmly to dole out room keys.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="318" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="318" name="Lanternside Inn, Lobby" note="Lanternside Inn|Herb Play Restaurant">
    <description>Two twin windows, shuttered on the outside, stare inwards towards a brightly upholstered couch and a small wooden end-table.  Across from the end-table, the wall is set with a brass sign made in the shape of a dancing herb leaf.  The mutterings of conversation and clinking of dinnerware spill out from the sign's neighbor, an artistically carved arch.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="317" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="319" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carved arch" destination="354" />
  </node>
  <node id="319" name="Lanternside Inn, Hallway">
    <description>The smooth painted walls leading to the lobby stop at the chair rail, giving way to a textured surface of plaster.  Small bits of shell and coral stuck in the plaster turn the upper walls into a mosaic of pink and beige spirals ascending a set of carpeted stairs.  Other than a couple of brass candelabras to light the hall, there are no adornments to distract any of the inn's tired customers from a direct course upwards and to a comfortable bedroom.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="318" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb carpeted stairs" destination="320" />
  </node>
  <node id="320" name="Lanternside Inn, Upper Floor">
    <description>An out-of-place tapestry barely covers several gaps where time and vandalistic wayfarers have removed bits of attractive coral from their resting places set in the walls.  A richly colored carpet runs through the hallway and down the stairs to the lobby below.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="322" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb carpeted stairs" destination="319" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue-painted door" destination="321" />
  </node>
  <node id="321" name="Lanternside Inn, Canal Room">
    <description>Curtains, the color of a blue and green streaked river, almost hide a picture window with a view of the outdoor dining area of the Herb Play.  A driftwood bedstand sits quietly by the bed, pushed snugly against the chair rail that splits the walls.  The lower half of the walls are painted in pastel shades of green, while the upper is a soft creme not unlike the color of a frothy stream churning up sand.  Only a small rug covers any of the hardwood floor, nestled at the foot of the bed.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue-painted door" destination="320" />
  </node>
  <node id="322" name="Lanternside Inn, Upper Floor">
    <description>Small bits of coral and seashell peek out from the plaster of the walls, mixed in during the construction of the inn.  Lightweight tapestries have been arranged intermittently down the hall, showing various scenes of a musical performance.  A narrow vase rests in its own bed, a small linen-covered table pushed tightly against the wall and out of the way of yawning wanderers stumbling towards their rooms.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="323" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="320" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red-painted door" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="323" name="Lanternside Inn, Upper Floor">
    <description>A portrait framed in dark wood and lit by a small piece of gaethzen hangs on the rough plaster wall.  The shells and coral that poke from the plaster along the other sections of the inn are not absent here, and form intricate spiral patterns around the edges of the portrait.  A small brass plaque is embedded below.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="322" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green-painted door" destination="325" />
  </node>
  <node id="324" name="Lanternside Inn, Volcano Room" note="Volcano Room">
    <description>A plush red carpet covers the entire floor, thick and wooly but for one triangular shaped spot near the red-painted door worn thin from the door's use.  A matching set of fiery curtains hangs about the window, brushing just against the obsidian-topped bedstand.  A bright orange bedspread lays on the bed, continuing the theme of fiery color.  Even the tropical plant in the corner shares the theme, if in design rather than color, as it rests in a stone pot filled with ashy dirt.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red-painted door" destination="322" />
  </node>
  <node id="325" name="Lanternside Inn, Island Room" note="Island Room">
    <description>A large bed carved realistically in the shape of a giant seashell dominates the center of the room.  Its wood has been painted in shades of pearlescent pink and white, and a pale blue bedspread drapes over the edge of the bed.  A deep blue curtain hangs around the window, and a nightstand decorated with bits of coral squeezes itself between it and the bed.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green-painted door" destination="323" />
  </node>
  <node id="326" name="Oceanhome Apartments, Mer'Kresh" note="Oceanhome Apartments" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Most of the floor has been swept free of debris, revealing a mosaic of faded pastel tiles.  Black dirt, spared by the broom, still clings in the corners of the room.  Hung crookedly on one wall, a message board wears an assortment of smudged papers proclaiming long-past resident meetings.</description>
    <position x="340" y="265" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="327" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="327" name="Oceanhome Apartments, First Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A set of rickety stairs ascends to the next floor as the giant-sized face of a smiling Rissan beams down the hall.  Originally painted in extreme colors, the face is now partly veiled by a thin layer of soot and dust.  Tightly clutching to a foaming mug with one hand, the happy Rissan indicates his prized drink with a pointing finger.</description>
    <position x="340" y="245" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="326" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety stairs" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="328" name="Oceanhome Apartments, Second Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Holes pockmark the walls, some the size of a fist, while others are no larger than a finger.  Bits of plaster and wood lie on the floor, roughly corresponding to the locations of the gaps.  On the ceiling, brown-edged water stains mock celestial bodies, their origins not nearly as mysterious or impressive.</description>
    <position x="360" y="245" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety stairs" destination="327" />
  </node>
  <node id="329" name="Oceanhome Apartments, Second Floor">
    <description>A lonely red door sits at the end of the hall, the floorboards just before it swept clean by some industrious soul.  Nearby, an open window reveals a sight of Gull Circle, though not by design -- the window is missing several of its glass panes.</description>
    <position x="360" y="265" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="330" name="Ristmuir's Armory, Showroom" note="Ristmuir's Armory|weapons" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Ristmuir's tidy establishment is a study of craftsmanship, from the riste racks cleverly built into the window casement to the fine detailing of the showroom's wide-planked floor.  An array of weapons covers the back wall, arranged by their decorative appeal in an attempt to lure shoppers into making a purchase.  In the corner, a tall bin holds a selection of ammunition for sale.</description>
    <description>Ristmuir's tidy establishment is a study of craftsmanship, from the riste racks cleverly built into the window casement to the fine detailing of the showroom's wide-planked floor.  Lanterns illuminate the array of weapons covering the back wall to draw the attention of evening shoppers.  In the corner, a tall bin holds a selection of ammunition for sale.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="331" name="Mer'Kresh Crafting Society, Vestibule">
    <description>The building is constructed of stone, mined locally, to withstand years of abuse from the salty air that blows in off the ocean.  Tall, fluted columns stand near each corner of the room, helping to support the raised dome ceiling decoratively covered in silver leaf.  Tiny lights hidden within the roof's architecture reflect off the metallic surface to highlight an intricate, mosaic map of M'Riss inlaid into the tile floor.  A pair of crossed hammers adorns the top of an archway leading to the Forging Society.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="316" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="332" />
  </node>
  <node id="332" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Entry Hall" note="Forging Society">
    <description>Across the room from an archway leading to the main edifice are a pair of wooden benches, which are the only furniture provided for the customer's comfort.  Periodically, custodians hired to keep the area tidy wander through, occasionally muttering as they sweep the stone floor clean of all the grime people drag in with them when they leave the foundry.  On one wall, an artist has painted a portrait of the Undogoz Forge as a memorial to the now closed building where many Rissans learned their craft.  Insulating the space from the searing heat of the smithy is a heavy oak door, covered on each side with a sheet of steel for added protection.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="333" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="331" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="341" />
  </node>
  <node id="333" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Bookstore" note="Forging Books" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A long, cypress counter serves as a partition between the bookstore and a much smaller office area, making it easy for Master Smith Kapric, who runs the facility, to keep an eye on customers when they enter and offer assistance when necessary.  Tall racks are filled with sample books for the shopper who prefers to peruse the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="334" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="335" />
  </node>
  <node id="334" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Supply Shop" note="Forging Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Crude, wooden pallets stacked with recently mined ore create cramped aisles throughout the room, giving customers a chance to inspect the selection before making their purchase.  Off in the corner, several crates contain additional materials for sale, including already smelted ingots.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="333" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="335" />
  </node>
  <node id="335" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Tool Shop" note="Forging Tools" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Despite the building's thick, rock walls, the faint sound of metal hitting metal can sometimes be heard, its repetitive pattern becoming almost lyrical.  Clerks keep busy checking to make sure the displays of tools and supplies for sale are filled, often rushing to the backroom to load up on any stock that is missing.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="336" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="334" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="333" />
  </node>
  <node id="336" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Maker's Mark Shop" note="Maker's Marks" color="#FF0000">
    <description>White paint coating the stone block walls serves as a neutral canvas for the sketches of sample designs aimed at helping potential customers decide on what aspects they desire in their maker's marks.  Tools, templates and patterns hang above a small work area where artisans construct the purchased orders promptly as they come in.  Heat emanates from cracks around a leather curtain leading to the foundry.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="335" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="337" />
  </node>
  <node id="337" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Foundry">
    <description>Along the top of one wall, a row of exhaust vents siphon off some of the oppressive heat generated by the fire in an attempt to make the room's temperature more comfortable for forgers busy at their craft.  An ingot cutter salvaged from the Undogoz Forge sits near a large pile of fuel and a leather curtain leads to the Maker's Mark shop.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="342" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="336" />
  </node>
  <node id="338" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Foundry">
    <description>Already dark by its nature, the stone walls of the forge are blackened further by soot, ash and dust kicked up by the constant stream of workmen the forge serves on a daily basis.  Custodians hired by the city wander in and out checking the large waste bucket, making sure the discarded pieces of metal are cleaned up off the floor and keeping the foundry as clean of trash as possible.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="337" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="339" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="343" />
  </node>
  <node id="339" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Foundry">
    <description>Emanating from the fire, patchy clouds of soot cover the ceiling and form streaks down the walls like black rain during a tropical storm.  Ashy dust fills the air, spiraling up in the heat as it blows off a pile of fuel.  A rhythmic hammering sound drifts over from the smithy to the west, followed by an occasional curse indicating things probably didn't go the way the forger desired.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="340" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="344" />
  </node>
  <node id="340" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Foundry">
    <description>A combination of sweat and molten steel intertwine to permeate the air with a slightly acrid, sour smell that varies in intensity depending on the time of day.  Suspended by heavy chains secured to a blackened wooden beam is a huge granite crucible.  Piled high in the corner of the room is a large pile of crushed coal, waiting for the next forger to feed it to the fire.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="339" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="341" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="345" />
  </node>
  <node id="341" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Foundry">
    <description>Once servicing the Undogoz Forge, select pieces of equipment, which still remain in good working condition, have found a new home here as part of the city's attempts to keep costs down.  In the room's center, a constant fire burns in the circular firepit with a small pile of fuel by its side, waiting to be added to increase the flames to a blazing inferno.  The clang of metal against metal drifts over from the smithy to the west and a heavy, oak door leads to the entry hall of the society.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="340" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="346" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="332" />
  </node>
  <node id="342" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Smithy" note="Forge1">
    <description>The back wall of the smithy area is covered with a grimy grey and red dust from the constant attention of the grindstone.  Several small windows along the top of the wall vent some of the choking dust and heat from the forge, but solid steel grates prevent anything larger than a gauntlet from passing through and into the canal beyond.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="337" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="343" />
  </node>
  <node id="343" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Smithy" note="Forge2">
    <description>Despite being swept on a regular basis by diligent custodians, metal shavings and bits of broken steel litter the floor, creating a sparkling effect when lit by the flames of the forge's roaring fire.  The smell of burning coal and heated metal fight for dominance here, indicating the amount of work this room normally sees.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="342" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="344" />
  </node>
  <node id="344" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Smithy" note="Forge3">
    <description>An oversized, glowing forge dominates the center of the stone floor, banishing all other equipment to the outlying corners of the room.  Nicknamed -- The Beast -- it's constantly consuming the red-hot coals in its belly and demanding more fuel from the pile, much like a ravenous animal.  From the smell of burning flesh lingering in the room, many craftsmen have felt its fiery bite.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="343" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="339" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="345" />
  </node>
  <node id="345" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Smithy" note="Forge4">
    <description>The floor bears the burns and scars from regular sprays of stray sparks.  Should only the stone surface be an ocean, the equipment scattered about would make a parody of an armada of ships, possibly in mockery of the failed attempts of the Dragon Priest Empire to subdue Mer'Kresh.  In reality, though, the only subduing going on is that of iron and steel beneath a determined worker's tools.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="344" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="340" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="346" />
  </node>
  <node id="346" name="Mer'Kresh Forging Society, Smithy" note="Forge5">
    <description>Constant waves of scalding heat flow through the smithy, set into motion by the sizzling fires and red-hot metals being worked.  Even sounds seem warped and muffled, but somehow the echo of clanging tools and crackling of fiery sparks manage to cut through the thick air.  Nothing is spared the attentions of the temperature and dust, and both stone and metal tools wear the scars that the environment has delivered.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="345" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="341" />
  </node>
  <node id="347" name="Carillon Park, Footbridge">
    <description>Rising gently, the footbridge's arched shape is barely noticeable as it spans the narrow brook.  Spilling from the bridge's railing, roses and honeysuckle trail into the water and are tugged by the current.  Within the brook, glints of golden fish flash among the plants and sparkling coins thrown from the bridge by wishers and seekers.  The path away from the carillon parts the tufts of grass and cattails vying for space on the stream bank.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go footbridge" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="north" destination="348" />
  </node>
  <node id="348" name="Carillon Park, Stone Lions" note="Stone Lions">
    <description>Sheltered beneath a camphor tree, a proud basalt lion watches over his stone pride as they lounge in the flower-speckled clearing.  One lioness rolls on her back, one sniffs at a clump of lilies, while yet another sculptured lioness licks her cub.  Several stone cubs gather around a bronze paladin seated upon a basalt slab.  At the north end of the clearing, a grass and bamboo gate closes the path from further exploration.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" destination="347" />
  </node>
  <node id="349" name="">
    <description />
    <position x="95" y="100" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="350" name="Perpetual Blossoms of Mer'Kresh, Salesroom" note="Perpetual Blossoms of Mer'Kresh|Blossoms of Mer'Kresh|florist" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Perpetual Blossoms is like an endless spring in Mer'Kresh.  Flowers bloom all about the room, and a gablefruit vine climbs across the walls, flourishing in the illumination of a skylight set in the ceiling above.  Large displays, including those in the front window, hold freshly cut blossoms and bouquets that fill the air with intoxicating scents.  Floral clerks discretely watch over the domain, gently tending flowers and customers alike with gracious smiles.</description>
    <position x="240" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="351" name="Mer'Kresh, Carousel Family Services" note="Family Vault">
    <description>A series of guarded arches line the southern wall.  The complicated framework of iron and timbers spans across the ceiling.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights form the strikingly complex mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="0" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="352" name="The Sweet Life Candy Shoppe, Salesroom" note="Sweet Life Candy Shoppe|sweet|candy" color="#FF0000">
    <description>White paint covers the room from floor to ceiling, providing a blank canvas for the decorative exhibits of candy placed throughout the shop.  Strategically placed near the front window, a glass case filled with colorful, novelty candies works as free advertising to lure in customers from the street.  A long counter displaying an abundance of gourmet chocolates fills the space along one wall and across from it a table holds containers for sale so shoppers can make their own gifts for friends.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained arch" destination="353" />
  </node>
  <node id="353" name="The Sweet Life Candy Shoppe, Salesroom" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Recessed into the ceiling, a collection of gaethzen orbs bounce light off the whitewashed walls to help keep this interior space bright during business hours.  Placed against one wall, a long counter displays an array of colorful confections created with the shop's adult clientele in mind.  Across the room, a strong scent of liquor wafts into the air from the neatly stacked chocolates waiting to be purchased on the glass case.  Tucked into the corner is a table filled with containers shoppers can buy so they can pack up their sweets to take home for family and friends.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained arch" destination="352" />
  </node>
  <node id="354" name="The Herb Play Restaurant, Host's Station">
    <description>A brilliantly colored wooden partition angles from the host's stand towards the opposite wall, blocking the majority of the restaurant beyond from view, and the host's station from the view of seated patrons.  Likewise, any diners glancing towards the exit are spared the sight of the host turning away unsavory types, and are only met by the gazes of the myriad of colored masks affixed to the decorative screen.</description>
    <position x="-315" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carved arch" destination="318" />
    <arc exit="go" move="ask host about booth" destination="355" />
  </node>
  <node id="355" name="The Herb Play Restaurant, Dining Room">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres hang behind green shades, lending a soft glow that still reflects in the highly buffed and polished hardwood floors.  The only tables are those small enough to be carried by waiters, and remain in place only long enough for food to be transferred to an awaiting booth.  Screens of wood and paper create private dining areas for those artists too smug to allow others a watchful eye of their affairs.</description>
    <position x="-330" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="354" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="356" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go padded booth" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cushioned booth" destination="358" />
  </node>
  <node id="356" name="The Herb Play Restaurant, Dining Room">
    <description>Beautiful etched-glass doors twinkle as the outside deck's torches dance in the night air.  Gaethzen orbs, dangling from delicate chains above, glow with steady illumination, vanquishing the darkness just enough to reveal diner's plates.  The scent of food and smoke drifts from the kitchen, visible as wispy grey threads around the lighted orbs.</description>
    <position x="-315" y="225" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go leather booth" destination="359" />
  </node>
  <node id="357" name="The Singer's Booth, Herb Play Restaurant" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A horseshoe shaped seat curves around the dining table, obviously packed full of fluffy down given the odd feather that pokes out.  Along the sides of the seat, musical instruments of all types have been carved into the wood and rubbed with oil to a high sheen.  Someone has painted a cryptic signature with gold-colored paint on a small black shield etched with concentric circles that hangs overlooking the tabletop.</description>
    <position x="-345" y="195" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="355" />
  </node>
  <node id="358" name="The Actor's Booth, Herb Play Restaurant" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several miniature portraits line the walls and screens around the booth.  Representing theater performers of some by-gone era, it's likely that most of the faces portrayed have found a stage on the Starry Path by now.  In contrast to the faded color of the portraits, bright purples and yellows streak the walls, and even the seat of the booth itself has been dyed in vivid shades.</description>
    <position x="-315" y="195" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="355" />
  </node>
  <node id="359" name="The Dreamer's Booth, Herb Play Restaurant" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A bold deobar carving of Hodierna perches over the booth, arms outstretched and a sly smile spread across her face.  White alfar statuettes descend from her embrace, pierced by metal rods that hold them in place in the vignette.  To enhance the drama, the depiction of a clear night sky slowly dissolving into a sunrise has been painted in grand colors.  A few wavy letters mark the signature of the artist right near the side of the table.</description>
    <position x="-330" y="225" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="356" />
  </node>
  <label text="Gardens">
    <position x="-4" y="-211" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="City of Mer'Kresh">
    <position x="-383" y="-264" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="North Barricade (Super Celps)">
    <position x="-245" y="-207" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="South Barricade Celps">
    <position x="-220" y="520" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Jolas to Hara'jaal">
    <position x="260" y="450" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Galley to M'riss">
    <position x="230" y="-150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Healer">
    <position x="105" y="-241" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bloodfish/Celpeze">
    <position x="-110" y="-98" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="are in blue rooms">
    <position x="-111" y="-85" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Jail">
    <position x="50" y="80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pets">
    <position x="70" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="MAMAS">
    <position x="-20" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Barb Guild">
    <position x="134" y="40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="WM">
    <position x="189" y="137" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Guild">
    <position x="184" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Vaults">
    <position x="-50" y="40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Paladin Guild">
    <position x="-150" y="0" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Forge">
    <position x="-210" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Origami">
    <position x="-210" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Repair">
    <position x="-160" y="160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Weapons">
    <position x="-210" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Caress-of-the-Moons">
    <position x="-140" y="410" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Barber">
    <position x="30" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Lanternside">
    <position x="-360" y="230" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Inn">
    <position x="-340" y="240" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Saja's">
    <position x="-350" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Premium Bank">
    <position x="190" y="-80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cleric Guild">
    <position x="60" y="120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bundles">
    <position x="30" y="180" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pawn">
    <position x="40" y="260" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bank">
    <position x="-76" y="212" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Town Hall">
    <position x="-103" y="122" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Orlogs">
    <position x="-120" y="162" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Favors">
    <position x="-57" y="243" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Deeper's">
    <position x="287" y="386" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tavern">
    <position x="288" y="399" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Herbs">
    <position x="-246" y="-11" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Library">
    <position x="19" y="332" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Candy">
    <position x="-110" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>