<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Himineldar Shel" id="123">
  <node id="1" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal" note="RTF32|RT-AGF-S" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The road moves among low hills, through a patchwork quilt of fields and wood lots.  The cry of a boatman on the nearby river breaks the night silence from time to time.</description>
    <description>The road moves among low hills, through a patchwork quilt of tilled and fallow fields parted by an occasional wood lot.  Oxen plowing, cattle grazing or field hands working are familiar sights along the way, and one sees plenty of travelers this close to the ferry.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal" note="RTF02|RT-AGF-HEG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>One might almost call traveling the Haalikshal Highway a pleasure, even at night: the road is well marked and maintained, solid underfoot and free of the overhanging foliage that would make the way even darker.</description>
    <description>One might almost call traveling the Haalikshal Highway a pleasure, given the luxury of a good road, pastoral surroundings and views of majestic mountains.  Why, even the scarecrows are distinctive, judging by the one erected some distance from the road.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal">
    <description>The Highway makes its paved way through farm and foothill, and the traveling-companion wind conjures up images of what might lie on either side, bringing the scent of wood smoke or turned earth or ripening fruit.</description>
    <description>The Haalikshal Highway makes its paved way through farm and foothill, linking the hazy blue mountains to the west and the Segoltha River to the east.  Each turn of the road reveals some rural delight: here the even rows of an apple orchard, there a freshly plowed field, redolent with a yeasty scent.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal" note="RTF03|RT-AGF-FB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The road rises and falls over the hills that slope from the western mountains to the river landing.  The evidence of Dwarven industry lies on every side, and not just farming or herding --  cultivated wood lots testify to a thriving logging business, and loaded ore wagons rumble from the mines to the forges of Hibarnhvidar.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal" note="RTF04|RT-AGF-RP" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Rugged terrain forces the road to sometimes hug a hillside or avoid an outcropping of rock.  But the Dwarven penchant for straight lines is evident in the stone bridges that leap streams and the fills and cuts that smooth the way.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal">
    <description>The Dwarven road, smoothly cobbled, well drained and in good repair, marches through, around and over the knees of the mountains to the west.  They rise rank on jagged rank, and the road points straight to their heart.</description>
    <position x="20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow road" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Haalikshal Highway, Himineldar Shel to Ain Ghazal">
    <description>Steep, high walls on each side reduce the view overhead to a narrow strip of sky, and the gradual curve of the defile blocks off the view very far ahead or behind.  The excavation is an engineering feat, and given the potential of the cut for an avalanche, a defensive asset.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Haalikshal Highway, Aws Munar">
    <description>The great gates of Aws Munar, entrance to the Road Beneath the Mountain, are set at an angle into a high cliff.  Hammered bronze plates cover their surface with panels showing scenes of Dwarven kings and heroes.  Majestic in size and massive in construction, they completely seal the tunnel mouth when closed.  When open, they keep eternal watch on the road winding downhill to the northeast.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gates" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>Just inside the great gates of the entrance stands a statue of Kertigen lit by oil lamps on both walls.  He faces the entrance, where the lamplight reflects from the polished bronze panels on the gates, as if welcoming visitors on the road to Hibarnhvidar.</description>
    <description>Just inside the great gates of the entrance stands a statue of Kertigen, stretching from floor to ceiling and diverting travelers to one side or the other.  He faces the entrance to the north.  To his right, the eastern wall of the tunnel is pierced with a multitude of openings, carvings of such intricacy that the wall resembles a curtain embroidered in stone.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gates" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>Lamplight high on the walls reveals the stone petals, leaves, stem, and even thorns of an immense rose carved into the rock.  Across the wide hall from it stands a huge statue of a Dwarven maiden.  A mantle flows from her shoulders to the floor, its train gathered in folds at her feet.</description>
    <description>The petals, leaves, stem, and even thorns of an immense rose are carved into the top half of the outer wall.  Concentric circles of openings pierce the rock, outlining and forming the face of the flower.  Light from the embrasures falls on a statue against the western wall.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>The outer wall bears a panoramic carving in relief: it shows a wide door set into the face of a mountain with troll-like figures on either side of the door.  The guards (if that is what they are) have their hands raised, palms outward, as if forbidding entrance.  The ominous sculpture contrasts sharply with the rather domestic statue on the western wall.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>The variety and size of the wall carvings along the highway speak of countless hours of patient labor by master craftsmen and designers.  In this stretch of the tunnel, openings form the silhouette of a vast city skyline in the outer wall, showing towers, walls, temples, and bridges in fine detail.  Against the west wall stands a huge statue.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>High on the outer wall, at the limit of the lamps' beams, is a row of shafts bored through the stone.  They might be for light or ventilation, but their shapes are those of arcane symbols -- moons in all their phases, constellations of stars, the planets.  The temptation is strong to linger and see what happens when one of the celestial objects fills the corresponding opening.</description>
    <description>High on the outer wall, just where it begins to arch toward the center of the ceiling, is a row of shafts bored through the stone.  Beams of light stream through these openings, dappling the highway with pools of brightness in the shapes of arcane symbols -- moons in all their phases, constellations of stars, the planets.  None of the light quite reaches the statue against the inner wall.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>The underground highway bends in a wide curve past a huge statue against the outer wall.  Oil lamps high on both sides of the passage light the way, looking like twin rows of stars extending in both directions beyond the range of sight.</description>
    <description>The underground highway bends in a wide curve past a huge statue against the outer wall.  Twin rows of lights extend to the west, receding to a vanishing point beyond the range of sight.  To the north, the way is lit by the light of day.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>Lamps brightly illuminate the tunnels' polished surfaces and the statue against the south wall.  Yet something seems odd about the light in the vicinity, as if the lamps here were not quite aligned with those to the east and west, and the floor feels slippery underfoot.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>A row of stone benches offers comfort to travelers who want to pause in their journey.  Instead of facing the highway, however, the benches are turned in a half-circle toward the towering stone figure against the north wall, as if waiting for an audience.  Nearby, a fountain on the wall splashes into a bronze basin.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>A statue against the north wall watches over a highway that looks broad enough for three mammoths to walk abreast with the tops of their howdahs never touching the ceiling.  Oil lamps hang from bronze brackets set high on the fluted half-columns spaced evenly along the polished stone walls.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>A statue of a Dwarf three times life-size stands against the north wall between two glowing oil lamps.  To the east, lines of bright lamps recede into the darkness of the tunnel as far as the eye can see, but to the west the lines end a short distance away.</description>
    <description>A statue of a Dwarf three times life-size stands against the north wall between two glowing oil lamps.  In the distance to the west, the light from the entrance silhouettes a figure reaching from the floor almost to the high ceiling to the east, lines of bright lamps recede into the darkness of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="The Road Beneath the Mountain">
    <description>Just inside the great gates of the entrance is a statue of Hodierna, dividing the traffic that streams to her right or left and towering over the travelers who pass by.  A riot of carved figures covers the walls and arches high over the statue's head.  The stone seems almost supple, flowing into interlaced columns, branches of trees, and limbs of animals in a design that teases the eye and awes the imagination.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gates" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Haalikshal Highway, Sang Munar">
    <description>A ring of torches flares around the great gates of Sang Munar, rising from the valley floor like the entrance to a dragon's treasure vault.  They mark the west portal of the Road Beneath the Mountain, the underground link on the highway between Ain Ghazal and Hibarnhvidar.</description>
    <description>The great gates of Sang Munar are set in a steep, wooded slope rising from the valley floor like the entrance to a dragon's treasure vault.  They mark the west portal of the Road Beneath the Mountain, the underground link on the highway between Ain Ghazal and Hibarnhvidar.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gates" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ford" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Stark ironwood trees form a nearly impenetrable barrier around this small clearing, dark gaps open at each end to allow travelers to pass from the trade road to the Seord Kerwaith.  A squat inn sits just off of the narrow beaten path.  Built with thick timbers exposed against whitewashed walls, the two-story building appears rugged enough to withstand even the harshest of Forfedhdarian winters.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow road" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go squat inn" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Dense forest closes in on either side of the path, creating an absolute darkness no matter how bright the stars above the trees.  The rustle of animals and the occasional howl of wolves permeate the night, the only evidence of life.</description>
    <description>Dense forest closes in on either side of the path, creating the dimness of twilight no matter how bright the sun above the trees.  The rustle of animals can be heard in the distance, and the dark flash of the occasional leaping deer is the only visible sign of life.</description>
    <position x="60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Delicate and pale, a cluster of white snowdrops blooms in the hollow of a rotten log lying alongside the path.  The dead tree's fall opened the canopy of leaves and allows a limited view of the night sky.</description>
    <description>Delicate and pale, a cluster of white snowdrops blooms in the hollow of a rotten log lying alongside the path.  The fallen tree's death seems to have caused the only spot of sky visible here, allowing a ray of sunshine to hit the fragile flowers.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" note="Mine">
    <description>Closing oppressively around the rocky path, overhanging pine branches provide a wake-up call to wanderers not paying attention to the landscape.  Overhead, birds twitter unseen.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go abandoned mine" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Echoing through the leafy woods, the howl of the wind coming down the mountain is an ever-present reminder of the harsher, colder conditions to the south.  Pine needles cushion the path underfoot, fallen from the abundance of conifers that stretch towards the sky.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" note="Mountain Giants|Giants">
    <description>A steep stretch of the path joins the lower route to the west with the rugged ascent across Himineldar Shel.  Craggy stone juts from between stalks of hardy scrub grass, the large chunks of granite reminiscent of blocks of black ice.  The forest thins here, only sparse adventurous pine trees sprouting further up, leaving their hardwood brethren behind.</description>
    <position x="140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Sparse patches of brambles dot the steep path which winds its way up the stony mountainside.  The rare patch of dirt reveals the prints of some kind of large feline.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Chill winds howl constantly along the mountain road.  Every now and then, a stray flurry of snowflakes swirls down the path from a sudden gust of wind somewhere upwards.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Here and there a fragile snowdrop pokes its head up through the thin layer of frost that covers everything from this part of the mountain up.  Among the delicate flowers is a single frostbane bush, its dull burgundy hue bright against the whiteness of the landscape.</description>
    <position x="200" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" note="Frost Angiswaerd|Angiswaerd">
    <description>Footprints in the snow are barely discernible, though quite a few congregate in the area of a small cave mouth nearby.  Animal bones, the same bland white as their surroundings, lie scattered about, only the dull stain of blood at the ends ruining their camouflage.</description>
    <position x="220" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small cave" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Short and scraggly, a cluster of pine trees huddles together like bent old men standing side by side for warmth.  Beneath the largest conifer lie the shredded remains of a rough sackcloth lean-to, now covered by a thin layer of dirty ice and completely unusable.</description>
    <position x="240" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Amid the rocky crags and icy snowdrifts is a small area encircled by chunks of stone, the space just large enough for a Dwarf to lie down in.  At the fore is a small monument of crossed pickaxes, their blades dull and rusted and handles lashed together with heavy twine.  Placed just below it is a crude ice sculpture of a raven, with some black substance mixed into the water before freezing to give it a dusky hue.</description>
    <position x="260" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Stretching out in all directions, the craggy mountainside's icy and monotonous pallor is in stark contrast to the view of Forfedhdar it presents from here.  A thin plume of smoke is barely visible from an inn at the mountain's northern foot, settled in the only visible clearing amidst the dense forest below.</description>
    <position x="260" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>A gentle dusting of snow, like finely sifted powdered sugar, covers the surrounding landscape, growing in density towards the twisted summit of the Himineldar Shel.  Stooped trees jut randomly from the snowy ground underfoot, their partially bare canopies swaying in the chill breeze.</description>
    <position x="280" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>The steeply angled, stone-strewn road weaves between several large boulders protruding from the snow.  Icy wind, speeding down the rough slope of the mountain, seems to cut into any exposed flesh like an invisible blade, bringing with it a dull howl.</description>
    <position x="280" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>The roadway narrows slightly as it hugs the steep exterior of the mountain, its outer edge overlooking the sheer rock wall falling far below.  A few lifeless plants and miniature trees cling precariously to the slopes, their tangled roots weaving between the shallow cracks in the partially frozen facade.</description>
    <position x="300" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Cutting a narrow swath into the rough exterior of the mountainside, the roadway weaves along the steep exterior of the rock face.  Little can be seen of what lies far below in the darkness.</description>
    <description>The roadway weaves along the mountainside, cutting a narrow swath into the rock face.  Far below, dagger-like rocks jut from a grey stone basin midway down the sheer eastern face of the Himineldar Shel, their icy surfaces glistening in the sunlight.</description>
    <position x="280" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Glistening icicles dangle from countless narrow ledges hanging from the sheer rock face above, peeping out from beneath the densely packed snow.  The air is filled with the howl of the deathly chill wind as it sweeps over weathered stone, spinning shimmering flakes snow about in a hurricane of white.</description>
    <position x="260" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Curious shapes rise from the densely packed snow, concealing whatever might be lurking beneath the shifting sea of pristine white crystals.  The walkway cuts a narrow path into the Halfling-high snow, and the track's shoulders are covered in a thin layer of crystal-clear ice.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>As if rolling out a pristine white welcome mat, the summit of the Himineldar Shel spirals skyward to the west.  Howling blasts of bone-chilling wind curl downward from the peak of the mountain to sweep though the area, sending crystals of ice and snow dancing across the frozen landscape.</description>
    <position x="220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Several paces off the frozen pathway, a clawed ice-covered hand protrudes from somewhere beneath the snow, having paid the ultimate price for straying from the path formerly laid before the poor soul.  The landscape is a sea of snow and ice, the shimmering surface rolling along the uneven ground.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>The restless assault of the elements sweeps across the frozen landscape with an almost malevolent intelligence, as if driven to consume all living beings upon the icy slopes.  Howling mountain winds devour all other sounds with a brutal hunger, whipping across the craggy stone that protrudes from the smooth surface of snow.</description>
    <position x="180" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Ice monoliths tower above the landscape.  Several crates and the shattered remnants of a gilded caravan rest in a heap alongside the manmade pathway cut into the shifting snow drifts, carelessly discarded in an attempt to escape the bitter cold elements of the Himineldar Shel.</description>
    <description>Ice monoliths tower above the landscape, refracting the available light like mammoth prisms and casting rainbows of color upon the pristine driven snow.  Several crates and the shattered remnants of a gilded caravan rest in a heap alongside the manmade pathway cut into the shifting snow drifts, carelessly discarded in an attempt to escape the bitter cold elements of the Himineldar Shel.</description>
    <position x="160" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Rising amidst the shifting mass of snow and ice, a jagged rock wall ascends to the foot of the twisted pinnacle that marks the summit of the mountain.  In the lee of the rock facade in a small niche carved out by the elements, a stunted sapling sits within a thick cocoon of white ice.  A gentle rain of shimmering snow crystals tail downward from the ledge high above, swirling along upon the bitterly cold wind.</description>
    <position x="140" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road">
    <description>Darkness creeps along the narrow mountain road with the stealth of an assassin.  Nightfall is the harbinger of bitter cold temperatures and treacherous footing as the lengthening shadows make the icy trail extremely hazardous.  Blinding snow storms occur frequently in this region, striking with little warning and greeting the unprepared traveler with an untimely demise.  In a futile war against the ancient mountains, howling winds punish the rock walls with incessant fury.</description>
    <description>Covered in ice, a narrow trail hugs the sheer rock face as it winds through the mountains.  Fierce winds punish the pass with their incessant fury, a timeless war of element against element.  Blinding snow storms strike with little warning throughout the region.</description>
    <position x="160" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Night falls quickly upon the region, plunging it into an inpenetrable veil of inky blackness.  In the darkness, the monotonous landscape that dulled the imagination during the day becomes a trail of traps and pitfalls.  Ascending and descending, each successive shadow-covered mountain lulls the traveler into a false sense of security.  It is when the mind is weakest that nature will strike, be it blizzard, avalanche or the slip of the foot -- each has its own perils.</description>
    <description>Distant mountains loom along the horizon, their peaks lost in swirling clouds of windblown snow and ice crystals.  The monotonous landscape, consisting of unbroken, blinding white snow fields with scattered brown or grey rocky outcroppings, does little to stir the imagination.  Ascending and descending, each successive mountain lulls the traveler into a false sense of security.  It is when the mind is weakest that nature strikes with unbridled fury, be it blizzard, avalanche or the slip of the foot.</description>
    <position x="180" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="ice southeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="ice northwest" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>As night descends upon this mountainous region, falling temperatures increase the wind's bitter fury.  Blinding clouds of snow race across the slopes, disappearing into the darkness of the night.  The awesome power of nature unleashed against the mountain's solid stone is spellbinding.  Shadowy peaks, barely visible in the dark, are a reminder of the endless procession of mountains.</description>
    <description>Incessant storms rage throughout this region, the bitter cold winds a constant companion to travelers.  Blinding clouds of snow race across the slopes, covering everything in an ever-increasing blanket of white.  The awesome power of nature unleashed against the mountain's solid stone is spellbinding.  Towering mountains dominate the landscape and stretch as far as the eye can see, an endless procession of white-capped peaks.</description>
    <position x="200" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="ice east" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="ice northwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Creeping across the mountains, the deepening shadows slowly engulf the trail in darkness.  Fractured rocks, the shattered bones of the mountain, tell the tale of a recent slide and lie scattered about the path.  Howling winds, strengthened by nightfall and plunging temperatures, rush down from the highest peaks with a banshee-like shrieking.  Along the horizon rise the shadowy images of majestic snowcapped mountains, standing in silent judgment in the darkness.</description>
    <description>Fractured rocks, the shattered bones of the mountain, tell the tale of a recent slide and lie scattered about the trail.  Larger splinters thrust up through the deep drifts, the dull greys and browns in stark contrast to the purity of the white snow pack.  Howling winds rush down from the highest peaks, screaming through the pass with a banshee-like wail.  Majestic snowcapped mountains stretch across the horizon with regal splendor, their beauty belying their cold-hearted truth.</description>
    <position x="220" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="ice east" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="west" move="ice west" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Plunged into darkness and assaulted by brutal winds, the narrow trail slowly wends it way through the pass.  Sheer rock walls, rising to either side of the path, do nothing but increase the fury of nature.  The raging winds frequently dislodge large boulders from the cliffs above.  In the darkness, these missiles, with little warning, shatter violently on impact with the bottom of the pass and shower the trail and snow drifts with debris.</description>
    <description>Assaulted by an endless series of storms and brutal winds, the narrow trail slowly wends its way through the pass.  Sheer rock walls rise on either side of the path.  In the distant past a river raced through the tight confines of this gorge.  The raging gales frequently dislodge large boulders from the cliffs above.  With little warning these missiles plummet and shatter violently on impact with the bottom of the pass, showering the trail and snow drifts with debris.</description>
    <position x="240" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="west" move="ice west" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Channeled and strengthened by the confining rock walls, fierce winds race through the pass, their fury increased by falling temperatures.  In the darkness, the splintered remnants of past slides resemble the scenes of a battle, warriors and monsters frozen in time.  The crumbling stone and suffocating blanket of drifting snow lend an eerie stillness to the pass, broken only by the howling of the wind.</description>
    <description>Jagged cliffs rise on each side of the twisting trail, the rock walls channeling and strengthening the fierce winds that race through the gorge.  Deep snow drifts, a constant presence through this region, cover the pass like the swells of a frozen sea.  Splintered fragments of rock, remnants of past slides, litter the blanket of snow making for a hazardous journey.  The crumbling stone and suffocating layer of white lend an eerie stillness to the pass broken only by the howling wind.</description>
    <position x="260" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="ice southeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Nightfall covers the region in a blanket of darkness, cloaking the area's scenic treasures until the arrival of day.  Rugged mountains, hidden in shadow, form a protective circle around a small plateau, sparing it from the harshest weather.  In sharp contrast to the torturous winds and storms beyond, this small spot is peaceful and serene.  Snow crystals, blown aloft from the highest peaks, float lazily through the still air, their occasional sparkle lending a magical quality to the small fell.</description>
    <description>Majestic snowcapped peaks and an undisturbed blanket of snow are but a few of the treasures this region has to offer.  Rugged mountains form a protective circle around a small plateau, sparing it from the harshest weather.  In sharp contrast to the torturous winds and storms beyond, this sheltered spot is peaceful and serene.  Snow crystals, blown aloft from the heights, float lazily through the still air.  Their graceful flight lends a magical quality to the small fell.</description>
    <position x="280" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="ice northwest" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>An inky blackness descends upon the narrow rugged trail, the fall of night sped by the imposing cliffs.  Water trickling from a hidden spring somewhere on the rugged rock walls freezes, forming hideous misshapen monstrosities.  Howling winds tear through the pass and occasionally dislodge the icy growths.  These bizarre ice sculptures plummet uncontrollably in the darkness, sending the figures flying in an awkward dance before shattering at the bottom of the gorge.</description>
    <description>Imposing rock walls rise above the narrow trail, their incredible height blocking the feeble light of day from reaching the bottom of the gorge.  Water trickling down from a hidden spring freezes, forming hideous misshapen monstrosities that glare down upon the snowy passage.  Howling winds rip through the pass dislodging the icy growths, sending the figures flying in an awkward dance before shattering at the bottom of the gorge.</description>
    <position x="260" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Winding its way along the shattered mountain, the twisting trail hugs a vertical rock wall overlooking a deep gorge that plunges into a fathomless blackness.  Unforgiving by day, the small path becomes treacherous at night with a darkness familiar only to the dead.  Raging winds race through the narrow chasm with a high-pitched shriek assaulting the ears and mind.</description>
    <description>Cataclysmic events shattered this mighty mountain, creating a basalt wall that rises high into the sky.  A twisting trail, barely wide enough to walk along, hugs the sheer rock face overlooking a deep chasm that plunges into unseen depths.  Raging winds race through the narrow gorge, assaulting the ears and mind with their high-pitched shriek.</description>
    <position x="240" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Along the sheer walls that surround the roadway, thick sheets of ice cling to the rough stone beneath.  Within it hang rocks, stones and various other debris, appearing to rest weightless in midair.  Sharp gusts of wind sweep down the mountainside, pulling shards of ice from the face of the glacier to send them careening into the gorge far below.</description>
    <position x="220" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="west" move="ice west" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>The road curves sharply as it slides along the sheer walls of ice that coat the mountainside.  Along the outer side of the path, a deep chasm sweeps downward to end in a gorge filled with dagger-like rock protrusions littered with the remnants of wood and bone.  Rushing icy water spews down from a wide crack in the mountainside, the spray freezing instantly upon contact with the frigid air, making travel very hazardous.</description>
    <position x="200" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="ice east" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="ice northwest" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Himineldar Shel, Fortress Gate" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>The remnants of a massive stronghold set into the rock stand in disarray, having borne the brunt of the elements over countless years.  Massive gates with deep gold filigree lean against the crumbling archway that frames the enormous structure, pulled from their hinges.  Ice-covered skeletons, that of both S'Kra Mur and Dwarves, lie crumbled beneath the rubble, skeletal hands still clutching frozen weapons.</description>
    <position x="180" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="ice southeast" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Far below, a lush valley is visible, framed within jagged peaks of icy black stone.  A gentle mist rises from the jungle as tropical birds sweep amongst the stone-grey canopies that push in close to a massive black spire set into the southeastern wall.  The low babble of water reverberates off the icy walls of the mountainside, slowly slipping downward in semicircular beds of ice that follow the contours of the roadway.</description>
    <position x="180" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Himineldar Shel, Mountain Road" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Crystal fonts of spring water trickle from jagged crevices that streak across the stone facade of the Himineldar Shel, forming curious icy sculptures and giving the appearance of an enormous crystal fountain.  From time to time, shards of ice or rock tumble from the treacherous cliffs above, landing in the gorge below with a resounding impact.  The road tightly hugs the sheer cliffs as it cuts a pathway though the rugged landscape.</description>
    <position x="160" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="ice southeast" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Himineldar Shel, Rope Bridge" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>The path slants along the rock face at a sharp angle and ends suddenly at a makeshift wooden bridge, reaching across the gaping maw of a chasm at a nearly vertical angle.  Numerous trickles of crystal clear water sweep downward along the massive formations of ice, slipping quietly off the side of the chasm with a gentle gurgle.  An opaque mist swirls around the swaying, ice-slick bridge, giving an oddly unreal quality to the rushing gurgle of unseen water in the chasm below.</description>
    <position x="180" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="ice northwest" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rope bridge" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Himineldar Shel, Rope Bridge" note="Rope Bridge">
    <description>Spanning the massive gap over a curving canyon that follows the lower contours of the Himineldar Shel, the bridge sways hazardously in the swirling breeze sweeping upward from the raging river below.  Massive icicles dangle from every surface of the rickety structure, occasionally snapping loose to tumble from sight.  The landscape beyond is shrouded by a thick opaque mist, giving the air a nearly tangible presence.</description>
    <position x="200" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>An ice-covered arch frames the entrance to a rickety bridge that spans the gaping canyon.  Pillars of black rock rise high above the path, each with a jagged apex unsmoothed by time and the elements.  High above, the infamous Himineldar Shel towers above the surrounding landscape, its snow capped peaks glinting in the available light.</description>
    <position x="220" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rope bridge" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>The pathway narrows slightly as it curls inward onto itself, meandering amongst the sharp-edged formations of black rock that dot the landscape.  Several stone steps, covered in layers of lustrous ice, allow easier travel down to the basalt valley nestled in the shadow of the mountain.</description>
    <position x="240" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>The raging wind trailing down from the frozen peaks fills the air with a high-pitched shriek as its cuts though the jagged stone that towers above the narrow road.  Deep scratches covered in a thick layer of ice sweep gracefully across the black stone, the remnants of some long forgotten melee fought on these icy slopes.</description>
    <position x="260" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>The air is filled with the overwhelming stench of sulfur, and sickly yellow smoke billows from a narrow crack in black stone floor.  Shallow pools of brackish water fill gentle dips and niches carved into the stone lining the roadway, their surfaces covered with a papyrus-thin layer of ice.</description>
    <position x="260" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>Flecks of pristine white snow sweep between jagged stone formations, the crystals in stark contrast to the night-black of the surrounding rock.  The pathway curls around in a steep bend that meanders around an ice-covered boulder and several stone monoliths.</description>
    <position x="280" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Rocky outcroppings blanketed in snow stand out in sharp contrast to the deep gloom of night.  Snow-covered crags tower in the distance, their lofty peaks casting deeper shadows across the high mountain fell.  Winds rushing down from the highest peaks carry bitter cold air across the region.  The trail, barely wide enough to walk two abreast, slowly winds its way through the darkness and leads deeper into the mountains.</description>
    <description>Snow-covered crags tower in the distance, their lofty peaks hidden in swirling clouds of ice and snow.  Rocky outcroppings in shades of muted brown and grey stand out in stark contrast to the endless blanket of white drifting snow.  Winds rushing down from the highest peaks carry bitter cold air across the mountain.  The trail, barely wide enough to walk two abreast, slowly winds its way through the crags and deeper into the mountains.</description>
    <position x="0" y="470" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Night on the mountain is filled with the ghostly shadows of rocky outcroppings.  Large expanses of barren rock, cracked and splintered by years of exposure to cold and ice, make a treacherous path for the unwary.  Frigid winds rushing through the area offer little comfort to the ill-prepared traveler.</description>
    <description>Exposed to frigid temperatures and limited sunlight, the narrow trail winds its way along the mountainside.  Large expanses of barren rock, cracked and splintered by years of exposure to cold and ice, make a treacherous path for the unwary.  Bitter cold winds rush through the area, sapping what little warmth is provided by the feeble light of day.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="490" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>In the darkness, ice-covered rockslides create treacherous shadows on the trail.  Snowfields blanket much of the surrounding area, a thick icy covering that results in treacherous footing.  Howling winds, rushing down from the highest peaks, create a haunting wail that echoes eerily in the night air like the sound of lost spirits wandering the mountains searching for a way home.</description>
    <description>Meandering between snow-covered rockslides, the narrow trail leads ever deeper into the towering mountains.  Snowfields blanket much of the surroundings, a thick icy covering protecting the delicate crystals from what little warmth penetrates the chill air.  Howling winds, rushing down from the highest peaks, create a haunting wail that echoes throughout the gorges like the sound of lost souls wandering the mountains for a way home.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="510" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside" note="RTF38|RT-FB-IG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Darkness settles like a blanket across the mountain slope.  The trail, already hard to discern in the ice-covered rock and scree, is obscured by blowing snow.  Wailing like a banshee, the howling wind rushes across the slope with a bitter chill that saps the strength.</description>
    <description>Winding deeper into the mountains, the narrow trail is all but hidden in the snow-covered rock and scree.  Periodically, the blowing snow lessens and the briefest glimpse of a stone structure can be seen rising between two peaks in the distance.  Around each bend in the trail another towering mountain rises.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="530" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Cresting the top of a ridgeline, the trail opens onto a high mountain fell only dimly visible in the darkness.  Sheltered somewhat by the surrounding mountain peaks and ridgelines, the plateau is a welcome respite from the unrelenting wind of the pass.  Snow covers the ground in a deepening blanket of cold.</description>
    <description>Cresting the top of a ridgeline, the trail wanders into a small open fell surrounded by high mountain peaks.  The snow-covered plateau offers a welcome respite from the unrelenting wind of the mountain pass.  Snow clouds, their bellies darkened and heavy with moisture, are harbingers of additional snowfall.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="530" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>The darkness brings both falling temperatures and rising gales.  Blinding clouds of snow and ice crystals, whipped into a frenzy by the howling winds, race across the plain.  Between two storm-wrapped mountains, a tongue of white ice is dimly visible, its slow ponderous movement unnoticeable as it grinds its way through the pass.</description>
    <description>Remnants of glacial ice cling tenaciously to the high mountain ridges like climbers frozen in mid-stride.  Raging winds whip across the frozen plateau, raising swirling clouds of ice crystals and snow.  Between two storm-wrapped mountains, a tongue of white ice is dimly visible, its slow ponderous movement unnoticeable as it grinds its way through the pass.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="550" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Without the dim light of day, the glacial plain becomes a vast barren expanse devoid of any recognizable landmarks.  Sudden storms often rush down from the high mountains without warning, the blizzards easily leading travelers astray.  Hidden chasms and crevasses, covered by a deceptively thin layer of ice or snow, become hazardous in the darkness of night.</description>
    <description>The trail wanders across the desolate mountain fell, barren of recognizable landmarks, avoiding hidden chasms and crevasses covered by a deceptively thin layer of ice or snow.  Sudden storms often rush down from the high peaks without warning, the blizzards easily leading travelers astray.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="570" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Reminiscent of castle turrets, the nearby peaks serve only to cover this region in shadows deeper than the night.  Blasts of wind charge down the mountainsides to assault the glacial plain with unbridled fury.  Deep-throated rumbling echoes in the darkness, the voice of the ancient icy river on its slow, ponderous journey through the mountains.  Standing in defiance against nature's fury, a dark stone pillar rises from the plain.</description>
    <description>Mountain peaks, reminiscent of castle turrets, cast a persistent shadow over this region.  Rarely does the sun's warm embrace penetrate the chilly gloom.  Blasts of wind charge down the mountainsides to assault the glacial plain with unbridled fury.  Deep-throated rumbling echoes across the plain, the voice of the ancient icy river speaking on its slow, ponderous journey through the mountains.  Rising from the plain, a dark stone pillar stands resolute against nature's fury.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="570" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Covered in perpetual winter, the high mountainside has proven to be inhospitable to all but the hardiest of explorers.  Bitter night temperatures, howling winds and blinding snowstorms serve only to disorient.  The cold-hearted night welcomes the unwary in its embrace, comforting the lost with chill arms as they die upon the mountain.  A solitary stone pillar stands in resolute silence.</description>
    <description>Covered in a perpetual winter, the high mountainside has proven to be inhospitable to all but the hardiest of explorers.  Frigid temperatures, constant winds and sudden snowstorms are all part of the daily experience in this region.  Perhaps, in some distant past, this mountain range was exposed to warmer temperatures and seasonal changes, though only the spirit of the mountain knows.  A solitary dark stone pillar stands in resolute silence.</description>
    <position x="0" y="570" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Rising from the shattered glacial plain, monolithic shards of ice reach into the night sky.  Lying beneath a blanket of snow, an insidious pattern of crevasses and trenches has been created by the relentlessly slow grinding process of ice against stone.  Occasional tremors, violent by their sudden onslaught, wrack the ice field as the mountain surrenders to the tremendous weight and pressure of the frozen river.  Hidden in shadow, a dark stone pillar stands in solitude on the desolate plain.</description>
    <description>Blue-tinged monoliths rise from the shattered glacial plain, a result of the relentlessly slow grinding process of ice against stone.  An insidious pattern of crevasses and trenches lies buried beneath a blanket of snow, their presence betrayed only by slight depressions.  Occasionally the great ice field is wracked by violent tremors as the mountain surrenders to the tremendous weight and pressure of the frozen river.  A dark stone pillar stands in solitude on the desolate plain.</description>
    <position x="20" y="570" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Crashing against the mountainside has caused the ancient glacier to become broken and shattered.  Crevasses, visible during the day, have become dark shadows crisscrossing the glacial field.  Gigantic shards of ice, thrust up from the depths of the glacier, have become eerie monstrosities reminiscent of legendary creatures.  Toppled and lying on its side, a dark stone pillar has proven no match against the forces of nature.</description>
    <description>Crashing against the mountainside has caused the ancient glacier to become broken and shattered.  Crevasses crisscross the glacier, their icy blue hues deepening with their distance below the surface.  Gigantic shards of ice, thrust up from the depths of the glacier, twist as they reach for the sky.  Toppled and lying on its side, a dark stone pillar has proven no match against the forces of nature.</description>
    <position x="20" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Blinding, swirling clouds of ice crystals further compromise the already treacherous footing on the slippery, glacial ice.  Nearly hidden in the darkness, a yawning crevasse runs the length of the mountainside as if the mountain has opened its maw waiting to devour the unwary adventurer.  The size of the crevasse gives rise to concern as to the safety of this region, as only incredible stresses could cause such a fracture.  Leaning drunkenly, a dark stone pillar stands partially obscured in shadow.</description>
    <description>Blinding, swirling clouds of ice crystals further compromise the already treacherous footing on the slippery, glacial ice.  A deep crevasse gives rise to concern for one's safety in this region, as only incredible stresses could cause such a fracture.  Leaning drunkenly, a dark stone pillar stands silent watch over the snow field.</description>
    <position x="20" y="610" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>A small rocky outcropping with towering drifts of snow to either side provides limited shelter and respite from the elements.  Plummeting temperatures, ferocious winds and swirling clouds of ice particles make the night all the more dangerous.  The distant mountain peaks, once visible, are now lost in the blinding sleet.  A dark stone pillar, lost in night's shadow, lies partially buried in a snow drift by the outcropping.</description>
    <description>Little can survive the constant onslaught of the bitter cold winds rushing across the exposed mountainside.  Towering drifts of snow have formed to either side of a small rocky outcropping, providing limited shelter and respite from the elements.  Partially buried in one of the drifts stands a dark stone pillar, perhaps a route marker for a lost trail.  In the distance, shrouded in clouds of blowing snow and ice crystals, the tallest peaks of the range are visible.</description>
    <position x="0" y="610" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Towering mountain peaks, majestic during the day, now cast malevolent shadows across the snowfield.  Already bitter cold during the day, the temperature plunges even lower as night falls.  Large drifts of snow cover the mountainside, similar to the dunes of a desert and equally difficult to traverse.  A mysterious dark stone pillar uncovered by the constant winds stands near a large snowdrift, several bones scattered at its base.</description>
    <description>Towering mountain peaks rise high above this glacial plain, their tops lost in swirling clouds of windblown sleet.  A nearby peak casts a shadow over the ice field, creating a noticeable difference in temperature.  Large snowdrifts cover the mountainside, similar to the dunes of a desert and equally difficult to traverse.  The bleached bones of an unknown pack animal and its owner lie exposed at the base of a dark stone pillar.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="610" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Buried deep in night's shadow, the snowfield is subjected to freezing temperatures.  Cyclonic gusts tear down from the high peaks to race across the mountainside, causing a banshee-like wail to issue forth from the deepest crevasses and chasms marring the terrain's icy blanket.  Blinding clouds of snow and ice, stirred by the constant winds, serve only to disorient the unwary.  A dark stone pillar, unstable as a result of glacial tremors, leans into the wind.</description>
    <description>Resting in the shadow of taller peaks, the mountainside is subjected to frigid temperatures.  Cyclonic gusts tear down from the summit to race across the landscape, causing a banshee-like wail to issue forth from the deepest crevasses and chasms marring the terrain's icy blanket.  Blinding clouds of snow and ice, stirred by the constant winds, serve only to disorient the unwary.  A dark stone pillar, unstable as a result of glacial tremors, leans to one side.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Surrendering long ago to the onslaught of a glacier, the mountain now lays buried beneath an impenetrable blanket of ice.  The inky blackness of night serves only to compound the ferocity of the frigid winds whipping across the glacial surface.  Thousands of tiny shards of ice, each like a miniature weapon, are capable of flaying exposed skin.</description>
    <description>Surrendering long ago to the onslaught of a glacier, the mountain now lies buried beneath an impenetrable blanket of ice.  Frigid winds whip across the glacial surface stirring thousands of small crystals, each tiny shard capable of flaying exposed skin.  Feeble rays of sunlight are useless in dispelling the unyielding bitter cold.</description>
    <position x="0" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>The chill of the brisk mountain wind cuts though to the bone, the current gracefully sweeping amongst the curious black rock formations that line the pathway.  Thick curls of dark smoke can be seen to the east, giving some hint of civilization in these barren lands.</description>
    <position x="300" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>The road cuts a narrow path though the maze of black stone, curling around in complex angles, dips and ascents that give anyone brave enough to traverse this dangerous territory the sensation of walking in never-ending circles.  Silvery veins crisscross in a delicate spiderweb pattern across several of the basalt monoliths, partially obscured by a gentle dusting of snow.</description>
    <position x="320" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>Massive basalt monoliths blend seamlessly together to form two sheer walls that lean inward around the road.  Gentle rivulets of frigid water trickle over the pinnacle, each sharp drop echoing off the back stone.  Small bits of wood and discarded food scraps rest at the foot of the canyon, covered in a thick layer of clear ice.</description>
    <position x="340" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>Thick layers of ice cover the sheer black walls that press in around the pass, bathing the area in eternal shadow.  Icy winds swirl though the narrow channel, carrying a flurry of snow with every forceful gust.  The road curves sharply to and fro upon its meandering path though the maze of unforgiving stone.</description>
    <position x="340" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountain Road">
    <description>A large section of black stone has broken away from the surrounding walls and extends several feet off the ground.  Gentle streams of yellowish water trickle down the sundered rock before seeping into a crevice at its base.  The distant smell of sulfur is barely discernible upon the bone-chilling mountain gusts.</description>
    <position x="320" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Seord Kerwaith, Crystalline Gorge">
    <description>Resting in the shadow of the Himineldar Shel, the dark pass cuts a treacherous path over snowy slopes to the wilderness of Forfedhdar beyond.  With every breath, the freezing mountain air claws at travelers, seeming to steal the warmth from their very lungs.  The walls enclose the valley tower high above, its surface glimmering in the available light.  A gentle rain of snow and ice cascade from the mountain summit high above, dusting the area with a light powdering of pristine snow.</description>
    <position x="340" y="580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rock wall" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Seord Kerwaith, Crystalline Gorge" note="RTF36|RT-RP-FB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The darkened walls that enclose the pass widen to give ample space for a small army to pass with room to spare.  The black stone, covered in a semitransparent ice, glistens in the available light cast from the small portion of sky overhead.  Every minute sound is magnified nearly tenfold as it reverberates off the thick walls, filling the barren pass with curious echoes.</description>
    <position x="360" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Seord Kerwaith, Crystalline Gorge" note="RTF35|RT-RP-HEG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The distant sound of chatter and the warm scent of fresh cooking sizzling on an open fire drifts over on the chill mountain air from somewhere behind the walls of Raven's Point to the south.  A maze of curious ice formations fill the interior of the valley, casting tangled shadows upon the dark walls that enclose this sheltered black rock gorge.</description>
    <position x="340" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Seord Kerwaith, Crystalline Gorge">
    <description>Curious formations of ice line the interior of the valley giving it the appearance of a gallery displaying a collection of crystal statues.  The ice formations stand like motionless sentinels, occasionally glinting as sporadic light strikes them.  The distant sound of dripping water reverberates though the expansive valley, its rhythmic tone constant and ceaseless.</description>
    <position x="320" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Only dimly visible, the surrounding mountains show only as dark, brooding masses rising in all directions.  To the east, a low cliff rises sharply, its loose and crumbling rock ice-covered and slippery.</description>
    <description>Mountains rise in all directions, their peaks obscured in almost constant cloud cover.  On the rare occasions when the weather breaks, the dark green of a pine forest can be dimly seen carpeting the valleys between distant hills and mountains.  To the east, a low cliff rises sharply, its loose and crumbling rock ice-covered and slippery.</description>
    <position x="0" y="510" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crumbling cliff" destination="270" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Nearly constant wind races across the shadowed mountainside, whipping into life frenzied dervishes of blinding ice and snow crystals.  Treacherous by day, footing at night is nigh impossible as the twisting path is all but hidden by darkness.  Southward, a rocky ledge offers a path upward.</description>
    <description>Nearly constant wind races across the mountainside, whipping into life frenzied dervishes of blinding ice and snow crystals.  Footing, already precarious on the ice, is made even more challenging by its overlay of fresh snow.  Barren mountains rise in the distance, their peaks shrouded in wind-blown clouds.  Southward, a rocky ledge offers a path upward.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ledge" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Winding between two rocky outcroppings, the path twists through a small natural shelter.  The chilling winds are unable to penetrate the small oasis, protected by walls of drifted snow and overhanging rock.  On the underside of the outcropping, large rings of dark soot are visible, evidence this area has been used as shelter in the past.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="570" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside" note="RTF37|RT-FB-AGF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Barely visible in the darkness, tumbled blocks of shattered ice, snow, and fractured rock cover the mountainside trail in an unstable layer, evidence of a recent avalanche.  Gigantic boulders, their surfaces scratched and gouged, speak of the violent nature of the slide.</description>
    <description>Tumbled blocks of shattered ice, snow, and fractured rock cover the mountainside trail in an unstable layer, evidence of a recent avalanche.  Gigantic boulders, their surfaces scratched and gouged, speak of the violent nature of the slide.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="550" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>In the distant past, some cataclysmic event sheered off a section of the mountain to create a smooth rock wall.  A narrow ledge, the result of a natural fault in the rock face, serves as a footpath up the mountain.  Ice covering the ledge in a thick slippery sheet makes for dangerous travel.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="550" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ice-covered ledge" destination="271" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Seord Kerwaith, A Narrow Ledge">
    <description>The darkness creates looming shadows and hides the treacherous footing of the narrow ledge.  Wind rushing through the valley creates a bone-chilling howl.  Far below, the valley floor is invisible in the night and blowing snow.</description>
    <description>Covered in a thick blanket of snow, the narrow ledge weaves its way up the side of the mountain.  From here, the craggy tops of several distant buttes can be dimly seen when the clouds of ice and snow are momentarily shredded by the wind.  A natural stone bridge, barely visible in the distance, leads to one of the buttes.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="610" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ledge" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Seord Kerwaith, A Narrow Ledge">
    <description>A rockslide has damaged a large portion of the ledge, creating a dangerously unstable section.  The surface of the trail is splintered and fractured, and portions have been completely destroyed by the falling debris.  Gale force winds batter the rock wall with brutish force.</description>
    <description>A rockslide has damaged a large portion of the ledge, creating a dangerously unstable section.  The surface of the trail is splintered and fractured, and portions have been completely destroyed by the falling debris.  Gale force winds batter the rock wall with brutish force.  </description>
    <position x="-60" y="630" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Seord Kerwaith, A Narrow Ledge">
    <description>In the darkness, the shadows of shattered buttes common to this region loom on the horizon.  Repeated freezing of snow and ice have created gigantic fissures and chasms throughout the flat topped mountains resulting in the formation of small minarets.  These solitary spiny pinnacles thrust up into the night sky like ancient watch towers, their fires long ago extinguished, and guards over an inhospitable land.  High above, a natural stone bridge connects the mountain to a distant butte.</description>
    <description>Shattered buttes loom along the horizon, carved by the eroding effects of snow and ice over the centuries into gigantic fissures and chasms, forming small rocky minarets.  The spiny pinnacles thrust up into the sky like ancient watch towers, guardians over an inhospitable land.  High above, a natural stone bridge connects the mountain to a distant butte.</description>
    <description>Shattered buttes loom along the horizon, carved by the eroding effects of snow and ice over the centuries into gigantic fissures and chasms, forming small rocky minarets.  The spiny pinnacles thrust up into the sky like ancient watch towers, guardians over an inhospitable land.  High above, a natural stone bridge connects the mountain to a distant butte.  </description>
    <position x="-60" y="650" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Seord Kerwaith, A Narrow Ledge" note="RTF41|RT-FB-MG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Slowly winding its way along the mountainside, the ledge is increasingly difficult to traverse.  Large fractures in the rock split the path, and the gaps in between gape blackly, their depths hidden in the darkness.  Rock protrusions along the mountain side of the trail hinder the ability to walk upright in places.</description>
    <description>Slowly winding its way along the mountainside, the ledge is increasingly difficult to traverse.  Large fractures in the rock split the path, and the gaps in between provide a magnificent view of the chasm below.  Rock protrusions along the mountain side of the trail hinder the ability to walk upright in places.</description>
    <description>Slowly winding its way along the mountainside, the ledge is increasingly difficult to traverse.  Large fractures in the rock split the path, and the gaps in between provide a magnificent view of the chasm below.  Rock protrusions along the mountain side of the trail hinder the ability to walk upright in places.  </description>
    <position x="-60" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Gigantic boulders, dislodged from the high mountain peak, lie scattered across the mountain trail.  The shadows of the large rocks make travel slow and cumbersome, and at times the path becomes too narrow to follow resulting in backtracking to locate another passage across the mountain.  It is not hard to imagine how a traveler could quickly become disoriented in the dark and tight corridors.</description>
    <description>Gigantic boulders, dislodged from the high mountain peak, lie scattered across the mountain trail.  Travel between the large rocks is slow and cumbersome, and at times the path becomes too narrow to follow resulting in backtracking to locate another passage across the mountain.  It is not hard to imagine how a traveler could quickly become disoriented in the tight corridors.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside" note="RTF40|RT-FB-BS" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Deepening night brings forth fierce and bitter winds that rip across the landscape with untamed rage.  Barren rock outcroppings rise from the shadows, centurions from another time stranded on a desolate landscape.  Little survives in these frigid temperatures and the infertile mountain soil is incapable of supporting all but the most primitive of life forms.  If not for the howling winds a spectral blanket of eerie silence would cover this region during the hours of darkness.</description>
    <description>Subjected to ferocious winds, this region of the mountain pass is nearly devoid of snow.  Barren rock outcroppings, some covered with a thick layer of ice, lend an eerie sense of desolation to the landscape.  Little survives the bitter temperatures and the infertile mountain soil is incapable of supporting all but the most primitive of life forms.  Hidden between some of the larger boulders, small patches of snow struggle to maintain a foothold on the mountain.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="710" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Monstrous drifts of snow block the mountain trail, making forward progress nearly impossible.  Escorting the darkening shadows of night are the screaming gale force winds common to this area.  Fierce winds blast at the drifts, stirring blinding clouds of ice crystals causing white out conditions.  More than one caravan, greed driving the traders onward at night, has found itself plunging to the bottom of the gorge, the screams of the animals lost in the howling of the winds.</description>
    <description>Monstrous drifts of snow block the mountain trail, making forward progress nearly impossible.  Screaming through the mountains, fierce winds blast at the drifts stirring blinding clouds of ice crystals.  Whiteout conditions are commonplace in this area and are notorious for leading a traveler off the edge of the trail into the emptiness of space.  More than one caravan has plummeted to the bottom of the gorge, the screams of animals and traders lost in the howling of the winds.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="710" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Bitter temperatures and raging storms frequent the hours of darkness throughout this area.  Dense clouds, the harbingers of blizzards, will rise suddenly to obscure the path.  Frequent storms last for days, disorienting travelers and driving them to madness.  Winter, a season for many, is a constant companion here, its cold embrace unforgiving.  Warmth has not blessed this region in countless ages and is but a distant memory to the mighty mountains.</description>
    <description>Frigid temperatures and blinding snowstorms rage throughout this area.  Without warning the area may suddenly be cloaked in dense cloud cover, which is the harbinger of blizzards.  Frequent storms can last for days, disorienting travelers and driving them to madness.  Winter, a season for many, is a constant companion here, its cold embrace unforgiving.  Warmth has not blessed this region in countless ages and is but a distant memory to the mighty mountains.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="730" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Darkness spreads a chilling cloak over the mountains.  Unusual rock formations rise along the trail, their shadows resembling the twisted shapes of trolls and goblins.  Precariously balanced boulders lie atop rocky outcroppings which hang over the path, another hazard for the passerby.  Snow, a continual presence in the mountains, hides a wicked trail of loose stones and rubble.  A hasty traveler can easily slip in the blackness of night and fall over the edge of the path.</description>
    <description>Through the natural processes of erosion and freezing, landslides are frequent here.  Unusual rock formations have been created, some resembling the twisted shapes of goblins and trolls.  Precariously balanced boulders lie atop rocky outcroppings, as if waiting in anticipation to topple on the next passerby.  Snow, a continual presence in the mountains, hides a wicked trail of loose stones and rubble.  A hasty traveler can easily slip and fall over the edge of the path.</description>
    <position x="0" y="750" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Lofty mountain peaks rise high in the sky, their shadows deepening the inky blackness of night.  Covered in snow and ice, a narrow trail wends its way through the range that is subjected to punishing winds and sudden storms.  Peering over the edge of the trail, one looks out into an empty void where distance and depth are lost in the darkness.  Up a small rise is a bridge.</description>
    <description>In the distance majestic mountains stretch across the horizon, their lofty peaks covered in a permanent blanket of white.  Chilling winds, storms, ice, and snow all greet the traveler on this narrow trail wending its way through the mountains.  Over the trail's edge, a faint green hue hints of the thriving vegetation in the valley below.  In contrast, the dreary greys and browns of the high mountains, covered in pale white, create a peaceful yet disturbing and uneasy quiet.  Up a small rise is a bridge.</description>
    <position x="0" y="730" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Night, black as pitch, envelops the mountains.  A natural stone bridge rises above the gorge, spanning the distance to a flat-topped butte on the horizon.  While crossing the bridge, there is no protection from the turbulent winds rushing through the gorge.  Walking into the darkness over an empty void can quickly bring on a sense of vertigo, and many have made the trip across the bridge at night crawling like a baby on their belly.  The trail continues down a small slope.</description>
    <description>In the distant past, a cataclysmic event sheered off a large section of this mountain.  Far below, a fracture in the rock face serves as a narrow footpath and weaves its way across the mountain.  A natural stone bridge rises above the gorge, spanning the distance to a flat-topped butte.  While crossing the bridge, there is no protection from the turbulent winds rushing through the gorge and an icy surface complicates the crossing.  The trail continues down a small slope.</description>
    <position x="20" y="730" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bridge" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Seord Kerwaith, Bridge">
    <description>Arching across the fathomless blackness of night, the narrow stone bridge serves as the only access to the flat-topped butte in the distance.  While traversing the expanse, reliance upon natural dexterity and reflex is a must.  The howling winds racing through the gorge can easily unbalance a load with their powerful blasts, usually resulting in an uncomfortable trip to the bottom of the gorge.  Snow has not gained a foothold on the bridge, but a thick layer of slippery ice coats the surface.</description>
    <description>Arching across the fathomless gorge, the narrow stone bridge is the sole means of gaining access to the flat-topped butte in the distance.  While traversing the expanse, reliance upon natural dexterity and reflex is a must.  The howling winds racing through the gorge can easily unbalance a load with their powerful blasts, usually resulting in an uncomfortable trip to the bottom of the gorge.  Snow has not gained a foothold on the bridge, but a thick layer of slippery ice coats the surface.</description>
    <position x="40" y="730" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Blizzards rage across the mountains, reducing the landscape to shades of white, grey and brown.  Along the horizon, the never-ending procession of snow covered mountains is engulfed by the blackness of night.  The vast desolation of this region produces a sense of monotony and futility.  Foolish travelers, taking a moment's rest, are easily disoriented by the featureless landscape and are never heard from again.</description>
    <description>Blizzards rage across the mountains, reducing the landscape to muted shades of pale white, grey and brown.  The vast desolation produces a sense of monotony and futility.  Foolish travelers, growing weary of the dreariness and constant storms, take a moment's rest only to become disoriented by the featureless landscape and are never heard from again.</description>
    <position x="60" y="730" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bridge" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Seord Kerwaith, A High Promontory" note="RTF39|RT-FB-RP" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Like a stealthy thief, night robs warmth from the high ridge, leaving the air bitter cold.  Fractured rock and stony spires grasp greedily at the sky, while fathomless chasms and fissures plunge deep into the heart of the range, their actual depths lost in the inky blackness of night.  Meandering between spectral outcroppings and bottomless channels, the small trail leads the traveler across the promontory.  The rumblings of distant rockslides and avalanches echo across the mountains.</description>
    <description>Like the spine of a sleeping dragon, the high ridgeline twists and winds its way through the mountains.  Fractured rock and stony spires rise into the sky, while fathomless chasms and fissures reach into the heart of the range.  Rolling plains can be seen in the distance.  Meandering between outcroppings and across deep channels, the small trail leads travelers across the promontory.  The rockslides and avalanches common to this area are evidenced by frequent rumblings heard echoing across the mountains.</description>
    <position x="30" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Seord Kerwaith, A High Promontory">
    <description>Deep shadows cast by the towering mountains accentuate the darkness of night upon the high promontory.  Crumbling stone pinnacles rise along the ridgeline like abandoned watchtowers.  Their shadowy presence is disturbing, as if sentinels from a bygone era are still keeping silent vigil over the mountain pass.  Freezing temperatures, blinding snowstorms and lose piles of ice-covered scree are just a few of the hazards greeting travelers in these mountains.</description>
    <description>Towering mountains rise above the promontory, their shadows casting a false night upon the trail.  Crumbling stone pinnacles stand along the ridgeline like forgotten watchtowers, sentinels from a bygone era.  Winds, howling with unbridled fury, race across the ridgeline and exact their toll from all who dare venture through the region.  Freezing temperatures, blinding snowstorms and piles of loose ice-covered scree are a few of the hazards greeting travelers in these mountains.</description>
    <position x="60" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Seord Kerwaith, A High Promontory">
    <description>Night plunges the high promontory in a blanket of darkness.  Vast rolling plains, visible by day, are hidden under the looming shadows of high mountain peaks.  Howling winds and falling temperatures combine in a deadly mixture.  Lured by the bluff's peaceful serenity during the day, the traveler is faced with nature's fury at night.  Exposed to the elements, little hope exists for survival and only the strongest will see day conquer night again.</description>
    <description>Surrounded by majestic snow-capped peaks, the worn bluff stands out in sharp contrast to the high mountains common to this area.  From the heights of the promontory, distant rolling plains are visible and are a welcome respite from the barren rock and snow of the mountains.  Exposure to the winds prevents the bluff from being covered by snow, but a few small drifts have gathered around rocky outcroppings.  A peaceful serenity wells up from the bluff in defiance of the harshness of the mountains.</description>
    <position x="90" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Night brings blinding clouds of snow and swirling winds.  Monstrous drifts block the pass, and tunneling through them becomes the only means of progress, which is numbingly slow.  Buried beneath the mountains of snow, loose rock and stone can easily twist or break an ankle, a nightmare for many a caravan.  At night, between gusts of wind, an eerie supernatural stillness blankets the mountain.</description>
    <description>A continuous blanket of white covers the region, an occasional barren outcropping of dull grey rock breaks through the crystal plain.  Drifting and blowing snow make travel along the pass slow and difficult, at sometimes tunneling through the drifts is the only means of progress.  Buried beneath the mountains of snow, loose stone and rock can easily twist or break an ankle, a nightmare for many a caravan.  When the wind stops blowing, an eerie, unnatural silence reigns over the mountain.</description>
    <position x="90" y="730" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Shrieking like a thousand tormented souls, the wind races through the narrow confines of the pass.  Falling from the upper reaches of the gorge, loose pieces of ice and snow are carried by the winds to shatter against the towering rock walls.  Winding its way along the bottom of the chasm, the narrow trail is veiled in muted shadows.  The feeble light lends lifelike qualities to piles of ice-covered rock, appearing out of the dimness like bizarre monstrosities mystical creatures frozen in time.</description>
    <position x="110" y="710" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Night covers the narrow gorge with an impenetrable veil of darkness.  The inky blackness devours the remotest hint of shape or shadow, and nothing is distinguishable in the black void at the bottom of the chasm.  Fragments of lose rock and ice dislodged by the winds plunge unseen into deep snow drifts with thunderous crashes.</description>
    <description>Unrelentingly, the chilling winds blast through the narrow chasm, and their merciless assault against the towering rock walls dislodge large pieces of ice.  Rock falls from high atop the gorge are commonplace and with little warning, gigantic boulders plunge into deep snowdrifts with thunderous crashes.</description>
    <position x="130" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>A narrow gorge splits the mountain asunder, its depths lost in the blackness of night.  Vertical rock walls, soaring high above, plunge the chasm into a hauntingly spectral darkness.  Channeled by the confines of the chasm, howling winds race through the pass with an ear shattering roar.  Barricades of drifting snow and fractured rock serve as guardians against intruders while massive blocks of falling ice shatter explosively on impact at the bottom of the gorge.</description>
    <description>A narrow gorge has split the mountain asunder, vertical rock walls tower above the pass.  Channeled by the confines of the chasm, screaming winds press their relentless assault upon the mountain with an ear shattering roar.  Massive blocks of ice, dislodged by the raging winds, shatter explosively on impact at the bottom of the gorge.  Barricades of drifting snow and fractured rock litter the bottom of the pass, guardians against intruders into this nightmarish realm of bitter cold and ice.</description>
    <position x="110" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Deepening night brings additional hazards to the treacherous mountain trail wending through this inhospitable landscape.  Traversing precarious ledges overlooking bottomless chasms travel by caravan is for the foolhardy.  Entering deep gorges, blocked by drifting snow, shadowed by towering mountain peaks, the darkness of nightfall engulfs the traveler with sudden finality.</description>
    <description>Mountains stretch across the horizon, a monotonous parade of snow-covered peaks and deep valleys.  Wending through this frigid inhospitable landscape is a narrow, treacherous mountain trail.  The path traverses precarious ledges overlooking bottomless chasms and gorges reserving travel by caravan for the foolhardy.  Twisting through the mountains, the trail enters deep gorges blocked by drifting snow, shadowed by towering mountain peaks turning day into night.</description>
    <position x="110" y="650" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Darkness overshadows the distant snow capped mountains, their peaks hidden by ghostly veils of swirling clouds of ice crystals.  Deceiving by day, the mountains at night ensnare the foolish in their cold hearted grasp, treachery in their hearts.  A serpentine path twists and winds through the night, so narrow only single file passage is possible.  Buried under an icy blanket in the bottomless depths of the countless chasms and gorges lie the remains of many unfortunate travelers.</description>
    <description>Like the bleached bones of a monster, snow-capped mountains rise to towering heights, their peaks hidden in a mystical veil of swirling clouds of ice crystals.  Deceiving in their beauty, the mountains hold nothing but hatred, bitter cold, and treachery in their hearts.  A serpentine path twists and winds through the range, so narrow only single file passage is possible.  Buried under an icy blanket at the bottom of the countless chasms and gorges lie the remains of many foolish travelers.</description>
    <position x="110" y="630" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Brooding in the darkness of night, giant fractured blocks of ice litter the mountain pass, megalithic standing stones, fallen warriors from the mountain above.  Damage to the path, a result of frequent avalanches, is hidden in deep shadow, those familiar with the hazard travel cautiously.  A narrow ledge, barely wide enough to walk across sideways, hugs the side of the mountain.  Larger pack animals must be left behind, the broken path incapable of supporting their weight.</description>
    <description>Fractured blocks of blue ice litter the mountain pass, megalithic standing stones, fallen warriors from the mountain above.  Damage from frequent avalanches has caused a section of the path to collapse into the depths of the gorge below.  An extremely narrow ledge, barely wide enough to walk across, hugs the side of the mountain, it is all that remains of the trail.  Larger pack animals must be left behind, the broken path incapable of supporting their weight.</description>
    <position x="110" y="610" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Plunging temperatures and rising winds accompany the spreading darkness of nightfall on the mountainside.  Rising in challenge, massive drifts of snow form natural barriers and obstacles.  Icy corridors have been carved through the deepest of drifts, if not for the tunnels travel would be nearly impossible.  Bitterly cruel winds combined with the disorienting effects of darkness and blinding clouds of snow make for a harrowing journey along exposed sections of the trail.</description>
    <description>Powerful blasts of bitter cold wind hurtle through the mountain pass creating massive drifts of snow and obscuring visibility.  Tunnels carved through the deepest drifts offer some protection from the elements.  The feeble light of day struggles to penetrate the blinding clouds of snow and the frigid temperature saps what little warmth is in the air.  Assaulted by the cruel winds, travel along exposed sections of the icy path makes for a harrowing journey.</description>
    <position x="90" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside" note="RTF42|RT-FB-IC" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Cold and unforgiving, an insidious blanket of darkness slowly settles across the region, nightfall arrives in the mountains.  Howling through the narrow chasms and gorges, raging winds carry out a never ending assault against the ancient rock.  Clouds of snow and ice, driven into a frenzy by nature's fury, race through the mountain pass without remorse.  Cold and heartless, the ancient mountains look down upon the weary traveler with disdain and contempt.</description>
    <description>Raging winds assault the range of mountains on a continual basis, many of the highest peaks are hidden behind obscuring clouds of swirling ice crystals.  Little survives in this frigid climate, the last vestiges of plant life suffocated long ago beneath a chilling blanket of snow.  Animals once thrived in these mountains, but have since abandoned this inhospitable region for more temperate climes.  Cold and heartless, the ancient mountains look down upon the weary traveler with disdain and contempt.</description>
    <position x="70" y="570" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Winding through the mountains, the narrow trail opens upon a dark sea of drifting snow.  Barely visible along the horizon are a series of lofty crags protecting the high mountain plateau from the fiercest storms.  While the rocky outcroppings stop the ravaging winds they do little to prevent the accumulation of snow.  The harshest sounds are muffled by the drifts of snow and the deepening gloom of night magnifies the dispiriting sense of isolation that has settled over this region.</description>
    <description>Winding through the mountains, the narrow trail opens upon a vast unbroken sea of drifting snow.  Lofty crags of barren, brown, stone stretch across the horizon protecting the high mountain plateau from the fiercest storms.  While the rocky outcropping stops the ravaging winds, they do little to prevent the accumulation of snow.  A forlorn silence lies over this region, the harshest sounds are muffled by the deep drifts increasing the dispiriting sense of isolation.</description>
    <position x="50" y="550" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Nightfall turns the narrow ledge, barely wide enough to call a footpath, into a treacherous trail.  Hugging the side of the mountain, the path is littered with shattered fragments of snow covered rock, remnants of past slides that serve as a reminder that another may occur without warning.  Splinters of rock and ice break free from the mountain and plunge into the blackness of the chasm below, their violent impacts echo through the pass.</description>
    <description>Avalanches, common to this region, frequently cause havoc and may block the pass for weeks or months at a time.  A narrow ledge, barely wide enough to call a footpath, is the only means of travel across the mountain.  Shattered fragments of snow covered rock litter the trail, remnants of past slides that serve as a reminder that another may occur without warning.  Splinters of rock and ice break free from the mountain plummeting into the chasm below, their violent impacts echo through the pass.</description>
    <position x="30" y="550" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Seord Kerwaith, Mountainside">
    <description>Crushed between the sheer walls of the chasm, the winding mountain trail twists and turns without reason amidst piles of snow-covered boulders.  Visibility, hampered by blinding clouds of wind-blown snow, leaves much to be desired.  As soon as one massive drift of snow is conquered, another awaits around the next bend.  The bitter cold of the gorge offers little warmth and comfort and the stone mountains glare icily down upon travelers.</description>
    <position x="150" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Seord'Kerwaith, A Cave Entrance">
    <description>Imposing rock walls rise into the night sky, their suffocating closeness heightening the effects of nightfall.  Spreading tendrils of darkness creep across the bottom of the chasm devouring the last remnants of day.  A forbidding dark fissure, almost lost in the inky blackness, mars the rock face and plunges deep into the cold heart of the mountain.</description>
    <description>Imposing rock walls rise high into the air, their tops lost in the clouds of wind-blown snow.  Visibility, reduced by swirling clouds of icy crystals, is limited further by the twisting confines of the chasm.  A forbidding dark fissure mars the rock face and plunges deep into the cold heart of the mountain.</description>
    <position x="150" y="650" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fissure" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Seord Kerwaith, Walls of Raven's Point" note="RTF34|RT-RP-AGF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Rough-cut wooden beams set firmly into the frozen ground mark the exterior of the outpost, forming an impenetrable barrier that sinks seamlessly into the black stone walls of the valley.  The clanking thud of armored boots striking the battlements perched atop the walls of Raven's Point echo amongst the curling ice structures that line the valley floor.</description>
    <position x="360" y="640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Seord Kerwaith, North Gate" note="Kraelyst start point|travel start point" color="#808000">
    <description>Set within the impressive facade of sharpened logs that enclose the inhabitants of the outpost, the massive iron gate stands as the first defense against those who would wish to claim this land at their own.  High overhead, several guards clad in thick furs keep a careful eye on the landscape, searching for threats that dare challenge the battle savvy Dwarves of Hibarnhvidar.</description>
    <position x="320" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Seord Kerwaith, Walls of Raven's Point" note="RTF33|RT-RP-MG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The sweet aroma of pipe tobacco and rum drifts into the area from somewhere beyond the battle-scarred walls of Raven's Point, carried upon the bitter cold mountain air that swirls about the crystalline valley.  Several rows of icicles cling to the sharpened peaks of the rough-cut walls, trembling slightly as the fur-clad guards stomp along their patrols with military precision.</description>
    <position x="300" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Seord Kerwaith, Crystalline Gorge">
    <description>The frigid bite of the mountain wind sweeps though the valley, filling the air with a gentle hum as it vibrates the curious crystal-like ice formations.  Several caravan tracks are worn into the rock of the valley floor from countless years of supply deliveries to the outpost of Raven's Point.  Twisted rock monoliths, entombed within a thick layer of black ice, protrude from the ground at haphazard angles along the valley floor.</description>
    <position x="320" y="640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Seord Kerwaith, Collapsed Tunnel">
    <description>The remnants of a tunnel cut into the western wall lies strewn about the ground, having been obviously closed to seal something within the black rock.  Several S'Kra Mur skeletons dressed in rusted suits of plate armor lie trapped beneath the fallen remains of the tunnel, their talons worn down to nubs as they attempted to claw through the hard stone.  Wrought iron lanterns have been hastily hammered into the walls around the rubble, bathing the area in a pallid yellow light.</description>
    <position x="300" y="640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Raven's Point, North Gate" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Houses here were constructed nearly atop of one another and lean sideways at odd angles, looking as if they could topple over in the slightest breeze.  Groups of people dressed in layers of thick fur shuffle along the cramped streets, careful to avoid the occasional overloaded caravan delivering supplies though the north gate.  Thick clouds of black smoke bellow from the sagging chimneys that protrude from the roofs of the numerous homes within the outpost, filling the air with sharp smell of burning wood.</description>
    <position x="380" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Raven's Point, Town Square" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Towering above the other ramshackle buildings of the outpost is the commerce center, serving as the hub that the wheel of life in Raven's Point revolves around.  Rows upon rows of uneven granite tiles have been arranged in a circular pattern in the center of the square, encircling the massive stone monument placed in the center.  Four large pillars marking the cardinal directions are hung with numerous deep blue icicle-shaped wind chimes, filling the square with the delicate sound of singing crystal.</description>
    <position x="400" y="700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go commerce center" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Raven's Point, Northern Square" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>An elaborate chapel rises above the crooked homes of Raven's Point, its candlelit mikkhalbamar archway bathing the towering facade in a pale yellow glow.  Rows of icicles dangle from the overhanging roofs of the houses that surround the rectangular square, glittering dangerously within the cloak of night.  The frigid mountain air is filled with the lingering scent of smoldering wood, as the remnants of the last days cooking fires slowly burn themselves out.</description>
    <description>An elaborate chapel rises above the crooked homes of Raven's Point, its mikkhalbamar archway welcoming all who seek solace and comfort upon its sanctified ground.  Rows of icicles dangle from the overhanging roofs of the houses that surround the rectangular square, glittering dangerously in the available light.  The air is filled with the lingering scent of fresh cooking and the sharp thud of boots as they strike the icy cobbles inset into the ground.</description>
    <position x="400" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mikkhalbamar archway" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Raven's Point, Gear Gate" note="Raven's Point">
    <description>The massive gear gate is a flurry of constant motion as war-worn generals dressed in bulky suits of ornamental armor bark orders at the legions of soldiers, prepared to defend the outpost at a moment's notice.  Countless Forfedhdarian archers stationed on the towers keep a careful watch on the southern pass.  A squat stone building with a sturdy door covered in pelts rests amidst the ramshackle hovels, its double-wide red brick chimney spouting a curling pillar of inky black smoke.</description>
    <position x="400" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sturdy door" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gear gate" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Raven's Point, Western Square">
    <description>The weathered log walls that enclose the outpost curve inward sharply around the narrow walkway that winds between ramshackle homes, pressing nearly flush against the weathered stone of the canyon.  High above, the silhouetted figures of the guards on patrol sweep back and forth along the top of the walls, scanning the distance for invading forces.  Within the shadow of an overhanging ledge the entrance to a cavern splits the uneven stone of the western wall.</description>
    <position x="360" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone bank" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Raven's Point, Collapsed Tunnel">
    <description>A wide path has been cut though the maze of stalagmites, winding along the cold cobblestone floor to halt before the collapsed remnants of a massive archway.  The intricately carved surface of the stone has been sundered savagely from the jagged walls of the cavern, taking with it a large amount of the surrounding stone.  Two burly Dwarven guards clad in impressive suits of gem-encrusted armor hold a constant vigil, keeping careful watch for approaching intruders.</description>
    <position x="340" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Raven's Point, Training Yard">
    <description>The air is filled with the sound of clashing swords as tenderfoot and veteran alike hone their skills on the equipment arranged around the training yard.  A massive barracks protrudes from the face of the sheer rock wall, its reinforced structure equipped with several ballistas and onagers.  Each one is manned by a group of heavily armored archers and guards.  High above, a massive twisted horn rests upon a ledge, used to warn the outpost's citizens to run for cover in time of siege by invading forces.</description>
    <position x="420" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mikkhalbamar gate" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="The Raven's Nest, Entry Hall">
    <description>Formed from what was once an expansive cave, the room is dominated by glistening stalactites hung with iron-wrought lanterns that dangle downward from the ceiling.  Elegant arches carved with worn symbols support the black stone overhead, crossing paths at the pinnacle of the triangular room.  Numerous Dwarven soldiers stride purposefully along the polished black stone floor, spreading outward to their unknown destinations.</description>
    <position x="440" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mikkhalbamar gate" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="The Raven's Nest, Great Hall">
    <description>Slightly more narrow then the entry, the great hall has been decorated with fur that lines the polished floor, resting beneath the banners dangling from the stalactites overhead.  Softly flickering orbs dangle from the rock ceiling overhead, bathing the expansive hall in a pale yellow light.  A thick mikkhalbamar door, flanked by two burly Dwarven guards, leads into the commander's office.</description>
    <position x="460" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mikkhalbamar door" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="The Raven's Nest, Dormitory" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Narrow passages cut through the stone of the dormitory twist away out of sight, giving glimpses of doorway upon doorway.  Muffled sounds trickle from behind the squat opening, echoing along the passage.  Small pools of water have collected in narrow grooves worn into the stone floor, casting rippling beams of light upon the black stone walls.</description>
    <position x="460" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="The Raven's Nest, Dormitory" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Dust-covered tapestries are hung from the walls between the unending row of doorways set into the walls of the dark stone passage.  Stomping to and from their assigned dwellings, residents show signs of extreme fatigue and stress across their weatherworn visages.</description>
    <position x="460" y="770" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="The Raven's Nest, Dormitory" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The sound of running water fills the narrow chamber, emanating from a shallow stone fountain carved into the eastern wall around a natural spring of icy mountain water.  The numerous doorways that fill the dormitory follow the sharp curve of the passage, basking in the dull glow of several torches set midway up the walls on either side.</description>
    <position x="470" y="770" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="The Raven's Nest, Dormitory" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A few elaborate suits of ancient armor rest in the unadorned sections between the closely set doorways, their polished silver surfaces shimmering softly in the torchlight.  Steel planks bridge a jagged crack in the stone floor below, revealing a narrow gorge that descends into shadows far below.</description>
    <position x="470" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="The Raven's Nest, Mess Hall">
    <description>Brightly illuminated, the hall is filled with the sounds of clattering dishes, groaning screeches of benches upon the polished stone floor and the low rumble of muttered speech, all combining to form a whirlwind of sound.  Along the eastern wall, a long rack displays a selection of food heavily picked over by the masses of warriors that come and go from the mess hall.  Tightly packed rows of tables make it difficult to keep up with the mess left behind.</description>
    <position x="480" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Smoky Bandit's, Shop" note="Smoky Bandit's|Tobacco" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pungent to extraordinarily sweet, the heavy aroma of tobacco of all kinds assails the senses in this small, cramped room.  Shelves lined with dusty glass jars of varying translucency vie for space with hooks hung with pouches, and tiered tables display handmade pipes.  Centered on the back wall is a large portrait of an extremely aged Dwarven man with a long pipe dangling from his mouth.</description>
    <position x="420" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sturdy door" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Smoky Bandit's, Lounge">
    <description>Rocking chairs and couches with rock-hard cushions are arranged in a semicircle around a large fireplace, above which is a detailed mosaic landscape done in a variety of rough native stone.  A snowbeast pelt rug is spread in the center of the space, a squat stone table atop it holding refreshments for customers to enjoy while puffing on their pipes.  The stale scent of tobacco clings to every surface despite the cloudy glass window kept open a small crack for ventilation.</description>
    <position x="430" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trapdoor" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Bank of Raven's Point, Lobby" note="Bank">
    <description>Incredibly thick slabs of stone form this bank, the sheer impenetrability giving the impression that the building was carved from an outcropping of stone at the center of the town.  There is no decoration here, just low bronze braziers which illuminate the room and stain the walls with their soot.  The doorway of the bank itself is open, though a massive stone cleverly designed to roll into place rests beside it.  Several ornery-looking guards armed with enormous battle axes stand at the ready.</description>
    <position x="360" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Bank of Raven's Point, Exchange" note="Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A small square hole is cut into the stone wall, leaving just enough room to speak to the clerk behind it and to slide coins back and forth -- security is no joke at this bank.  The only break in the monotony of the grey stone walls is a plain exchange rate board and a small calendar set into the wall.</description>
    <position x="370" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Bank of Raven's Point, Depository" note="Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Chiseled into the cold stone walls of the bank is a tiny opening which leaves just enough room for the teller behind it to squint through and pass coins.  The flat grey of the room is unbroken, save for a few pale scuffs and a streak of old blood on the thick wall nearest the lobby.</description>
    <position x="350" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Frozen Tunnel">
    <description>Carved into the icy stone, an expansive cavern winds its way downward into glimmering shadows far below. Broken bones are casually stacked against the slanted walls, the space between each pile cutting a narrow pathway down the midline of the dank chamber.  The craggy fissure that splits the southern wall offers an obstructed view of the mountains beyond, the pristine snow catching the light, its pale blanket smoothing the harsh lines of the mountain's visage.</description>
    <description>Carved into the icy stone, an expansive cavern winds its way downward into glimmering shadows far below.  Piles of broken bones are casually pushed against the slanted cavern walls, the space between them cutting a narrow pathway down the midline of the dank passage.  Gentle beams of flickering light dance across the slanted stone floor, streaming through the craggy fissure that leads to the jagged mountainside beyond.</description>
    <position x="150" y="630" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fissure" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos">
    <description>Lined in an immense layer of ice, the cavern expands outward into chamber after endless chamber.  Stalactites, nearly three times the height of a mature Gor'Tog, stretch from ceiling to floor like glassy assassin's daggers, threatening to fall at a moment's notice.  Along the northeastern wall, a curving stone passage rises upward at a steep angle, partially bathed in a pale illumination cast from some unknown source.</description>
    <position x="210" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos">
    <description>Cloudy drops of mineral-rich water cling to the stalactites lining the ceiling as if fighting for their very survival.  In the end, the battle is always lost, and the droplets plummet to the cavern floor.  Massive claws have raked the wall, leaving behind deep gouges.  A narrow man-made crevice cuts through the luminescent pale blue ice, allowing passage to those brave enough to squeeze though the tight space.</description>
    <position x="190" y="710" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos">
    <description>The expansive pale blue passage of glittering ice seems to stretch on forever, as if viewed from within the heart of a faceted diamond.  Like the inner fire of a gem, a luster refracts from the polished surface of the ice, bathing the area in a shifting hue of color.  Small bits of fabric, bone, and frost-covered wood fill the deep crevices of ice that wind around the cavern, the sign someone or something inhabits this seemingly barren cavern.</description>
    <position x="170" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos">
    <description>As though carved from a single frozen mass, pillars of glass-like ice trail from ceiling to floor in tight groups.  Every step and sound fills the air with sharp echoes as even the minutest sound reverberates around the cavern's expanse, tripling in strength before dying off into uneasy silence.  A few spear-like tips of rock thrust out from the icy walls, glimmering softly in the available light.</description>
    <position x="210" y="650" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos" note="RTF43|RT-IG-FB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Shifting beams of light filter through a partially obstructed opening that splits the pinnacle of the ceiling, causing the surrounding walls to glisten like a freshly cut diamond.  Snow-dusted icicles hang between rough patches of stone that protrude from the foot of the gap, stretching down the faceted walls to just above the floor.</description>
    <description>Shifting beams of dancing sunlight filter in though a partially obstructed opening that splits the pinnacle of the ceiling, causing the surrounding walls to glisten like a freshly cut diamond.  Snow-dusted icicles hang between the rough patches of stone that protrude from the foot of the gap, stretching down the faceted walls almost to the floor.</description>
    <position x="250" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos">
    <description>Curiously mummified creatures, contorted into odd postures by the slow movement of the ice, rest beneath the surface of the walls and floor.  Their baleful eyes gaze blankly from behind the faceted flow, almost pleading for release from their frigid tombs.  A tracery of faint cracks emanates from beneath a twisted stone that has fallen from the ceiling an oval of tortuous white imperfections marks the collision, stark upon a sea of blue ice.</description>
    <position x="250" y="650" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos">
    <description>Like a maze of mirrors, the crystal-clear surfaces of the ice reflect the distorted images of those who have found themselves within its icy walls.  Along the northern wall, the frozen cascade of a waterfall captured in a single moment in time spills from the ceiling down into a pool of jagged ice and stone.  The faint aroma of musk mingles with the chill scent of stale water, tickling the senses as it drifts about the expansive grotto.</description>
    <position x="230" y="630" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Jeol'gelvmoraen, Ice Grottos" note="RTF44|RT-IG-MG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Countless niches, cut into the otherwise smooth surface of the shimmering pale blue ice, reach up to the stalactite-lined ceiling.  Several matted white pelts, each bearing large and unsightly stains, rest atop thick beds of straw and decayed plant matter that line the frozen floor of each niche.  Small shards of white bone and tattered bits of armor have been neatly piled near a frozen basin dug into the ground, surrounded in a liberal dusting of fine black ash.</description>
    <position x="270" y="630" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Haalikshal Highway, Stember's Ford" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A shallow ford crosses a small stream running north down the valley.  A wide road leads from it to Sang Munar, the entrance to the tunnel beneath the eastern mountains.  To the northwest, the road crosses the valley to the foot of the western mountain range.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road">
    <description>A high valley spotted with wildflowers lies between two lines of mountain peaks.  Across a ford to the southeast, the entrance to the underground highway beckons, but the view to the northwest awes rather than welcomes: a road twists and bends up the western range, switching back and forth and looking impossibly steep.  As it dwindles from sight, high and far away, one can understand why it's called The Sky Road.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ford" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road" note="RTF05|RT-HEG-HC" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The road lies along the side of the western range, passing from sight at times as it follows the contours of the hillside.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road">
    <description>The highway takes a sharp bend, turning in a sweeping curve along the almost vertical wall of the mountainside.  A landslide in the past must have torn the road from its former path, requiring the hard labor of cutting away the hillside to reroute the road around the gap.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road">
    <description>At one spot along the way, nature has provided one of her surprises -- fractures in the rock have divided the cliff wall into several nearly equal panels with smooth surfaces.  And passersby have taken advantage of the oddity to use the panels as their tablets on which to address the world.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road">
    <description>A rocky spur thrusts out from the face of the western range, and the road bends sharply around it, commanding sweeping views to the north, east, and south.  At the valley side of the highway stands a telescope in a small paved area with a stone parapet.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road" note="RTF06\|RT-HEG-MG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>For a stretch of several hundred yards the road widens, taking advantage of a natural ledge.  The area offers unobstructed views of the roadway for a good distance up and down the slope, and the level ground allows caravans or wagons going in opposite directions to pass in safety.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road" note="RTF07\|RT-HEG-AGF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>A spate of water roars down the mountainside with deafening noise and drenching mist, rushing under a stone bridge that carries the road across its path.  A high brick parapet on the side toward the cataract screens the roadbed from the worst of the spray.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road" note="RTF08\|RT-HEG-RP" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Nearing the summit, the road traverses its steepest grade in its passage along the mountainside.  A stone parapet lines the valley side of the roadway, giving warning and some protection against a misstep.  Iron eyebolts have been driven into the cliff face, spaced about a furlong apart, for wagons that need to be secured while the team is changed or repairs are made.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road">
    <description>A short distance up the hill, torches light a wooden gate in a stone wall.  In the other direction, to the southeast, a wide, graveled road descends into the darkness of the valley below.</description>
    <description>This spot just below the summit of the ridge commands sweeping views to the north, where a broad river runs far below, and to the east and southeast, where another range fills the horizon.  A short distance up the hill is a gate in a stone wall to the southeast, the road skirts the side of the western range to the valley far below.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Lewkar Awg, The Courtyard" note="Lewkar Awg">
    <description>Lanterns light a round tower in a small cobblestone courtyard.  Their flickering beams reflect off the water in a trough and off a brass-studded door in the tower.  In the east and west walls are gates made of stout timbers.</description>
    <description>A small cobblestone courtyard serves travelers as a place for a short rest, offering a water trough for the animals and benches out of the wind for their riders.  In the east and west walls are gates made of stout timbers strapped with brass.  A few stone steps lead up to the door of the round tower in the center of the yard.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go west gate" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go east gate" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Haalikshal Highway, The Sky Road" note="Map116_Hibarnhvidar.xml|Hibarnhvidar">
    <description>The lights of a distant settlement dot the darkness to the southwest.  To the northeast, flickering torches flank a gate in a wall at the crest of the hill.  Behind the wall, a tower is dimly visible.</description>
    <description>To the southwest, the steep but wide road rises from a distant valley, climbing to a gate in a stone wall to the northeast.  Behind the wall, a grey tower three or four stories high dominates the skyline.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Lewkar Awg, The Reception Room">
    <description>The round and rather spacious reception room occupies the whole ground floor of the tower.  A copper kettle hangs from a bracket over the fireplace.  A rough desk sits by the fire, and a few benches provide seating near a passage to the north.  The only other furnishing is a handsome welcome mat near the entrance door.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Lewkar Awg, The Tower Barracks">
    <description>It's good that the room is big, because either each guard supplied his own bedding or the barracks was equipped from a used furniture sale.  Every kind of resting place except a grave seems represented, among them a four-poster bed, a brass bed, a frame-and-canvas cot, a threadbare couch, a hammock hung from the ceiling, and a straw tick on the floor.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Lewkar Awg, The Tower Watchroom">
    <description>Barred windows at the eight cardinal points of the compass pierce the stone walls of this round, empty room.  From here, guards can watch the comings and goings to and from Hibarnhvidar in every direction.  To aid the absent-minded or forgetful, the arms of a compass rose set in the floor stretch to the corresponding windows.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Lewkar Awg, The Tower Kitchen">
    <description>The kitchen looks functional, with a table and bench, a big storage cabinet for supplies, and even a crate of bread ready for use.  An iron stove stands on one side, its pipe running out through the wall.  A pot is bubbling away on the hot stove, and a coal scuttle sits alongside.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Haalikshal Highway, Ferry Dock" note="Map113_West_Segoltha.xml|Ferry|Ilaya Taipa|River Clan|Segoltha River|Ain Ghazal">
    <description>An ample dock lies in an elbow of the river, and to its stones is fastened the stout chain that guides the ferry.  Although many a fisherman would like to tie his punt or rowboat here, the ferrymen fend them off, warning them against fouling the tow-line or, with more urgency, against getting caught between the heavy timbers of the ferry and the stones of the dock.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Cragstone Vale, Roadway" note="Map69_Shard_West_Gate.xml|Cragstone Vale|Shard">
    <description>The road hugs the river, culminating in a bridge that once spanned the flow, leading to the mouth of the valley.  Scorched, scarred earthworks are all that now remain of a long abandoned fortification.  The great rents in the defenses must have been torn by a devastating force, exposing a massive shard of black rock resting at its heart.</description>
    <position x="380" y="580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rock shard" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Commerce Center, Entryway" note="Commerce Center">
    <description>Matted and worn from the stomp of heavy boots, a large rug of unidentifiable brown fur covers the floor of the foyer.  Braziers billow heat from the corners of the room, set to warm the three main sections of the commerce hub of Raven's Point: the furrier to the west, the general store to the north, and the gembuyer to the east.</description>
    <position x="460" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched door" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Stedh's Furs" note="Stedh's Furs|Bundles" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Dominated by a long stone counter, this small room is filled with the heavy scent of the partially preserved pelts and hides that hang on every surface of the walls.  A dirty window overlooks the town square of the tiny village.  The shop's burly owner, Stedh, keeps the store in a barely controlled state of disarray -- though only between flirting with every lass who walks through his door.</description>
    <position x="450" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Gimsta's Gimstaan" note="Gimsta's Gimstaan|Gems" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Glass baubles in rich jewel tones hang before a glistening window that faces the street, the faux gems catching and refracting the sunlight into a rainbow of colors.  A thick white fur rug lies in front of a polished stone counter behind which is a cushioned stool and a golden loupe hung on a small hook.  Brocade tapestries of Forfedhdarian landscapes cover the walls, their brilliant hues and refined appearance a rarity in this cold mountain village.</description>
    <position x="470" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="General Store" note="General Store" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Hardly more than a handful of miscellaneous supplies, the general store of Raven's Point is a hub of activity for visiting hunters, warriors, and miners.  A pitted bronze weapon rack takes up most of the display wall, the gleaming armaments hung above a long stone table.</description>
    <position x="460" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Himineldar Shel, Along the Trail">
    <description>A broken, ivy-covered dry stone wall can be seen alongside the trail in this small natural clearing.  Lines of pine trees encircle the last vestiges of grass and wildly growing flowers of what used to be a garden.  Beyond the wall the sun gleams off a small pond surrounded by tall reeds.</description>
    <description>An occasional soft splash is heard in the darkness beyond a wall that runs alongside the trail.</description>
    <position x="200" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Himineldar Shel, Trail's End" note="RTF47|RT-MG-IG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>As the trail abruptly leaves the wooded area, a large cracked boulder almost completely blocks the path.  In the distance, the winds and weather have left only the hardiest of pines and shrubs on this face of the mountain.</description>
    <description>As the trail abruptly leaves the wooded area, a large cracked boulder almost completely blocks the path.  In the distance, the face of the mountain rises up out of the darkness.</description>
    <position x="220" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="On the Mountainside, Stony Trail" note="RTF49|RT-MG-RP" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Stones underfoot make traversing the trail precarious, as every step dislodges bits of rubble to send them skittering down the path.  On one side of the trail, scrub and sturdy pines cling tenaciously to the boulders that jut out of the mountainside.  On the other is air, though a fall here would deal little damage.</description>
    <description>Stones underfoot make traversing the trail precarious, as every step dislodges bits of rubble to bounce away into the darkness.  On one side of the trail, scrub and sturdy pines cling tenaciously to the boulders that jut out from the mountainside.  On the other is air, though a fall here would deal little damage.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="On the Mountainside, Cleared Flat" note="RTF09\|RT-MG-FB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Three tall stone slabs, one resting across the other two, form a convenient bench -- for someone about three times as tall as a 'Tog, perhaps.  The ground around the boulders is bare of the rocks strewn along the rest of the trail, as if scuffed away.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="On the Mountainside, High Trail">
    <description>Though wide enough to hold several hikers walking abreast, the trail falls sharply off to the west.  Shifting rubble underfoot forces travelers to clutch at the branches of stunted pines, leaving bits of bark and broken brown needles to litter the ground.  A large crevice can be seen in the distance halfway to the summit.</description>
    <description>Though wide enough to hold several hikers walking abreast, the trail falls sharply off to the west.  Shifting rubble underfoot forces travelers to clutch at the branches of stunted pines, leaving bits of bark and broken brown needles to litter the ground.  An occasional faint glow can be seen sometimes in the darkness halfway up the summit.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="On the Mountainside, Plateau">
    <description>The ground levels out and widens here, providing a safe area to rest before the challenging trail ahead.  A large depression in the ground has collected water from the last rainfall.  Droppings and paw prints impressed in the muddy surface around the pool mark this as a watering hole for local animals.</description>
    <description>The ground levels out and widens here, providing a safe area to rest.  A large depression in the ground has collected water from the last rainfall.  Skittering in the darkness is evidence of wildlife that might use this as a watering hole.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="On the Mountainside, Rock Face">
    <description>The trail narrows, forcing travelers to edge carefully along the overhanging rock face to avoid a painful fall.  Looking down, all that can be seen is a dauntingly long stretch of open air between you and the broken boulders and pale bones littering the bottom of the slope.</description>
    <description>The trail narrows, forcing travelers to edge carefully along the overhanging rock face to avoid a painful fall.  Nothing can be seen in the darkness below, but the occasional rock that is dislodged seems to take forever before hitting solid ground.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="On the Mountainside, The Flat">
    <description>A large firepit filled with muddy ashes is in the center of what is clearly a campsite.  From this vantage point a crevice further up the trail can be seen.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="On the Mountainside, The Trail">
    <description>The trail is devoid of any real hazards to your footing -- a good thing, as a fall from this spot would surely be deadly.  Small figures and wagons move along the road far below, while an occasional hawk or eagle soars near the summit.</description>
    <description>The trail is devoid of any real hazards to your footing -- a good thing, as a fall from this spot would surely be deadly.  From time to time, something rustles in the darkness, or sends a rock clattering down the slopes to startle the unwary.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="On the Mountainside, The Crevice" note="RTF11|RT-MG-HEG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Seismic force has sundered the mountain, splitting the summit to leave behind a vast crevasse.  Pine trees, gnarled and stunted at this altitude, grow in scattered clumps with fallen trunks littering the area.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Mountainside, Thin Path">
    <description>The path thins here between a line of boulders on one side and trees and shrubs against the mountainside.  On a ledge overhead, the scattered pieces of a long-abandoned nest are decorated with feathers caught on the bark.  Just out of reach, a cracked egg shell rocks with any errant breeze.</description>
    <description>The path thins here between a line of boulders on one side and trees and shrubs against the mountainside.  Occasionally an eerie scratching noise from the ledge above follows an errant breeze.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Mountainside, The Ledge">
    <description>The path ends abruptly on a ledge of crystalline stone that overlooks the canyons and lakes far below.  Across the expansive vista, the majestic Himineldar Shel -- peaks occasionally wreathed in clouds -- are visible in the distance.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="In the Mountain, The Crevice">
    <description>Instead of the expected close walls of a crevice, the area opens up into a large crater that is not detectable from outside the pine-covered entrance.  Large boulders lie about everywhere and trees grow thick along the sides, protected from the weather.  The path forks, each direction well traveled, possibly by the wild animals that come here for shelter.</description>
    <description>Instead of the expected close walls of a crevice, the area opens up into a large crater that is not detectable from outside the pine-covered entrance.  The shapes of large boulders and trees growing along the sides can be made out in the darkness.  The path forks, each direction well traveled, possibly by the wild animals that come here for shelter.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="In the Mountain, The Bone Yard" note="mountain giant">
    <description>A large ledge overhangs what has clearly been used as a bone yard by the occupants of this crater.  Most piles are haphazardly arranged with no order, though the rim of the ledge has been carefully lined with a row of grinning skulls that range in size from field mouse to mammoth.  The path winds to the northeast through this macabre setting.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="In the Crater, Kitchen">
    <description>In the center of this cleared area is an enormous fire pit that is aflame even though no caretakers are visible.  Filled with a grey bubbling concoction, a grey mammoth skull lies on a pile of stones in the flames.  To one side of the fire pit, a pile of raw half-gnawed animal legs and rib cages rests, for those that can't wait for the stew to be ready.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="In the Crater, Communal Area" note="RTF10|RT-MG-IG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Clearly composed of broken pieces of caravans and wagons, a large, disorganized semicircle of debris occupies the center of the area.  One oddly decorated caravan remains mostly intact, placed by itself beneath a small ledge.  Dark red and brown stains have soaked into the ground in the cleared area inside the crescent of rubbish.</description>
    <description>Clearly composed of broken pieces of caravans and wagons, a large, disorganized semicircle of debris occupies the center of the area.  One oddly decorated caravan remains mostly intact, placed by itself beneath a small ledge.  Darkened areas on the ground are in the cleared area inside the circle.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="In the Crater, Sleeping Area">
    <description>Occupants are sheltered from the weather by the ledge overhanging this flattened area.  Enormous piles of untanned skins litter the ground, all in various states of decay.  A smoothed slab has been placed at the end of each pile, grimy with grease and stains.  The stench is almost unbearable as the soft murmur of flies fill the air.</description>
    <description>Occupants are sheltered from the weather by the ledge overhanging this flattened area.  Enormous piles littering the ground can be made out in the darkness.  The stench is almost unbearable as the rustle of small creatures can be heard from unknown sources.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="In the Crater, The Pit" note="RTF48|RT-MG-BS" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Moving around a line of pine trees, the rise in the ground prevents falling into the deep pit that fills the whole area.  A ledge overhangs the pit, allowing light to penetrate but still protecting it from weather.  The path follows the edge to the northwest, any other way blocked by the pit or large boulders.</description>
    <description>Moving around a line of pine trees, the rise in the ground prevents falling into the deep pit that fills the whole area.  A ledge overhangs the pit, allowing any available light to penetrate but still protecting it from weather.  The only passable path seems to be to the northwest, as other ways are blocked by looming obstacles in the darkness.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Abandoned Mine, Storage Area">
    <description>This area was once a staging area of the old mine.  Now broken bottles, piles of debris and rotting food litters the floor and surrounds a small fire pit.</description>
    <description>This area was once a staging area of the old mine.  Meticulously carved sandstone tiles form a decorative veneer over the walls' crumbling mortar, hinting at former prosperity and natural artisanship.  Now, broken bottles, piles of debris and rotting food litter the floor surrounding a small fire pit.  To the south, ambient light from the entrance fades into murky grey shadows.</description>
    <position x="60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mine entrance" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Abandoned Mine, Storage Area">
    <description>Away from the uncertain light of the entrance, the walls are slick with greasy mold leaving the room dank and musty-smelling.  Shadows lurk along the corners, masking the progressive state of decay and the ragged gaps in the sandstone veneer.  Glittering glass shards cover the floor, fanning away from a ruined cupboard.  Keeping vigil beside the mine's door is a kneeling figure, its outstretched hands holding a black marble slab upon which to rest an offering.</description>
    <position x="60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel-barred door" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Abandoned Mine, Tunnel">
    <description>The caliginous light makes it difficult to see far.  Broad timber struts partition the crumbling sedimentary walls and shore up the low ceiling joists.  One strut bears a blackened halo above a corroding metal bracket where the miners placed their torches.  Thick wooden beams, or track ties, lock a pair of pitted steel ridges into place as they disappear around a sharp curve into the shadows.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel-barred door" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Abandoned Mine, Tunnel">
    <description>Following the bend, the old tracks continue through a square arch of splintered timbers, disappearing beneath a formidable mound of rubble.  The relic of an old rock fall, the tumbled stones and dirt make passage through the arch a tight squeeze.  A derelict mining cart, its wheels rusted tight, lies overturned below a torch bracket that hangs precariously by a corroded bolt.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go square arch" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Abandoned Mine, Sloping Tunnel">
    <description>An old lantern emits a faint glow to hold the suffocating darkness at bay.  The large hill of rubble and gravel peters out into sludge the consistency of porridge that sticks to boots, clothing, and skin, and makes the going quite difficult.  The tracks extend from a pile of rubble that partially blocks the arch to the north, only to drop away down a steep slope.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go square arch" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep slope" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Abandoned Mine, Sloping Tunnel" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>The damp and darkness have taken their toll on the wooden ties below the iron tracks, fostering a home for borers and beetles in the dark, crumbling wood.  Thankfully, the tracks have long ceased to need the ties and continue to mimic the dips and curves of the slope.  Debris of old washouts, roots, rocks and gravel caught between the tracks and sleepers makes the way perilous for the hasty.  The danger for travelers is somewhat alleviated by a rusted handrail loosely bolted into the fragmenting rock wall.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep slope" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Abandoned Mine, Rock Shelf">
    <description>The tracks emerge from a declivitous tunnel onto this broad sandstone shelf before again disappearing down the slope of a wide, dark hole.  The spluttering light of a solitary lantern dimly catches the sumptuous colors of limestone shawls, delicately stained by mineral deposits.  Overhead, cracks in the ceiling continuously bleed drops of lime-rich water that fall with a plop around the hole, wearing away at the rock to form a smooth set of shallow pockmarks.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="go" move="rt sit;go dark hole" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Abandoned Mine, Rock Ledge">
    <description>The slopes of a dark hole pierce the broad shelf above this narrow ledge.  Beyond the crumbling edge, vaulted cavern ceilings soar and staggering canyon depths plummet into shadowed depths, a vast emptiness surrounded by glory.  Magnificent limestone shawls drape the walls in multicolored splendor, twinkling as faceted crystals reflect the dim light.  The rust-laden tracks lie forlorn and forgotten veering off to the east, a dreary contrast to the resplendent backdrop.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark hole" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Abandoned Mine, Cavern">
    <description>In the dim light, the tracks are barely visible, hugging a jagged bend in the rock shelf's wall before they turn east onto a long, narrow bridge suspended from two immense wooden girders.  The workmanship of the aerial walkway speaks of experienced engineers, although the materials seem somewhat primitive.  Leading off to the northeast a rotting platform depends from a network of wrist-thick wires.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Abandoned Mine, Bridge">
    <description>Massive ropes, spliced and bound with steel wire, are pulled taut against the girders to support the weight of the bridge.  Between the steel wire and the rotting slats, zigzagged ropes reinforce the handhold and border the aerial walkway.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Abandoned Mine, Bridge">
    <description>An ever-present air current from the chasm below causes the bridge to sway gently from side to side, sending small trickles of dust down between the wood to dissipate in mid-air.  The ropes creak and protest at the added stress and only the steel cable reinforcing the fist-thick rope serves as reassurance that the bridge will indeed not snap and break.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Abandoned Mine, Bridge">
    <description>The wooden planks stop short at a hole.  Damp air, borers and age have won their battle with the bridge, leaving behind a gaping hole that offers a wide view of the chasm below.  The far side of the breach is shrouded in darkness, with only vague shapes being visible from here.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Abandoned Mine, Rotting Platform">
    <description>Suspended by rotting cable fixtures overhead, the platform bounces gently as air currents swirl, and the cable dips a little lower over the plummeting depths of the chasm.  It is not obvious why this platform is here but vacant cable fixtures seem to indicate aborted plans to extend it.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Abandoned Mine, Rotting Platform">
    <description>Tiny particles of dust continually drift down from the fittings.  Some are heavy enough to settle on and between the planks, eventually sifting away into the blackness below.  Others float away idly like tiny twinkling motes in the air.  To the south, you can see the long bridge, but the gap between this platform and the bridge is widening.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Abandoned Mine, Rotting Platform">
    <description>Supported by a rickety, makeshift trestle connecting it to a bridge, the platform comes to an abrupt end here.  Creaking timbers and shifting debris mingle with the high-pitched squeals of bats, sending echoes whispering through the sepulchral chasm.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="211" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Abandoned Mine, Bridge">
    <description>Rotting timbers tumble over the edge of a gaping hole, held to the bridge by fraying ropes.  Reinforced beams stand sentinel at the ledge, though cut marks mar their steel surface and most of the cables which once supported the bridge have long since snapped, leaving behind only a few strands.  Fallen rocks and other rubble litter the remaining planks, the debris growing denser to the east.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="212" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Abandoned Mine, Cave-in">
    <description>A mountainous cave-in has spewed huge rocks and tons of rubble toward the bridge, and blocks the way further east.  Curiously, a set of deep wheel ruts carve their way through the silted ground and stop abruptly at an enormous boulder.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Abandoned Mine, Fractured Ledge">
    <description>Careless mining practices have left the walls without reinforcement, resulting in rock falls that litter the ledge with mounds of rubble.  From time to time, a loose stone will clatter down the pile before tumbling over the edge into the abyss, leaving behind an expectant silence as you wait in vain to hear it strike the bottom.  A rope tied to an iron stake dangles over the precipice.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rope" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Abandoned Mine, Hollow">
    <description>A cramped dugout has been carved into the crumbling cliff face, probably the handiwork of an exploration team.  A long rope suspended from an overhead spike swings gently from side to side, brushing against a ledge and fraying the fibers.  Below the hollow, the rope ends at a small wooden platform dangling precariously into the mouth of a yawning abyss.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden platform" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rope" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Abandoned Mine, Wooden Platform">
    <description>This small platform hangs suspended a short way into the abyss, the old rope tied securely to the metal framework.  Although here the rope and frame are still in good order, the timber slats are beginning to rot.  Gaps in the flooring show only a sheer vertical cliff face shrouded in darkness.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cliff;climb cliff" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rope" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Abandoned Mine, Vertical Cliff Face">
    <description>A soft phosphorescent glow emanates from huge patches of fungus that coat the rocky outcrops jutting from the walls of this sheer cliff face.  Even so, the surroundings are difficult to make out in the low light.  All that is readily visible are shallow handholds in the immediate vicinity that appear like daubs of shadow pocking the luminous fungi.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fungus-covered outcrop" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb handhold" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Abandoned Mine, Vertical Cliff Face">
    <description>The darkness is only slightly ameliorated by the soft phosphorescent glow emanating from huge patches of fungus that coat the rock walls of this narrow crevice, making it difficult to fully discern the surroundings.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb face cliff" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb handholds" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Abandoned Mine, Chasm Floor">
    <description>Huge patches of phosphorescent moss cling to the slick sides of the creviced wall, lending a ghostly glow to the surrounds.  The ground is smooth and dusty, littered with tiny bits of gravel that have fallen from above.  An occasional drip plops into a body of water nearby and the sound echoes eerily before the deep hush settles once more.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb creviced walls" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Underground Lake, Shoreline">
    <description>The ground gradually slopes down, dipping below the surface of a murky lake.  Thick, phosphorescent fungus sprouts out of crevices in the cave wall, grasping out for moisture dripping down the stone.  Small ripples in the lake refract the pale light, causing an effect similar to moonlight dancing off the water.  Something can be heard dripping into the lake from further into darkness to the east.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Underground Lake, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The chilly water in the shallows of this subterranean lake is crystal clear, showing the silted bottom.  It looks only knee deep.  Drops of condensation occasionally plummet from somewhere unseen, far up above.  A large rock rises up out of the water to the east, making straight travel impossible.  The lake stretches out to the southeast, around the rock while the gravelly floor rises up to the west.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Underground Lake" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The water here laps carefully against the massive boulder to the north.  Spotted, glowing fungus has taken up resident on the edge of the rock, casting a sickly pallor across the water.  The ethereal light dances on top of the lake, but makes it impossible to see what lies below the surface.  Water drips steadily into the water from walls which are slick with condensation.  The cool water continues its path northeast and northwest around the rock.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Underground Lake" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The lake casually winds north alongside the protruding rock to the west.  Another boulder rises up from the inky depths to the east, not quite breaking the surface of the water.  Slick layers of moss have coated both rocks, swaying slowly in the lake's gentle current.  The water is so deep here that what lies below cannot be seen through the murk.  Trickling water can be heard coming from beyond the eastern boulder.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Underground Lake" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The lake dead ends here in a stagnant pool pushed up against a solid wall of huge stalactites and fallen boulders to the north.  The water is warm due to the lack of circulation, but the amount of moss and algae on the walls have increased greatly.  Chunks of finger-like fungus have drifted to the surface of the water here and the air is rich with the stench of rotting plant matter.  Cooler water can be felt drifting in from the south, but it has little effect on the overall temperature.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="224" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Underground Lake, Rocky Shore" color="#0000FF">
    <description>This false shore is formed by a low rock shelf, the floor not quite rising above the surface of the lake.  As the water laps up against the shelf wall, it trickles into a large chute which has been naturally formed to the east.  A few deep gouges mar the rock walls, many of which have been turned into shelters for a spongy type of fungus.  The ground drops away to the west into the gloomy lake.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="go" move="rt go chute" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Abandoned Tunnel, Sludge Pit" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>The smell of stagnant mud is heavy in the air here and the ground has the consistency of old porridge.  Standing water mixed with fine dirt rests atop a treacherous bottom of thick mud, making movement in this area difficult.  Water occasionally drips into the mixture from the hole that rests high on the western wall.  Some shoring begins to the northwest and the ground appears to gain some semblance of structure.</description>
    <position x="60" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="rt northwest" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Dead End" color="#993300">
    <description>The soil is almost too soft to support a body's weight.  Apparently, those who excavated this tunnel realized the futility and stopped a little southeast of here.  Far to the west is the remnant of a last attempt at shoring the walls, and in all other directions, the floor gently slopes upwards.  While the slope seems innocuous, a brief test would reveal that the soil is only slightly more firm than mud.  The deceptive slope mocks any attempts to climb up and jealously guards the secret of what lies beyond</description>
    <description>The soil is almost too soft to support a body's weight.  Apparently, those who excavated this tunnel realized the futility and stopped a little southeast of here.  Far to the west is the remnant of a last attempt at shoring the walls, and in all other directions, the floor gently slopes upwards.  While the slope seems innocuous, a brief test would reveal that the soil is only slightly more firm than mud.  The deceptive slope mocks any attempts to climb up and jealously guards the secret of what lies beyond.</description>
    <position x="40" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Eastern Corridor" color="#993300">
    <description>The walls gradually widen until there is no need to brace them for comfortable walking.  Heavy moisture in the air has penetrated the soil, causing it to be soft and formless.  Some failed remains of an attempt to hold the saturated walls back is barely discernable, most of the structure having rotted away.  Three metal bands and a pile of decaying wood appear to be all that is left of some sort of barrel, whose original contents one might only guess at.</description>
    <position x="60" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Eastern Corridor" color="#993300">
    <description>As the corridor continues, the damp smell is unavoidable and much stronger.  The wooden wall braces steadily become more frequent presumably to defend against the lack of consistency in the soil, which appears to have sloughed off after years of neglect.  Partly obscured by decades of accumulated dust, the imprints of boots are still faintly visible on the floor.</description>
    <position x="40" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Eastern Corridor" color="#993300">
    <description>The faint smell of lingering mold and a heaviness in the air both betray the presence of moisture in this roughly-hewn corridor.  The rotting remains of wooden braces line the walls, occasionally bearing a blackened hole ideal for holding a torch or lantern hook.</description>
    <position x="20" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Crevice" color="#993300">
    <description>The floor of this crevice would dead end to the west at the foot of a towering rock shelf if not for the beginnings of a tunnel carved into its base.  Wooden supports and miscellaneous debris can be seen further west in the tunnel, while the crevice path continues to the east.  The walls of this chasm fade into nothingness above you as a vast expanse of shadow ceilings the cavern, the faint but consistent sound of dripping the only answer to your gaze.  To the north is a low opening.</description>
    <position x="0" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb long rope" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Staging Area" color="#993300">
    <description>A low opening expands into this broad cave.  While hardly a home away from home, it looks like this was used as a meeting room for a team that came some time before the tunnel's construction began.  A few aging wooden chairs surround a fallen table, all resting atop a tattered hemp rug.  A rusted iron lantern depends above the sitting area, providing awkward lighting at best.  Scraps of cloth, torn-out pages, and frayed rope-ends show that many preparations were executed here.</description>
    <position x="0" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Storage Area">
    <description>Long abandoned and stripped of anything useful, this room still retains the notable odor of steel and weapon oil.  On the western wall leans a warped cabinet, its door hanging from one rusty hinge.  On the eastern wall hang various iron racks, suited for holding weapons and armor while keeping them readily available for use.  Dark oil stains pattern the floor.  Large barrels and boxes lie discarded some even smashed, in a corner of the room, obvious remnants of depleted food stores.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabinet" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="In The Cabinet, A Prayer Niche">
    <description>Amidst the decay, a broken panel guards this small prayer niche like a drunken sentinel.  Even so, there is a hush here reminiscent of a holy place.  Two iron sconces hold dusty candles that have long ago burned down, leaving beaded streams of milky wax to sink to the floor in lacy strands.  Further back in this peaceful nook sits a tumbledown altar, covered in similarly exhausted candles, and there at its feet, between two candle stubs rests a worn, leather-bound journal.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go panel" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Western Branch" color="#993300">
    <description>All sounds become short and claustrophobic, losing the familiar echo as the walls close in.  Heavy, but aging wooden structural supports line walls of this section of the tunnel, holding back the immense pressure of the rock shelf surrounding it.  Various mining tools, now worthless, lay scattered haphazardly about the area, a hint at the flurry of activity this tunnel may once have seen.  To the east, a seemingly roofless chasm opens up, as the cramped mining tunnel plunges on to the west.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Western Branch" color="#993300">
    <description>Pebbles skitter down the tunnel dislodged by the slightest movement of air.  Rocks jut out of the sides of the tunnel, scraps of rotting cloth caught from some unwary passerby.  Many of the sturdy supports are soot stained, marking the locations of torches long since expired.  To the southwest, the tunnel continues downward, while higher ground is to the east.  At the side of the corridor, a patch of burlap is half-buried by a small cave-in.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Western Branch" color="#993300">
    <description>A large crack runs perpendicularly through this part of the tunnel.  The strong timbers are heavily reinforced in order to compensate for the structural weaknesses that the crack implies.  While narrow at the floor, the crack's width at the ceiling looks almost large enough to fit a gnome.  The gap in the floor is filled with rocks and dirt to make a smooth passage across, but the filling seems to be blotchily discolored.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Western Branch" color="#993300">
    <description>The tunnel continues west with its uniform look of sturdy support beams and messy mining leftovers strewn about in a hasty fashion.  Every noise seems to fall short, causing the tunnel to feel unnaturally cramped.  The darkness that closes in on the tunnel from east and west makes it seem possible that it continues on forever into the rock.  Slightly off the middle of the walkway lies a half-buried bird cage.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="rt east" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="west" move="rt west" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Western Branch" color="#993300">
    <description>The passageway stretches on to the east and west with no end in sight.  The vastness makes time feel dilated, presumably affected by the absence of significant differences in the surrounding environment.  Even the rocks sent tumbling by any footstep seem to skitter to an abrupt halt, providing no alleviation to the seemingly endless repetition of the deserted tunnels.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Western Branch" color="#993300">
    <description>A brilliant quartz vein surfaces in the wall here, glowing from some unknown phosphorescence.  Deep within the vein, there are dark spots presumably indicating the presence of a denser mineral.  Someone in search of the hoped-for gold or perhaps trying to get to the dark spots within has gouged out a large chunk of the quartz, damaging the natural splendor of the vein and littering the floor with the off cuts.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Ledge" color="#993300">
    <description>The tunnel comes to an abrupt westward end, as a rockslide has collapsed a good portion of the floor.  The only way to continue on the path west is down a steep cliff of fallen rocks mixed with the splintered remains of some support beams.  Attached to a sturdy rock at the edge of the ledge is a steel cable, which hangs stiffly down the side of the low cliff.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cable" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Rockslide" color="#993300">
    <description>Snaking its way amongst the litter of the rockslide is the steel cable that hangs from the ledge above.  Small rocks and skittering pebbles make getting a foothold difficult and the way uncertain.  To the southeast, resting on some rocks is a massive split girder arrested in its downward descent.  There perched rather forlornly is an old decaying boot lying on its side, either discarded by some unfortunate or perhaps ripped off their foot.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb girder" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cable" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Rockslide" color="#993300">
    <description>The precariously lodged girder cuts off here, its savagely splintered end hanging in mid air.  That might have been the end of the journey, were it not for two solid metal pins driven into a boulder.  Suspended from this surprising discovery is a rope ladder that hangs down the slope.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb girder" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Old Camp" color="#993300">
    <description>Rubble surrounds a long-expired fire pit.  Ever-higher piles of rocks to the west block the way forward.  Short of excavation, there is no way to go further.  To the east is a high rock wall that looks very difficult to climb except for the rope ladder that provides a way out.  Years of non-use have worn down what may have once been a makeshift camp.  A few discarded ration wrappers lie decaying between and under two large stones.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Abandoned Tunnels, Way out" color="#993300">
    <description>It is obvious that this was an initial excavation site some time ago.  Mining tools that have been worn down to the nub lie scattered about this wide tunnel, while sturdy wooden shoring lines the rough stone walls.  Oddly, a substantial-looking axe handle with a rope tied to it has been wedged in between two rocks near a rocky ledge.  The northern wall has been dug away to reveal a large hole, causing a brisk mountain wind to whistle through the hallway.</description>
    <position x="20" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb long rope" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>The weather outside suddenly seems beneficent.  Once the frigid wind enters this cavern, whether howling through the cave mouth or swooping in a hole in the mountainside, it gets trapped and gains power as it spirals between gaps in the cavern floors, walls and ceilings.  Each gust spreads a damp, brittle cold that chills even through the thickest armor while appearing to caress a variety of ice formations.  Depth perception is erratic as ice walls almost act like mirrors, reflecting what may not be there.</description>
    <position x="320" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cave mouth" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>A slight slope to the ice floor results in a slipping hazard that has been somewhat alleviated by battles fought in the area.  Constant melting and refreezing has mercifully ruined the smoothness of the cave floor, barely visible in some spots under clouded ice protrusions.  Gouges and ruts in the ice allow for last minute balance corrections, saving many a sore behind.</description>
    <description>A slight slope to the ice floor results in a slipping hazard that has been somewhat alleviated by battles fought in the area.  Constant melting and refreezing has mercifully ruined the smoothness of the cave floor, barely visible in some spots under clouded ice protrusions.  Gouges and ruts in the ice allow for last minute balance corrections, saving many a sore behind.  </description>
    <position x="340" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="ice southeast" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="south" move="ice south" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern" note="RTF46|RT-IC-MG" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Slippery tunnels, narrowed by ice, seem to twist and turn in no ordered direction.  A huge stalagmite forming here hampers progress even further.  Slick deposits of lime and frost coat the floor so thickly that in places only the most agile can safely pass between it and the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="340" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="ice west" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>Frigid air stiffens anything warm-blooded and makes navigating the slippery cave more treacherous.  The thick ice encasing an extremely narrow passageway to the northeast seems pearlized, as if it was exposed to outside light.  Close inspection of some dark spots in the floor reveals rusted items trapped in the ice.</description>
    <position x="300" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern" note="RTF45|RT-IC-FB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Claustrophobia easily affects those susceptible, as perspective in here is skewed: the floor slopes slightly upward while the ceiling seems to plunge suddenly, looming just above a Gor'Tog's head.  Protrusions of thicker ice along the tunnel-like walls narrow the passageway further.</description>
    <position x="360" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="ice northwest" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>Shards of ice litter the floor and crunch into tiny crystals under foot.  A few strands of matted hair are half frozen into the floor.  Puddles of water covered in a frigid glaze mask what lies beneath, increasing the challenge of choosing safe footing.  The slick walls act like mirrors, reflecting what may not be there.</description>
    <position x="380" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="ice northeast" hidden="True" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="east" move="ice east" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>Winds come from all directions, sighing noisily as they change course inside the cavern.  Capriciously spewed snowflakes and ice crystals swirl through the holes in the floors and whip around the glacial impediments.  Situated in their path, one polished pillar of ice reflects ghost passages, further confusing movement.</description>
    <position x="420" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="ice southwest" hidden="True" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>Already precarious, travel through this section is complicated by a gaping hole in the dead center of the floor.  A ragged ledge of frozen ice to the east appears solid enough to withstand some weight, enabling passage to another area over a corner of the precipice.</description>
    <position x="380" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="ice north" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="east" move="ice east" hidden="True" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>The ceiling is caked with ice that has seeped through the mountain into this cavern.  Several varied and unusual frozen sculptures appear to be the result of a fast defrost and a slow refreeze.  The solid wall directly ahead is coated in a frozen glaze that resembles a fast flowing vertical river.</description>
    <description>The ceiling is caked with ice that has seeped through the mountain into this cavern.  Several varied and unusual frozen sculptures appear to be the result of a fast defrost and a slow refreeze.  The solid wall directly ahead is coated in a frozen glaze that resembles a fast flowing vertical river.  </description>
    <position x="380" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="ice east" destination="256" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="Himineldar Shel, Ice Cavern">
    <description>Thick frozen spires jut up from the slick floor, never quite meeting those that hang down from the roof of the cavern but coming close enough to force a change of direction.  Gaping holes in the cave floor plunge into inky depths below the frost line causing passage through the area to be slow and careful.  In some spots, newly formed ice tentatively creeps over old holes, but counting on its ability to hold weight is for the foolhardy.</description>
    <position x="400" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="ice south" hidden="True" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Foyer" note="Momma's Bed and Breakfast">
    <description>This large foyer looks the same as when it was used as a home by the family.  A small table holding a wide ledger that is propped open sits beside a high-backed bench.  Beside the door is a basket half-filled with muddy shoes and boots.  Through a darkened doorway, stairs leading downwards can be seen.  Large entries to the east and west lead into the actual living quarters.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go front door" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" destination="263" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Parlor">
    <description>Low ceilings and darkened wall panels in this room make candles necessary throughout the night and day.  Everything is very tidy right down to the pine floor that has recently been swept.  Mismatched armchairs and stools have been arranged in an attempt to provide private seating areas.  Hung in a place of honor over the mantel of the fieldstone fireplace is a broken axe handle.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Hallway">
    <description>A brown runner goes the length of the hallway.  Embroidered flowers in plain pine frames are mounted on the walls between the doorframes.  Small tables sit to the right of the doors, a water pitcher and chamberpot resting on a lace doily atop each one.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark door" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cherrywood door" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Dining Room" note="Dining Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Filling most of the room, a thick pine dining table with benches on each length always has place settings.  Made from cast iron, a stove in the corner has a large pot simmering on the back.  Swinging doors at the end of the room must lead to the kitchen, evidenced by the wear and tear on the floor.  A pine sideboard has been pushed into the corner opposite the stove.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go swinging door" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, The Kitchen" note="Kitchen">
    <description>Overly large, the stove has pots bubbling away on top and the smell of fresh baked bread fills the air.  A pie safe with punched tin doors faces a long counter piled high with cleaned plates.  Sitting next to the back door, a wood bin is filled to the top with roughly split logs.  Bundles of fresh herbs hang to dry from the low rafters, adding to the odors of the constant cooking.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go swinging door" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go back door" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Back Yard">
    <description>A glow through the back door shows rocking chairs that have been set up under the extended eaves off the back of the house.  From the darkness, the occasional squawk of a chicken alarmed by something in the night can be heard.  The shape of a well can be seen in the middle of the yard.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go back door" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Momma's Room">
    <description>What was clearly once a root cellar from the lingering earthly odor is now a small bedroom.  Pristine in its tidiness, the room is uncluttered by anything fancy.  Spartan to an extreme, a sleigh bed with a faded quilt and a pine dresser are the only pieces of furniture.  A small woven rug sits beside the bed where Momma must swing her feet out every morning.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Side Room">
    <description>Neatly mended lace curtains have been pulled closed.  A soft blue quilt has been drawn up over the pillow on the single bed.  Polished pine, used in the building of the dresser and nightstand, matches the bed's wood.  The floor is immaculate and the white rag rug has been well beaten.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark door" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Dormitory">
    <description>This room was clearly added onto the home in later years as evidenced by the newer wall panels and floor.  What must have been the master bedroom has been turned into a dormitory of bunk beds with little room between them to put anything.  A locker sits at the end of each row, a neatly folded towel and cloth on the top of each one.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Momma's Bed and Breakfast, Guest Room">
    <description>A sparkling white goose-down comforter and soft, plush pillows with embroidered slips adorn this high post bed.  Fresh flowers in a porcelain vase sit upon a dressing table.  Finishing off the furnishings of this room is an armoire with carving on the doors that almost seems out of place with the rest of the inn.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cherrywood door" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="The Chapel of Raven's Point" note="Chapel of Raven's Point|Altar">
    <description>In stark contrast to the hovels that fill the walls of Raven's Point, the interior of the chapel is adorned with rare gems and metals gathered from the four corners of Forfedhdar.  A massive raven, carved from black stone streaked with glittering veins of gold, dominates the rear of the church, its talons curling tightly around the edges of the altar and holding it aloft.  Halos of lingering incense hover above the burning candles that line the foot of the exterior walls, fending off the pressing darkness.</description>
    <description>In stark contrast to the hovels that fill the walls of Raven's Point, the interior of the chapel is adorned with rare gems and metals gathered from the four corners of Forfedhdar.  A massive raven carved from black stone streaked with glittering veins of gold, dominates the rear of the church, its talons curling tightly around the edges of the altar and holding it aloft.  Halos of lingering incense hover above the burning candles that line the foot of the exterior walls, fending off the pressing darkness.</description>
    <position x="400" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mikkhalbamar archway" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Seord Kerwaith, Gear Gate" note="Map69_Shard_West_Gate.xml|Gear Gate">
    <description>Rough-cut logs with sharpened peaks reach across the rough stone walls to block further passage though the pass to the north.  Thick curls of black smoke spiral into the sky from beyond the makeshift walls of the outpost, the air filled with the pungent aroma of blood sausage and smoking cedar.  In the direct center of the fortification, a massive gear gate has been sandwiched between the sharpened log walls, reaching across the valley to slide seamlessly into the black rock walls of the valley.</description>
    <position x="420" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gear gate" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="The Raven's Nest, Commander's Office" note="Commander's Office|General Bazrid|Bazrid">
    <description>The elongated office has been hung with numerous parchment maps displaying the treacherous roadways of the Seord Kerwaith, but drawn and painted from various angles and declinations.  A roaring fireplace fills the office with its warming glow, assisted by several braziers hung along the walls.  A golden eagle rests on a scratched stand resting next the commander's desk, blinking lazily as it casually observes the area with its dull orange eyes.</description>
    <position x="460" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mikkhalbamar door" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Seord Kerwaith, A High Ledge">
    <description>From this vantage point, high above the trail below, the view would be spectacular -- if only the constantly wind-whipped snow would clear long enough to allow a good look.  The mountain rises with a sheer slope, curving slightly overhead so that this ledge is somewhat protected, but also preventing any possible climb further.  The ledge itself is wide enough for comfort standing, but not so wide that one is tempted to remain for any length of time.</description>
    <position x="20" y="510" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crumbling cliff" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Seord Kerwaith, A Soaring Precipice">
    <description>Rising high above the valley, the narrow ledge terminates at the top of the sheer cliff face.  The vertical drop from the precipice is obscured by wind-blown clouds of icy particles.  Although partially hidden by drifting clouds of snow and ice, a distant tower of grim black stone rises between two mountain peaks.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="550" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ice-covered ledge" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Smoky Bandit's, Hideaway">
    <description>Stacks of crates are piled high in this small underground room, though it's clear that this cellar is meant for more than just storage.  A rack of weapons with a battered shield resting against it sits near a blazing torch, and close by is a small shelf stacked with preserved foodstuffs.  In the far corner is a heap of thick fur blankets ready to defend against the cold.  A sturdy ladder leads up to a trapdoor in the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="440" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy ladder" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <label text="To Ilaya Taipa">
    <position x="130" y="-80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hibarnhvidar">
    <position x="-370" y="-60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Mountain Giants">
    <position x="280" y="-120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Malodorous Buccas, Stone-throwing Imps">
    <position x="-160" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Young Cave Trolls">
    <position x="-220" y="290" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Albino Cave Fish">
    <position x="-60" y="290" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Retch Fiends">
    <position x="60" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Frost Angiswaerd">
    <position x="320" y="-30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Raven's Point">
    <position x="390" y="630" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Frostweyr Bears">
    <position x="-45" y="685" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Jeol Moradu">
    <position x="190" y="610" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Icy Road">
    <position x="190" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ice Cavern">
    <position x="360" y="50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Momma's Inn">
    <position x="-60" y="-100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="To Shard West Gate">
    <position x="350" y="560" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bank">
    <position x="346" y="765" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Raven's Nest">
    <position x="430" y="784" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gems">
    <position x="463" y="662" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bundles">
    <position x="411" y="662" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Frost Trolls">
    <position x="-30" y="615" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>