<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Moon Mage Guild NTR" id="14d">
  <node id="1" name="North Road, Plains" note="Map7c_NTR_Part2.xml">
    <description>Small weeds and tufts of grass grow right up to the road's edge, almost obscuring the faint traces of a trail heading westward.  The trail appears to head towards the volcanoes, but you can see no signs that anyone has used it for quite a while.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>The evening sky draws her cloak over the rocky path, iridescent bits of cooled lava glittering like stars caught in the earth.  Tiny motes of dust swirl as mottled light from the sky catches them in mid-air.</description>
    <position x="20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>Rocks are pushed to one side of the road to make a slender path through debris.  It looks scarcely traveled, the way lined by sparse vegetation.</description>
    <position x="0" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>Patterns of leaves and paw prints are barely visible in the walls of stone nearby.  The fossilized remains are an eerie reminder of the life trapped forever within the ash.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>The evening smiles down on a small flower lingering near the road side.  It appears withered and dying at first glance, but as the night unfolds, so does a pure white snowblossom - one spot of beauty within a realm of decay and death.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>Splintered wagon wheels lie alongside a corroding iron frame.  It appears as if a Trader ran into some difficulty -- difficulty he was unable to recover from.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>A dried watering hole stands forlorn amidst the skeletons of animals large and small.  All scraps of flesh have been worn or torn away leaving only the dusty ivory bone beneath.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>Darkness trails over the shadows of both volcanoes - the Greater and Lesser Fists.  Standing tall and proud, they serve as silent sentinels beneath the night's unsleeping eye.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>Coarse gravel lines the earth, a bed of sharp stones, like jagged teeth peering out of the earth.  Ready to pierce the foot of the unwary traveler, they stand sparkling against the spartan dirt.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Lava Flow, Rocky Path">
    <description>Fronds of wilting palm trees scatter on the ground, the wind blowing them across the loose dirt.  Trunks and stalks lie half-buried by ash and crumbling stone.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Lava Flow, Standing Stones">
    <description>Tall stones rise in small circular patterns, their forms eroded by wind and water both.  The designs they held have long since faded into invisibility, their meaning now undecipherable.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Lava Flow, Standing Stones">
    <description>The dark side of evening seems to linger here, languidly basking over the ruins as if gloating.  The shadows seem to tug and pull at the fallen buildings, as if taunting them, whispering seeds of unrest to long-dead spirits.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Lava Flow, Standing Stones">
    <description>The ancient frieze of a tall arch is slowly crumbling to dust, paint and tile flaking off.  Burn marks streak the mural, obscuring what images were once there.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Lava Flow, Path of Thorns">
    <description>Dried and cracking brambles wrapped around a wrought iron fence line the road.  Flanking the dusky earth, the brackish thorns peek out from withering branches, daring to jab and stab at passers by.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Lava Flow, Path of Thorns">
    <description>A heart-shaped wrought iron sculpture is overgrown, writhing vines coiled around it.  The thick spike-like thorns appear to pierce the center, the sharp points gleaming with moisture.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Lava Flow, Path of Thorns">
    <description>A tangled mass of thorny bushes guard the roadside, making passage beyond the slender path impossible.  Small birds find ways to hide unscathed amidst the brambles, tiny forms huddled inside small cathedrals of withering vines.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Lava Flow, Path of Thorns">
    <description>The masses of thorny growths thin to the north.  Wrought iron sculptures where vines of roses once grew stand bare, metal corroding and long untended.  The eerie shapes stand like hollow souls over the dead ash-covered earth below.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Lava Flow, Path of Jade">
    <description>Flecks of shattered jade lie strewn amidst the rough gravel of the road.  Images etched into the flat panels of rock that were once a busy street are now worn to nothingness, their patterns long forgotten.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Lava Flow, Path of Jade">
    <description>Slender jade obelisks mottled with dust and ash stand guard over the narrow road.  The way is clear, footprints from recent travel constantly being worn over one another in the soft earth below.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Lava Flow, Path of Jade">
    <description>An ornate jade plant rests amidst a circle of pale white stones.  Each leaf is delicately carved from the blushing green stone.  Despite being covered in filth, it remains a beautiful work of art.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Lava Flow, Path of Jade">
    <description>An elaborate golden stand is firmly bolted to the stone of the road.  Remnants of a jade-green glass sphere lie in sharp slivers on the surrounding grass.  Bits of coarse vegetation grow between the pieces of glass.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Lava Flow, Path of Jade">
    <description>Prickly, spine-covered bushes grow close to the ground.  Ripe red fruit tauntingly dangles from behind long, sharp thorns.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Lava Flow, Wall of Swords">
    <description>A tall barrier lines each side of the road, bladed edges topping the polished wooden beams that compose the wall.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Lava Flow, Wall of Swords">
    <description>Wooden panels in the fence are carved into the jagged images of swords and weapons from lands far and near.  The barbed metal partitions holding them together make touching the wall a most unpleasant thought.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Lava Flow, Wall of Swords">
    <description>The volcano of the Lesser Fist looms over the barricade.  It ominously shadows all below it.  A glimpse of something reflective glints from near the maw of the fortress.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Lava Flow, Way of Swords">
    <description>Ashes and dust coat the stone wall, covering the rock with a granulated layer of grey that abates only near an inset bronze plaque.  A sparkling crystal hand is attached over the polished metal, also clear of the choking dust.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Lava Flow, Esouvar's Rest">
    <description>The signs of ancient battle mark the area.  A tall statue, at least thirty feet in height, towers far above the parched landscape.  Eyes of faceted blue crystal sparkle brightly from the ash-streaked marble face.</description>
    <position x="-400" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Lava Flow, Esouvar's Rest">
    <description>A red-veined marble fountain proudly shimmers with droplets of clear, cool water.  Small flameroses grow up its sides, their tender green tendrils bearing small jade-green leaves that perfume the air with a heady scent.</description>
    <position x="-420" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Lava Flow, Garden of Ash">
    <description>Once a lovely garden, little remains of its original beauty.  Recent plantings line the roadside, clippings and trees freshly cultivated in an attempt to renew the land.</description>
    <position x="-440" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Lava Flow, Garden of Ash">
    <description>The soft blue-white blossoms of a moonflower bush open their luminous faces to the night sky.</description>
    <position x="-460" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Lava Flow, Garden of Ash">
    <description>The long shadow of the Lesser Fist of Heaven dominates the small garden.  The formidable fortress to the west rises high above the ground below, with the silhouette of the Greater Fist behind it towering yet farther into the reaches of the sky.</description>
    <position x="-480" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Lava Path, Dwindling Way">
    <description>A volcano lies to the west.  Fortified and well-guarded, it serves as the Fortress of the Crystal Hand.  The dark path, made from hardened lava, is streaked with veins of polished obsidian that glisten with a dull satin sheen.</description>
    <position x="-500" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Lava Path, The Stone Stairway">
    <description>A large stone staircase winds its way down the front of the volcano, carved into the face of the rock.  A glimmering crystal formation to the west seems to catch the scarce light, glowing with a scintillating aura.</description>
    <position x="-520" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Lava Forge, Lobby" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dust drifts through the archway over the cooled lava floor and piles in the corners of the stone building.  A bored Human attendant relaxes on a stool near a leather curtain that closes off the rest of the forge.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Outside the Fortress, Obsidian Doors">
    <description>Shadows of night embrace the stalwart doors leading into the fortress.  The dark obsidian panels glisten with the light of the crystal hand set into the volcanic rock above them, their spiraling patterns and angular runes shimmering in the sparse illumination.  A spartan staircase travels down the face of the stone walls.</description>
    <position x="-520" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Inside the Fortress, Atrium">
    <description>The night sky peeks through the mouth of the volcano, the crystal dome sparkling far above.  A quiet settles over the atrium, a serene calmness that drifts through the air and the soul.</description>
    <position x="-500" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Inside the Fortress, Atrium">
    <description>The coolness of evening drapes itself around the atrium and mottled shadows are cast over a tall marble statue.  Burning incense drifts through the air, its heady scent almost dizzying.</description>
    <position x="-500" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Inside the Fortress, Stone Garden">
    <description>Small iridescent grey rocks carpet the rough lava floor.  They are meticulously raked into ornate spiraling patterns.  A slender obsidian walkway winds geometrically through the garden, dividing the crushed stone into abstract triangular shapes.</description>
    <position x="-520" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Inside the Fortress, Stone Garden">
    <description>A dark walkway of obsidian frames the field of grey crushed stone at the center of the room.  Monks wander along the path, heads bowed in quiet contemplation.</description>
    <position x="-540" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Inside the Fortress, Meditation Room">
    <description>The walls and ceiling are featureless grey rock with a smooth polished surface.  Dark linen pillows, flat and hard to the touch, are placed around the area.  A small censer lets the potent scent of sweet incense drift lazily about.</description>
    <position x="-520" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Inside the Fortress, Weapon Salle">
    <description>Racks upon racks of weapons line the walls, most staves or keen-edged spears.  Some blades, well-polished and edged, gleam from among their wooden, practice counterparts.  The floor is clean and well-kept, the signs of monks recently training lingering about.</description>
    <position x="-480" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Inside the Fortress, Rough Stairway">
    <description>A tall stairway carved into the rock of the volcano winds its way precariously upwards, leading to a slender catwalk far above.  It appears impossibly steep, but several monks ascend the way with no problem.</description>
    <position x="-460" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="On the Catwalk">
    <description>The dark evening blankets the slender catwalk masking its treacherous positioning as it stretches most precariously over a vast expanse of darkness.</description>
    <position x="-460" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="On the Catwalk, Above the Foyer">
    <description>The heavenly bodies dance and spiral, taunting the mortal hand to step from the catwalk just an inch closer.  The night sky descends over the crystal dome and through it, stars surrounding you, close enough to seemingly touch them.</description>
    <position x="-480" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Platform's Edge, Seat of the Guildmaster" note="Moon Mage Guildleader Tiv" color="#80FF00">
    <description>A large circular stone platform rests suspended in mid-air over the center of the volcano.  The precarious catwalk extends to its edge.</description>
    <position x="-500" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Inside the Fortress, Guild Library">
    <description>Monks kneel and sit on the charcoal gunny pillows scattered about the room.  In hushed whispers, they read and debate combative and mystical theory alike.  Glowing orbs of polished crystal illuminate the room, providing a gentle light for study and the gaining of wisdom.</description>
    <position x="-460" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Library, Archive Room">
    <description>The silence of the archives is broken only by the soft sound of scratching pens as monks work copying ancient texts that have begun to decay.  Files, treatises and endless scrolls of parchment line the bookcases to aid visitors in their researches.</description>
    <position x="-440" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Archive Room, Museum Foyer">
    <description>The foyer to the Guild museum is sparsely decorated.  Featureless walls of polished lava rise up to the crystal dome, the edge of the catwalk barely in sight.  A winding spiral staircase descends into the stronghold below.</description>
    <position x="-420" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hallway Foyer">
    <description>An elegant staircase made from polished stone spirals upwards to the main level.  A passage north leads to a series of catacombs carved into the base of the volcano.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>The chambers of the museum appear to be carved from the basalt rock of the volcano.  A dark indigo silk runner lines the cold stone of the floor.  Silver sconces embracing small orbs of glowing tzgaa line the walls.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>A large glass panel flanks the wall, parchment pages held securely in place behind the protective display.  A small brass plaque is tacked to the wall beneath it.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>A large contraption, composed of many gears and glassine parts, focuses one thick crystal lens over an almost invisible specimen.  A sliver of something almost imperceptably small glitters beneath.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>This room is plain and spartan, containing only an enclosed glass case bearing a treasure from ancient days.  Even the obsidian walls are featureless, the black rock smooth and polished.  A silverwillow sign hangs from delicate chains over the display.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>Swaths of velvet lie draped over this exhibit, one curtain drawn back to reveal a cracked oval mirror.  Ropes cordon off the display.  Most people lower their eyes as they pass, not daring to look, nervously shuffling onward.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Beneath the Fortress, Promenade">
    <description>Tapestries and paintings from various provinces of Elanthia cover the walls in this area.  Sculptures and other remnants from past civilizations attest to their age.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>A bold bright blue banner hangs above this exhibit.  Older monks pass by, nodding and winking at each other, the occasional one bowing reverently towards the large painting on display.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Beneath the Fortress, Hall of Relics">
    <description>Three panels of cloth hang from the walls depicting various scenes from the Guild's past.  One notable portrayal is that of Katzel's execution.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <label text="NTR Part 2">
    <position x="-50" y="-60" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>