<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Dirge" id="13">
  <node id="1" name="Lava Fields, Narrow Trace">
    <description>The barest hint of a path undulates along the irregular crests of frozen rills of lava.  Here and there, the stump of a tree, burned and dead, pokes above the bleak landscape but does little to break the monotony of the lifeless scene.  The eerie desolation eats into your spirit and fills your mind with visions of death, while endless chill shadows and unnamed fears caper and dance at the edge of your senses.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Lava Fields, Narrow Trace">
    <description>Faint markings etched into irregular boulders are your only guide in this trackless waste.  Static waves of rock rise high on either side, looking like a black ocean locked into an eternity of timeless rigidity.  Once this solid waste flowed with a thick and sullen life of its own, burning and destroying all before it.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow trail" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Lava Fields, Narrow Trace">
    <description>To the west, broken layers of lava and basalt rise in irregular piles.  To the east and north, a narrow plane opens out between steep mountain shoulders.  The black tide of volcanic destruction and molten has buried all that once was here and only a thick layer of ash remains, dancing in the erratic winds to give even a hint of life.  Off to the extreme north, you can make out a narrow valley.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Lava Fields">
    <description>Acres of ruined farmlands stretch out on either side of the road here.  Dead and buried, they lie under ragged sheets of once-molten rock now chill and barren.  Flows of magma, once white hot and liquid, cover the road in places.  A stinging grit rides the wind, the only crop now grown in this sere and lifeless waste.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crater" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Lava Fields">
    <description>The black stone hereabouts blends into the black night and you worry you may lose track of the shallow path labouriously carved into the unyielding rock.  Something white gleams faintly near your feet.</description>
    <description>Rising shoulder high to a tall human, the magma forms rough walls that block the breezes.  The air smells of flinty dust and your feet kick up small clouds with each pace.  Someone has hacked a narrow path through the hard rock with great labor.  To one side, a smooth white protrusion rises from the lava.  It forms a sharp contrast to the drear and dark colors that abound in this deathscape.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Lava Fields, Ruins" note="sanrisi tree">
    <description>Endless fields of magma stretch out to the surrounding mountains.  Nearby, the charred beams of a ruined farmhouse still erupt from the uneven landscape, as if striving mutely to free themselves from their cold tomb of lifeless stone.  A few scraggly bushes have found a precarious perch in pockets of wind-blown soil but they are grey and sickly.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ruined farmhouse" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Lava Fields, Ruins">
    <description>Skirting a ruined farmhouse, you pass among boulders and mounds of ash.  Plumes of steam rise from the mounds and you smell a sulfur stink that makes your eyes water.  Everything is coated in a fine yellow dust.  To the west, the mountains run close together to form a narrow valley.  A few thin streams of smoke or vapor show pale grey against the black rock that surrounds it.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Lava Fields, Valley" note="RTZ11|RT-D-K" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Fields of broken lava give way to a relatively open valley tucked between two gigantic rock outcrops.  Almost mountains in themselves, the outcrops rise steeply from the valley floor.  Nestled between them sits a small, drab-looking town.  Buildings made of the same black rock as the mountains straggle across the tiny valley and back into the narrowing gorge behind it.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Volcanic Ruins, Dirge" note="RTZ12|RT-D-HF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Cinders and debris crunch beneath your feet as a cold wind stirs the ashes into small dust devils that dance about you in a curiously mocking way.  To the north, twin volcanic cones loom high into the sky.  The small town tucked between their towering masses seems to huddle in on itself.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Outside Dirge Town">
    <description>The road beneath your feet was once well paved but now shows the marks of fire and time.  The stones were blackened and scorched by some great heat, warping some and breaking others.  There is a heavy grey ash everywhere that blows in your face and eyes.  Blocking the road north, a high stone wall guards a small group of buildings nestled between the volcanoes.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Dirge, Outside Gate" note="Gate|Kraelyst start point|travel start point" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>A road stops here at a ruined gate of charred and splintered wood.  Beyond it lies a small town of uniformly dark colors huddled beneath the towering volcanic heights.  To one side, a compact stone building stands watch over the infrequent traveller and the gate.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ruined gate" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road">
    <description>Among the cinders and ash, someone has raked a path leading along the outside of the walls.  Running from the town gate to a small hill to the west, the path wanders through a landscape even bleaker and emptier than that of the town itself.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road" note="RTZ13|RT-D-XNE" color="#C2B280">
    <description>A narrow path of relatively smooth cinders and crushed stone ambles aimlessly among dead grey ash-heaps and piles of stone that once were houses.  To the west and a bit north, a small hill rises, bleached white by the sun and the foul air until it resembles an exposed skull left unburied among the ruins.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road">
    <description>A narrow lane of crushed rock and cinders kept raked by unknown hands passes among heaped ruins of stone.  Here and there, fragments of bone mingled among the rubble gleam whitely.  The air is still and there is a bitter tang to it that leaves you unsatisfied with the act of breathing.  It feels as if all vitality has been sucked out of the world, leaving only shades of grey and emptiness.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entrance" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road">
    <description>Jumbled rows of stone slabs, many stacked into untidy piles, catch your eye.  You wonder as to their purpose as you pass among them along this dead path of cinders.  Mixed among them are heaps of broken bones in no particular order or pattern that you can discern.  The land here is dead beyond your imaginings, as if life had never existed and you yourself were but some vague phantasm hovering above a landscape that was never meant to be.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road South">
    <description>Untidy piles of ruined headstones line both sides of this stony path.  A building of dark grey stone rises to the south.  Grit and dust grate beneath your feet and even between your teeth.  Dry as flint, it rises in clouds and settles over everything.  A chill wind moans between the broken stones and flings more grit into the heavy air.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road South">
    <description>Southward, a small building of grey stone surmounted by a broken chimney broods over mounds of dirty white ash.  The remains of a shattered wall surround it with heaps of rubble, topped here and there by grinning skulls set in ragged rows.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Dirge, Crematorium Building">
    <description>Before you is a low, windowless building, squat and ugly, with heavy walls that resemble a fortress more than anything else.  The stub of a ruined chimney rises from the center, a broken finger aimed skyward.  Heaps of brick and stone lie tumbled all about from its fall.  A low fence of some dirty grey stone surrounds the edifice.  Here and there, grinning skulls colored a dingy yellow by the sulfur-laden airs, leer at each other in some private amusement.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low building" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Crematorium, Foyer">
    <description>The stench of burning hangs in the air, despite the obvious fact that this place does not seem to have been used for its intended function in years.  Faded velvet draperies cover tatters of some once-rich wallpaper.  Dust and ash are thick on every surface, though there are well-worn paths in the dust.  A pile of broken and crushed wood and metal fragments are heaped in a corner where the dust seems most disturbed.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Crematorium, Retort Chamber">
    <description>A huge iron and stone construction, large enough to hold several Gor'Tog rises up to the ceiling.  Heavy iron doors hang upon rusted hinges in front of an opening darker than the lowest pit of perdition.  The aura of death emanates from every nook and crevice in this place of flame and destruction.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doors" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Crematorium, Workroom">
    <description>Tucked behind the massive retort, this was once the workroom and storage area.  A few sacks of coal, now split open and scattered, still remain.  A rusted and broken shovel rests beneath a massive pile of ash and bone fragments that seem strangely fresh and undisturbed by the passage of time.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Dirge, Ash Yard">
    <description>Mounds of ash and piles of weathered bone are heaped in untidy rows.  In the time of the volcano, the dead came faster than they could be properly disposed of, and their remains now blow in the wind and grate beneath your feet.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crematorium" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Dirge, Ash Yard">
    <description>What began as a graveyard rubbish dump has become a general garbage site for all the Dirge citizenry.  A vast quantity of unsightly debris stretches as far as the eye can see in squalid, ash-covered heaps.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Dirge, Ash Yard">
    <description>There are no signs of life in this area, just shifting hills of grey, desiccated bones, deserted even by the city rats.  Tattered bits of clothing wave futilely in the breeze.  Even the stench of rotting flesh is gone, leaving behind only a dust that is as dry and empty as death itself.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Dirge, Dead Garden">
    <description>Small stones once neatly divided this town garden into several colorful patches of herbs and vegetables.  Now the stones lie jumbled about.  The ground is covered with a permanant layer of suffocating ash.  It gets in the lungs, on the clothes.  It clogs the eyes.  Only when it rains does the bombardment of airborne ash cease.  Then it turns into a viscous river of oozing grey mud underfoot.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Dirge, Dead Garden">
    <description>The cracked earth is pockmarked here by large, round holes.  Each bears a tightly closed, barely visible black blossom, which remains strangely unmolested as chittering scorpions scurry back and forth.</description>
    <description>The ground is sere and broken here.  Cordlike vines poke out of large holes, each bearing a heavy black blossom that exudes the odor of rotten meat.  You see a small toad clasped inside one tightly closed blossom, its back legs kicking frantically.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Dirge, Dead Garden">
    <description>Death has not grown this garden.  Death is a void, but he sent his dog, Corruption, to breathe upon it.  The result is a vile jungle of suety weeds covered by green pustules.  The slightest movement of air causes some pustules to break, releasing a yellow ichor and fetid smell that fills the area.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Dirge, Hangman's Road">
    <description>Bones, piles of bones, heaps of bones, spill out across the cinder path.  Someone has stacked a hundred or more skulls into a gruesome pyramid to one side, each bony jaw grinning at you in mockery of life.  Slabs of stone with faintly etched lettering give a clue to the nature of this bizarre place.  The town cemetary it seems, has had as unquiet a time as the town itself.  Even death is without peace in this tormented land.  To the northwest, a small hill of bare rock rises.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Dirge, Gibbet Hill">
    <description>Here, at the base of a bare stone hill, a ruined cemetery sprawls in untidy heaps.  Bones and stones mingle together and grinning skulls perch on marble slabs, leering at you grimly.  The remains of the town cemetery it seems, ruined and scattered, holy ground no longer once fire and pain came to dwell.  Above the unliving scene, the stark white hill glowers, keeping its own secrets.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone hill" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Dirge, Gibbet Hill">
    <description>You pass gingerly among the hanging bones and swaying masses of rotted flesh.  Many stand empty, their occupants having long since crumbled away, or worse.  To judge from the splintered and gnawed bones beneath one partially dismembered corpse, few of the dear departed have been allowed to rest in peace.  A narrow path winds in two directions around the hill's middle.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Dirge, Gibbet Hill">
    <description>You stumble among the remains of a sickening feast.  A firepit has been dug and someone was roasting something unwholesome here recently.  A broken skull with glistening bits of brain remaining in it hints at the sort of meal you have interrupted.  Around you, dozens of gibbets hold their gruesome vigil.  A chill wind raises the hair on your neck as a bit of rock rattles down towards you from above.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Dirge, Gibbet Hill">
    <description>A path here leads to the barren summit of this bizarre hill.  Neatly arrayed along both sides, stand rows of gibbets, each with its unliving ornament.  One corpse nearest you was hanged with one arm nailed stiffly outwards across a post, its dead hand urging you upwards.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark burrow" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Dirge, Gibbet Hill" note="Gibbet Hill|Fake Necromancer Guild|Gallows">
    <description>The hillcrest here once served the town in its more civilized days as a place for punishments and public executions.  The remains of a wooden gallows still rise above you, and around the rim of the hill stand several wooden stocks.  Each stock now holds a grinning mummified body, and surmounting the gallows, dangling from a silken noose, is a corpse arrayed in white linen robes.  Even in death, there is a suggestion of madness and power about this figure.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Gibbett Hill, Ur's Rest">
    <description>Assorted roots and loose rock adorn the fetid walls which frame this deeply-spiraling path beneath the hill.  Tiny things creep, occasionally bite, and make incredible nuisances of themselves as they swarm to taste the warm flesh which has entered their darkened abode.  A tentative shimmer of light teases the lower edge of the passageway, never really promising to remain.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Gibbett Hill, Ur's Rest" note="Ur's Rest|Melcorek">
    <description>Hundreds of lit tapers flicker from niches cut deep in the walls of this cavernous lair.  Pinpoints of light dance and waver, forcing the darkness between them into ominous shapes that dodge and strike across the moistened, blackened floor.  A confusion of footprints in the dirt at the center of the pit speaks of recent use, of stepping patterns rehearsed repeatedly in the pursuit of perfection.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Dirge, Gibbet Hill">
    <description>A dozen gibbets surround you, their corpses even more puzzling than they are gruesome.  Perhaps the town went mad in times past, for here they have executed numerous household and domestic animals.  The sight of half-mummified dogs and goats and other animals seems beyond explanation or reason.  The sight of recent feasting among them seems beyond comprehension.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Dirge, Gateway Road" note="Dirge">
    <description>You stand next to the ruins of the Town gate.  Little traffic disturbs the thick coat of grey dust that seems to be everywhere.  The town is tucked here between the cold peaks of the volcanoes and the outer wall of dull black stone.  To one side, a building still shows evidence of habitation and a sign painted with a large keg indicates that perhaps a drink or two may be had even in this desolation.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dingy stables" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go inn" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ruined gate" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Dirge, Crossroads">
    <description>A small east-west road crosses the larger one leading further into town.  Known as Merchant's Row, the few shops the town boasts can be found along its dusty length.  To the west, a small bit of greenery brightens an otherwise dull black landscape.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go travellers bank" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Dirge, Merchant's Row West">
    <description>The road here passes between a tiny shop on one side and a large stone building built against the town wall on the south side.  Farther west, the land rises sharply and you can make out some trees on a tall outcrop of stone.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny shop" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Dirge, Merchant's Row West">
    <description>The road ends here at the base of a steep pile of rocks leading up to a wide outcrop of the volcanic cone above.  The sounds of a hammer ringing on an anvil come from a large and well-kept stone building to the north.  A sign hangs on a polished brass rod above the shop.  The air is rich with the smell of heated iron and the tang of oil.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb pile rocks" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Dirge, Gateway Road North">
    <description>Leading away from the gate and into the center of town, this stretch of road passes between a shop and one side of the Town Hall.  The bleak stone walls reflect the sound of your footsteps making you feel as if you were being followed with every move you make.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-253" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shop" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Dirge, Town Square South" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The road here passes a row of worn but still-neat houses.  Small but with some attempt at keeping them tidy, they look less bleak than other parts of town.  One house has even managed to keep some flowers growing despite the dust and dryness.</description>
    <position x="93" y="-273" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carousel square" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Dirge, Town Square West" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The road runs northeast here, following the narrowing line of the mountain as it hems in the town.  A few houses are scattered here facing the central Square, but room is left for a large cave entrance cut into the rock face.</description>
    <position x="73" y="-293" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cave entrance" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town square" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Dirge, Town Square South" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Gateway Road widens out here into the small Town Square.  The few houses the town boasts front along it as does Town Hall.  A tired fountain juts up from the center of the dusty square and a curiously shaped pyramidal structure rises north of it.  A pair of unwashed boys play a dispirited game of catch among the weeds and dirt of the once green Common.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-273" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town square" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Dirge, Town Square East">
    <description>A low, squat building containing the Town Hall fronts on this side of the square.  The narrowing valley hems in the town to the northeast with almost sheer walls rising steeply to unclimbable heights.  Faded greenery from the town's small park merges into the black dust of the road with no perceptible margin.</description>
    <position x="133" y="-273" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ash-coated tent" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town hall" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town square" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Dirge, Town Square North">
    <description>The entire town narrows here, almost to a point.  This gives an odd emphasis to the peculiar pyramid shape that stands at the northern end of the town.  The building is not all that tall but it commands attention nonetheless.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-313" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town square" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Dirge, Temple of the Volcano" note="Temple of the Volcano">
    <description>You are standing before the outer gate of the town's only temple.  The entire building, walls, paving and roof, is formed from dull black rock.  Built in a rough pyramid form, it was created when the former Temple on this spot was incinerated by one of the larger eruptions in the recent past.  Few in this town come here except when the fire mountains are troubled and the earth trembles.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-333" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go temple gates" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Dirge, Town Square" note="Town Square">
    <description>The remains of a once-green central square are now sere and burned.  Here and there, paths of grass struggle to grow among the ashes and cinders that crunch underfoot.  In the center of the square, a small fountain still produces a trickle of water and offers a small spot of greenery from some bushes that have somehow survived.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-293" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Dirge, Merchant's Row East">
    <description>East of the town's main crossroads, the lane passes along the narrow, windowless flank of the Darkstone Inn.  A shop with heavily curtained windows stands to the north, while farther east, you can hear the whinnying of horses.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained shop" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Dirge, Merchant's Row East">
    <description>You pass by a shop made of the inevitable dark stone used hereabouts.  One odd feature of the store is the doorway, which appears to have once been the door of a rather large and sturdy vault.  Made of heavy black iron, it stands open now but still looks quite serviceable.  Eastwards, you can see the road ending at the base of one of the volcanic hills.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny shop" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Dirge, Merchant's Row East">
    <description>The road ends here with a small store and the entrance to the town livery stables.  The outer wall curves in to meet the flank of the mountain but some of it has collapsed into a huge pile of unstable-looking rubble.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small store" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go livery stables" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small home" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Dirge, Livery Stables" note="Livery Stables|Stables">
    <description>The livery stables are as run-down as the rest of the town.  The stable building has partly collapsed and the few horses still to be found are corralled by makeshift fencing salvaged from the ruined stables.  The few stalls left standing indoors are being used to store hay and additional animal fodder to keep it dry.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Dirge, Militia Barracks" note="Barracks|Militia Barracks">
    <description>Once the barracks for the local militia, the building has been taken over by ruffians who work for the town Boss.  This was the assembly room, now used mostly to store pilfered gear and a motley assortment of chests and boxes, mostly broken open and rifled.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Dirge, Barracks Mess-hall">
    <description>The mess-hall and dining room for the militia, the place now shows little sign of use.  The fireplace is cold and bare of ashes and the furniture is gone, leaving only some shelves and empty food lockers.</description>
    <position x="30" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Dirge, Barracks Dormitory">
    <description>This large upper room has only narrow windows looking out.  Really more arrow slits than windows, this was obviously meant to be a redoubt in case of attack.  In safer times it also served as the dormitory for those townsfolk who stood guard.  Someone still uses the place for there are several cots with rumpled and dirty bedding piled upon them.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep ladder" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Dirge, Barracks Roof">
    <description>The roof of the barracks is of solid stone like most of the construction hereabouts.  A high stone wall set with embrasures and firing slits provides many vantage points for any defenders.  The remains of a wooden look-out tower still rise from the side of the building facing the town wall but it is no longer usable, as most of the upper-works have burned away in some past fire.</description>
    <position x="50" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep ladder" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Darkstone Inn, Stables" note="Trading Clerk|Shipment Clerk Dirge" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The local traders guild runs its supply out of this dingy excuse for a stable.  Moldy hay is piled in the corners, while the pitiful sounds of cramped animals calls up from the stalls.  Perched on the latest shipment of flour is a greasy-looking boy who can only be the clerk.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep stairs" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Darkstone Inn, Private Bar" note="Trading Minister|Trade Minister Dirge" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This room is a stark contrast to the public bar downstairs.  Looking like a slightly faded but still handsome gentleman's study in some prosperous town, the walls are done in polished oak trimmed with brass.  A crystal chandelier casts a flickering light over the room and a large fireplace with a stone mantel waits to be used.  Looking closer, you note the brass is tarnished and the mantel is cracked, but the overall effect remains.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go heavy door" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep stairs" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Darkstone Inn, Upper Hall" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>This end of the hall is well carpeted and clean.  Oak panelling frames a heavy oak door.  Set nearby is a serving tray full of empty glasses and flasks, the remains it seems, of some private party.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Darkstone Inn, Upper Hall">
    <description>In odd contrast to the squalor downstairs, this upper hall is relatively tidy and clean.  Worn but unsoiled carpet covers the floor, and the walls are laid with a faded but still elegant wallpaper done in silver and blue tones.  Several doors set widely apart show rooms of some size wait within, while the hallway itself continues on a bit.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go heavy door" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silverwood door" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cramped stair" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Darkstone Inn, Silver Suite">
    <description>The room is surprisingly elegant for the surroundings.  The walls are panelled with burlwood and silverwood.  Thick carpets woven in complex patterns cover the floor completely.  A huge four-poster bed dominates the room and its function possibly explains the elegant decor.  Curtained windows set with frosted glass provide privacy while filtering the light into something soft and warm.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Darkstone Inn, Blue Suite">
    <description>This room is decorated in shades of cool blue, reminding you of the far distant ocean.  Thick blue carpet, sculpted into patterns of waves and shells, flows across the room to a large bed arrayed in the same motif.  A lamp made from cut and polished strips of translucent shell gives a golden light to the scene like sunlit waves.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Darkstone Inn, Pleasure Room">
    <description>This is a very odd and unusual room.  The walls are covered entirely with leather in a dark wine color.  A massive four-poster bed dominates the room.  There are several padded benches scattered here and there as well as a pair of very comfortable looking chairs.  Darkly polished metal and burnished leather decorate every surface.  Even the bedstead is trimmed with metal and leather.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Darkstone Inn, Hallway">
    <description>This narrow hallway leads from the main bar back to the storerooms and the owner's office.  A cramped staircase leads to the upper story but looks treacherous.  A faded and water-spotted bit of carpet still lies on the floor, looking sad and ill-used.  The dark walls are scuffed and blotched with cracks in the paint.  A smell of must and mildew makes the air here thick in your nostrils.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cramped staircase" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Darkstone Inn, Storeroom">
    <description>The storeroom of the tavern makes the public areas look bright and cheerful.  A rusted old lantern, chimney caked with soot, provides a sputtering light that is barely enough to see by.  Rows of old beer kegs squat here waiting for the demand of the occasional patron outside.  Here and there, one has split from age or heat or simply from the effects of time and puddled the floor with spoiled ale.  Dozens of huge black roaches skitter about, half-drunk on the dregs left unmopped.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Darkstone Inn, Office">
    <description>This room is quite a surprise after the rest of the Inn.  Comfortable and even plush, it is furnished with heavy drapes hung on the walls and a large desk made of fine silverwood that gleams in the soft light shed by a brass oil lamp.  The owner seems to be doing a much better business than the outer rooms would indicate.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Darkstone Inn, Bar">
    <description>The bar itself was once a grand sight.  Being a solid slab of dark wood, polished and fitted with the traditonal brass rail, it was kept lovingly waxed and spotless.  The wood is now blotched and smeared with countless unwiped spills and the rail has long since been pulled up and sold for scrap.  Behind the bar, a few bottles and nondescript barrels and casks make up the liquid stock for sale here.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go main barroom" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark hallway" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Dirge, Darkstone Inn" note="Darkstone Inn|Inn|Bar" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The main room of the Inn, once well decorated and painted but now decayed and faded, still serves as a gathering place for those who dwell here or for the rare traveller.  A long wooden bar, now splintered and broken in many places, still stands at the far end of the room, while a scattering of tables gives the few patrons someplace to sit.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark corner" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go back bar" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Darkstone Inn, Dark Corner">
    <description>Tucked in one dark corner of the main room, this table retains some signs of former glory.  A bit of shine still lingers in the surface and the top is less scarred by knives and burns than others here.  The chairs, each one different, are mostly comfortable and clean.  A faded painting, apparently of the town in happier days, brings a touch of color to the drab walls.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go main bar" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Lava Fields, Narrow Trace">
    <description>Close by, a primitive pathway has been scratched out of the hard rock and basalt to the east, where it wanders into grey shadows of dust and floating ash.  A narrow road lies between high boulders in the other direction.  Faint marks etched into the coarse dark stone point towards the path and away from the caravan road.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go faint roadway" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="North Roads Caravansary" note="Map7_NTR.xml|NTR">
    <description>The road runs northwest past a cluster of stone buildings and stables to one side.  A narrow path branches off to the east following a rough line of hills while another section continues southeast.  You hear the lowing of sheep and the bleating of goats from nearby and an errant breeze brings the smell of something roasting over a fire.  Elsewhere, you might wonder just what was being cooked that smells so strongly, but here and now you find you are both famished and in dire need of drink.</description>
    <position x="40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Lava Fields, Switchback Trail">
    <description>Walls of cooled lava rise high above, seeming to melt downward in rounded flows.  Any footfalls which might echo through this canyon are muffled by the layers of ash which cover the twists and turns of the trail.</description>
    <position x="180" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow trace" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Lava Fields, Switchback Trail">
    <description>The trail continues to twist and turn here, well out of sight of the Northern Trade Road.</description>
    <position x="200" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Outside Gate" note="Gorbesh Fortress">
    <description>The terrain breaks slightly to reveal a wooden fort smeared with ash and mud to blend in with its surroundings.  A guard tower rises above the fortress gate, providing an eagle-eye view of any who approach.</description>
    <position x="200" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Practice Yard">
    <description>The ground in this open square is trampled flat and remarkably free of ash.  Ragged target dummies bearing crude parodies of the guild crests are tied in nooses from a wooden beam.</description>
    <position x="200" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ladder" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Stable">
    <description>Facing out onto the practice yard, these few covered stalls once provided temporary shelter for the mounts of the officers.  A few bits of straw are caught in the slats of a hayrack.</description>
    <position x="220" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Mess Hall">
    <description>Low benches are pulled up to long wooden tables.  Some sort of greyish crust stains the tables in spots.</description>
    <position x="180" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Firepit">
    <description>Two iron rods ending in hooks are planted in the ground next to a sooty bowl-shaped depression.  Judging from the trail of colorful splats and splotches on the ground leading west to the mess hall, this is where the Gorbesh prepared their food.</description>
    <position x="200" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Storage">
    <description>Empty hooped barrels are wedged into the corners of the room, nailed to the walls with metal spikes.  The ceiling is lined with dozens of hooks.  A sign in an unknown language is carved into the wall.</description>
    <position x="220" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Meeting Room">
    <description>High-backed chairs sit around a scarred table.  Blobs of candlewax discolor the table and floor, telling the story of long hours spent in planning, lasting deep into the night.</description>
    <position x="200" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Officers' Quarters">
    <description>Rank may have its privileges, but you wouldn't know it to look at this room.  A half-dozen cots are lined up neatly, with one table and washbasin to serve all the inhabitants.</description>
    <position x="180" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Barracks">
    <description>The bunks filling the barracks are huge, a testament to the sheer size of the Gorbesh warriors.  There is room for little else here, and the occupants must have had to crawl over each other to reach the door.</description>
    <position x="220" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Guard Tower">
    <description>The tower walls are notched and charred, apparently damaged in a pitched battle.  Deep gouges along the outside timbers of the guard tower tell the tale of a brutal assault -- one the archers who stood here could not withstand.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ladder" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Dirge, Iron Mountain Weapons" note="Iron Mountain Weapons|Weapons|Othien" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This place is even shabbier and dirtier than the rest of the town.  Bits of broken armor and scraps of half-done weapons are scattered everywhere.  The owner, a disgraced dwarf exiled from his tribe, presides over the dim smoke-filled shop with a heavy hand.  Infamous for his lethally vicious weapons, Othien deals with a tight fist and few are known to walk out with a bargain.  Most customers seem to go out of their way to avoid glancing at each other as they sidle into the store.</description>
    <position x="10" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Dirge, Ahnglor's General Store" note="Ahnglor's General Store|General Store" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A small store packed to the rafters with a little bit of everything.  Ahnglor, the proprietor, has a reputation as a packrat and you can easily see why.  Piles of clothing long out of fashion teeter next to odd bits and pieces of armor of half a dozen types.  A low wooden counter holds sacks and packs and a multitude of unguessable items.  There is barely enough space to conduct business.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Dirge, Garn the Grocer" note="Garn the Grocer|Grocer" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This shabby little shop, tucked across from Town Hall, represents the only source of groceries and foodstuffs for the entire town.  A few bins hold dispirited greens that are wilting.  A few joints of unpleasant looking meat hang from the rafters.  A dirty counter offers a selection of moldy cheeses and less identifiable comestibles.  The proprietor, a fat and greasy looking Elf of uncertain ancestry, glowers at you as if you were more a disturbance than a source of profit.</description>
    <position x="133" y="-253" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Scorched Earth" note="Scorched Earth|Fireplaces" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A series of crude firepits, dilapidated braziers and cracked kilns line the walls of this dimly lit tent.  Lumpy piles of grey ash serve as a floor, though whether they originate from the nearby volcano or scrapings from the dingy merchandise is anyone's guess.</description>
    <position x="163" y="-273" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Dirge, House of Dying" note="House of Dying">
    <description>This place, carved into the cold stone of the hillside, was once the home of healers.  When the volcanoes awoke, many people fled and many more were wounded.  The healers remained, healing and aiding those around them as they themselves died.  Now this chill cave is where those who are dying come or are brought.  With little hope, they lie on stone slabs or huddle in the corners.  Rumors persist that one healer survived and some wait in hope she will return.  They hope and they wait and they die.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Dirge, Healer's Cave" note="Healer's Cave">
    <description>This room was once used for more intensive care when healers yet worked here.   The walls were hung with white curtains soaked in cleansing solutions that the air might be pure.  Tattered and yellowed now, most of them have been torn down to wrap the dead for burial.  In the middle of the room, a large slab of white alabaster, now crusted with ash and dried blood and other things, still stands.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crack" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb alabaster slab" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Dirge, Healer's Cave">
    <description>On top of this slab, the seriously ill once lay.  Now it is used mostly for those who wish to lay out their dead and wash them and clothe them for interment.  Dried blood and crusted gore mar the smooth surface of the stone.  There is a faint stink of putrefaction.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>Dozens of niches carved deeply into the wall contain an overflowing abundance of bones.  Skulls and femurs, finger-bones and kneecaps litter the stony ground and roll everywhere.  Centuries of burial have crammed every crack and corner of the cave with the grim relics of the departed.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go jagged crack" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A narrow, twisty passage wends among unclimbable mounds of broken rock.  Here and there, a skull rests upright by some chance upon a ledge or flat surface.  Each one seems to leer with silent mirth as you stumble and lurch on the uneven pathway.</description>
    <position x="-340" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A funnel-shaped area narrows to the northeast and widens out into a huge spherical chamber to the southwest.  The rock walls are featureless black stone, all texture melted and smoothed into a dull, glassy surface.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A narrow passageway opens out into a roughly spherical cave.  The walls are a curiously porous stone, resembling a petrified sponge.  The overall effect is that of being inside a bubble formed by some strange quirk of nature when the rock was soft and pliable.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A trio of spherical caves, like ebony pearls in a row, form a line one after another.  Shaped perhaps in the time of the volcano by hot gases surging outward, the inner surface of the rock is a mass of frozen froth.  In places it shows ripples and waves and flow marks, resembling custard stirred and left to harden.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A bubble-shaped cavern rises on all sides, nearly perfect in its symmetry.  The walls are a curiously porous rock, laced with millions of lesser bubbles.  The edges are brittle and sharp for all the seeming softness of the stone, caught in mid-flow and solidified.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>What was once a large cavern, roughly spherical in shape, has collapsed into formless heaps of rubble.  Unlike its brethren to the north, there is nothing of graceful arcs and curves here.  Only hard and brittle boulders of dull grey and black rock, jagged and misshapen lie within view.</description>
    <position x="-400" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb large boulder" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>This large grey lump of ancient stone lies against the curve of the cave wall.  Above, on the wall itself, a dark pocket with jagged edges shows from whence it came.  Time has worn the boulder's surface into a series of pits and fissures.</description>
    <position x="-420" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow fissure" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>The inside of this boulder is cracked and fissured, so much so, one can find a limited amount of room to move about.  Jagged slabs of broken rock form rude walls, blocking vision and hampering movement.  Gravel rolls beneath your feet, making the footing uncertain.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow fissure" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>Stone walls curve in close above your head and jagged flakes of rock form shaky walls inside this oddly hollow boulder.  Something has made a nest here, tufts of rank hair and a few scattered bones attest to meals once consumed and dried droppings attest to their aftermath.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A few largish rocks and scattered pebbles litter the otherwise smooth floor. The cramped confines hem all movement and obscures vision.  The air is dead and still.  No wind has stirred here for ages and the air tastes of ashes and rock dust.  Dry and sere, it seems to lack any vitality.  It can be breathed, but it does not encourage one to linger.</description>
    <position x="-360" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>There is scant space to turn or move, broken slabs of rock nearly pin you against a cold wall of stone.  Flinty dust rises in a dry choking fog all about.  Silence hangs thick like a musty blanket.  The closeness is oppressive, daylight and fresh air are all but forgotten.</description>
    <position x="-380" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>Chunks of crumbling rock litter the cramped floor in this narrow hollow inside a huge boulder.  The rough ceiling presses down on heavily and the air is thick with dust.  A rising sense of claustrophobia grips at your mind.</description>
    <position x="-400" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>This cramped space resembles a niche, someplace to place an idol or statue on display.  The entire weight of the massive, hollow boulder feels as if it might come crashing down at any moment.  Tiny flakes of rock drift everywhere in a constant rain, like dessicated snow.  They grate underfoot and coat every surface with a grey dust.</description>
    <position x="-420" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A cramped and twisted passage leads from one cavern to another.  Bone fragments litter the ground and larger remnants lie heaped against the walls. Chill breezes, scented with a tinge of rot, stir the air.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>Sometime in the distant past, this passageway was wider.  A huge slab of rock has forced its way up from beneath like a stony wedge, narrowing the path almost to uselessness.  Occasional bits of bone litter the cracked and fissured ground.  The air is curiously damp, enough so that the walls are covered with a thick fur of moss or mold that gives off a musty stench like rotting leather mixed with rancid butter.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>This is a large cavern, almost circular in shape, with a domed roof of worked stone arching high overhead.  A low altar rises in the center of the cave.  Hundreds of bone-filled niches tower on all sides, climbing up the curving walls.  One great stalactite descends from the shrouded heights of the dome like the accusing finger of an angry god.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>Broken and cracked rocks encumber your feet and the roof is a crazed mass of rotten stone that appears ready to crash down with no warning.  Splintered bits of bone poke out from among the piles of rock.  There is no way to tell if they are the remains of the ancient dead, or someone of more recent vintage who got very unlucky.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>The dark walls show signs of once having been smooth, but some upheaval of the earth has turned the arched dome into a jagged mass of splintered rock and shattered stone.  Mounds of bone lie heaped along the ruins of the walls, where their burial niches once held them.  There is little rest, even for the dead, in this world.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb bones" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>Balancing on a knife-edge of rock, darkness hangs over you like a heavy cloak.  Mounds of bones and gravel-sized rock slope steeply downward to the east and west.  Straining to pierce the Stygian blackness, there is the faintest glimmer of light from the west.</description>
    <description>Balancing on a knife-edge of rock, darkness surrounds this strange perch like a heavy cloak.  Mounds of bone slope steeply to the east and west.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb east mound" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb west mound" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A vast echoing space swallows your senses into utter darkness.  Unseen air currents brush by with cold, clammy hands.  Faint gleams of bone amongst piles of rubble mark the narrow edge of a seemingly bottomless crevasse.  A huge mound of bones to the east rises up to a darker spot in the darkness.  Far overhead, a few specks of light shine like stars against the dark rock.  Apparently when the roof collapsed, rifts opened to the outer air.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb bones" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow crack" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>You are wedged into a narrow crack in the rocks.  Jagged edges chafe at every bit of exposed flesh.  Crablike sideways movement is all that is possible.  The floor below pitches at a steep angle and one would surely fall if not held in a stony embrace.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow crack" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb shadowy crevice" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A faint breeze stirs the air, it appears to come from the direction of a twisting crack in the basalt wall.  Grit and dust covers the stony ground and a few dried leaves caught in a corner indicate a possible route to the outer world.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb twisted crack" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Dirge, Ossuary Caverns">
    <description>A precipitous ledge leads down into inky depths.  Cool air, tinged with a flinty dryness, drifts bits of dust and feather fluff about your feet.  The remains of numerous bird's nests lie scattered about on the ground and in every nook and crevice.  A wide crack in the rock leads to a painfully bright daylit exterior.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ledge" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide crack" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Dirge, Volcano Ledge">
    <description>A narrow ledge has been hacked out of the side of one of the volcanoes that dominate Dirge.  Whether carved by nature or mortal hand none can tell.  The mountain falls away steeply below, and any attempt to traverse that slope would lead to a painful and lonely death on the jagged spires far below.  The route upward is as hopeless, so you remain like some spirit of air, poised between heaven and earth.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb shadowy crack" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Dirge, Temple Courtyard">
    <description>The Temple's courtyard is flat and paved with dull black basalt blocks.  There is no decor and the place echoes emptily.  A dried-out tumbleweed skitters about in the uncertain winds that reach past the high walls.  The Temple itself stands in the midst of this bleak scene.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-353" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go old tent" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go temple" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go outer gates" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="A Musty Tent" note="Blade|Divorce|Rose" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Stale dusty air mixes with the smell of rotting canvas to create a stifling atmosphere within the tent.  However, the Halfling acolyte does not seem to mind at all.  He sits leaning against several crates packed with mildewed straw.</description>
    <position x="103" y="-353" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Dirge, Temple Interior">
    <description>The rough basalt blocks have been piled up so that they meet overhead to form a crude pyramidal shape.  The walls are sparsely decorated, mostly with scenes showing sacrifices being made to the volcanoes.  As these seem to involve unwilling participants being thrown in, you hope they are of historical interest rather than current events.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-373" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go conical altar" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Dirge, Temple Altar" note="Temple Altar|Depart" color="#400040">
    <description>Less an altar than a dormant volcanic caldera, the central feature of this dark temple rises before you.  Some six feet high, it spews a thin stream of smoke.  Heat washes from it, hot enough to bring the sweat to your brow.  Trickles of lava have worked their way down the sides and out onto the stone floor, cracking and splitting the rock.  Rows of skulls of many races are set into the cone near the rim where the sulfurous fumes have stained them a sickly yellow.</description>
    <position x="113" y="-393" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Dirge, Oak Grove">
    <description>Tall trees surround you and the air is rich with the scent of growing things.  The ground is soft underfoot as if well-watered.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go standing stone" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb pile rocks" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Dirge, Standing Stone">
    <description>Here, in the center of the circle of oaks is a large standing stone.  Made of a crystal-flecked granite, it rises some four feet and is shaped like a rough pillar.  The stone is unworked save that the crown has been hollowed into a smooth circular basin.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small clearing" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Dirge, Alchemist's Shop" note="Alchemist|Ardeleanna Golt-Tieri|Golt-Tieri">
    <description>Dust and debris litter the floor in this tiny cramped shop.  Withered bunches of herbs and rotting bundles of decaying plants seem to be the main stock in trade.  A kettle sitting on a small stove gives off a noxious steam as something vile simmers in it.  An aged crone huddles on a wooden stool stirring the pot.  She seems to take no particular notice of you as she scoops a ladle full of the noisome brew to her lips and slurps loudly.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Dirge, Traveller's Bank" note="Bank|Exchange|Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A last glimmer of more prosperous times, the bank retains some remnants of the town's faded glory.  A marble counter for the tellers stands solidly to one side, though now there is but one clerk left.  Several large windows have been hastily boarded up and reinforced with stout bars.  A few other patrons lounge about waiting for the teller.  One or two of them look you over casually but with a wariness in their cold eyes.</description>
    <position x="90" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Dirge, Tromlyn's Tannery" note="Tromlyn's Tannery|Tannery" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tromlyn, the proprietor of this small shop, sits behind a small wooden counter.  At one end of the counter sits a large rock troll skull which has been mounted on wood and rests beside a catalog.  Prepared hides have been stretched in wooden frames and mounted on the wall in between shelves displaying merchandise, while bearskin rugs cover the stone floor.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Dirge, Greyka's Jewelry" note="Greyka's Jewelry|Jewelry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A low, lava stone counter rests near one of the walls.  Behind it is an elegantly carved rocking chair upon which sits a stout Dwarven woman.  Rugs made from animal pelts adorn the floor while the small window is covered with a curtain fashioned from troll skin.  In addition to the sparse decorations, a nondescript door leads to another room.</description>
    <position x="110" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Dirge, Gatehouse">
    <description>This small stone building appears to have once served as both gatehouse and tollbooth for the town.  A well-made counter still divides the room in half and the tatters of a large sign flutter on the wall.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Dirge, Narrow Cave">
    <description>This narrow cave resembles a hallway of sorts.  A cool breeze filters up from the darkness but it bears a hint of foulness and corruption.  The walls and floor are smooth and dry, though cold enough to seem clammy.</description>
    <position x="-300" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crack" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Dirge, Ossuary Cavern">
    <description>This cavern is circular, with walls and floor polished smooth by time and human effort.  The air is thick with mingled odors and an odd white dust covers the floor.  The walls are crammed with hundreds of carved niches, rising far overhead on all sides.  Those nearest you are piled high with bones and skulls of all sizes and conditions.  A strong smell of decay and rot wafts up from a large pit in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go jagged crack" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Dirge, Charnel Pit">
    <description>The bottom of this pit is filled with a dark, thick liquid.  Viscous and foul-smelling, it fills a deeper pit almost to the rim.  Small waves travel across its surface though there is no wind to cause them.  Dozens of corroded bronze cages hang from the walls attached to long chains.  For centuries, the dead of Dirge have been brought here to have their flesh eaten away by the liquid in the pit and their polished bones laid in niches of remembrance in the room above.</description>
    <position x="-320" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Dirge, Ga'Run's Locks and Keys" note="Locksmith|Locks and Keys|Ga'Run">
    <description>Thick shadows crowd about this large shop save for one brightly lit area in the center.  A high table, crowded with locks and picks and various other implements for manipulating delicate and complex mechanisms, is the only clearly visible feature.  A wizened Gor'Tog sits hunched over the table, a jeweller's loupe in one eye, apparently scrutinizing the insides of a confusing device that appears to involve dozens of small geared wheels.  Despite his huge size, he handles his tools with amazing dexterity.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="A Dimly-lit Home">
    <description>The flickering of candlelight flame is insufficient to light this moderately sized room, leaving shadows obscuring the papers strewn out over an oaken-hewn desk.  Comfort seems an afterthought, with only two plain chairs a nod to the need for relaxation.  Shelves affixed to the walls hold small ivory trophies and knickknacks, all carefully arranged.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Entrance" note="Wicked Burrow Mine|Mine" color="#993300">
    <description>A steady breeze whips past, billowing out from the depths of the mine.  Rows of torches line the walls and cast dancing shadows down the long tunnel ahead.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>The ceiling and walls gradually narrow towards the northeast.  Bits and pieces of broken rock litter the floor, remnants of recent mining activity.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>Scattered debris litters the sloped rock floor.  Few torches remain lit here, and they appear to be extinguished entirely in the northern branch.  A marked difference in the coloration of the stone separates the mine entrance from the depths below.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Steep Slope" color="#993300">
    <description>Jagged stalactites reach towards the floor and small pools of water collect along the ground of this natural cavern.  The clank of metal hammering rock echoes from farther into the mine.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Supplies Stand" note="Mining Supplies|Supplies Stand" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This open section of the cavern houses a supply depot for storing mined-out materials.  Several merchants sell tools from a makeshift stand.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Slope" color="#993300">
    <description>A thin layer of moss coats the damp walls in this section of natural tunnel.  Abruptly, the tunnel slopes downward and into the poorly-lit depths below.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Slope" color="#993300">
    <description>Rivulets of water stream down the smooth cave walls and collect in small surface puddles.  Haphazardly placed torches illuminate the way deeper into a freshly hewn section of tunnel.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>Generous flows of water pass through this section of the mine, making the floor slick and the air damp.  Sounds of cracking rock and groaning laborers echo out from deeper within the mine.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Crevice" color="#993300">
    <description>The tunnel curves around to a narrow crevice illuminated by torches on both sides.  A burly man stands next to a sign indicating only Estate Holders may proceed past this point.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="go" move="rt go narrow crevice" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>Sounds from rushing water fill the area, echoing off the walls in a chaotic chorus.  Every step becomes a potential hazard here from the excessive rubble strewn about the path.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rocks" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Stream Bank" color="#993300">
    <description>Water drips and pours from every inch of stone, all headed down the bank and into the fast-moving stream below.  A small bit of light shines in from the west, barely illuminating the barren walls.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stream bank" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rubble-clogged passageway" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Slope" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Tendrils of icy water rush forth from a large crack in the mine's walls.  A crescendo of noise echos from deeper into the mine as evidence of more turbulant water upstream.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stream bank" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Stream" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Churning waters rages past, sending a foamy spray into the air!  Darkness hides the low cavern ceiling that enhances the water's deep rumbling.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Twisting in various directions, the tunnels each lead to individual sections of the cavern.  Several skeletal remains scattered upon the ground rest near the pile of rocks.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rocks" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Cramped between two walls, the pathway barely offers enough room to squeeze through.  The echoing of babbling voices filters through the hall, though what is being said cannot be discerned.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Dropping down a steep distance, the pathway comes to a sudden halt.  Pebbles breaking off from the cavern walls ping against the rocks before landing on the ground below.  A fraying rope dangles over the edge, offering a way down into the bowels of the cavern.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fraying rope" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, A Ledge">
    <description>Dangling from the pathway above, a frayed rope offers passage further up the wall, while a makeshift rope ladder leads further down into the cave.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rope ladder" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fraying rope" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths Beyond" color="#993300">
    <description>Layers of chipped rocks and pebbles that have fallen from the ledge above line the floor in a scattered mess.  A makeshift sign leans precariously against the wall.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rope ladder" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths Beyond" color="#993300">
    <description>Etched into thick stone walls, various amateurish depictions of trolls hunting their prey decorate the makeshift room.  Broken bones scatter the ground in such a way that it is nearly impossible to pass through without stepping upon them.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths Beyond" color="#993300">
    <description>Weapon racks crafted from various bone types line the walls of the cavern hall.  Standing between the racks on either side are poorly carved stone statues depicting menacing cave trolls, which serve as nothing more then a decorative deterrent to all who trespass here.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths Beyond" color="#993300">
    <description>Chipped stone tables and chairs line along the narrow hall leaving barely enough room to pass by.  Securely affixed to the wall is a life-sized replica of a skull and crossbones, perhaps hung in attempt to warn intruders of what awaits them.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths Beyond" color="#993300">
    <description>Flat stone beds stacked three high span the far end of the room.  Within the middle of the chamber is a carefully crafted fire pit, over which hangs a spit dangling the daily dinner catch.  Various thick fur pelts cover the floor in attempt to create a homey feel for the otherwise dank space.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Crevice" note="Premium Mine|premium mine" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>A long, freshly-hewn corridor lined with well-kept torches extends into the distance.  Attendants scurry back and forth with wheelbarrels and sleds piled high with rocks and ore.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crevice" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Winding Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>Wooden supports criss-cross the tunnels branching out from this place.  The occasional rumble shakes the floor and drowns out the sound of pickaxes and shovels striking rock.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>Extra effort was taken to expand the tunnel in this section of the mine.  Additional supports line the walls and numerous torches fully illuminate the mine's rocky accoutrements.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>The tunnel straightens out but continues a gentle trend downwards, deeper into the mine.  A fine mist begins to accumulate in the air and forms halos around the many torches lining the walls.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Grotto" color="#993300">
    <description>The walls emanate a steady heat and the mist-filled air makes breathing difficult.  A small pool of bubbling water, roughly the size of a dinner plate, occupies the grotto's center.  Fewer miners work in this section of tunnel, perhaps warded off by the heat or peculiar nature of the bubbling pool.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Winding Tunnel" color="#993300">
    <description>Thick grooves from attendants dragging sleds laden with materials mar the smooth stone floor.  Several flattened boulders provide a sitting spot for workers worn tired from the day's labor.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Rock Shelf" color="#993300">
    <description>The tunnel abruptly ends with a steep rock shelf cascading downward into a giant chasm below.  Ropes and support beams prevent further exploration below.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Pit" color="#993300">
    <description>The winding, uneven tunnel abruptly ends at the edge of a jagged pit surrounded by a sturdy guard rail.  A steady howl reverberates from the deep chasm, but does little to interrupt the mining progress taking place here.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Crematorium, Retort">
    <description>A cramped and narrow space, full of memories of fire and burning, closes in around you.  Heavy iron gratings cover the floor to allow the flames to rise up and consume the departed.  Far overhead, a chimney rises to vent the smoke and fumes.  Thick layers of greasy ash coat the walls, and bits of it flake down in a dark rain.  The outer doors, once closed, would trap one in here, and you wonder just how rusted those hinges actually are.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Stream" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Racing jets of water crash down upon this rock-strewn stream bed.  Deeper into the mine the rumbling sounds even louder.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, Waterfall" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The low cavern ceiling opens up into an inky blackness from which a towering wall of water crashes down.  The frothy mix of water and rubble quickly flow down along a path carved into the rock.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stream bank" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>A cacophonous rumbling echos all around from the rapid movement of water somewhere above.  The tunnel narrows deeper into the mine.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stream bank" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Cracking tendrils perforate the ceiling's smooth surface.  The ground is littered with fractured rock slabs covered in a fine coat of dust.  Several smaller passageways branch off this area, the fragile entrances holding the promises of riches below.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Trickling down the rocky cavern walls, small streams of water flow through deep crevices set into the rough stone.  Chunks of rock that have fallen from the ceiling scatter across the floor making passage through a bit treacherous but still manageable.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Nearly caved in, passage through this wing of the cavern is tight but possible.  Echoes of voices are muffled by the sounds of hammers pounding against stone.  A single lit torch fastened to the wall provides barely enough light to see one's way through the halls.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Piles of rock upon the ground line the chipped stone walls.  Discarded tools and burnt out lanterns scatter the ground in disarray.  Small slivers of light from nearby create shadows through the cavern hall, though nothing visible to the eye seems to match the figures they shape.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Hole" color="#993300">
    <description>An expansive cavern opens above and a pinprick of light shines through a hole in the distance.  Cables and ropes hang down and allow attendants to hoist materials out of this section of the mine for easy transport.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>A gigantic slab of rock hangs precariously perched on two pumice pedestals worn smooth by the constant drip of water.  A faint rushing noise echoes down the walls from rushing water in the distance.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Stalagmites bubble up from the smooth ground and form marvelous designs in these cold depths.  The drip-drop of water and occasional chitter of an insect carries across the rocky depths.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Wicked Burrow Mine, The Narrow Depths" color="#993300">
    <description>Treacherous clusters of speleothems zig and zag deeper into the mine until the passage becomes too narrow for further travel.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Dirge, Town Hall Interior" note="Town Hall">
    <description>The interior of Town Hall is as drab and dull as the exterior.  The walls were once painted with some attempt at bright colors but the paint has long since chipped and peeled, leaving only a fleck or two to show what once was there.  An old door propped up on two saw-horses seems to be the current habitat of the town clerk.  The rest of the room is bare of furnishings save for one old and very battered safe in one corner.</description>
    <position x="153" y="-293" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mayor's office" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hidden doorway" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Dirge, Mayor's Office">
    <description>This is the office of the Mayor.  Most of the paint remains yet on the walls so the room is almost bright and cheerful compared to much of the town.  A good-sized desk takes up most of the floor and there are several chairs scattered about, indicating this place also serves as an occasional meeting hall.</description>
    <position x="163" y="-293" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Dirge, Storeroom">
    <description>Tucked behind the safe, this room was obviously meant to be overlooked by the casual passerby.  Ruined and charred file cabinets have been carelessly shoved into a corner.  The rest of the room appears to be in use as a gathering spot.  Several tables are pushed together in the middle and there are many empty bottles set on them with spilled puddles of ale or wine to judge by the smell.  You surmise this may be where the local ruffians hang out who have replaced the town militia.</description>
    <position x="153" y="-303" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Dirge, Carousel Square">
    <description>A massive building dominates the square, rising in an impenatrably black cone to its pinnacle far above.  Scarred by wind-driven pebbles and sand, the structure stands as a monument to the imminent power of nature and time.  A weatherbeaten wooden sign set above an oval doorway reads THE CAROUSEL.</description>
    <position x="93" y="-263" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oval doorway" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="south" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Dirge, The Carousel" note="Vault" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A thin scattering of grit spreads across the drab floor, collecting in packed deposits at the base of the curved wall ringing the building's center.  A flat circular roof supports a vast framework of iron and timbers rising to the building's distant pinnacle.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights within the structure form the strikingly complex and beautiful mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="83" y="-263" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slate desk" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Dirge, Carousel Desk" note="Lost and Found" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A long wooden desk spans the width of the western wall.  Brass lanterns hang from the ceiling, and the floor behind the desk is covered in spotless red tile.</description>
    <position x="73" y="-263" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Arthelun Flats, Cambrigweld">
    <description>Sheer-sided and sandy, this massive crater is utterly bereft of life.  A sharp smell, like heated metal, permeates the area.  A faint track picks its way up the southern slope of the crater back toward the main road and a narrow lava tube on the northwestern face leads into darkness.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb track" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tube" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Arthelun Flats, Lava Tube">
    <description>An uncomfortable heat radiates from the smooth, round walls.  The tube ends here with the southern maw opening into a massive crater.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tube" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Arthelun Flats, Lava Tube">
    <description>An uncomfortable heat radiates from the smooth, round walls.  The tube slowly curves here concealing either end of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Arthelun Flats, Lava Tube">
    <description>An uncomfortable heat radiates from the smooth, round walls.  The tube slowly slopes upwards towards the eastern maw.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tube" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Arthelun Flats, Lava Flow">
    <description>Undulating sheets of long hardened lava flow forth from an old lava tube.  A few stray cobblestones have survived both the lava the more recent explosion from which the massive crater to the south resulted.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tube" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Arthelun Flats, Crater Overlook">
    <description>The road is almost nonexistent here, effectively obliterated by the drifting grey ash that pervades the area.  Alongside the road the jagged remnant of a black marble statue is half-embedded in the ground, its broken-off legs jutting skyward.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Arthelun Flats, Old Imperial Road">
    <description>A crooked fissure brings the road to an abrupt end, glowing sullenly and casting forth an acrid sulfuric reek.  A collapsed black marble column serves as a makeshift bridge, allowing relatively safe passage to the northeast.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go column" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Arthelun Flats, Old Imperial Road">
    <description>A crooked fissure blocks passage to the southwest, a fallen black marble column serving as a makeshift bridge.  The road continues to the southeast, though it has been almost completely obliterated by drifting ash.  A rocky trail leads northwards to the collapsed ruins of a stone building.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go column" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Arthelun Flats, Old Imperial Road">
    <description>The road ends abruptly here, a treacherous jumble of massive rocks making passage onward all but impossible.  The volcano looms to the northwest, rumbling and muttering like a sleeping giant.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb jumble rocks" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>The ground here is blanketed in ankle-deep ash the rocks and masonry hidden beneath making for treacherous footing.  A plinth from a massive black marble column lies shattered in two pieces the scattered remains of the pillar stretching southward like an out-flung arm.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>The sky to the northwest is aswirl with burning, shifting colors, reflections of the fire blazing at the heart of the Greater Fist.  Fine ash and drifting embers eddy and swirl with each gust and breeze, moving through the air like swarms of fireflies.  The ground is littered with cracked masonry and bits of shattered mosaic, their colors dull and flat beneath a heavy coating of soot and grime.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>The parts from a shattered humanoid statue are scattered here, interspersed with jagged blocks of pumice and tile fragments from ruined murals.  A slender, long-fingered marble hand juts upward from a mound of debris, seeming to wave cheerfully at those who pass this way.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>A massive black marble plinth dominates this area, largely intact, if empty.  The bits of floor visible despite the ash and dust are deeply scarred and gouged, the mosaic here almost completely destroyed.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>Some rubble-choked steps dominate this area, the massive, black marble blocks that comprise them scattered about like a child's abandoned toys.  The scent of brimstone is more pungent here, the fickle breezes that play through the area stirring the ash that blankets the ground.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steps" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>A small, bright-red flow of lava oozes across the edge of the courtyard, stretching forth like a questing finger.  Varicolored tiles are scattered everywhere, their bright hues dampened by the ubiquitous ash and soot.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Arthelun Ruins, Courtyard">
    <description>The floor here is almost totally obscured by a long-cooled lava flow, rucked and wrinkled like the skin of an elderly human.  Only one part of the mosaic is visible and unblemished -- a cracked, unblinking eye staring blankly skyward.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>A pair of mostly-intact caryatids stand at the top of the steps, their hands extended in an emphatic gesture of warning.  The roof above is in ill repair, but still intact, the black marble women bearing their burden with stalwart grace.  The broad steps leading to the courtyard below are scattered with debris and jagged shards of black marble.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steps" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>The broken stumps of several black marble caryatids stand here, their blasted remains strewn down the broad steps that lead to the courtyard below.  The roof has collapsed on this side of the building, leaving the ruin open to the weather and the fury of the volcano looming to the northwest.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>Several shapeless black marble caryatids stand here, their faces and forms lost to time and erosion.  The roof above remains intact, sheltering this spot from the weather and the fury of the volcano to the northwest.  A questing finger of red-hot lava probes its way across the stairway that leads to the courtyard below.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>The back wall of the building still stands, but the roof has collapsed, scattering the floor with large chunks of debris and jagged shards of black marble.  A female face, exquisitely carved from black marble, gazes upward from the rubble.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crevice" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>The back wall of this structure is a glory of color, covered from top to bottom by a lush, flame-hued mosaic.  A massive gouge mars the floor where part of the ceiling has fallen in, but the roof seems to be in much better repair here than to the west.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>A stately fountain depicting a supine woman dominates the area, the figure laid out upon a massive plinth.  The marble comprising the fountain is charred to a matte finish its empty basin strangely free of debris.  The roof is intact here, as though unwilling to crush the woman in her slumber.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Arthelun Ruins, Edifice">
    <description>A black marble statue looms in the corner of this space, its cloaked and hooded form poised as if to take a step forward.  One outflung arm ends in a jagged stump, but its other arm -- brandishing an ornately carved staff -- is still whole.  Though the roof has not collapsed here, the ever-present ash and debris still makes for treacherous footing.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Arthelun Flats, Amidst the Boulders">
    <description>Surrounded on all sides by a jumble of boulders, this nook is sheltered somewhat from the incessant ash fall.  A peculiar glyph has been carved along the edge of one of the massive rocks, though the inscription is weathered as if it was placed there long ago.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fall" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Akul'tiz Tunnels, Treacherous Entry">
    <description>The cloying smell of rot and mildew enfolds you like a clammy cloak, the moist air feeling strangely warm.  A jumble of dirt, rubble and scree makes passage nearly impossible and provides sharp obstacles for any who pass this way.</description>
    <position x="0" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go passageway" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Mushroom Grove">
    <description>The bulk of the fungal infestation appears to have clustered upon and around a desolate sana'ati sapling in the center of the area, as if feasting on its essence.  A narrow, circular walkway provides arduous navigation about this eerie garden, while a foul stench emanates from the area to the northeast.  </description>
    <position x="-20" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Mushroom Grove">
    <description>A multitude of massive mushrooms chokes the area, many of the fungi aglow with violescent traceries.  Their dim reflection of light does little to illuminate this spot, however, instead dazzling the eye and making navigation more difficult.  A circuitous narrow track that is nearly clogged with fungus provides passage to the west.</description>
    <position x="20" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Fresh Diggings">
    <description>This end of the cavern is dominated by the comparatively wholesome smell of freshly turned earth.  The beginnings of a new tunnel are evident to the west, though as yet it is nothing but a shallow dead end.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Feed Yard">
    <description>Piles of succulent roots stacked like bales of hay occupy the northern end of this spot.  A massive, makeshift trough sits to the south with a crude ladder propped against each end.  In between, the floor is churned to mud, the reek of urine and feces indicating that the muck is not just earth and water.</description>
    <position x="0" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Living Area">
    <description>The walls of this area are sturdy, undressed stone.  Braided root mats adorn the smooth, hard-packed dirt of the floor and twisted, root ropes hang like garlands from the generously high ceiling.  Pale leather pallets are arranged in groups along the walls.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Gathering Hall">
    <description>Several concentric circles of crude stones are arranged in the middle of this cavernous hall, the outer rings slightly larger than those within, giving the whole an appearance similar to a shallow amphitheater.  The height of the ceiling adds to the effect, shrouding the top of the hall in utter darkness reminiscent of a vast, starless sky.</description>
    <position x="20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="211" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Deep Cathedral">
    <description>The walls, ceiling and floor of this cavern are elaborately carved with repeating patterns of shrikes, moths and eyes.  The north end of the hall is dominated by an unfinished humanoid statue, its crude limbs arranged with incongruous grace.  A low, half-finished altar rests below the stony figure.  Echoing through the hall is a low susurration formed from whispered snatches of Common and Gamgweth mingled into a bewildering, nigh-unintelligible tangle.</description>
    <position x="0" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Akul'tiz Gardens, Spawn Corral">
    <description>Stones of many disparate shapes and sizes are stacked haphazardly, creating an improvised corral.  A pungent animal smell reminiscent of urine and sweaty, unwashed bodies assaults the senses, mingling unpleasantly with the pervasive, dank reek of mold and mildew.  Piles of dung fester within the corral.</description>
    <position x="40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Entrance">
    <description>Choked with stony debris and rubble, the pitch-dark stone of this corridor crowds oppressively.  High above, tiny growths of phosphorescent lichen glow like strange, cheerless stars, providing just enough light to make out the worst of the hazards.  An awful reek permeates the area, its acrid pungency so pronounced that it is tasted more than smelled.</description>
    <position x="60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Dunien rae Orek">
    <description>The pervasive reek takes on a strong note here, the acrid odor of guano mingling unpleasantly with the smell of decay and rotting meat.  Detritus from a long-ago rock fall is scattered all around, mixed with more organic refuse.  High above, sickly green cave lichen glows sullenly, a scaly infestation on the face of the dark stone.</description>
    <position x="100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Dunien rae Orek">
    <description>A dainty teacup rests on its side amid heaps of mounded guano, its delicate rosebud design nearly obscured beneath a layer of grime.  The phosphorescent lichen glowing high above gives off barely enough sickly green light for navigation.  An awful reek permeates the area, its acrid pungency so pronounced that it is tasted more than smelled.</description>
    <position x="120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Dunien rae Orek">
    <description>The rocky cave floor is littered with a multitude of tiny white bones, pointed obstacles for all who pass this way.  High above, phosphorescent lichen casts forth a sickly green light, the tiny pinpoint growths clustered in groups like strange constellations.  An awful reek permeates the area, its acrid pungency so pronounced that it is tasted more than smelled.</description>
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Dunien rae Orek">
    <description>Mounded stones and debris form treacherous obstacles as the floor slopes downward.  Dark brown stains mar the dark rock forming the back wall of the cavern, the splotches forming no discernible pattern.  The air here is strangely chill, the cold driving away some of the pervasive reek afflicting this place.</description>
    <position x="100" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow fiss" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Dunien rae Orek">
    <description>A massive pile of shattered porcelain dominates this spot, the multitude of pieces in myriad patterns and colors.  Nearby, a smaller pile of humanoid bones is stacked with uncanny neatness, their bleached white color painted a sickly green in the illumination of the glowing cave lichen high above.</description>
    <position x="60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Dunien rae Orek">
    <description>A massive infestation of phosphorescent lichen flourishes on the dark stone, its pallid green glow contrasting sharply with the unrelieved gloom in the rest of the cavern.  The uneven, rocky floor is nearly clear of debris here, though the slick stone is treacherous footing.</description>
    <position x="40" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>The air here is strangely dry and chill, with a flat, stale odor.  The dark stone floor of the cavern is swept clear of rocks and debris, its uneven surface shining wetly.  High above, phosphorescent lichen casts forth a ruddy red-brown glow, arcing in rough spirals across a ceiling otherwise lost in darkness.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow fiss" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>This spot is free of the phosphorescent lichen infesting the rest of the cavern, the area directly overhead a pitch-black void that seems to stretch upward forever.  The lichen elsewhere in the cavern creates an ambient glow that is barely enough to navigate by, the slick, dark stone of the floor almost as lost to sight as the ceiling high above.</description>
    <position x="100" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>The cavern here is preternaturally still and silent, as if the stale air disdains to transmit sounds.  Crude, reddish-brown designs mar the sloping cavern wall, barely illuminated by the sullen red light of the arcing spirals of lichen high above.</description>
    <position x="120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>A trickle of dark liquid seeps down the face of the cavern wall, marking the stone with vivid crimson streaks.  Despite this moist ooze, the air here is dry and chill, with a flat, stale odor.  High above, phosphorescent lichen casts forth a ruddy red-brown glow, arcing in rough spirals across a ceiling otherwise lost in darkness.</description>
    <position x="140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>A massive force has wracked the ceiling, scraping great swathes from the phosphorescent lichen high above.  Bits of fallen fungus litter the dark stone of the cavern floor, their ruddy glow extinguished.  The air here is strangely dry and chill, with a peculiar odor reminiscent of heated metal.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>The cavern ceiling grows oppressively low here -- barely high enough to accommodate a Gor'Tog.  Above, spiraling growths of phosphorescent lichen seem to pulse and undulate unwholesomely, the dim light lending a sullen sanguine hue to everything it touches.</description>
    <position x="80" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Li Surmi Gelv, Abule rae Seord">
    <description>A stalagmite bursts from the dark stone of the floor, its multi-pronged bulk clutching the chill air like a massive, mangled hand.  High above, phosphorescent lichen casts forth a ruddy red-brown glow, arcing in jagged spirals across a ceiling otherwise lost in darkness.</description>
    <position x="60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" note="Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>In the darkness, gnarled hawthorn trees arch over the broken cobblestone road like the tentacles of a great sea creature, creating a shadowed tunnel above this once-thriving community.  A shingled road sign dangles from a single remaining chain amid large, white limestone markers and dried up plants that line the roadway.  Pitched at an odd angle to one side is a burnt out caravan, its missing front wheel lies in splintered pieces scattered about the area.</description>
    <description>Gnarled hawthorn trees arch over the broken cobblestone road, the charred branches attempting to create a shadowed tunnel over this once-thriving community.  A shingled road sign dangles from a single remaining chain amid large, white limestone markers and dried out plants that line the roadway, now covered in a heavy layer of soot.  Pitched at an odd angle to one side is a burned out caravan, its missing front wheel lies in splintered pieces, scattered about the area.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The gnarled tentacles of the sprawling trees rise out of the darkness that surrounds the neighborhood homes, the area's deteriorated state lit only by the occasional light through a nearby window.  Rotted and decayed rail carts lie overturned near the roadside tracks, their ash-covered stony contents littering the area and making travel difficult.  Rusted ironwork attempts to fence in a nearby weed-choked garden, while across the lane, a frayed rope dangles a broken swing from twisted branch overhead.</description>
    <description>The neighborhood shows clear signs of neglect, having succumbed to the ravages of time and apparent disaster.  Rotted and decayed rail carts lie overturned near the roadside tracks, their ash-covered stony contents littering the area and making travel difficult.  Rusted ironwork attempts to fence in a nearby weed-choked garden, while across the lane, a frayed rope dangles a broken swing from the gnarled branch of one of the surrounding hawthorn trees.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Cracked and worn, grey cobblestones pave the debris-riddled lane as it makes a sharp bend, wending its way amid the meager homes and partially collapsed buildings.  In the dim light of a single lantern, a haggard-looking wooden sluice system teeters on weathered stilts as it extends into the area from the small lake nearby.  Making a series of angled drops, the trough empties into a large sun-bleached tub, its current flow reduced to nothing more than a mere trickle.  Across the lane, several yards are cluttered with rusted mining tools and broken toys, a surreal contrast to life within the working neighborhood.</description>
    <description>Cracked and worn, grey cobblestones pave the debris-riddled lane as it makes a sharp bend, wending its way amid the meager homes and partially collapsed buildings.  A haggard-looking wooden sluice system teeters on weathered stilts as it extends into the area from the small lake nearby.  Making a series of angled drops, the trough empties into a large sun-bleached tub, its current flow reduced to nothing more than a mere trickle.  Across the lane, several yards are cluttered with rusted mining tools and broken toys, a surreal contrast to life within the working neighborhood.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The ash-laden air chokes the village green with its pallid dwellings, each in desperate need of repair.  Guttering lanterns cast strange, shifting patterns of light and shadow over the small sward as their light is cast over the gnarled, barren trees and splintered wooden benches at its center.  Tattered curtains flutter in a broken window nearby, while weathered kegs litter the landing of a crumbling mining depot.  Some mossy stone steps collapse downward into the darkness towards small lake nearby, a distant towering shadow barely visible between the homes.</description>
    <description>The ash-laden air chokes the village green with its pallid dwellings, each in desperate need of repair.  Barren trees with thorny branches hunker over a pair of splintered wooden benches, the broken cobblestones encircling the small sward.  Tattered curtains flutter in a broken window nearby, while weathered kegs litter the landing of a crumbling mining depot.  Some mossy stone steps collapse downward towards small lake nearby, a distant stone windmill barely visible between the homes.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Entombed by tall weeds, the decomposing skeleton of a termite-riddled gazebo serves as a haunting reminder of the forsaken neighborhood's lost splendor.  Along with the ruins of the local stables, several homes line the dark cobblestone lane, lit only by the light from an occasional window.  Iron-banded kegs are stacked along many of the sagging porches, while a withering pumpkin patch divides several of the buildings.  A trio of collapsed mining carts teeters upon the iron rails that run throughout the community.</description>
    <description>Entombed by tall weeds, the decomposing skeleton of a termite-riddled gazebo serves as a haunting reminder of the forsaken neighborhood's lost splendor.  Along with the ruins of the local stables, several homes line the worn cobblestone lane.  Iron-banded kegs are stacked along many of the sagging porches, while a withering pumpkin patch divides several of the buildings.  A trio of collapsed mining carts teeters upon the iron rails that run throughout the community.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A scant few lanterns reveal the dilapidated homes that crowd one side of the narrow lane, a stained and broken doll peeking out from beneath the overgrown shrubbery.  Across the road, a considerable amount of trees have been cleared, providing several cords of firewood and unorganized stacks of cumbrous shoring beams.  Near a broad stump pierced by a long-handled axe, a small wooden cart lies toppled to one side, one of its wheels collapsed beneath it.</description>
    <description>Dilapidated homes crowd one side of the narrow lane, a stained and broken doll peeking out from beneath the overgrown shrubbery.  Across the road, a considerable amount of trees have been cleared, providing several cords of firewood and unorganized stacks of cumbrous shoring beams.  Near a broad stump pierced by a long-handled axe, a small wooden cart lies toppled to one side, one of its wheels collapsed beneath it.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Rising out of the surrounding darkness, several surviving blackberry bushes threaten to choke off the short bend in the roadway, their redolent scents sweetening the evening air.  Stacked stone piles rise amid dried weeds, placed like markers among the many homes that line the narrow cobblestone lane.  A weathered butter churn rests in one yard, while splintered shutters dangle precariously from the candlelit window of another nearby residence.</description>
    <description>Several surviving blackberry bushes threaten to choke off the short bend in the roadway, their redolent scents filling the area in the summer months.  Stacked stone piles rise amid dried weeds, placed like markers among the many homes that line the narrow cobblestone lane.  A weathered butter churn rests in one yard, while splintered shutters dangle precariously from the window of another nearby residence.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Dirge, Hawthorn Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The gnarled branches of the surrounding hawthorn trees overhang the area, creating a weblike canopy that shadows the end of the worn cobblestone lane.  Bordering a partially collapsed riverstone barrier that once enclosed the nearby cemetary, a crude rack is hung with rusted shovels caked with dried mud.  The bedraggled homes huddle together as if guarding from what lies beyond, their decayed fences missing a majority of the pickets which lie buried amid the tall, surrounding weeds.  A single lamp post supports a battered lantern, providing minimal lighting in the dead of night.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="235" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Hawthorn Lane, Cemetery" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>An unsettling pall hangs over the desecrated cemetery at the end of the road.  Fringed by a dense foreboding forest, freshly opened graves and defiled crypts have left their pilfered remains scattered about the area.  Broken headstones and weather-worn bones are strewn across the dried, ash-covered scrub that grows sparsely over the area.  A few discolored monuments still stand amid the depredation, looming in the darkness like malevolent guardians.</description>
    <description>An unsettling pall hangs over the desecrated cemetery at the end of the road.  Fringed by a dense foreboding forest, freshly opened graves and defiled crypts have left their pilfered remains scattered about the area.  Broken headstones and weather-worn bones are strewn across the dried, ash-covered scrub that grows sparsely over the area.  A few discolored monuments still stand amid the depredation.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Lava Fields, Ruined Farmhouse">
    <description>Charred and broken beams stand silent watch over this ruined farmstead.  Undamaged roof tiles lie scattered about in untidy windrows.  Amid the destruction and waste of what was once someone's home, the head of a child's doll pokes up from a mound of ash and melted rock.  Blue painted eyes on a porcelain head stare mutely at you and ask questions no mortal can answer.  If there was anything of value left here, it has long since been looted.  Footprints in the dust lead north to the road.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Arthelun Flats, Oven of Cinders">
    <description>The way north is clogged by a massive jumble of basalt bolders, many of them curiously hexagonal in form.  A hot, keening wind screeches though a narrow crevice at the north end of this area, its harsh atonal voice rising and falling in volume and pitch with each gust.  Volleys of ash and grit are flung unceasingly against anything impeding the wind, creating numerous, ever-changing dunes and drifts.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Arthelun Flats, Oven of Cinders">
    <description>Cinders clog the passage here like drifts of sooty snow, making movement in any direction a perilous slog.  A strong, hot wind from the northwest stirs the ash, carrying with it a sulfurous reek.  High above, dark stalactites reach downward, their angular shapes suggesting roosting bats or massive sharks' teeth.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Arthelun Flats, Oven of Cinders">
    <description>A narrow slice of sky is all that is visible of the outside world from inside this cramped volcanic fissure.  Though wide enough for a large Gor'Tog to pass by, rocky prominences make passage this way difficult.  A few tough lichens cling tenaciously to the undersides of a few stones their grey-green tones somewhat softening the pervasive sooty black.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Arthelun Flats, Oven of Cinders">
    <description>A hot, dry wind howls through this enclosed space, catching the ubiquitous black grit and hurling it viciously into any object or creature blocking its passage.  The air seems to shudder and moan like a despairing prisoner raging against a barred door.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Arthelun Flats, Oven of Cinders">
    <description>Though shaded from above by a jagged overhang of slabbed volcanic rock, this spot is still terrifically hot.  The sandy black soil is dry and gritty underfoot, strewn with rocks of all sizes, all combining to make the footing here extremely uncertain.  No plants or animals are evident, despite the relative shelter from the winds and elements.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Arthelun Flats, Oven of Cinders">
    <description>A large basalt slab stretches across the northeast edge of this spot, serving to muffle the unceasing gusts of wind and ash that pervade this area.  High above, a hexagonal bit of the sky can be seen, this modest opening admitting a breath of moister, cooler air.  The barest trickle of water decorates the basalt rocks in the lee of the slab, giving sustenance to a stunted sirese plant.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Arthelun Ruins, Back Chamber">
    <description>Time and the collapse of the main building have obscured the purpose of this area.  Now it is filled with a jumble of stones and debris, which fills the corners and divides the area into smaller open spaces.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crevice" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Arthelun Ruins, Back Chamber">
    <description>Little remains but a pile of rotting shelves to indicate the original function of the room.  A few slabs from the ceiling have fallen onto the floor, their cracked and broken surfaces mute testimony to the forces that destoyed this building.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Arthelun Ruins, Back Chamber">
    <description>A damp, musty smell wafts through the area, combining with the everpresent dust to create a haze in the air.  Mold has crept up the walls from a tiny trickle of water that flows along the junction between the floor and the walls.  The water disappears into a tiny crevice with a musical gurgle.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Dirge, Carousel Family Services" note="Family Vault" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A series of guarded arches line the southern wall.  The complicated framework of iron and timbers spans across the ceiling.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights form the strikingly complex mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="83" y="-253" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Dirge, Rundmolen Post Office" note="Post Office|mail" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tucked up against the looming building is a low stone counter made from cut stone blocks.  Vast, countless rows of differently sized shelves are behind the counter, and complex Dwarven mechanisms can be heard as they rearrange the package-covered storage.  Clerks shuffle endlessly back and forth between the counters and shelving as they assist patrons with their packaging and mailing needs.</description>
    <position x="93" y="-253" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <label text="crazed madmen">
    <position x="-270" y="-50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="ghouls">
    <position x="-320" y="-130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="scavenger troll">
    <position x="230" y="60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="NTR">
    <position x="10" y="0" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="lesser skeletons">
    <position x="-411" y="-304" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="corpse grubs">
    <position x="-386" y="-199" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gorbesh Fortress">
    <position x="155" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Town Square">
    <position x="33" y="-323" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Temple">
    <position x="123" y="-373" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Darkstone Inn">
    <position x="-821" y="-160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wicked Burrow Mine">
    <position x="-128" y="-60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Lava Drakes">
    <position x="175" y="-186" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Darkstone Inn">
    <position x="141" y="-140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Arthelun cabalists">
    <position x="210" y="-279" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="umbral moths">
    <position x="-9" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Akul'tiz Gardens">
    <position x="-78" y="105" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Li Surmi Gelv">
    <position x="55" y="108" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>