<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Ilaya Taipa River Clan" id="112">
  <node id="1" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Leaves littering the surface of the damp road await their final fate:  being slowly ground into the mud, then decaying into the earth to create another layer of rich, dark loam.  Sloping downward to the southwest, this section of road is a long, gentle bend following a curve from the northwest.</description>
    <position x="120" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="rt southwest" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="rt northwest" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Light filtering through the branches casts a hazy, warm glow to all it touches, from the snake-like moss roped around the trees to the new shoots of vegetation pushing up through the moist soil at the edge of the road.  Staggered puddles of water fill the deep wheel gashes slashed into the trail.  As each wagon passes, the puddle configuration changes, as the waters mingle and advance down slope toward the marshland.</description>
    <description>The wind filtering through the branches sings a soft evening lullaby, accompanied by the creak of limbs and gentle percussion of the snake-like moss thumping the trees.  Staggered puddles of water fill the deep wheel gashes slashed into the trail.  As each wagon passes, the puddle configuration changes, and the waters mingle and advance down slope toward the marshland.</description>
    <position x="100" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Old Crank's Road, Marsh" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Thick planks of wood are layered lengthwise across the path at uneven intervals in an attempt to make the marsh passable.  Even with the lumber supports, the deep muck reaches halfway to the hub of a wagon wheel.  Swarms of invisible insects bite the exposed flesh of person and beast alike -- and more than one traveler has emerged from the marsh with a new, parasitic companion.</description>
    <position x="100" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="rt north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Old Crank's Road, Marsh" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Mud and water make sucking sounds against the lumber supports as the weight of vehicles and pedestrians presses down hard upon the sludge-soaked road.  Water pools among the reeds and fronds of grass.  A wagon has been shoved into the marsh, and from its decayed appearance, the wagon has been there a very long time.  Southward, the marsh gives way to a small section of fields.</description>
    <position x="100" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="rt north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Old Crank's Road, Field" note="RTZ24|RT-IT-LF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The dark soil is damper to the north where the road emerges from the marsh than it is to the south.  The dryer earth has been cultivated with cotton -- in the spring the delicate plants push through the dirt, the early summer brings rich full-bodied plants heavy with pink blossoms and the late summer foreshadows winter as the boles of cotton burst open to give the appearance of a heavy snowfall held aloft by dark, leggy stalks.</description>
    <position x="100" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Old Crank's Road, Carleen's">
    <description>Set some distance off the road on the opposite side of a clearing large enough to accommodate dozens of caravans, Carleen's is housed in a garishly decorated building replete with signs touting the wonders to be found within:  "Nutlogs!" "Thick Beer!" and "Souvenirs!"  A picnic table and benches offer a respite from the rigors of life's journeys.  For those who can resist Carleen's blandishments, the road curves westward toward a large meadow.</description>
    <description>Set some distance off the road on the opposite side of a clearing large enough to accommodate dozens of caravans, Carleen's is housed in a garishly decorated building replete with signs touting the wonders to be found within:  Nutlogs! Thick Beer! and Souvenirs!  A picnic table and benches offer a respite from the rigors of life's journeys.  For those who can resist Carleen's blandishments, the road curves westward toward a large meadow.</description>
    <position x="80" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garish building" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Old Crank's Road, Meadow">
    <description>Stretching in a general east to west line, the road follows the topography of the gently rolling meadowland, at one point following a wide stream, at another veering across an expanse of grass, colorful flowers and mushroom rings.</description>
    <position x="60" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Forest and meadow meet at the easternmost curve of the dirt road.  As the eye follows the transition of woods melting into meadow -- or meadow rising to become woods -- the trees begin to dwarf and the shrubs become giant, giving the impression there is no sheer demarcation, but a gradual, subtle transformation.  At the eastern most part of the path, where the meadow begins, several colonies of pale puffball mushrooms dot the side of the road, growing peacefully beneath the cover of overgrown weeds.</description>
    <position x="20" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Moss, shrubs, vines and trees are an overwhelming presence of unrelieved green.  The pearlescent droplets of moisture that cling to the tree trunks and leaves have taken on the green hue of their host.  Even the pathway underfoot, carpeted by a squishy lichen, is an unexpected green-brown.</description>
    <position x="20" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" note="RTZ25|RT-IT-LNW" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Considerably drier than the lower lying points of the forest, the dirt road threading this section of land is firm and the ruts are less noticeable.  The air has a fragrant tang from the pines and firs growing in profusion, and seasons of fallen leaves coating the path muffle the sounds of travel.  Northeast, the ground seems to slope slightly upward.</description>
    <position x="0" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Dodging the trees and thorny bushes, the muddy path swings from the west to a northeasterly course.  A moldy green film coats the tree trunks and clings to the rock surfaces.  As the road bends further into the forest, the earth looks drier and the wheel gashes left in the soil have a crusted appearance.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="west" move="rt west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" note="RTZ26|RT-IT-GPN" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Leaves and debris fallen from the trees have done little to soak up the moisture from the soft, damp earth that composes the road.  Heavily rutted, large puddles of muck fill the deep tracks sliced into the trail by passing wagons.  A narrow ditch runs parallel to the path, but the water that drains into it is not enough to dry its surface.</description>
    <position x="-70" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="rt east" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="west" move="rt west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Beneath the cover of the bushes, a quartet of red-capped mushrooms grows among grasses lining the road.  Overhead, the limbs of the canopy sway, sending shivers down the ropes of moss that hug the tree trunks and dangle from the branches.  Maneuvering tightly between the trees, the dirt path swings from the northwest to an easterly course.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Clumps of ferns and weeds carpet the spaces between the massive trees.  Curving tightly to the southeast, the narrow, dirt cart path picks its way more deeply into the woods, skirting the myriad of trees and roots and tall shrubs.  Northwest, a break in the trees offers some promise of escape from the forest.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go break" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Ilaya Taipa, Southwest Gate">
    <description>The land around the town wall has been cut clear of brush and trees, leaving an open area about twenty paces across.  The forest looms nearby, however, with tall trees and closely growing shrubs making it hard to see the road beyond the break in the trees.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go southwest gate" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go break" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Ilaya Taipa, Southwest Gate">
    <description>Vivid red and gold lacquer decorates the iron bands of the gate to the southwest.  The stone walls of the town are carved with images of fierce beasts and fanciful creatures, and the gate itself is framed by a pair of oversized granite mermen holding tridents at the ready.  The forest crowds close around the town walls, no more than twenty paces beyond the gate.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go southwest gate" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>A broken board has been mended with a support brace, carefully secured with bent-over nails.  The new wood is lighter in color than the surrounding slats, not yet greyed by exposure to the elements.  Sailors and merchants brush past on their way to and from the ships swaying beside the nearby pier.</description>
    <description>A broken board creaks underfoot despite the carefully secured cleat used to mend it.  Ships sway at their moorings along the nearby piers.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden pier" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Stone walls, stained green by years of exposure to water and weeds, provide a barrier between the shore and the deep waters along the southern end of the cove.  A bucket of whitewash sits beneath the railing of the boardwalk, its acrid smell mingling with the aroma of drying fish, and that of the resinous pine boughs from the forest outside the town.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Huddled amongst the gulls that scream noisily atop the wooden pilings of a nearby pier, a local wag has placed an articulated wooden pelican.  Its deep bowl-shaped beak bobs up and down, spilling dribbles of rainwater as it does, to reveal a golden fish swimming within, while its wings are poised to spin in the breeze.</description>
    <description>Barely visible in the gloom, an articulated wooden pelican hunches atop one of the pilings on a nearby pier, surrounded by sleeping gulls.  From time to time, its wings spin as a breeze drifts in from the water of the cove.  Torches flicker in their tall reed holders along the boardwalk, bathing the area in a fitful light.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden pier" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>An occasional metallic clang echoes beneath the boardwalk, drawing attention to a rope tied to the harbor-side railing.  At the other end of the rope, flies congregate, thick and black, around a bucket of chopped fish half-submerged in the water below.  The rope holds the bucket in place, keeping the fish cool until it is needed for bait later in the day.</description>
    <description>An occasional metallic clang echoes from the water beneath the boardwalk, drawing attention to a rope tied to the harbor-side railing.  At the other end of the rope, barely visible in the dim light, a tin bucket floats, half-submerged, in the water below.  Given the strong smell of dead fish along that side of the walkway, this is probably a local fisherman's supply of bait, kept cool in the water until the next morning.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Water splashes against the weed-cloaked wooden pilings of a nearby pier.  Merchant ships stop off at the village in the course of their trading, visiting family or replenishing supplies, but always offering their goods for sale during their visit.  The wares available change from day to day as one ship leaves and another takes its place, but the piers offer a place for shoppers to find almost anything, eventually.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden pier" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shipyard">
    <description>Suspended in the wheeled wooden frame of the dry dock, an elderly trawler is having its hull scraped of weeds before receiving a new coat of buckram wadding and tar to make it water-tight.  An assortment of lumber lies off to one side, ready for any repairs which might be needed during the course of the work.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby harbor" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shipyard">
    <description>An elaborate wooden frame cradles a half-finished ship.  Broad-beamed with a shallow keel, the vessel looks to be a typical craft of the River Elves, made to ply the waters of the Selgotha or hug the coast of the ocean, rather than to venture in the open seas.</description>
    <position x="0" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby harbor" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shipyard">
    <description>Freshly painted dinghies lean against the frame of an empty dry dock, the colors vivid against the faded grey wooden struts.  Neat coils of rope and fishing tackle shelter beneath each upended boat.</description>
    <position x="20" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby harbor" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>A willow tree sways in the wind, its green branches trailing down to kiss the waters of the cove.  On the opposite side of the road, the plaster walls of the inn bear the impressions of seashells of various shapes and sizes, the textured surface mirroring the carvings along the town's stone walls.</description>
    <position x="20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small inn" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Fish swim in low tanks in front of a small, reed-thatched plaster cottage, half-hidden behind dense thickets of water plants.  Swaying above the door is a sign carved in the shape of a bristle-nosed catfish holding a flowing ribbon painted with the words, Fernwyk's Fisherie.</description>
    <position x="20" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shallow ramp" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plaster cottage" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>A two-story building with a stucco exterior, wide shuttered windows and a red tile roof sprawls to one side of the road.  Side wings stretch out to the north and south from the central courtyard, the northern wing containing a stable with stalls for pack animals, dimly visible in the shadows, while the southern wing appears to hold living quarters.  Seashells impressed in the plaster above the front door have been carefully arranged to form a mosaic ship, sails billowing before the wind.</description>
    <position x="20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go two-story building" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>The walkway's wooden boards sag beneath the weight of foot and wagon traffic, allowing the muddy ground to ooze up between the gaps.  Brighter beams reveal recent patches, but soon enough they, too, will fade to a weathered grey beneath the onslaught of the elements.</description>
    <position x="20" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Warehouses rise in the shadow of the shore wall, providing storage for Elothean cotton and Elven silk, Halfling brass work and Dwarven gold -- anything that would be shipped up and down the river by the River Elves.  Workers trundle in at all hours, laden with anonymous barrels and bundles.</description>
    <position x="0" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Rickety wooden frames leaning against the town wall support an array of butterflied fish in various stages of desiccation.  Smoke wafts up from a hut to one side, and the air is redolent with the scent of apple wood.  Apprentices work outside the fishmonger's stall, packing the salted and smoked product into barrels for shipment throughout the lands.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fishmonger's stall" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Wooden planks laid in the muddy ground provide support for wagons and passers-by alike.  Vivid enamel paint highlights graceful carvings of fish and water plants in a frieze along the length of the town's stone wall.  Few houses huddle beneath the shadows of the battlements -- most of the town's permanent residents prefer the comfort of their ships, or the stilt-like homes built directly over the waters of the cove.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Ilaya Taipa, Northern Gate">
    <description>Wagon wheels leave deep ruts in the wooden planks of the town's wall road.  Traffic passes through the elaborately carved gates beneath the watchful eyes of guards armed with fishing spears.  Vivid red and gold enamel picks out the details of the gate frame's carvings, and stone mermen, their nets forming the portcullis, stand sentinel on either side of the gatehouse.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go northern gate" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Stretching out to the southwest, the river wall rises from a stone causeway to block the mouth of the cove.  The wall ends in a high tower halfway across, connected by a bridge to its mate further on.  Sturdy gates barred by heavy beams provide access to the piers outside the walls.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Ilaya Taipa, Northeast Harbor Wall">
    <description>Stone walls run almost the entire length of the harbor, save for a gap about thirty paces wide through which ships may enter their home port.  A log boom stretches between two towers to bar that gap, allowing only those whose identity has been verified by the guards to make their way into the village itself.  Heavy oak doors in the wall provide access to the outer docks where foreign traders may unload their wares.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak doors" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Ilaya Taipa, Northeast Harbor Wall">
    <description>A creaking sound harmonizes with the rhythm of the water as it flows between the two towers along the river walk.  To the southwest a door leads into the tower proper, while a stone bridge arcs between the two roofs, high enough to allow tall-masted ships to pass beneath.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go harbor tower" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Harbor Tower, First Floor">
    <description>A sturdy desk stands about five paces from the door.  Papers lie in neat stacks along the edges, recording the entry and exit times of ships visiting the village docks, along with brief notes on their cargoes.  Maps on the walls detail the twists and bends of the Selgotha, with thick grease pencil marks on the glass covers marking temporary variations: sandbanks, log jams or any other hazards to navigation.  A curving stone ramp winds around the tower wall, leading up to the living quarters above.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone ramp" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Ilaya Taipa, Water Walk">
    <description>Flimsy wooden crates lie piled one atop the other outside a nearby building.  From the smell, each holds some kind of animal, though it's difficult to make out just what kind.  Bundles of herbs hang from the eaves, drying slowly in the damp air of the harbor.</description>
    <position x="0" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small shop" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Ilaya Taipa, Water Walk">
    <description>The walkway's wooden lathes have been arranged in a decorative herringbone pattern, angling into a fan shape as a smaller walk branches off to the northwest.  Simple homes cluster along the edge of the smaller walk, the stilt-legged structures swaying slightly with the current.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plaster shop" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Ilaya Taipa, Yol Dushmal">
    <description>Like the other buildings along the water walks, the homes on either side of Yol Dushmal are simple, round structures supported above the water of the harbor by bamboo reeds lashed together to form flexible pilings.  The result is a building which bows before forceful winds, setting up a gentle rocking motion reminiscent of a ship's deck.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden shack" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Ilaya Taipa, Yol Dushmal">
    <description>Not unlike a garden in a land-based dwelling, the boardwalk winds its way through water gardens.  Mangrove trees shade the walkway, their gnarled roots lifting their trunks clear of the harbor, while around them, cattails and tall, purple-spiked flowers cluster densely in the shallows and floating pink-petaled water lilies drift in deeper waters.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Ilaya Taipa, Yol Dushmal">
    <description>Near the shore a willow tree leans harborward, its pale green branches trailing over into the water around the homes.  Bright orange jewelweed clusters along the bank, the tiny flowers looking somehow faded in the sunlight.</description>
    <description>Near the shore a willow tree leans harborward, its pale green branches trailing over into the water around the homes.  Bright orange jewelweed clusters along the bank, the vibrant color of the blossoms faded beneath the moonlight.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Ilaya Taipa, Yol Dushmal" note="Telescope">
    <description>The overhanging trees so prevalent along the twisting walkway thin out along the end, providing a clear view of the sky.  Only a few homes cluster about, leaving room for future growth of the village.  Beside the railing a brass telescope is tilted up toward the sky.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Ilaya Taipa, Water Walk">
    <description>The sound of water is strong here, drawing attention to a nearby chapel.  Fragrant cedar boughs cover the building's thatched roof and small glass mobiles of soaring seabirds dangle from its eaves.  The pale plaster frame is impressed with images of the sea and of merfolk swimming within its embrace.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plaster chapel" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Ilaya Taipa, Water Walk">
    <description>Standing alone in majestic splendor, the council hall is the largest building along the water walk with a wide deck surrounding the circular thatched-roof structure to provide additional space for gatherings in warmer weather.  Wooden benches along the railings on either side of the walkway provide a place to relax and watch the ships in the harbor or to fish in the water below.</description>
    <position x="-110" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Water Deck">
    <description>Impressed into the soft white plaster of the well of the council hall, images of shells and fish mingle with pictures of fantastical sea creatures.  Beneath the frieze, wooden benches nestle in the shelter of the overhanging thatched roof, while a rope ladder, swaying over the side of the railing, leads down to the water below.</description>
    <position x="-130" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Water Deck">
    <description>An opening in the walls, veiled by a curtain of swaying bamboo reeds, leads into the council hall to the south.  The breeze from the water cools those who loiter on the deck with its gentle caress.</description>
    <position x="-150" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Water Deck">
    <description>Sunlight reflects upward from the water, an effect anticipated by the designers of the council hall.  The deep carvings on the frieze along this length of the plaster walls angle outward, casting shadows that emphasize the design of marine life and merfolk and give a sense of half-seen creatures hidden behind the wavering plants depicted in the image.</description>
    <description>Moonlight reflects upward from the water, an effect anticipated by the designers of the council hall.  The deep carvings on the frieze along this length of the plaster walls angle outward, casting shadows that emphasize the design of marine life and merfolk and give a sense of half-seen creatures hidden behind the wavering plants depicted in the image.</description>
    <position x="-170" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Water Deck">
    <description>Wooden planters overhang the railings allowing cascades of bright orange jewelweed blossoms to spill over the edge of the deck.  The fragrant flowers perfume the air on lazy summer afternoons, though the fragrance is considerably less noticeable the rest of the year.</description>
    <description>Wooden planters overhang the railings allowing cascades of moon-bleached jewelweed blossoms to spill over the edge of the deck.  The fragrant flowers perfume the air on cool summer evenings, though the fragrance is considerably less noticeable the rest of the year.</description>
    <position x="-170" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Water Deck">
    <description>The sound of music drifts over the water from the ships around the water walk, jaunty jigs to set the listener's toes to tapping.  Vines sway from window boxes set along the edge of the council hall's thatched roof, shading the seats beneath the eaves from the bright glare of the sun.</description>
    <description>The sound of music drifts over the water from the ships around the water walk, soft, dreamy melodies that are perfect for dancing or just for snuggling with a loved one.  Thick vines grow in boxes along the edges of the thatched roof of the council hall, shading the seats beneath the eaves and providing a quiet place to linger and talk.</description>
    <position x="-150" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Water Deck">
    <description>The southern side of the deck looks out over the shipyard to the southeast where workers labor at the hulls under construction.  The sound of hammers and saws busily at work echoes over the water, competing with the shrill whine of pulleys as sails are raised and lowered.  Through it all the sharp scent of pine resin overlays the mustiness of decaying weeds.</description>
    <description>The southern side of the deck looks out over the shipyard to the southeast, now silent in the darkness.  Outside the town, the harsh cries of forest animals mingle with the soft splash of unseen oars in the nearby water.  Through it all the sharp scent of pine resin overlays the mustiness of decaying weeds.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Gathering Room">
    <description>A dais at the end of the hall provides a place for musicians to play during dances, the sound carrying through the open doorway to the deck that encircles the building.  The hall sways slightly before the wind as its bamboo supports flex in response, setting up a gentle rocking motion reminiscent of a ship's deck.</description>
    <position x="-150" y="157" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Meeting Room">
    <description>Most of the work of the council is conducted in the meeting room with its wide glazed windows and the vine-curtained opening onto the building's deck to the north.  Wooden chairs with comfortable cushioned seats snuggle around the central table, and high braziers in the corners provide both light and warmth.</description>
    <position x="-150" y="143" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Gathering Room">
    <description>The council hall features wide windows shaded by the overhanging eaves, allowing a cooling breeze to flow through the long chamber during the hotter months.  The gathering hall, occupying the southern half of the circular building, is a place for town meetings, dances, and other public assemblies.</description>
    <position x="-137" y="157" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Entrance" note="Council Hall">
    <description>A thick blue carpet cushions the floor of the entrance hall, flanked by torchieres on each corner.  The flickering lights illuminate the entry and help take the chill from the room.</description>
    <position x="-123" y="157" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Ilaya Taipa Council Hall, Judgement Chamber">
    <description>A dais at one end of the room holds a bench and table behind which the council may sit in judgement.  The carefully arranged accessories atop the table include a bell with a matching brass hammer, a log book, and several tightly rolled scrolls.</description>
    <position x="-137" y="143" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shipyard">
    <description>The scent of pine trees drifts over the walls from the nearby forest.  Within the town, wooden frames erected by the shore hold ships in various stages of construction.  Nearer the walls, stacks of lumber and tall pine masts, carefully arranged and rotated from time to time, dry before use.</description>
    <position x="20" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shipyard Gate">
    <description>Tall stone guard towers shaped like spiraling shells frame the wide wooden gates that lead to the forest outside the walls.  Like the main gates on the northern side of the town, the interior side is carved with elaborate images of sea creatures, highlighted with vivid enamel.</description>
    <position x="0" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shipyard gate" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shipyard">
    <description>The wooden walkway winds back and forth between stacks of lumber and supply sheds, passing further from the shore as it makes its way through the shipyard.  Green glass floats sparkle on nets hanging along the side of a sailmaker's loft.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>A wooden pier branches off from the boardwalk, home to assorted ships visiting the port.  Pale green net bags hang along the railing, holding wild onions and hot peppers and other ingredients for the spicy local cuisine.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden pier" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Wooden barrels split in half hold a pair of small balsam trees that scent the air with their resinous fragrance.  Red ribbons tied to their branches hold scraps of paper with prayers for a safe voyage or the return of an overdue ship.  Sailors consider the balsam lucky, and many of the ships anchored in the cove sport garlands wound around a mast or wreaths decorating the figurehead.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Ilaya Taipa, Shore Road">
    <description>Wooden pilings frame a nearby pier, the rising posts carved to resemble waist-high wooden soldiers painted in bright colors.  The paint has rubbed off on some of the figures where mooring lines have worn away at the finish.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden pier" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Ilaya Taipa, Southwest Harbor Wall">
    <description>A thick granite wall stretches across the mouth of the harbor, broken by a gap between two towers to allow ships passage within the town.  Two stories tall, the wall is wide enough for two guards to walk abreast on their rounds.  Ships of outsiders remain moored on the river side of the wall, their crews allowed to visit only on foot.  An iron-rung ladder fastened to the harbor side of the walkway leads down to the water.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron-rung ladder" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Ilaya Taipa, Southwest Harbor Wall">
    <description>The river wall's inner walkway ends at a door into the southwest tower, propped open by an overturned barrel.  The sides of the tower, smoothly joined blocks of granite, rise straight up from the water, offering no way for intruders to slip into town without passing through the scrutiny of the guards.  Overhead a stone bridge arcs between the roofs of the two towers, connecting them and reinforcing the structures.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go harbor tower" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Harbor Tower, First Floor" note="Harbor Tower|Weapons" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Racks of weapons line the walls, from distance weapons to boarding pikes, axes to harki knives.  Though the village is not martial in nature, the guards handle training the town's youngsters in basic self-defense and ship-to-ship combat tactics before any are expected to take up formal posts aboard ships.  The practice salle, with its weapons for sale, fills that need admirably.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone ramp" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Harbor Tower, Second Floor">
    <description>Stew bubbles in an iron pot atop the stove, permeating the air with the fragrant aromas of wild game and sweet onions.  Guardsmen can help themselves to a meal at any time, eating at the horseshoe-shaped table that encircles a spiral staircase leading up to the third floor.  Arrow slots run along the perimeter of the room, interspersed with wooden beds, most neatly made, a few sagging beneath the weight of an off-duty guard.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron staircase" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone ramp" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Harbor Tower, Bridge Floor">
    <description>Most watchrooms are similar throughout the world, the function dictating the form.  Double-glassed panes cover the windows along the perimeter, hinged to swing open like shutters when it's warm or closed against the wind when it's colder.  The windows afford a view of both the village below and the traffic along the river.  A narrow iron ladder leads up to the tower's roof.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron staircase" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Ilaya Taipa, Harbor Tower Bridge">
    <description>Wind whistles around the bridge passage, making the glass windows shiver before it.  The smell of soup or stew slowly simmering sends fragrant tendrils wafting from the southwest, the tower where the town guards reside.  To the northeast, the other tower handles the more administrative functions.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Ilaya Taipa, Harbor Tower Bridge">
    <description>High above the harbor gate, the tower bridge sways slightly with the wind, flexing before its force.  Flat-bottomed barges and tall-masted darters working the river pass beneath the bridge on their way to and from the town docks, heavily laden with trade goods.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Ilaya Taipa, Harbor Tower Bridge">
    <description>Glass windows line either side of the bridge passage that connects the two harbor towers, affording views of both town and river.  In cooler months, they trap the sun's heat, warming the walkway, while in hotter weather they will be flung wide to let in any cooler breeze.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron staircase" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Harbor Tower, Bridge Floor">
    <description>All along the tower walls, tall windows offer a view of the surrounding lands to the guards on watch.  Cleverly hinged like traditional wooden shutters, the doubled glass panes are left open in the warm weather to catch the river breezes, and closed tight during colder months to make watch duty less onerous.  A narrow iron ladder leads up through a trapdoor to the roof, and a passage to the southwest leads to the bridge connecting the two harbor towers.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron staircase" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Harbor Tower, Second Floor">
    <description>Wooden boxes line the tower walls of the storage room.  Files and provincial regulations vie with maps and impounded contraband for space in the seemingly chaotic assortment of containers.  A curving stone ramp coils around the outside of the room, making it easy for boxes to be moved up and down between storage and the main room of the guardhouse, while a circular iron staircase leads to the bridge deck above.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone ramp" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron staircase" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Ilaya Taipa, Pier" note="Pier 4 Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Blandly anonymous, as all such places are, the weathered boards of the pier creak underfoot.  Heavy pilings on either side are lashed together by layers of tarred rope.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="330" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go water" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Birds perch atop the pilings of a nearby pier, their raucous cries echoing across the water of the cove.  From time to time, one takes off with an ungainly lurch, spiraling as it rises on a thermal, or diving down beneath the surface of the water to disappear, emerging a few moments later with a wriggling silver fish caught in its beak.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby pier" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Frogs skim beneath the surface of the cove, strong thrusts of their hind legs sending them speeding, half-seen, through the murky water.  From time to time, a vivid blue kingfisher circles overhead, the predator's attention focused on its next meal.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Ilaya Taipa, Pier" note="Pier 2 Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Blandly anonymous, as all such places are, the weathered boards of the pier creak underfoot.  Heavy pilings on either side are lashed together by layers of tarred rope.</description>
    <position x="-170" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go water" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Ilaya Taipa, Pier" note="Pier 1 Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Blandly anonymous, as all such places are, the weathered boards of the pier creak underfoot.  Heavy pilings on either side are lashed together by layers of tarred rope.</description>
    <position x="-190" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go water" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The floor of the harbor is sandy at this end, the water a pale green unclouded by silt.  Dredging keeps the water deeper than most areas along the shore, allowing boats to sail to and from the nearby shipyards for repair.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shipyard" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Pinemast Field, Outside the Gate" note="Pinemast Field">
    <description>Light from the village illuminates the area just outside the gate, casting strange shadows.  Stumps and rocks grow into large and ominous shapes, while the slopes of nearby hills blend into the encroaching night.</description>
    <description>The vivid detailing of the village gate and wall is at odds with the bleak, barren land fronting them.  The rotted stumps of a few pines dot the ground, along with some coarse grass and weeds.  The trail from the gate runs northerly between sloping hillsides and randomly strewn rocks, while less definite paths run off in other directions.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go northern gate" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Pinemast Field, Winding Trail">
    <description>Large, loose rocks are scattered about the trails leading northeast and east, making them even rougher in the dark.  Sounds of insects chirping from the forest and small animals wending their way home fill the night air.  To the south, the only break in the perfectly smooth wall is a gate.</description>
    <description>To the south, the only break in the perfectly smooth wall is a gate.  Near the wall, sounds from the village intermingle with the faint sounds coming from the Segoltha's bank.  Faint tracks can be found leading off towards the more dense areas of growth in the field.  The trails leading northeast and east over the low-lying rocky hillocks are rough in spots, overgrown with weeds and grass in others.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Pinemast Field, Winding Trail">
    <description>Only stones and dirt mark the trail for what it is, making it difficult to traverse the path at night.  Careful steps are required to avoid stepping on small animals skittering here and there, amongst the other dangers of an overgrown pasture.</description>
    <description>Large boulders and pieces of fence keep the cattle from wandering beyond this pasture.  Small animals skitter through the overgrown field, while bird cries can faintly be heard coming from the riverbank.  Most of the area is covered with rocks and patches of grass, leaving few spots clear enough to mark a path here.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Pinemast Field, Winding Trail">
    <description>Even on the darkest of nights, one can feel the slow rise and fall of the drumlins while winding a path around them.  Though the path is not easily determinable, it's much easier than trying to climb the rock-strewn hills.  In contrast with the sparse foliage is the forest to the east, thick with trees and other vegetation.</description>
    <description>Drumlines rise across the field, making a straight path across the field nearly impossible.  Better luck is found winding around each of the low hillocks.  Overgrown grass, weeds and the occasional bush litter the area.  In contrast with the sparse foliage is the forest to the east, thick with trees and other vegetation.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Pinemast Field, Forest's Edge">
    <description>Pine trees loom on the upper slopes, standing guard over the backwoods through the night.  Shrubbery melds into rounded shapes forming a shadowed wall skirting the forest's edge.  Acorns crunching underfoot incite a faint rustling of leaves that echo in the darkness.</description>
    <description>Perched on the upper slopes pine trees flourish, patiently waiting the day of harvest to fulfill their destiny.  Along the backwoods stumps become less prevalent, and grasses give way to increased shrubbery, forming borders that fringe the forest's edge.  Ripe acorns, gifts dropped from elder oaks, entertain greedy squirrels, providing them with food as well as ammunition for the torment of unsuspecting adventurers.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Pinemast Field, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>Standing like sentinels edging the forest, tops of tall pines are swallowed in the darkness of night.  Covering the ground, nature has laid a blanket of leaves that's soft underfoot, muffling the sound of travel.  Large golden-capped mushrooms shine through the darkness in clusters around thick tree roots, thriving in the compost that scents the air.</description>
    <description>Standing like sentinels edging the forest, tall pines compete with white oaks in a never-ending race towards the sky.  Fallen needles blanket the ground, fragrant underfoot.  Large golden-capped mushrooms prized by local residents cluster around thick tree roots, thriving in the compost that scents the air.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Pinemast Field, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>Staggered pine trees form a windbreak, which borders this vast rolling field of low grass and beaten animal tracks.  Low stumps pepper the landscape, suggesting in the past the forest once spread quite a bit further toward the river to the west.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Pinemast Field, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>A rolling field covered in low verdant grass and branching animal trails falls away from the tree line, sloping down to the west only to rise gently again as it continues toward the river.  Tree stumps gradually give way to rockier loam, causing passage over land to be cautious at best and near impossible for anything other than foot traffic.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Pinemast Field, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>Through the darkness, only the outline of the looming forest is visible.  From the distance, a lone howl floats out from deep within the darkened woods.</description>
    <description>The field meets the edge of the forest here as mighty pine and oak trees reach upward, beginning to close off the view of the sky.  The ground is covered with branches and pinecones that have been blown off the nearby trees by a gust of wind.</description>
    <position x="0" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Pinemast Field, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>The darkness obscures the branch and twig-covered ground, with every step resulting in a loud cracking of a branch being broken.  The smell of pine fills the crisp night air as a gust of wind howls through the forest, warning travelers against entering the darkened timberland.</description>
    <description>The forest encroaches upon the field as grass gives way to broken branches and limbs.  The large trunks of the pine and oak trees make it difficult to see further into the woodland.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Pinemast Field, Along the Village Wall">
    <description>The occasional breeze from the west brings the scent of the Selgotha and the noise of revelry from the village along with it, enlivening the land.  The track is poorly seen at best, dark holes in the ground threatening to send travelers sprawling in the night.</description>
    <description>The occasional breeze from the west brings the scent of the Selgotha and the noise of the village shipyard along with it, enlivening the land.  The track this far south of the gate is still well-used, scarred by the hoof prints of bovine animals across the ground's surface.  The grasses continue to be cropped close, perhaps by the same animals.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Pinemast Field, Along the Village Wall">
    <description>Torchlight from the village casts the field in greys, showing the land to be devoid of the flourishing plant life found in the nearby forest.  The only objects that stand out in the dim light are the rotted stumps of trees and scattered rocks.</description>
    <description>The village wall runs through the area, the land paralleling it a sterile tract devoid of the flourishing plant life found in the nearby forest.  It makes an ideal killing ground should the village come under assault.  The only objects that mar the unremarkable ascent into the eastern hills are tree stumps and the occasional rock.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Pinemast Field, Grazing Tract">
    <description>In the distance, small sparks of light frame the village, like stars on a clear night.  The smell of fresh manure mingled with rotting wood hangs thick in the air.  An abandoned cart softened by the shadows appears much larger, looming over a delicate pink flower that stands out like a beacon in the darkness.</description>
    <description>Pine relics mark the field, left behind to defend the nearby village.  Stretches of overgrown scrub grass conceal thick roots that snake out from the stumps' bases, making travel risky.  The faint smell of manure mixed with freshly cut wood thickens the air.  An abandoned cart, overturned on its side, exposes a broken axle obviously beyond repair.  Remnants of an iron-rimmed wheel frame a lone pink lady's slipper orchid, showing its strong will despite its delicate beauty.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Pinemast Field, Grazing Tract">
    <description>Walls of pine join with an enormous boulder, casting a shadow that consumes the adjoining hillock's peak on moonlit nights.  Darkened shapes break through the land, appearing to march towards the forest.  Damp evening air carries the strong scent of elderberry, providing a perfect backdrop for a concert being performed by chirping insects who remain hidden from view.</description>
    <description>Off in the distance, an enormous boulder framed by walls of pine dominates the adjoining hillock's peak.  Scattered outcroppings, small hiccups of rock breaking through grassy surfaces of land, rise towards the forest's edge.  Trailing hoof prints pattern the dirt, pointing out favored grazing areas.  Briars of elderberry grow together in a wild tangle, bursting with flat plates of purple fruit, providing shelter and sustenance for chattering blue jays that harass cattle tempted by the bountiful treats.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Pinemast Field, Narrow Track">
    <description>Looming like a shadow over the uneven rocky terrain, a dark silhouette rises against the night sky.  The faint singing of the wind in the dry grass is the only sound in the vast silence of the empty land.</description>
    <description>Forming a tor atop one of the more prominent mounds, a line of protruding rocks provides shelter for bursts of wild grass that cling to them against the gusts of wind which sweep across the crest.  The land rises and falls in several directions, the swells of the uneven rocky landscape like gentle river waves.</description>
    <position x="0" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Pinemast Field, Narrow Track">
    <description>The sheer size of the boulder here makes it impossible to miss in the dark of the night.  Scatterings of smaller rocks about its base, treacherous enough by day, are even more hazardous in the evening, which adds to the perils of the already rough and tricky terrain.</description>
    <description>About the size of a mammoth sow and easily as difficult to shift, an enormous boulder dominates a depressed section of land, surrounded by a scattered litter of smaller rocks which the ravages of beasts and weather have caused to break off from the larger mass.  Coarse vegetation clings to the rocky soil, spread like a threadbare blanket.</description>
    <position x="20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Pinemast Field, A Grassy Hillock">
    <description>Walking is made slower and more dangerous by the wheel marks carved into the soft ground by wagons headed toward the nearby village.  In the distance, the faint sound of music rises into the air from the direction of the village.</description>
    <description>This grassy hillock lies between the fields to the north and the forest to the south.  On the hillock, the grass has been cropped closely in patches, and the softer portions of the ground show hoof prints.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Pinemast Field, Along the Village Wall">
    <description>The darkened corner of the field runs up against the wall, while to the south the path is blocked by a dense forest.  To the north in the distance, flames of the village torches are barely visible, and faint sound of music can be heard spilling out from inside the village walls.</description>
    <description>The sound of daily life from the nearby village floats through the air.  This area has been cleared of trees, leaving behind only stumps of the hapless victims ravaged by the village carpenters.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Pinemast Field, Winding Trail">
    <description>Wild and untamed, the field is perilous to climb through at night.  Stumps are scattered here and there, giving the weary traveler a brief respite from the dangerous work of climbing over and around these hillocks.</description>
    <description>The snaking paths are wild with weeds, rocks and grass.  Here and there, a pine tree's stump can be found, just tall enough to rest on for a moment or two.  On the western edge of the field, smooth walls are at odds with the wild land lying before it.  On the eastern side, the land is thick with trees.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Pinemast, Rocky Hills">
    <description>A looming darkness at the bottom of the hills blocks passage, while an occasional indistinct outline rises up out of the ground.  The crunch of small rocks alternates with the soft padding of grass underfoot.</description>
    <description>The land about has been thoroughly cleared, leaving no place of concealment for groups of any size.  Large boulders sit within the low spots between hills, forcing travelers onto their summits to continue.  Stumps of the pines that gave this place its name are scattered about, mostly overgrown with scrub grass and other low-lying vegetation.</description>
    <position x="-30" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Ilaya Taipa, Baso Dock" note="Map113_West_Segoltha.xml|Dock|Ain Ghazal">
    <description>The harbor wall towers high above the Baso, or Stranger's, dock.  While the interior town walls are elaborately carved and even highlighted with vivid, jewel-toned enamel, the outer have been smoothed as sheer as the stonemason's art can make them, providing no cracks where climbers could make their way up.  Foreign merchants must dock here to take on or offload cargo, or to pick up passengers for the trip up the river.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go skiff" hidden="True" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak doors" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Ilaya Taipa, Trader Outpost Furrier" note="Bundles|Knain" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Dominating the wall opposite the entrance, the stuffed head of a massive storm bull nearly distracts from the stench of decay and harsh chemicals.  Arches cut into the other walls lead to different parts of the outpost, elaborate carvings decorating their edges.  Oblivious to the commotion of business being conducted throughout the large space as well as the smell, the tanner works at the stained and warped wooden counter piled high with animal skins in various stages of curing.</description>
    <position x="40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Ilaya Taipa, Trader Outpost Gem Buyer" note="Gems" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A multitude of boxes stack upon the shelves lining the walls on the far end of this chamber, each a different size and type.  Decorated with a colorful mosaic, a polished counter dominates the room, giving space for record keeping.  Standing in the back corner, a guard keeps a watchful eye on all who pass through.</description>
    <position x="50" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Ilaya Taipa, Traders' Guild Outpost" note="Trader Outpost" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Despite the large board hung on the back wall and the built-in seating arranged around the room, this chamber appears to be used for no more than storage at the moment.  Shipping crates fill the area, a number of them open and their contents rummaged through.</description>
    <position x="30" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Ilaya Taipa, Trader Outpost Bank" note="Bank|Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Bright decorations offset the dim interior created by the dark paneling in this part of the outpost.  Shelves lined with vibrant textiles display an eclectic collection of multihued shells in varying sizes while an old fisher's net, mended with colorful threads, adorns the wall behind the counter.  A bored clerk stands idly nearby, waiting for business.</description>
    <position x="40" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wood counter" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Ilaya Taipa, Exchange Counter" note="Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Standing just to the side, the clerk that waits to help any patrons keeps a watchful eye on the items on the heavy wooden container.</description>
    <position x="50" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Old Crank's Road, Meadow">
    <description>Green and gold mingle at the boundary between the meadow and the wheat fields to the north.  The rutted dirt road meanders past a stand of trees, and bends southeast around a massive stump before entering a sparse forest.  A ring of blackened stones set away from the roadway marks a campsite used by many a traveler.</description>
    <position x="100" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Old Crank's Road, Wheat Field">
    <description>Continuing the interminable trudge through the wheat fields, a smear of color finally appears southward marking the edge of the vast grain sea where it meets a beach of meadow.  Northward, the plain ripples with a gilding of wheat, set with silos, barns, farms, and one lone, rutted road.</description>
    <position x="100" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Old Crank's Road, Wheat Field">
    <description>Deeply and unevenly rutted, this dirt cart path through the wheat fields makes for slow traveling as dray animals and those walking must both be careful of their step.  The ocean of grain stretches across the plain, the monotony of rich yellow broken only by an occasional farmstead or barn and the green band of weeds separating field and road.</description>
    <position x="100" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Old Crank's Road, Field">
    <description>Like a huge furrow plowed through a field of sun-drenched gold, the wide cart path follows a straight north to south course among the stalks of wheat rippling and swaying in the breeze.  In the distance, a dark-capped stone silo rises from the expanse of grain.</description>
    <position x="100" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Old Crank's Road, Plain">
    <description>Currently fallow, the land surrounding the cart track is deeply furrowed, with stray stalks of stunted wheat dappling the ground.  Encroaching from the forest's edge, weeds and wild taffelberry bushes threaten to reclaim this old field to the wild.  The road takes a gentle curve to the south and as it retreats from the wooded hills and continues downward to the cultivated acreage stretching out below.</description>
    <position x="100" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest Edge">
    <description>Southwest, the cart track leaves the forest and enters an area of fields and farms.  To the northeast, the road narrows as it enters the deep woods.  Stands of young ironwood and oak vie for space among the tall shrubs and weeds that border the road.  In the distant southwest, the terrain slowly flattens to a patchwork of fields and farms.</description>
    <description>Southwest, the cart track leaves the forest and enters an area of fields and farms.  Off to the northwest, the road narrows as it enters the deep woods.  Stands of young ironwood and oak vie for space among the tall shrubs and weeds that border the road.  Off in the distant southwest, the terrain slowly flattens to a patchwork of fields and farms.</description>
    <position x="120" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Splashing among the trees over a series of meandering stone terraces, a clear stream pauses momentarily to collect itself in a deep pool near the trail, then spills from the pool's lower lip to continue its winding path back into the deep forest.  A stone basin and water pump are set next to the trail, and directly opposite the basin is a series of hitching posts edging the cart track.</description>
    <position x="140" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Tufts of dragon lilies edge the rutted path, adding a vibrant wash of red and orange to the muted greens of the forest's trees, moss and weeds.  A nearby gurgle of water soaks the ear with sound, and the cool tang of damp earth tingles the nose.  Relatively straight through this section of the forest, the path becomes slightly wider as it flows southwesterly.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" note="Map61_Leth_Deriel.xml|Leth Deriel">
    <description>Stalks of spiny bladebrush growing along the roadside have been neatly pruned back to keep from attacking any passerby who stays to the trail, but the sharp fronds and thorn bushes discourage most from venturing into the woods.  A few scraps of tattered cloth and strands of beast-like hair prove that not everybody is so timid of the vicious plants.  The path is a misshapen fork, one tine pulling northwest, the other tine bending southwest.</description>
    <position x="180" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>In the waters near the shipyard, the sound of waves lapping against pilings mingles with the muffled peal of buoy bells.  A sharp tang of fresh pine and tar competes with the pervasive aroma of water and rotting wood common to any harbor town.</description>
    <description>In the waters near the shipyard, the sounds of hammers and saws mingle with the muffled curses of the unseen workers laboring at their craft.  A sharp tang of fresh pine and tar competes with the pervasive aroma of water and rotting wood common to any harbor town.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shipyard" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The harbor floor slopes up sharply to the east as you near the edge of the dredged channel leading from the river gate to the nearby shipyard, making the water appear lighter in color in that direction.  Small craft skim back and forth, skirting the edge of the water walk.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shipyard" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Ships make their way back and forth between the piers along the southwest side of town.  The village has few permanent shops, relying instead on the wares brought by merchants who ply their trade along the river.  One day, fiery hot peppers may be available, the next, ginger or a shipment of drums.  Though the shopkeepers may change with the tides, the village enjoys this way of life.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby pier" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Each bell on the buoys lining the channel has been tuned to a different key, creating a soothing harbor melody on calm days.  Their steady toll serves as a beacon for local pilots to navigate when other landmarks are obscured by darkness or rising mist.  Swelling waves result in a cacophony of sound before a storm to warn all who work the water to seek shelter.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A willow tree leans over the water, its branches floating down to enclose the area in a veil of pale green light.  The water flows gently here, a soft, rhythmic lapping against the pilings of the shore walk, contributing to the air of seclusion.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The bay is quiet now, save for the rhythmic slap of water against your body.  A blue-tinged glow to the north marks the glass of the chapel to Lemicus, beloved by the River Elves.</description>
    <description>Chanting drifts across the water, sometimes from workers in the shipyard, sometimes from the chapel on the water walk to the north.  Whatever the source, the sound carries, mingling with the sound of the bay itself, until the world seems filled with music.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The mouth-watering aroma of freshly grilled fish from a nearby restaurant drifts over the water, mingled with the scents of garlic and wild onions.  A shallow ramp provides access to the shore road for swimmers and any small craft which care to dock.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shallow ramp" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thick strands of rope lashed around bundles of bamboo reeds support clusters of freshwater mussels clinging to the pilings of the water walk.  Footsteps overhead echo beneath the walkway and cause the pilings to shiver, sending circular ripples across the surface of the harbor.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>An empty coracle drifts slowly across the harbor, rocked by the gently rolling waves.  The small wood-and-hide shell is popular with children despite, or perhaps because of, its instability.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Water splashes down along the glass sides of the chapel's sanctuary, located beneath the walk itself.  The flow splashes into the harbor, stirring up silt and sand, and clouding the interior of the room itself.  Wooden rungs nailed to a piling form an unsteady ladder connecting the harbor with the water walk above.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Swimmers must use caution this close to the water walk.  The current is tricky, the straight flow broken into a confusing swirl of eddies by the pilings.  Adding to the peril, tangled webs of lines lurk between the bamboo pilings to entrap the unwary, left by frustrated fishermen who favor the walk for their piscatorial pursuits, with the occasional carelessly flung fishhook, bait attached, providing comic relief.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The water surges back and forth, slapping against your body then quickly drawing away as waves stirred up by the traffic in the cove ripple toward the shore.  Beneath it all, pale sand and smooth pebbles appear to waver, distorted by the water between you and the harbor bed.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Here in the deepest part of the channel, the water is murky at best, as the current funneled through the narrow gap of the harbor gate churns up clouds of silt.  Despite regular dredging, the channel remains clouded by the rich, dark soil that settles near the shipyards to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pier" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The south side of the cove is too deep to touch the bottom, forcing you to tread water if you wish to look around.  Two-story walls surround the village, far enough away to look small from here, and the scent of evergreens drifts over the nearest wall from the forest outside.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>An intricate web of bamboo poles supports the buildings along the river walk, lashed together with hide lacings and fishing line.  The structures are carefully designed to press together in a wind, each slender pole reinforcing the next to allow the lightweight bamboo to support the heavier plaster buildings above.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Sweet-scented flowering vines spill over the railing of a balcony, trailing down to twine their glossy green tendrils along the close-lashed bundles of bamboo pilings that support the water walk.  Sounds carry across the water -- an unseen flutist playing a lullaby, a fishwife screaming at her children, or a bosun snapping orders aboard a ship.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A heron drowses in the shallows nearer the shore.  Gilded by moonlight, the blue-grey feathers stand out against the dark pilings of the shore walk.</description>
    <description>A heron, blue-grey feathers shimmering in the sunlight, wades through the shallows nearer the shore.  The feathers blend with the weathered grey of the wooden pilings along the shore walk, but it is visible from a distance as its head darts down to catch a small fish or something else in the water.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Local merchants ply their trade from nearby piers along the southwestern side of the village.  One day, a shipment of Dwarven brasswork may be available, the next, Elven flutes heading upriver to the Bards' guild.  The wares available change with the seasons and with the arrival and departure of the ships that ply the river trade.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby pier" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Brightly painted buoys mark the boundaries of the deep channel between the shipyard and harbor gates, and guide ships to the piers to the south and west.  Glass floats bob here and there throughout the cove, marking the location of fish traps suspended in the water.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Muddy green water laps against skin and tangles hair or fur.  In the distance, fishermen work from small boats to net fish swept into the harbor through the river gate.  These vessels stay out of the main channel to avoid fouling larger ships.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby pier" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Halfway between the residential part of the village to the northeast and the merchant piers to the southwest, the waters of the harbor are cool and dark, clouded with silt carried in from the river.  The silt settles as the current slows, and is then dredged from the bottom to keep the channels clear for larger ships, providing rich soil for the container gardens popular with local residents.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Barely visible in the silty water, sleek, silvery fish swim back and forth in search of food, brushing against your legs as they do.  The southern end of the harbor is busy with trading ships moored along the piers to the south and smaller ships carrying shoppers to greet any new arrivals.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Ships skim across the cove, tacking back and forth as they head toward the merchant piers along the southwest side of the village.  The larger vessels moored at the docks bring wares up and down the river -- dwarven stone and metalwork from the mountains, exotic foodstuffs and sundry other items.  On rare occasions, a ship may even carry trade goods from the Merelew.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby pier" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Cool breezes dance along the harbor, flirting with the ripples of the current and catching up wayward sprays of water.  To the northeast, the water walk rises up, an interlocking network of fragile bamboo reeds that support the homes and public buildings of the village.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Gulls skim across the water, their wings spread wide to catch the updrafts, ever alert to the possibility of food discarded by a passing ship.  To the east, the water walk rises on thick pilings from the harbor bed, curving slightly to shelter the stilt-legged plaster homes that sway in the wind above the water.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Lapping against your skin, the water near the entrance to the cove is darker than along the shore as silt from the river is churned up by water passing through the opening.  Black insects swim just beneath the surface, their legs moving in a crawling motion to propel them through the water at a fast pace.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Luminous moonlight reflects off the wake left by sailboats as they glide across the cove.</description>
    <description>Brilliant -- almost painfully bright -- light reflects off the ripples left in the wake of sailboats as they glide across the cove.  Small enough for children to handle, these craft are used for shopping and visiting between ships.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" hidden="True" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The residents of the cove are ever-changing as restlessness causes the locals to weigh anchor and move on.  No matter where they go on their journeys, however, they all return sooner or later to Ilaya Taipa.  The center of life is the village hall, a round, thatched-roof building on pilings at the end of the water walk.  A rope ladder sways near the water, allowing easy access to the hall from the harbor.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rope ladder" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Rough wooden pilings rise about a Tog's height above the surface, supporting the water walk.  While land-dwellers prefer to build their homes along the narrow shore, those River Elves who live here permanently tend to build along the water walk.  The resultant profusion of round, stilt-legged homes with thickly thatched conical roofs sway lightly as waves and wind act upon them, a rocking motion the residents find soothingly reminiscent of their beloved ships.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Narrow bamboo reeds are lashed together with fishing line at close intervals and sunk into the bed of the cove.  The interlocking scaffolds sway in the wind, bending but not breaking as they support the homes of local residents.  Above, a small neighborhood branches off from the main water walk, each home connected by walkways to its neighbor.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The deep, bass rumble of croaking frogs hidden beneath the wooden slats of the boardwalk mingles with the higher pitch of crickets on the shore.  From time to time the song of the wildlife is broken by the rhythmic splash of oars as residents make their way to and from their ships.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Damp laundry flaps on lines strung along the mast of a nearby sailing boat, the dull tans and browns of the clothing standing out against the background of the brightly colored sails.  Waves lap against the hull, providing a percussion accompaniment to the mournful melody of an unseen flutist.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A wide, conical straw basket floats in the water behind one of the houseboats, keeping some berries cool.  The smell of a cookfire drifts from another boat, as fish sizzles over a housewife's grill.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Reddish sand with crystal fragments sparkles beneath the surface here in the waters near the town gates.  A whitewashed boardwalk runs along the shore, its wooden boards creaking beneath the weight of foot and cart traffic as merchants carry wares between the ships and inland markets.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Flat-bottomed boats rock back and forth from rope-wound moorings sunk into the sandy bottom of the cove.  These ships are home to the local River Elves, who prefer to live on the water even when remaining in one place for extended periods.  Long poles allow the barges to be maneuvered from place to place when necessary, but for the most part these homes remain tied to the pilings.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Scraps of paper, skeletal leaves and other bits of debris from shore and ship surge back and forth against the base of the harbor walk, swept there by the current.  The footsteps of guards walking back and forth over the walkway echo over the water as they pace out their appointed rounds.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Constructed of red granite, the northern harbor tower looms high above the town walls.  A walkway runs along the inside of the wall, though the base is too steep to allow you to climb up to it.  To the southwest, the boom -- wooden logs connected by rusting iron chains -- stretches between this and the southern tower, preventing unknown ships from entering the village unless authorized by the guards.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The current surges strongly to the southeast, striving to tug you with it.  Gulls circle lazily above the water's surface, eyes alert to any food that might be tossed up by the flow.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Long tendrils of water weeds reach out to twine around limbs, lashed back and forth by the currents.  The limp green strands are hard to see in the silt-clouded water, but their touch makes their presence felt -- a cool brush against an ankle, a feathery caress of a wrist.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Water churns as it passes through the channel between the harbor walls, darkening the water with clouds of silt stirred up by the current.  A metal-rung ladder anchored to the side of the wall is slick with moisture and caked with flaking rust.  While it doesn't look terribly secure, it may allow you to scramble out of the water and onto the harbor walk.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb water-slick ladder" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>To the west, the southern tower of the harbor wall looms up over the water, rising steeply from the bed of the cove.  The channel is deep here, kept clear by regular dredging, to allow larger ships access to the village dockyards.  Wooden logs float across the entrance to the harbor, supporting a heavy iron chain that bars access to pirates and other unwelcome visitors.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Water swirls in fierce eddies as the current funnels through the gap in the harbor wall, carrying before it all in its path.  Small skiffs dart across the wake left by larger vessels to make their way toward the piers to the south.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Ilaya Taipa, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Lantern light flows across the dark water, the soft glow reflecting on the rippled surface as the current rushes through the harbor wall into the cove.  Small craft sail lazily back and forth across the water, carrying residents between their ships and the shore.</description>
    <description>Sunlight dapples the dark water with brilliant flecks of light as the current rushes through the harbor wall into the cove.  Small craft dart here and there across the water, carrying residents between their ships and the shore.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Ilaya Taipa, Pier" note="Pier 5 Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Blandly anonymous, as all such places are, the weathered boards of the pier creak underfoot.  Heavy pilings on either side are lashed together by layers of tarred rope.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="327" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go water" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Foyer">
    <description>A pallid fug of brandy fumes and tobacco wafts through the taproom's swinging doors, leaving a faint film on the golden oak paneling around the lobby.  From time to time, a jangle of keys being hung on or retrieved from their gilded hooks draws attention to the clerks who work behind the desk, but for the most part the room has a quiet club-like atmosphere, with thick red wool carpets, comfortable leather chairs and low tables around which visitors may gather to read or converse.</description>
    <position x="30" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go teak door" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go taproom" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide stairs" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Private Parlor">
    <description>Comfortable armchairs frame the fireplace in the private parlor, offering a peaceful spot for traveling couples or families to relax without having to endure the noise of the taproom.  Indeed, the overstuffed seats and the warmth of the fire have lulled many a weary traveler into a brief nap, only to be awakened by the sharp crack of a log breaking within the flames.  A slate menu stands atop the linen-draped table for those wishing to break their fast with the kitchen's offerings.</description>
    <position x="30" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Taproom" note="Zuhaichaga Inn|Taproom|dartboard" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Far livelier than the inn's foyer, the taproom bustles with traders and sailors perched atop wooden stools, haggling over business deals as they drink.  Sawdust covers the wooden floor, absorbing drinks spilled by barmaid or patron, and the long mahogany bar features carvings of voluptuous mermaids highlighted by gold and silver leaf.  The smell of tobacco dulls the aroma of food that wafts out each time the kitchen's door opens.</description>
    <position x="40" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Landing">
    <description>Delicate carved hollyhocks twined along a latticework background adorn the frame of a pale rose door on the landing.  To either side of the door, graceful palms sway in their hammered brass pots.  A narrow staircase leads up to the next floor, while wide stairs covered in floral tapestry runners sweep down to the foyer below.</description>
    <position x="30" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide stairs" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow staircase" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rose door" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Upstairs Hall">
    <description>A window seat nestles in a shallow nook at the end of the hallway where plush chintz-covered cushions provide a comfortable place to sit and look out at the lights on the harbor.  The hall itself is unremarkable, with no paintings or other decorations, just colorful painted doors to identify the guests' rooms: pale blue for the sirese blossom room and vibrant scarlet for the nightshade room.</description>
    <position x="30" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow staircase" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go scarlet door" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Sirese Blossom Room" note="Sirese Blossom Room">
    <description>A dried wreath of silver-green sage adorned with lavender and sirese blossoms hangs above the mantel, perfuming the air with a pungent herbal fragrance.  At the other end of the room, old-fashioned applique quilts cover the bed, a tall mahogany four-poster with a stepstool beneath it to allow guests to climb in.</description>
    <position x="40" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Hollyhock Room" note="Hollyhock Room">
    <description>White paper covers the walls, painted with images of hollyhocks in a range of colors, from dark red to pale pink and all the shades in between.  Cloudy wisps of gauze hang from the slender posts of the bed, and a white counterpane covers the feather mattress.  Bowls of dried lavender, mint and orange peel sit beside the hearth, perfuming the air with an intense, sweet fragrance.</description>
    <position x="40" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Fernwyk's Fish" note="Fernwyk's Fish|Fish|Aquariums" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Wooden stands line the walls, supporting water-filled glass tanks.  Some contain schools of silvery fish that wheel and dart in unison, others contain a single jewel-toned specimen against a backdrop of swaying water grass.</description>
    <position x="30" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Pischic's Pearls" note="Pischic's Pearls|Jewelry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Polished wooden apothecary cabinets hold row after row of tiny drawers along the far side of the shop.  Between the cabinets is a shallow workbench padded with soft velvet.  Soldering irons bristle amidst the coals of a brazier, kept hot until required for use.  Tendrils of smoke rising from the fire give the air of pleasant fragrance.  At the front of the store, an assortment of jewelry is displayed atop a dark case.</description>
    <position x="0" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Anyaila's Fine Clothing, Sales Floor" note="Anyaila's Fine Clothing|Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Shelves line the walls, filled with lengths of fabric in a wide range of colors and materials.  The wooden floor is littered with scraps of material and discarded bits of thread around the low stool where the seamstress works.  Above it all, a round shoemaker's lamp casts a steady light over the area.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Krimand's House of Stuff" note="Krimand's House of Stuff|General" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Layer upon layer of woven reed mats cushions the floor, doing little to disguise the tilting boards beneath.  Stacks of oilskin rain gear occupy a crate in the lowest corner of the store, while packs, panniers and other carriers hang from the center pole.  Assorted mirrors hang upon the far wall, swaying slightly with the movement of the water beneath the hut and sending rainbows of reflected light over the shop's flaking paint.</description>
    <position x="-30" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Ilaya Taipa, Fishmonger's Stall">
    <description>The smell is overwhelming as apprentices work packing fish into barrels of salt, into large stoneware jars with vinegar and capers, or onto drying racks.  Overseeing them all is Master Fisherman, Ynnve Todemar, a tall Elven man with dark hair and a sparse beard, wearing a leather apron to protect his clothes.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Ilaya Taipa, Fishmonger's Stall" note="Fishmonger's Stall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Fishing poles line up along the wall like soldiers standing at attention, their neat ranks broken by stacks of creels upon a small stand.  The stench of burning hair lingers around the workbench where a brazier smolders.  Beside the bench, an oversized wooden spool doubles as a table, holding an array of envelopes.  Still more envelopes are stuffed haphazardly into the workbench drawer, making it impossible to close.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Pinemast Field, Path to Forest">
    <description>A path winds through the rubble-strewn field between the Pinemast forest and the village gate.  Jagged stumps, about knee-high to an Elf, litter the surroundings -- relics of the shipbuilding for which Ilaya Taipa is known.  From time to time, teams of oxen strain against padded leather yokes as they drag a tall tree northward, but for the most part the trail is little used.</description>
    <position x="100" y="390" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go village gate" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Pinemast Forest, Outer Verge">
    <description>Scrubby bushes grow in tangled profusion along the edge of the forest, greedily drinking in the sunlight liberated by hewn trees.  The stumps of the fallen are left behind, littering the field around the village of Ilaya Taipa.  While not tall enough to provide any obstacles to archers within the walls, they do prevent the easy access of wagons except by the winding path.</description>
    <description>Scrubby bushes grow in tangled profusion along the edge of the forest, greedily competing for the light.  The stumps of fallen pinemast trees litter the field around the village of Ilaya Taipa, making the ground treacherous in the darkness.  While not tall enough to provide any obstacles to archers within the walls, they do prevent the easy access of wagons except by the winding path.</description>
    <position x="100" y="410" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Thick layers of rotting needles lie in rolling mounds at the base of the trees, enriching the soil and cushioning the footsteps of anyone or anything passing through the forest.  Though sunlight passes through the branches to cast lace-like shadows along the ground, the combination of rich soil and abundant illumination encourages the growth of dense thickets, sharp with thorns, that obstruct the view.</description>
    <description>Thick layers of rotting needles lie in rolling mounds at the base of the trees, enriching the soil and cushioning the footsteps of anyone or anything passing through the forest.  The rich soil encourages the growth of dense thickets, sharp with thorns, which make it hazardous to travel after dark.</description>
    <position x="110" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Shadows lurk beneath the branches of the pinemast trees, pooling amidst the fallen needles.  A faint path, little more than a deer trail, winds its way through the rough-barked trunks, splitting and twisting in a confusing tangle.  The lowest branch looms high above even a Gor'Tog's head, but rough scrub forms a thicket close to the ground, catching and tearing at clothing and skin of passersby.</description>
    <position x="90" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Straight and sturdy, the trunks of the pinemast trees rise around you, the rough black bark protected by mounds of thorny scrub.  The boughs rustle against each other in the wind, the lowest more than twice the height of a Gor'Tog.  Each tree is carefully nurtured by the local Elves, as the straight wood is favored for mast-making in their ships.</description>
    <position x="110" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>The sharp tang of pine needles fills the air as passing feet stir the thick layer of mulch fallen from the boughs of the pinemast trees.  Dappled patterns of light and shadow play across the ground, filtering through the branches to succor the tangle of thorny brush.</description>
    <description>The sharp tang of pine needles fills the air as footsteps stir the layer of mulch covering the ground, fallen from the high boughs of the surrounding trees.  Dappled patterns of starlight and shadow play across the forest floor, filtering through the branches and obscuring rather than revealing the tangle of thorny brush clustered around the path.</description>
    <position x="90" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Thick layers of pine mulch blanket the forest's floor and muffle the footsteps of its denizens.  The silence is broken from time to time by the cry of a bird or the sharp snap of a twig.  Only an occasional claw mark upon a tree trunk or feather fallen on the ground offers any indication that you are not alone beneath the overhanging boughs.</description>
    <position x="70" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>The thickets are thinner here as the tree trunks grow more closely together, filtering out the light.  Dense pools of shadow make it hard to see the trails that wind their way through the forest.  The skitter of a squirrel among the branches reverberates like the footfall of a giant as other senses strain to compensate for the reduced visibility.</description>
    <position x="130" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Beads of resin seep from the claw marks on the trunk of a pinemast tree, slowly healing the damage to the rough black bark.  Small insects can be seen within the sap, entombed in the sticky syrup as it hardened.  Branches rustle overhead, sending shadows dancing over the ground with each shifting movement.</description>
    <position x="130" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Elusive yet pervasive, the faint scent of smoke lingers in the forest, a reminder of the volatile nature of the resinous pinemast trees.  The dense scrub surrounding the tree trunks limits visibility and forces wayfarers to make their way carefully along the twisting trails through the woods.  Hidden from view, the crackle of branches and sound of birds singing are reminders that you are not alone.</description>
    <position x="110" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>A cleared space has been swept clean of pine needles and lined with rocks.  Within it, the cold ashes of a traveler's fire have mixed with rain and dew to form a brick-like mass that fills in the cracks between the rocks in the fire pit.  The scent of smoke is strong here, lingering long after the fire has gone out.</description>
    <position x="90" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>The scent of smoke tickles your throat, though the source cannot be seen.  Thick with resin, pinemast trees burn with fierce intensity that makes a forest fire an ever-present danger, especially during dry seasons.</description>
    <position x="70" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>Saplings battle for dominance in a small clearing, each vying for space as they race toward the sky.  Though slender and sparsely needled, the thin trunks' branches are disproportionately high.  As the trees grow, the lowest branch will be far above the ground, allowing secondary growth to sprawl along the forest floor.  The thorny nature of the scrub brush requires those who harvest the trees to wear thick clothing, or risk having the skin flayed from their bones.</description>
    <position x="110" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Pinemast Forest, Among the Trees">
    <description>The trails twist and wind about each other in a curious drunkard's path, swerving to avoid the thorny thickets that grow close around the trunks of the pinemast trees.  High branches result in plenty of air circulating along the ground, while the trees' fine needles allow light to filter through the canopy, creating ideal conditions for the scrubby bushes to thrive along the forest floor.</description>
    <position x="90" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Carleen's Emporium" note="Carleen's Emporium|Juggling" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Southwest, the cart track leaves the forest and enters an area of fields and farms.  To the northeast, the road narrows as it enters the deep woods.  Stands of young ironwood and oak vie for space among the tall shrubs and weeds that border the road.  In the distant southwest, the terrain slowly flattens to a patchwork of fields and farms.</description>
    <description>Stuffed with knick-knacks and kitsch treasures, this little shop is the perfect place to stop for a travel break.  Wooden shelves hold a variety of items suitable for mementos or gifts, and the back wall is devoted to a counter holding refreshments.  A note with a platinum kronar encased inside its glass frame hangs on the wall behind the attendant.</description>
    <position x="90" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Ilaya Taipa Chapel, Antechamber" note="Chapel">
    <description>Scattered along the polished grey floor, nubby silk cushions provide a place for worshippers to rest and chat with each other.  A low table in the center of the antechamber holds a small brazier filled with resinous woods that perfumes the air as it warms the room, the smoke rising in lazy circles to escape through vents in the thatched roof.  Wavering light reflects up a blue-green stairway from the sanctum below.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pointed arch" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go swinging door" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb blue-green staircase" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Ilaya Taipa Chapel, Library" note="Library">
    <description>Heavy oil lamps hang over each of the tables in the library, each suspended by three sturdy chains from hooks in the ceiling joists.  The arrangement of chains allows the lamps to sway freely as the building's bamboo supports flex before wind and wave, keeping the light steady yet reducing the chance of fire from an overturned candle.  Glass-fronted bookcases keep the chapel's precious books and scrolls safely tucked away until needed by a scholar.</description>
    <position x="-90" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pointed arch" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Ilaya Taipa Chapel, Schoolroom">
    <description>Rows of tables face a dais at the far side of the small room, each with a pair of low seats beneath it.  Here, the village priest doubles as a teacher to the young, instructing them in their letters as well as their heritage.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go swinging door" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Ilaya Taipa Chapel, Inner Sanctum" note="Depart|Lemicus|Shrine" color="#400040">
    <description>Blue-green stairs shimmer like ice as they curve around the outer perimeter of the room.  Something, either magic or mechanical, causes water to flow continuously down the outside of the sanctum's glass walls, flooding the interior with wavering light.  Concentric rows of benches angle down toward the central altar, a simple piece of polished grey driftwood decorated with scattered water lilies.</description>
    <description>Blue-green stairs shimmer like ice as they curve around the outer perimeter of the room.  Something, either magic or mechanical, causes water to flow continuously down the outside of the sanctum's glass walls, flooding the interior with wavering moonlight.  Concentric rows of benches angle down toward the central altar, a simple piece of polished grey driftwood decorated with scattered water lilies.</description>
    <position x="-90" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb blue-green staircase" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Harbor Tower, Roof">
    <description>High above the town walls, the roof of the tower commands a wide view.  A slotted bronze brazier, cold during the daylight hours, is fastened to the stone floor and surrounded by tempered glass panes that blunt the force of the wind.  At dusk, the brazier will be lit to guide ships on the river.  Mounted along the tower's wall, a sturdy telescope points up to the heavens.</description>
    <description>A bright fire burns in a slotted bronze brazier.  From dusk until dawn, the fires burn atop this and the neighboring harbor tower to guide river traffic to safety.  A sturdy telescope mounted along the tower's wall points up toward the heavens.</description>
    <description>High above the town walls, the roof of the tower commands a wide view.  A bright fire burns in a slotted bronze brazier, sheltered from the winds by tempered glass panels fastened to the stone floor.  From dusk until dawn, the fires atop this and the neighboring harbor tower are carefully tended, guiding river traffic to safety.  Evidently one of the guards is an amateur astronomer, for a sturdy telescope is mounted along the tower's wall.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Harbor Tower, Roof">
    <description>A hexagonal array of tempered glass panes surrounds a wide bronze brazier, shielding the signal fire from the wind and rain when it is lit.  Traffic along the river depends on the tower fires to navigate after dark.  In the daytime, the braziers remain cool and the bronze and glass are polished by young guardsmen to remove the night's accumulation of soot.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Ilaya Taipa, Pier" note="Pier 3 Shop|Dusktide Rising" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Blandly anonymous, as all such places are, the weathered boards of the pier creak underfoot.  Heavy pilings on either side are lashed together by layers of tarred rope.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go water" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Zuhaichaga Inn, Scarlet Nightshade Room">
    <description>Narrow tendrils of smoke curl up from a brass brazier nestled beside the hearth, as burning incense gives rise to a heavy sandalwood fragrance that permeates the room.  Black lacquer with gold leaf tracery decorates the pencil post bed and a thin black coverlet edged with bands of brightly colored abstract embroidery covers it.  Beside the fire, a pair of rattan armchairs provide a comfortable place for guests to relax before going to sleep.</description>
    <position x="30" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <label text="To Leth Area">
    <position x="140" y="50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="stormbulls">
    <position x="10" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="forest bandits">
    <position x="120" y="470" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ilaya Taipa">
    <position x="-80" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Ain Ghazal">
    <position x="-150" y="40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="aquariums">
    <position x="33" y="233" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="inn">
    <position x="45" y="263" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="bank">
    <position x="30" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="gems">
    <position x="55" y="152" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="bundles">
    <position x="35" y="165" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="chapel">
    <position x="-108" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="weapons">
    <position x="-255" y="212" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="general">
    <position x="-51" y="131" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pinemast Field">
    <position x="10" y="-50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Council Hall">
    <position x="-195" y="185" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pinemast Forest">
    <position x="-18" y="442" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>