<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Crossing Amusement Pier" id="1l">
  <node id="1" name="The Crossing, Esplanade Eluned" note="Map1_Crossing.xml|Crossing">
    <description>An apparent contradiction, the toney esplanade here is right in the midst of a group of warehouses to the north and the customs and storage house of Riverfront Portage to the west.  The strollers and workers mingle, with most of the leisure traffic centering around the noisy amusement pier to the south.</description>
    <position x="120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go amusement pier" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany building" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Amusement Pier, Entrance" note="Amusement Pier">
    <description>Throngs of children mill around, licking lollipops and poking at one another.  Salty air drifts upon the wind, causing bits of old paper to dance around freshly painted garbage bins.  Various buildings and attractions are visible further down the wide wooden and metal pier.</description>
    <description>Salty air drifts upon the wind causing bits of old paper to dance around half-full garbage bins, while sweepers go by cleaning up the day's refuse.  Various buildings and attractions are visible in the torchlight further down the wide wooden and metal pier.</description>
    <position x="120" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elaborate gate" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Amusement Pier, Este Lane">
    <description>Gentle waves lap against the huge poles that bear the weight of this busy pier.  Sturdy rails are placed along the edges, keeping stray children from tumbling off into the cold waters below.</description>
    <description>Gentle waves lap against the huge poles that bear the weight of this quiet pier.  Sturdy rails are placed along the edges, keeping stray children from tumbling off into the cold waters below.  Brightly lit lanterns attract colorful moths to dance within their flames.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Amusement Pier, Centre Lane">
    <description>The breeze carries with it a tangy citrus scent from a small wooden stand whose base is carved with painted lemons.  A few stools offer seating for those wishing to enjoy the fruity lemonade sold by a Gnome maid who wears a pointed hat dusted with glitter.</description>
    <description>The breeze carries with it a tangy citrus scent from a small wooden stand whose base is carved with painted lemons.  A few stools offer seating for those wishing to enjoy the fruity lemonade sold by a Gnome maid who wears a pointed hat dusted with glitter.  The torchlight gives her face a warm glow as she smiles at customers.</description>
    <position x="120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Amusement Pier, Wilde Lane">
    <description>Gentle waves lap against the huge poles that bear the weight of this busy pier.  Sturdy rails are placed along the edges, keeping stray children from tumbling off into the cold waters below.</description>
    <description>Gentle waves lap against the huge poles that bear the weight of this quiet pier.  Sturdy rails are placed along the edges, keeping stray children from tumbling off into the cold waters below.  Brightly lit lanterns attract colorful moths to dance within their flames.</description>
    <position x="80" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Amusement Pier, Este Lane">
    <description>Along the edge of the pier, rows of benches are set in a half-circle, all facing a big wooden theater.  Clothed in darkness, the images on its painted doors are barely visible in the flickering torchlight.  Sea birds often land upon the roof, squawking as though performing for a crowd.</description>
    <description>Placed along the edge of the pier an area is set up with rows of benches all facing a big wooden theater.  Clothed in darkness it sits, the images on its painted doors barely seen by the flickering torches placed near it.  Sea birds often land upon it, squawking as if performing for a crowd.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go row" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Amusement Pier, Centre Lane">
    <description>Miniature boats dart between cast-pewter figures of birds in flight that adorn a nearby fountain, cheered on by the calls of children.  The fountain also provides a haven for real birds who splash with gleeful abandon in the water, sending up waves that nearly swamp the tiny vessels.</description>
    <description>Miniature boats drift lazily between cast-pewter figures of birds in flight that adorn a nearby fountain.  Late night romance blooms as a young Bard plays softly on a flute, his thoughts his own in the night's dim light.</description>
    <position x="120" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Amusement Pier, Wilde Lane">
    <description>A bright red shop roofed with dark brown shingles stands here, with its wide-paned windows painted with apples.  Barrels filled with various kinds of apples stand against the shop, a small Gnome guarding them with a pointy broom.  The scent of fresh apples permeates the air, inviting all to enter and partake.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red shop" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Amusement Pier, Este Lane">
    <description>A dark establishment stands starkly in contrast with the gaiety surrounding it.  Wind gently swings the sign that names this place, Zackes.  An arched door stands open with a hint of ale drifting out upon the sea air.</description>
    <description>A dark establishment stands starkly in contrast with the gaiety surrounding it.  Wind gently swings the sign that names this place, Zackes.  An arched door stands open with a hint of ale drifting out upon the night air.</description>
    <position x="160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched door" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Amusement Pier, Centre Lane">
    <description>Big brawny lads and giggling maidens gather round to see who is the strongest in the lands.  A few Halfling children gawk at the huge Gor'Tog that blocks their view of the next contestant.</description>
    <description>Torches flicker as big brawny lads and giggling maidens gather round to see who is the strongest in the lands.  A couple of huge Gor'Togs snicker amongst themselves as a Gnome attempts the tower of strength.</description>
    <position x="120" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crowd" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Amusement Pier, Wilde Lane">
    <description>Crowds gather round to enter a man-made cave that slopes down into the water and off the edge of the pier.  A huge sign above it is decorated with the image of a dragon, a mighty warrior within its claws.  A couple of maidens dressed in gossamer and silk direct people into the cave in a disorderly fashion.</description>
    <position x="80" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Amusement Pier, Wilde Lane">
    <description>Nifty Gifts! proclaims the sign that hangs from above a picture of daisies and ribbons.  Brightly painted, this shop is crowded with young and old alike as they chatter about the goodies inside.  The scent of fresh-baked cookies drifts from the half-open door.</description>
    <position x="80" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted shop" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Amusement Pier, Carousel">
    <description>Bright ribbons dance upon the air as the huge carousel goes round and round.  Fun-loving passengers scamper through a black iron gate to reach the various carved animals supported by beribboned poles.  A young Elven lass has a bright smile for all as she stands ready to take their coin in exchange for a ride.</description>
    <position x="120" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted stall" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Amusement Pier, Este Lane">
    <description>Gentle waves can be heard lapping against the huge poles that bear the weight of this pier.  Sturdy rails have been placed along the edges, keeping stray children from tumbling off into the cold waters below.</description>
    <description>Gentle waves can be heard lapping against the huge poles that bear the weight of this pier.  Sturdy rails have been placed along to the edges to keep stray children from tumbling off into the cold waters below.  Large lanterns have been lit, where the moths gather to dance within their light.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go squat building" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Amusement Pier, Este Lane">
    <description>Gentle waves lap against the pilings that support the weight of this busy pier.  Construction appears to be going on as boards are stacked up and barrels of various tools and nails are piled along the pier's railings.</description>
    <position x="160" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Amusement Pier, Centre Lane">
    <description>Ribbon spirals up poles bearing colorful paper lanterns that line the walkway leading to the doors of a gaily-decorated shop.  A gigantic catapult stands toward the end of the pier, giving patrons cause to look carefully around when exiting the shop to make sure there is no one flying in their direction.</description>
    <position x="120" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gaily-decorated shop" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Amusement Pier, Wilde Lane">
    <description>A simple wooden booth stands here with faded colors reflecting the passage of time.  Laughter dances upon the air drifting from inside the gaming booth that offers a place to enjoy a bit of leisure time.</description>
    <description>A simple wooden booth stands here with faded colors reflecting the passage of time.  Small paper lanterns hang from it, surrounding it with a playful glow.  Laughter dances upon the air drifting from inside the gaming booth that offers a place to enjoy a bit of leisure time.</description>
    <position x="80" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Amusement Pier, Este Lane">
    <description>A decrepit shop, its doors stiff from rusted hinges, stands silent vigil over the street.  Coated windows stare blindly out, covered with some dark smelly substance -- though what it is exactly is anyone's guess.  At times the door quickly opens and shuts with a horrific squeal, allowing a person to rush away from the facade, their bowed head echoing the protective clasp on the bundles they carry off greedily.</description>
    <position x="160" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go decrepit shop" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Amusement Pier, Centre Lane">
    <description>Piles of hay lie scattered on the ground, providing a soft landing place for those flung from the catapult.  Giggles of children playing hide and seek mingle with the cheers of catapult spectators as they watch a particularly rough landing.</description>
    <description>Piles of hay lie scattered on the ground, providing a soft landing place for those flung from the catapult.  Giggles of young maidens playing hide and seek mingle with the cheers of catapult spectators as they watch a particularly rough landing.</description>
    <position x="120" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Amusement Pier, Wilde Lane">
    <description>Wave after gentle wave slowly laps against the pilings that support the weight of the busy pier.  Sturdy railings along the edges keep stray children from tumbling into the cold waters below.</description>
    <description>Wave after gentle wave slowly laps against the pilings that support the weight of the busy pier.  Sturdy railings are visible in the torchlight, keeping those patrons who reel in the wake of the local ale from tumbling into the cold waters below.</description>
    <position x="80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Bouncer's, Catapult">
    <description>Dominating this area of the pier is a massive catapult, its poles decorated with yellow and blue streamers.  Children watch amazed as daring adventurers take their turn in the catapult's wicker basket.</description>
    <description>Dominating this area of the pier is a massive catapult, its poles decorated with yellow and blue streamers.  The polished wooden frame reflects glints of light from the numerous paper lanterns used to light the area.</description>
    <position x="120" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Amusement Pier, Centre Lane">
    <description>A small inn sits at the end of this long pier, its wide doors painted with multi-colored flowers.  A porch made of dark blue and misty-green tile makes a semi-circle beneath the door.  A soft tinkling sound emits from the porch when visitors step on it, informing the owners that potential guests are near.</description>
    <position x="120" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide doors" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Fisherman's Corner, Este Lane">
    <description>The music of the sea is heard in the soft lulling sound of the waves lapping against the base of the pier and in the echoing calls of seagulls to one another.  A lone bench rests near the railing with fishing equipment casually leaning against it.</description>
    <description>The music of the sea is heard in the soft lulling sound of the waves lapping against the base of the pier and in the echoing calls of seagulls to one another.  Flickering lanterns cast a dim pool of radiance over a lone bench resting near the railing, glittering on the metal bits of the fishing pole leaning against it.</description>
    <position x="140" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Fisherman's Corner, Wilde Lane" note="Fishing">
    <description>Cantankerous old Humans come here, vying with one another for the best fishing spot.  Occasionally cheers are raised as one particularly large fish is reeled in.  The view off the pier is spectacular as ships sail by, friendly sailors waving from their decks.</description>
    <description>Soft, flickering flames dance from torches placed along the end of the pier, providing romantic lighting to nighttime strollers.  A slight breeze causes some to snuggle close to one another, while a scattering of Bards can be heard playing various instruments.</description>
    <position x="100" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Nightingale's Rest Theater, Seating">
    <description>Carved benches are strategically placed to face the theater, each with a perfect view of the entertainers that often perform.  The stage is decorated in bright colors with lit sconces laid along the base for nighttime viewing.</description>
    <position x="170" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Prize Stall" note="Prize Stall">
    <description>Rough wooden beams hold up this small prize stall.  Painted brown bears dance upon colorful balls along the walls, interspersed with prancing horses.  Each shelf is draped in decorative lace that holds assorted prizes, just out of the reach of small children.  A colorful sign has been nailed upon one wall, giving information about the different prizes.</description>
    <position x="140" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Prickle Tattoo Shop" note="Prickle Tattoo Shop|Tattoo Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pale oak walls are covered with various examples of the designs in skin art, ranging from the simple to extreme in detail.  The smell of fresh ink permeates the room, wafting from the shelves that line the far wall.  A couch lies in one corner, covered in dark tapestries with a footstool placed nearby, while some tables are evenly spaced about the shop.</description>
    <position x="200" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="A Carousel">
    <description>The gaily decorated carousel is painted with scenes of leaping fish, soaring birds, and fierce beasts.  Several carved and painted wooden animals are suspended by poles, beckoning a ride.</description>
    <position x="30" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="A Carousel">
    <description>The gaily decorated carousel is painted with scenes of leaping fish, soaring birds, and fierce beasts.  Several carved and painted wooden animals are suspended by poles, beckoning a ride.</description>
    <position x="40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="A Carousel">
    <description>The gaily decorated carousel is painted with scenes of leaping fish, soaring birds, and fierce beasts.  Several carved and painted wooden animals are suspended by poles, beckoning a ride.</description>
    <position x="40" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="none" move="none" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="A Carousel">
    <description>The gaily decorated carousel is painted with scenes of leaping fish, soaring birds, and fierce beasts.  Several carved and painted wooden animals are suspended by poles, beckoning a ride.</description>
    <position x="30" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Mighty Warriors, Strength Test Game">
    <description>Off to one side, a metal pole towers high above the crowds.  A sturdy wooden lever squats on the ground at its base, while a bronze bell tops the tall structure.  A roustabout leans on a heavy sledgehammer, hawking his game to passers-by.</description>
    <position x="100" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Nifty Gifts, Front Room" note="Nifty Gifts" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Like many other shops in the province, an array of wares is displayed for shoppers on shelves and racks.  A pot of tea is brewing in the corner, where the owner also keeps a crossbow loaded, prepped and ready for any would-be thieves.  Scents of homemade candy emanate from the beaded curtain that leads into the back room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beaded curtain" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Nifty Gifts, Back Room" note="Back Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A cloth-covered counter bears today's offerings to soothe a customer's sweet tooth.  Behind the counter a young Halfling works to keep up with the demand for sugar-coated jellies and frosting-covered cookies.  A small sign crookedly hung above the door reads, Tasty treats by the handful, enjoy!</description>
    <position x="30" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beaded curtain" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Simply Souvenirs, Lobby" note="Simply Souvenirs|Souvenirs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The lobby is wide open and welcoming without any clutter, with carpeted runners leading off to the different parts of the store.  Prisms of all shapes and sizes hang from the ceiling, catching the light filtering in from the hexagonal window, causing tiny rainbows to dance across the walls.</description>
    <position x="120" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Simply Souvenirs, Amazing Accessories" note="Amazing Accessories" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Knick-knacks and trinkets are placed all over the room, giving it a closed-in, cluttered feel.  A wide rack hangs on one wall, elegantly displaying a number of finely crafted fans that are for sale.  Next to the rack stands a tall fanciful tree made from glass, holding various accessories.</description>
    <position x="130" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Simply Souvenirs, Random Rarities" note="Random Rarities" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Far from the sounds of the busy pier, this room is cozy and comfortably furnished.  A playfully carved archway, depicting cartwheeling clowns is set in the south wall, with a thick felt curtain covering its contents.  Along the opposite wall stands a line of chairs, mismatched but all focused on the same point, a tall cushioned pedestal in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="120" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Simply Souvenirs, Plush Presents" note="Plush Presents" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A huge comical plush tree stands in the middle of the room, with a big goofy face painted on its front.  Its branches completely cover the ceiling, with long strips of green cloth hanging down like weeping leaves.  A round wooden counter painted to resemble a short stone wall encircles the soft tree.</description>
    <position x="110" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Shop of Horrors, Outer Chamber" note="Shop of Horrors" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rotted boards forming the walls are roughly thrown together, leaving splits large enough to reach into in some places.  Shadows obscure a shelf along the back wall, while on the side wall something heavy dangles from a hook.  A smoky lantern hangs from a pole in the center of the room, the only source of illumination.</description>
    <position x="200" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crooked arch" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go creaky door" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Shop of Horrors, Inner Sanctum" note="Inner Sanctum" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A thick cobweb covers the one small window, tiny trapped bodies in neatly wrapped packages here and there in its strands.  A shadowed figure lurks in the corner, larger than the rest, its eyes reflecting in the lantern-light.  An assortment of dark silhouettes rests on a rickety shelf, a crumbling display case squatting under it.  Remnants of carpeting lump under a lopsided table in one corner, the goods on it tilting sideways as if trying to hang onto the surface.</description>
    <position x="210" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crooked arch" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Shop of Horrors, Drowned Cellar" note="Drowned Cellar" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The sound of lapping water reverberates against the distorted walls that seem to melt into the water around your legs, but on second glance it's only the noxious slime dripping down its surface and into the fetid liquid.  Mold covers everything else, including the hole-riddled ladder missing several rungs in one corner.</description>
    <position x="220" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Gnoshy and Sons, Orchard's Bounty Ordering Room" note="Gnoshy and Sons" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A long wide counter dominates the small, but functional, lobby of Gnoshy's hastily constructed retail outpost.  A small, hand-lettered sign has been tacked to the back wall, next to a more elaborate menu.  Through large chinks and gaps in the wall, smells of cinnamon, honey, and chocolate drift pleasingly.</description>
    <position x="40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go swinging doors" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Gnoshy and Sons, Orchard's Bounty Store">
    <description>Empty bins, buckets, barrels, and crates lie in organized piles in the corners of the room, out of the way of the patrons and the occasional workers, who scurry to and fro amidst the browsing clientele.  Two long, low tables are situated near the back wall of this well-lit room.  A strong, cidery smell tinged with sweet and sugary undertones pervades the air.</description>
    <position x="30" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Zackes' Place, Bar" note="Zackes' Place" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Many a seaman calls this rough and tumble place home.  Its tall stools and carved oak bar are perfect for carousing the night away with friends.  On either side of the bar are different areas for letting off steam.</description>
    <position x="210" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Zackes' Place, The Pit">
    <description>The pit, as it is fondly called by the finest of warriors, is where the bravest grapple amongst taunts and cheers.  Water is often thrown over the encircling benches, clearing off excess mud.  Those daring enough to watch are often pulled in, to the amusement of all concerned.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Zackes' Place, Baths">
    <description>Warmth emanates from steaming hot tubs, giving off scents of musk and pine.  Small candles flicker against the dark wood walls from sconces placed in the corners.  Here is a quiet place that offers relaxation for those weary from the day's journey.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go porcelain tub" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden tub" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="The Dragon's Horde, Front Room" note="Front Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Intricately designed woven rugs line the floor of this spacious area.  Scents of jasmine and rose float through the air from candles lit on tall candelabras.  Highly polished counters and gilt inlaid racks hold various items for purchase with attentive clerks ready to assist those in need.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="The Dragon's Horde, Hunter's Room" note="Hunter's Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Polished armor gleams on tables of yew and oak, with edged weapons and bows carefully displayed on heavy pine racks.  The smell of new leather and fragrant candles mix with the scents of the pungent shoppers that often come to glance at the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="70" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="The Dragon's Horde, Furniture Palace" note="Furniture Palace">
    <description>Wooly rugs and ornate tapestries accent pieces of fine furniture that are orderly placed throughout the room.  Some clerks, wearing bright colorful smocks, assist shoppers with purchases while others wield cleaning rags and battle the dust that finds its way in.</description>
    <position x="90" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Bath, Hot Porcelain Tub">
    <description>Hot water caresses the senses and brings relief to aches and pains.  Inhaling the soapy scents can cause you to drift into a nap, while the extremely hot water can give even the hardiest Dwarf a nice pink tinge.</description>
    <position x="220" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Bath, Hot Wooden Tub">
    <description>Hot water caresses the senses and brings relief to aches and pains.  Inhaling the soapy scents can cause you to drift into a nap, while the extremely hot water can give even the hardiest Dwarf a nice pink tinge.</description>
    <position x="220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Rosealea's Inn, Front Room">
    <description>All who enter this small establishment are greeted by the smiling face of Rosealea or one of her many daughters.  Off to one side a spiral staircase leads to the rooms upstairs, while beyond a brightly polished wood arch is seen the main dining room.  Several seascapes line the walls, and its huge front window is outlined with rows of various seashells.</description>
    <position x="120" y="385" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wood arch" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Rosealea's Inn, Hallway">
    <description>Whitewashed walls are covered with paintings of children and small sea mementos.  A corner shelf holds odd fragments of crystallized rocks, seemingly out of place in this otherwise sea-oriented room.</description>
    <position x="120" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cherrywood door" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Rosealea's Inn, Main Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This room buzzes with activity, from harried servers bringing out steaming dishes to customers talking animatedly among themselves.  Red-checkered tablecloths atop wide oak tables have vases placed on them full of fragrant flowers.  Though crowded, the room fits everyone comfortably and offers a magnificent view of the river.</description>
    <position x="100" y="405" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched doorway" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Rosealea's Inn, Family Room">
    <description>Neat and tidy, this room is made to accommodate those with children.  The huge bed in the middle of the room is covered with many colorful pillows and knitted blankets.  A sofa along one wall is big enough sleep a couple of children, and makes a nice setting for lace pillows and a cross-eyed teddy bear.</description>
    <position x="140" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Rosealea's Inn, Bard's Rest">
    <description>Midnight silk covers the full-sized bed in this room while the fragrance of roses drifts from a vase full of the colorful blooms.  In the corner stands a gilded stool with a thickly cushioned seat.  A stand has been placed before the stool, offering a place to practice for any visiting bards.</description>
    <position x="120" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Rosealea's Inn, Honeymoon Suite">
    <description>A four-poster cherrywood bed towers over the other furnishings, framed by dark plum silk draperies.  The scent of jasmine creates a romantic ambiance for the newly bonded.  From its elegant settee to the champagne chilling on the bedside table, no expense has been spared to offer the visiting couple their perfect holiday.  Lace draperies flutter in the window that looks out over the water, while a fragrant fire crackles in the fireplace.</description>
    <position x="100" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cherrywood door" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Rosealea's Inn, Dance Hall">
    <description>Dark crystal sconces hold candles whose soft light seems to flicker in time with music being played by local bards congregating in the corner.  Several low couches surround the dark wood dance floor, offering a place to chat and relax.</description>
    <position x="80" y="405" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gilded alcove" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Rosealea's Inn, Rendezvous Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Aptly named the Rendezvous Room, a smiling Human man stands behind a dark mahogany bar, ready to take orders for drinks or to offer advice to any would-be listener.  The windows, which are normally thrown wide open, are drawn closed and covered in dark plum silk.</description>
    <position x="60" y="405" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <label text="Shop of">
    <position x="189" y="280" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Souvenirs">
    <position x="56" y="236" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Simply">
    <position x="64" y="224" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Nifty Gifts">
    <position x="9" y="206" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tattoos">
    <position x="178" y="206" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zackes'">
    <position x="171" y="139" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gnoshy">
    <position x="11" y="104" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="and Sons">
    <position x="8" y="116" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Prizes">
    <position x="123" y="162" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Strength">
    <position x="74" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Test">
    <position x="84" y="121" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crossing">
    <position x="134" y="-8" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Carousel">
    <position x="8" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Horrors">
    <position x="191" y="304" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Place">
    <position x="179" y="166" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Dragon's Horde">
    <position x="-10" y="10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Rosealea's Inn">
    <position x="130" y="380" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>