<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Crossing Temple" id="2a">
  <node id="1" name="Temple Grounds, Entry Gates" note="Entry Gates|Gates">
    <description>The immense outer walls of the temple meet here, a thick lacquered mahogany gate acting as their mediator.  The hardwood entrance has been banded with sturdy bars of steel to ensure its stamina in the most dire of times.  A cobblestone path leads to the north, winding off into the various parts of the temple grounds.</description>
    <position x="340" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany gate" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany building" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>The astonishing sight of the grand temple lies to the north, atop a massive stairway.  Three towers flank the sides of the structure, a complex network of walkways stretching between them and the temple's top levels.  A smooth cobblestone path runs east and west here, curving around to the grounds areas on either side of the temple.</description>
    <position x="340" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb massive stairway" destination="182" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="The Crossing, Immortals' Approach" note="Map1_Crossing.xml|Crossing">
    <description>This stretch of road is wide and paved with smooth stone blocks.  Cherry trees in carved stone planters border the sweeping approach while softening the exterior walls surrounding the Temple grounds.  Flames flicker from the tops of three tall towers standing guard over the orb of the Main Temple.  Fragile walkways lash the towers to each other high above the orb.  You also see a high granite wall surrounding the temple grounds, the locked almsbox and the Longbow Bridge.</description>
    <description>This stretch of road is wide and paved with smooth stone blocks.  Cherry trees in carved stone planters border the sweeping approach while softening the exterior walls surrounding the Temple grounds.  Flames brightly visible in the dark flare from the tops of three tall towers standing guard over the orb of the Main Temple.  Fragile walkways lash the towers to each other high above the orb.</description>
    <description>This stretch of road is wide and paved with smooth stone blocks.  Cherry trees in carved stone planters border the sweeping approach while softening the exterior walls surrounding the Temple grounds.  Flames flicker from the tops of three tall towers standing guard over the orb of the Main Temple.  Fragile walkways lash the towers to each other high above the orb.</description>
    <position x="340" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany gate" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path" note="Fidakel">
    <description>The cobblestone road curves gently here, the round stones smooth and freshly-swept by the ever vigilant groundskeepers.  A broad expanse of thick brambles stretches to the northwest, obscuring any vision of what may lie beyond them.</description>
    <position x="260" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>A thorny thicket of brambles obscures direct vision to the northeast.  The top half of the temple's massive orb is still visible, rising like the moon over the errant foliage, the veils of night draping lightly over it.</description>
    <description>A thorny thicket of brambles obscures direct vision to the northeast, although the top half of the temple's massive orb is still visible.  Its lustrous black ironwood surface gleams in the sunlight, accented by polished silverwood window frames and sconces.  A bizarre contrast with the errant foliage, indeed.</description>
    <position x="200" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>A black marble birdbath stands in the center of this three-way intersection in the cobble path.  The road is silent now, the various groundskeepers and other temple employees having gone home for the day.  A dedicated monk or priestess bustles by every so often, but naught else disturbs the intersection at this late hour.</description>
    <description>A black marble birdbath stands decoratively in the center of this three-way intersection, hurried townsfolk bustling by silently.  Many monks, priestesses, and others dressed in ceremonial garb are likely to be heading to the shrine of their patron deities for a few moments of quiet reflection and respite from the rushing world around them.</description>
    <position x="120" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>Thorny thistles skirt the northern border of the freshly-swept cobbled path, covered with bright purple and yellow flowers.  The prickly foliage hasn't discouraged the animal life, for a startled chittering sounds from beneath one bush as footsteps pass by.</description>
    <description>Thorny thistles skirt the northern border of the freshly-swept cobbled path, bare of their leaves and flowers in the cold winds.  The prickly foliage hasn't discouraged the animal life, for a startled chittering sounds from beneath one bush as footsteps pass by.</description>
    <position x="100" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Temple Grounds, Southwest Tower" note="Southwest Tower">
    <description>The cobblestone path winds to a close before the massive black tower that looms to the west.  Surely built with strategic defense in mind, this construct arcs outward into the northeastern sky.  Several walkways extend from it to the other two towers in a spidery weblike pattern with the temple itself serving as the nexus point.</description>
    <position x="80" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white cottage" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Temple Grounds, Beside a Stream">
    <description>Water tumbles over rounded stones in the stream that borders the gravel path.  A dense bramble thicket, dark and impenetrable, towers over the path, while on the other side of the stream, the fragrance of roses drifts on the wind from the wedding glade to the northeast.  The temple rises in the distance, its spherical surface like an eye constantly watching over its children as they scurry about their daily tasks.</description>
    <position x="120" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Temple Grounds, Courtyard">
    <description>The cobblestone path comes to a fork here, flanking a large shade tree to the east that grows amidst a lush garden of brilliant floral blooms in a veritable rainbow of color.  This garden has been well-tended by the temple groundskeepers, the carefully pruned bushes and healthy vibrant flowers being no accident of nature.</description>
    <description>The cobblestone path comes to a fork here, flanking a large bare tree to the east growing amidst a garden standing fallow in the winter cold.  This garden has been well-tended by the temple groundskeepers, the carefully pruned bushes and composted flower beds waiting only for spring warmth to bring them back to vibrant life.</description>
    <position x="100" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Temple Grounds, Beside the Bathing Pool">
    <description>A tiny rivulet of crystal-blue water babbles through the area, arcing outward from the pond to the south.  Independent of the miniature stream, a luxurious marble bath has been placed amidst a garden of fresh sirese blooms, flanked with ivory statues carved in the shape of graceful swans.  Several large stone pots stand beside the statues, placed conveniently to replenish the waters of the bathing pool when the sun's rays cause it to thirst.</description>
    <description>A thin rivulet of frozen water streaks through the area, arcing outward from the pond to the south.  Independent of the frigidly stagnant stream, a marble bath lies empty amidst a patch of barren ground, the sirese blooms absent in the winter frost.  Ivory statues carved into the shape of swans take on a quality of despair, their usually graceful forms covered with a burdensome layer of snow, icicles hanging from their beaks and wings.  Several stone pots stand in a lonely row, full of freshly fallen snow.  </description>
    <description>A tiny rivulet of crystal-blue water babbles through the area, arcing outward from the pond to the south.  Independent of the miniature stream, a luxurious marble bath has been placed amidst a garden of fresh sirese blooms, flanked with ivory statues carved in the shape of graceful swans.  Several large stone pots stand beside the statues, placed conveniently to replenish the waters of the bathing pool when the sun's rays cause it to thirst.  </description>
    <position x="80" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble bath" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Temple Grounds, Garden" note="Garden|vela'tohr plant|Eaadrich">
    <description>A veritable forest of color explodes before you as the cobbled path comes to an end amidst this lush garden, blooms of every flower imaginable skirting the path.  The vegetation here is oddly vibrant year round, as if bolstered by some subtle vein of life energy itself.</description>
    <position x="120" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Temple Grounds, Wedding Glade">
    <description>A stately white marble reception hall stands to the north, slightly eclipsing your view of the majestic orb-like temple that paints the backdrop of the northeastern sky from this vantage point.  The pungent smell of freshly-cut foliage wells up in your nostrils, wafting over from a cobblestone path that leads to the northwest, beneath a whitewashed latticework archway.  A thick patch of brambles obscures all vision to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="140" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go reception hall" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go latticework archway" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Temple Grounds, Wedding Glade">
    <description>The picturesque wedding chapel stands to the north, its vaulted steeple rising up to pierce the looming orb of the temple in the distance.  Several lush bushes, pruned to perfection, flank a pair of oaken double doors leading into the formal house of worship, bearing a crop of pristine white roses.</description>
    <position x="160" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>A small wooden shrine lies to the north of the cobblestone road, the southern side of the path cradled by the protective walls surrounding the grounds area.  A stubby stool stands before the shrine, allowing one to sit and seek audience with their deity.</description>
    <position x="400" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>Large mounds are scattered about in the grassy earth to the north of the cobblestone road, and a tall tree flanks the path to the west as it curves.  The mounds are home to the furry inhabitants of the temple grounds -- ever meddlesome pests to those who work to keep the foliage lush and alive.</description>
    <description>The cobblestone path is littered with slush and a crunchy coating of frost as it winds through the temple grounds.  A large tree flanks the path to the west, laden with a thick covering of icicles.</description>
    <description>A small host of burrows in the grassy earth directly north of the cobblestone road suddenly bustles with activity as you approach, small furry creatures retreating into their respective dens.  A pile of walnuts lies at the foot of a large tree to the west, apparently forgotten by the foraging animals in their mad scramble to safety.</description>
    <position x="460" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Temple Grounds, Memorial Shrine" note="Memorial Shrine">
    <description>The cobblestone intersection lies silent, the normally bustling traffic dispersed until dawn inevitably abates the dusk.  A broken statue stands in the middle of the intersection, wreathed in the cold, shadowy night air.  A scene of despair and sorrow, one might wonder what the statue looked like in its former glory.</description>
    <description>This broad cobblestone intersection bustles with traffic as people scurry about their daily routine.  Amidst all the confusion, a lone marble statue stands in disarray, its surface cracked and broken from some cataclysmic battle.  Perhaps once a statue depicting one of the Fae, this work of art is now but a sundered monument to blasphemy.  A single wing is left intact, its drooping form seeming to point downward, bringing subtle attention to a glass box lying at the feet of the statue.</description>
    <position x="540" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Temple Grounds, Memorial Shrine">
    <description>The deserted cobblestone path is bordered to the north by a small circle of sooty marble, creating an odd sort of shrine illuminated by the pale silver starlight.  A quietness settles over this solemn memorial of destruction.</description>
    <description>A small shrine surrounded by a low fence of soot-covered marble rubble lies to the north, apparently commemerating some horrid disaster of the past.  Priestesses, monks, and acolytes alike bustle by hurriedly, averting their eyes with a painful grimace.</description>
    <position x="560" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go memorial shrine" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Temple Grounds, Southeast Tower" note="Southeast Tower">
    <description>Gracefully-carved silverwillow accents adorn the giant ironwood tower, giving it a less ominous appearance.  The giant structure arcs up and to the northwest, reaching for the temple as a newborn reaches for the comfort of its mother.</description>
    <position x="580" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>The East Tower is a short distance to the southeast from here, stretching up and out above you to grasp toward the beacon area atop the temple.  A network of frighteningly thin catwalks stretches between the temple and its three towers, as people who appear to be the size of silverfish scurry to and fro upon them.</description>
    <position x="540" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Temple Grounds, Cobblestone Path">
    <description>The cobbled path meanders north and south here, creeping between the curving black ironwood walls of the temple off to the west and the massive granite outer wall directly to the east.  Colorful bursts of vibrant wildflowers have exploded in the lush green summer grass to either side of the path.</description>
    <description>The cobbled path meanders north and south here, creeping between the curving black ironwood walls of the temple off to the west and the massive granite outer wall directly to the east.</description>
    <position x="540" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Temple Grounds, Cemetery Approach">
    <description>The cobbled path sinks into the ground to the northwest, giving way to a trail of black gravel that crunches audibly with every footstep, no matter how light.  A large recess that has been carved out of the wall to the east appears to serve as the starting point for funeral processions.  To the west, a black steel-plate fence blocks the cemetery from sight.</description>
    <position x="540" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Temple Grounds, Mourner's Hollow" note="Mourner's Hollow">
    <description>This large recess within the eastern wall surrounding the temple grounds area is shrouded in black silken and velvet tapestries, marking the occasion of mourning.  A pristine white marble bier standing flush against the east wall serves to hold the body of the beloved aloft during the ceremonial blessing.  The somber sculpture of a woman is suspended upon the wall above the bier, her gaze affixed down at where the deceased are laid.</description>
    <position x="560" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Temple Grounds, Gate of The Mourned">
    <description>A pathway of crunching black gravel stretches out to the northwest with a black ironwood tower in the distance, looming behind the temple itself.  A freshly-oiled steel gate stands sentry to the west, guarding the temple's small cemetery.</description>
    <position x="420" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel gate" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Temple Grounds, Gravel Trail">
    <description>This side of the temple is poorly lit beneath the dusky shroud that has snuffed the sun's fire for the evening.  Shadows seem to move of their own accord, whirling about in the corner of your eye, but halting their dance the moment one attempts to catch them.  The looming branches of a tree to the west stretch out attempting to grasp at anyone that may happen to cross this path.</description>
    <description>A tall green silverwillow tree rises to the west of the black gravel pathway, enjoying the cool shadow cast by the temple.  A small nest of woven sticks and twigs lies in the crook of the tree, wedged between a thick branch and the light silvery bark of the trunk.  To the northwest, the North Tower stands sentry, guarding the temple's back.</description>
    <description>A tall silverwillow tree rises to the west of the black gravel pathway, branches barren in the winter cold and shivering in the mammoth shadow cast by the temple.  A small abandoned nest of woven sticks and twigs lies in the crook of the tree, wedged between a thick branch and the light silvery bark of the trunk.  To the northwest, the North Tower stands sentry, guarding the temple's back.</description>
    <position x="380" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Temple Grounds, North Tower" note="North Tower">
    <description>The rocky path of black volcanic gravel draws to a close, a somber carpet before the Northern sentinel tower.  The thick black ironwood outer walls curve sharply behind the structure to seal off the temple grounds, banded with steel for extra reinforcement to ward off a possible siege.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood doorway" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Cemetery, Road of the Dead">
    <description>Somber rows of statues and modestly marked graves line the pathway here, leading westward from under the steel gate to the east, deeper within the heart of the small cemetery.</description>
    <position x="360" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel gate" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Cemetery, Crystal Spire" note="Cemetery|Crystal Spire|Spire|Khurek" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The cemetery lies in eerie silence beneath the vacant cloak of night.  Shadows wreathe the ring of gravestones and statues gathered about a large crystal spire that rises up from the ground in the center of the area.</description>
    <description>A crystalline obelisk juts upward from the ground in the middle of the dirt pathway.  Rows of granite gravestones and marble statues have been set up in a circular pattern, with the unlit spire as their epicenter.</description>
    <position x="340" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Cemetery, Unmarked Graves" note="Unmarked Graves">
    <description>This small plot at the corner of the cemetery seems to be laid out for those who could not afford much ceremony, the dismal resting place of the poor and forgotten.  A small wicker basket has been placed on a bulging unmarked grave, filled with vegetables in offering, or perhaps apology, to a lost loved one.</description>
    <position x="320" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Cemetery, Memorial of The Beloved" note="Memorial of The Beloved">
    <description>Rows of bejewelled marble statues crowd against the cemetery path, their night-shrouded visages glowering forth at all who pass by.  An eerie sense of unrest lies with the gem-encrusted gargoyles, as if plotting in silence to rise up against those that intrude upon their domain.</description>
    <description>The daylight brings a gentle lifelike quality to rows of bejewelled marble statues that have been placed here in memory of relatives and friends who have passed along to their journey upon the Starry Road.  Professionally chiseled marble headstones prominently mark each grave in this small cluster.</description>
    <position x="340" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Memorial Shrine">
    <description>A large stone pillar rises in the center of this shrine, surrounded by a ring of sooty marble rubble, the walls of some grand structure of yore.  Delicate colored tiles have been inset upon the pillar in a valiant restoration of a destroyed mosaic, possibly belonging to a place of worship in days past.</description>
    <position x="560" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Temple Grounds, Guidepost">
    <description>A rich mahogany counter covered in neatly arranged stacks of parchment fills the small, yet well-kept cottage.  A pleasant demeanored monk garbed in crisp white linen robes stands just behind the counter, awaiting patrons.</description>
    <position x="320" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Temple Grounds, Bathing Pool" note="Bathing Pool">
    <description>The luxurious marble bathing pool lies sunken snugly into the earth, surrounded by a fresh garden of fragrant sirese blooms.  Butterflies, bees, and all species of small woodland creatures approach the garden now and then, creating a gentle atmosphere of nature and serenity secluded from the bustling cacophony of the city.  The pool is currently bone dry, all of the water having evaporated.</description>
    <description>The luxurious marble bathing pool lies beneath a deathly pall of frost and ice.  The water has been completely emptied from the pool to avoid cracking the delicate marble as it expands in the freezing process.  Surrounding the bath is a rather forlorn-looking garden, barren in the winter months and dusted with a faint snowy powder.  </description>
    <description>The luxurious marble bathing pool lies sunken snugly into the earth, surrounded by a fresh garden of fragrant sirese blooms.  Butterflies, bees, and all species of small woodland creatures approach the garden now and then, creating a gentle atmosphere of nature and serenity secluded from the bustling cacophony of the city.  The shimmering pearlescent waters of the pool are currently full, a gentle steamy fog rising up from them as they lap around you.  </description>
    <description>The luxurious marble bathing pool lies sunken snugly into the earth, surrounded by a fresh garden of fragrant sirese blooms.  Butterflies, bees, and all species of small woodland creatures approach the garden now and then, creating a gentle atmosphere of nature and serenity secluded from the bustling cacophony of the city.  The glassy, still waters of the pool are currently very full, shining with a luminous silver glow beneath the gentle starlight.  </description>
    <position x="60" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Temple Grounds, Scriptorium" note="Scriptorium" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This tiny one-room cottage is quite cramped amidst all the clutter that has been packed into it.  An oversized oak desk dominates the northern side of the room, just beneath a lustrous silver placard that displays several parchment titles and their prices.  Various cases built to hold delicate papers have been piled atop shelves and racks that flank the desk, while the larger ones hang in display upon the wall.</description>
    <position x="60" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Reception Hall, Foyer">
    <description>The bright light of glass-chambered lamps in silver sconces along the walls fills the room.  Vibrantly colored velvet ribbons streaming down the walls create a riot of color that contrasts sharply against the smooth white marble.  Scattered haphazardly along the floor surrounding several low birch tables are piles of velvet cushions in aquatic tones that complement the silvery grey tapestry rugs spread beneath them.</description>
    <position x="140" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted archway" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go velvet curtain" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Reception Hall, Refreshments">
    <description>Garlands of richly hued wildflowers braided with ivy hang from the pure white walls, filling the room with a gentle, lingering fragrance.  More garlands, woven with blue and silver ribbons that dangle nearly to the polished marble floors, are draped along the edges of the polished rosewood table and bar.  Near a festively painted archway leading to the foyer sits a rosewood cart festooned with multicolored streamers and covered with refreshments befitting the god of levity.</description>
    <position x="140" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted archway" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Reception Hall, Ballroom">
    <description>Polished walnut floors spread across the length of this chamber.  Chips of lighter wood inlaid in its center form an intricate mosaic, mirrored directly above in a majestic circular skylight set in the vaults of the arching ceiling.  Dozens of streamers in aquatic colors hanging to each side of the stage provide a vibrant backdrop for several ornate statues of alabaster fae.  Breezes sweeping through open windows into the room stir the silk streamers to surround the statues in their own aerial dance.</description>
    <position x="160" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Wedding Chapel, Foyer">
    <description>Sunlight filters through skylights in the vaulted ash ceilings above, reflecting off pristine white walls.  Its bright radiance falls upon the tapestries, hung to each side of passages leading to the north and south, whose hues echo those of a lavishly embroidered white velvet carpet spreading across the floor.  Guarding a tall silverwillow archway are two alabaster statues wound with tendrils of malachite ivy, while mirroring it to the west is a pair of oaken doors leading back outside.</description>
    <description>Candlelight flickers with warm luminance off the graceful figures of two statues guarding a silverwillow archway, diffusing the shadows found in the hours of darkness.  More candlelight pools from passages to the north and south, highlighting the edges of tapestries hung to either side of them.  Opposite the archway, a pair of large oaken doors reveals the way back outside.</description>
    <position x="180" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silverwillow archway" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken doors" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Wedding Chapel, Groom's Chambers">
    <description>Sunlight catches on the burbling surface of a brook that can be seen through a pair of panoramic windows to the north.  Cast into shadow between them is a polished mahogany desk framed by the dark velvet curtains.  A deep brown leather couch dominates the wall to one side, its dark hue matching those of soft armchairs scattered around it.  In their midst is a low mahogany table topped with glass.  A soft silvery grey carpet spreads along the floor underfoot.</description>
    <description>The light of the many silver candelabras fills the room with its warm glow.  Surrounding a low mahogany table is a soft couch and several deep brown leather armchairs sitting upon a silvery grey carpet.  A matching mahogany desk sits between two panoramic windows along the northern wall, its panes now dimmed with night.</description>
    <position x="180" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small door" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Wedding Chapel, Bride's Chamber">
    <description>The pale hues of the tapestries and velvet carpet reflect the light washing through two large windows along the southern wall.  Piles of velvet and tasseled cushions tossed on the floor bathe in a pool of sunlight, clustering around a low glass-topped ash table.  On the other side of the windows, a cheval mirror is poised to reflect the image of the bride and her attendants, with a carved ash vanity beside it for last-minute adjustments to hair and accessories.</description>
    <description>The glass windows now lay dark, glinting with the flickering glow of the lit candelabras sitting upon nearly every available surface.  Surrounding a low ash table topped with an etched glass pane are dozens of soft velvet cushions in shades of ivory and gold.  A tall ash-framed mirror stands next to a vanity on the other side of the room.</description>
    <position x="180" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small door" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Wedding Chapel, Dais">
    <description>Sunlight sets the panes of a large stained glass window afire with vibrant colors.  Standing before it like a pale ghost is a white marble altar framed by descending rows of tall white candles held in the arms of dancing alabaster fae.  Across the length of the dais lays a soft white velvet carpet embroidered with subtle golden threads that shimmer slightly where touched by the light.</description>
    <description>Golden light shines upon the faces and arms of dancing alabaster fae from the wax candles they hold in their grasp as they stand to each side of a low white marble altar.  Behind the altar is a darkened stained glass window, its colors still rich even when dimmed by night.  Across the length of the dais lays a soft white velvet carpet embroidered with subtle golden threads that shimmer slightly where touched by the light.</description>
    <position x="200" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Wedding Chapel, Seating">
    <description>Sunlight from the southern windows falls upon rows of padded oak benches facing the eastern end of the chamber.  An aisle carpeted with white velvet makes a straight path between them to a wide, brightly illuminated dais.</description>
    <description>The resplendent glow of dozens of candles sitting in tall candelabras chases away the shadows that come with the night.  Between the rows of padded oak benches facing the east end of the chamber is a carpeted aisle leading to a wide, brightly lit dais.</description>
    <position x="220" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Wedding Chapel, Atrium">
    <description>Sunlight dapples the patterned marble floor as it shines through arching windows to the north and south that offer a wide view of the temple gardens.  Two long tables sit sheltered by the undrawn curtains between them, covered wth an array of light refreshments and freshly picked flowers.  Next to a pair of oaken doors leading deeper into the chapel is a wrought iron stairway, the bottom steps carefully roped off to prevent outsiders from entering.</description>
    <description>The darkened windows glisten with the reflected glow of many candles, faintly throwing back the radiance to futher illuminate the room.  Two tables sitting in the shelter of the undrawn curtains between them offer a light array of refreshments and fresh flowers.  Almost hidden in the shadow of a pair of large oaken doors, a wrought iron stairway leads to the higher levels of the chapel.</description>
    <position x="200" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silverwillow archway" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silverwillow doors" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Resurrection Creche, Li Stil rae Kwego ia Kweld" note="Resurrection Creche|favor altar|depart" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Fragrant smoke drifts from censers to carry periodic ripples of sound from the rooms beyond, bringing the silvery chime of bells and rhythmic cadence of chant to rise and fall in the air like the heartbeat of the Temple itself.  An ivory rug cloaks the floor, surrounding an altar of translucent obsidian swirled with fiery highlights.  Stained-glass gaethzen orbs circle the altar with a misty nimbus of violet light shading to crimson and then to amber and gold -- the colors of dawn and of life renewed.</description>
    <position x="340" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Resurrection Creche, Chamber of Rains" note="Chamber of Rains">
    <description>Softly luminous gaethzen orbs hang suspended from polished brass chains.  The delicate-looking globes are draped with gauzy fabric in a myriad of soft blues and greens.  The veined granite of the far wall has been chiseled into a three-dimensional mural resembling lush foliage.  Gentle pattering laughter of a spring shower fills the room as water from a hidden source cascades in wide rivulets down the sculpted flora.  Large tapestry cushions carpet the floor with embroidered verdure.</description>
    <position x="264" y="358" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Resurrection Creche, Hallway">
    <description>Hanging from a golden brazier is a colorful wreath of branches bearing dark green leaves.  Sprinkled amongst the verdant boughs are pea-sized dirdel flowers of fiery red bearing triangular silver foliage.  The wreath adds a bit of color to the hallway of drab white.</description>
    <position x="213" y="298" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Resurrection Creche, Hearth Chamber" note="Hearth Chamber">
    <description>Flames crackle merrily in a large circular fireplace set upon an elevated flagstone dais in the center of the room.  A wrought iron hood is attached to a ventilation shaft which rises upward, leading to a grate on the far wall.  Fine mesh screens enclose the blaze, intricate patterns in the links forming the shadowy images of the thirteen avatars.  Richly woven panels of warm russet wool trimmed with heavy gold braid line the stone walls.  Thick black bearskin rugs carpet the floor beneath leather divans.</description>
    <position x="200" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Resurrection Creche, Hallway">
    <description>The long, slightly turning, white plaster walls are interrupted by a mahogany staircase leading upward.  The granite floor is slightly scuffed here, perhaps by the countless feet that have trodden upon it, or perhaps by some heavy object having been pushed along.</description>
    <position x="234" y="148" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany staircase" hidden="True" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Resurrection Creche, Hallway">
    <description>A golden candelabra, its treasured flame flickering in the passing breeze of each supplicant moving through the temple halls, casts a soft glow about the curving corridor.  The evened floor of cold granite absorbs what little warmth and comfort the tiny blaze gives off.</description>
    <position x="301" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Resurrection Creche, Hallway">
    <description>Flanked on either side by white plaster barriers, this smooth granite floor displays the image of a painted starburst pattern.  In the center of the bright red ornamentation, a white flower blooms as though newly touched by spring.</description>
    <position x="379" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Resurrection Creche, Hallway">
    <description>A low relief has been carefully carved into the rough granite overlooking a mostly nondescript arch, and through the wide arch the twisting granite-hewn steps of an ascending staircase can be seen.  The protruding depictions of the relief portray a group of people before what may be the sun.</description>
    <position x="440" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" hidden="True" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Resurrection Creche, Triage Hall" note="Triage Hall">
    <description>This brightly-lit interior is devoid of decoration, the utilitarian design allowing healers to focus on evaluating the wounded.  Patients are directed toward treatment according to severity and degree of life threat, and straw-filled pallets line the perimeter of the room for the most severe cases.  The walls have been scrubbed clean, their faint citrus smell not quite masking the coppery scent of blood.  Fresh rushes spread across the floor help to absorb the inevitable spills of bodily fluids.</description>
    <position x="479" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Resurrection Creche, Hallway">
    <description>The smooth arcing is just barely noticeable in the oblique hallway extending throughout the lower walls of the temple.  The curving white plaster partitions enclosing the corridor are adorned in spots by brown woolen tapestries depicting scenes ranging from a prostrate monk to a rearing unicorn.</description>
    <position x="467" y="298" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Resurrection Creche, Dispensary" note="Dispensary">
    <description>A bustle of activity greets each fresh arrival of wounded.  Long rows of narrow cots covered with immaculate white linen are reserved for recovering patients.  Empaths move efficiently through the room, offering words of comfort as they check on the status of their charges.  The smooth granite walls are adorned along the upper border with a brightly painted plaster frieze depicting long garlands of medicinal herbs interspersed with jadice flowers.</description>
    <position x="416" y="358" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Twin plaster columns rise on either side of a descending stairway, supporting the spheriform walls.  Along the inner curve of the hallway, an arched mahogany entrance leads to a white marble walkway that spans the distance between the circular rim and the High Altar at the center of the Temple.</description>
    <position x="479" y="160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go winding stairway" hidden="True" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Four beautifully detailed figures grace this intersection in the circular hallway.  Two mahogany carvings join in a proud arch, establishing an exquisitely veneered frame for the awe-inspiring view of the High Altar.  Glowing softly in the sunlight, the Altar is joined to the rim by a long gracious grey marble causeway, its tiles meeting up at the threshold of the arch.  Opposing the walkway, two molded plaster columns stand guard above a set of stairs which descends along the curve of the sphere.</description>
    <position x="201" y="160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" hidden="True" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Flickering torches secured in iron sconces illuminate a sprawling mural upon the walls.  Panoramic images depict a gathering of diverse figures joined in concentric circles about a large white boulder resting at the center of a forest clearing.  The pristine surface of the monolithic stone is scorched with a totemic simulacrum of a great horned owl in flight.</description>
    <position x="500" y="240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Curiously elusive, a faint musty smell intrudes upon an otherwise elegant hallway.  An antique crystal chandelier emits a warm golden glow that caresses everything from the central wooden pedestal to the narrow wooden staircase that ascends the outside wall.</description>
    <position x="479" y="320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>A fresh breeze wafts along the passage, bringing with it the gentle but fragrant scents of the garden.  Along the outside wall, a long curving planter filled with rich soil provides a tiny sanctuary for young saplings to grow.  Standing protectively in front of them, a mahogany pedestal rises like a monument to its living brethren.</description>
    <position x="420" y="379" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="The Crossing Temple, Entrance Hall" note="Entrance Hall">
    <description>Light flows like a stream from beyond a large archway, enveloping the entire entrance hall with radiance.  Beautifully carved pillars stand on either side of the arch, greeting visitors and monks that make their way towards the center of the globe.  Curving along the outer wall of the Temple, long plaster hallways with polished mahogany floors lead worshippers clockwise and widdershins around the sphere.</description>
    <position x="340" y="400" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany pillars" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Serene white plaster walls curve along the narrow temple passage, bowing up to the ceiling in a gentle arc.  Not a pinch of dust or dirt can be seen in the hall -- even the walls have been scrubbed to perfection.  Reflecting every movement, the immaculate low-lustre floors dance with hazy images of monks as they pass on their way to prayer.  In the center of the room is a small wooden pedestal, its surface guarded by a flawless glass case.</description>
    <position x="260" y="379" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="double doors" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Polished wooden floors meet a sweeping staircase which rises along the outer wall.  Clerics in colorful robes pass through the corridor or on the stairs, their footsteps echoing with a natural rhythm.  In the center of the passage, a pedestal sits on a tiny dais.  Illuminated by strategically placed mirrors behind the candle sconces, the pedestal demands attention, reaching out to onlookers as if it had a story to tell.</description>
    <position x="201" y="320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Light streams out from a torch set into a pedestal in the center of the room, creating distorted shadows on the curved walls.  Securely mounted along the outer curve is a display of battle-worn weapons, all old but obviously well cared for.  The presence of such items within the peaceful solemnity of the Temple acts as a grim reminder of the dangers in the outside world.</description>
    <position x="180" y="240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>The ceiling fixture in this room has not been lit, giving the hallway a darkened appearance.  Along the inner wall, a square patch of floorboards has a dull finish, unlike the polished wood which gleams through the rest of the hallway.</description>
    <position x="260" y="101" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Accented by the lingering smell of wood oils, the slippery surface of the glossy mahogany flooring reflects the hallway's illumination like carefully polished armor.  Standing guard in the center of the room is a simple wooden pedestal, shielding its display beneath a thin glass case.</description>
    <position x="340" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="The Crossing Temple, Hallway">
    <description>Candles glow softly behind stained-glass holders in the sconces along the walls, sending beacons of red and blue light dancing along the curve of the hallway.  Shadows pool sullenly along the baseboards and floor, driven down by the vivid illumination higher on the walls to meld with the dark wooden floorboards.  Tiny droplets of paint have been speckled into the floor's finish, spreading out from the base of the pedestal like miniature stars in a mahogany sky.</description>
    <position x="420" y="101" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="The Crossing Temple, Main Arch" note="holy water basin|basin">
    <description>Beneath the main arch, this alcove offers an awe-inspiring view of the High Altar.  A black marble promenade sweeps between two of the vast step-like seating areas as it heads towards a circular platform in the center of the domed sphere.  Prismatic light beams down upon the altar from above, its illumination stretching though the main arch, embracing everyone entering the Temple.  Beneath the apex of the arch is a golden basin set upon a humble wooden pedestal.</description>
    <position x="340" y="372" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany pillars" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Dark Promenade">
    <description>Toward the south, an alabaster archway has been inlaid with highly polished onyx to form the image of a spiked mace in low relief.  A mahogany pedestal cradling a shallow basin is visible beyond the arch, while in the opposite direction, black marble tiles line the ground between pale walls of granite and lead toward the temple's High Altar.</description>
    <position x="340" y="344" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Dark Promenade">
    <description>The sound of footsteps against black marble is trapped by the tall granite walls, sending a haunting echo down the length of the promenade.  Beams of light cast down from the temple's great skylight glint off the surfaces of the passage in cool luminescent streams, emphasizing a stark contrast between the dark marble underfoot and the pale grey stone that rises upward on either side.</description>
    <position x="340" y="316" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Dark Promenade">
    <description>The marble-tiled passage continues its path between the grey granite walls.  High above, rows of mahogany benches are visible as they sweep upward toward the rim of circular chamber.  Lining the promenade, murals have been etched into the stone's surface, depicting stylized renditions of the negative aspects of the Thirteen.</description>
    <position x="340" y="288" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Dark Promenade">
    <description>A circular mosaic formed of interlaced black, white and grey marble tiles cascades from the base of a granite platform.  A torrent of black marble streams out of the tiling, cutting through great walls of granite to form passage toward an archway to the south.</description>
    <position x="340" y="260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Southeast Stairway">
    <description>Seamlessly arranged around the altar platform to the northwest, tiles of white, black, and grey circle gracefully beneath the colorful Eyes of the Thirteen.  Rising with solemn pride, a line of granite stairs climbs the distance between this promenade and the ring of six arches far above, granting access to the upper levels of the temple as well as the southeastern seating areas.</description>
    <position x="360" y="260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairway" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Light Promenade">
    <description>A circle of small marble tiles has been laid over the floor surrounding a low grey platform, forming an exquisitely patterned mosaic of grey, black and white.  At this end of the promenade, the white marble streams out of the tiling and extends across the passage as it cuts northeast through the curving granite that rises above on either side.</description>
    <position x="360" y="220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, North Stairway">
    <description>Square tiles of white, black, and grey circle around the raised altar to the south, every footstep quietly sounding beneath the watchful gaze of the Thirteen.  Rising with steady confidence, a line of granite stairs climbs the distance between this walkway and a ring of arches far above, allowing access to the upper levels of the temple, as well as the coliseum-style seating areas.</description>
    <position x="340" y="220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairway" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Grey Promenade">
    <description>Upon a granite platform rests a metallic altar, its stone base surrounded by a mosaic formed of grey, white and black marble.  Underfoot, grey marble extends from the tiling and cascades to the northwest as smooth as a stream toward a mahogany arch.  Tall walls of granite are visible a few paces down the passage, rising on either side to form the promenade.</description>
    <position x="320" y="220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Southwest Stairway">
    <description>Tiles of grey, white, and black scatter around the altar platform to the northeast, every footstep resounding softly beneath the vigilant gaze of the Thirteen.  Rising with solemn pride, a line of granite stairs climbs the distance between this promenade and a ring of six arches far above, granting access to the upper levels of the temple, as well as the staggered seating areas.</description>
    <position x="320" y="260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairway" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, The High Altar" note="Shrine1-06|Ve Aevan Gaenan|High Altar" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>The gentle touch of the sun is caught by the temple's great skylight high overhead, falling in rays of prismatic light upon a large metallic altar poised on this pale granite platform.  The varied colors cast down from the domed Eyes of the Thirteen add to the day's brush of illumination, melding softly upon the altar's reflective surface.  From this sacred point, the massive chamber sweeps majestically upwards, stairways and benches rising to meet the archways and domes of light that circle above.</description>
    <description>High above, the temple's great iris skylight ushers in the stars' cool illumination, bathing the large metallic altar in pale light.  Drawn as if to a lodestone, soft glints of color from the domed Eyes far overhead lend their prismatic overtones to the clarity of starlight.  Sweeping majestically upwards from this raised platform, the stairways and benches lining the massive chamber dwindle into deepest shadow as they climb to meet the vague outlines of archways arrayed in a surrounding ring far above.</description>
    <position x="340" y="240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Grey Promenade">
    <description>Row upon row of mahogany benches lines the upper edge of the granite walls that border this promenade, marking a gentle slope that curves upward toward the rim of the spherical chamber.  A massive mural has been etched into the entirety of the spacious pale stone, spanning from the grey marble tiles to the upper edge of the wall, stretching so far above that the highest placed carvings slip from focus.</description>
    <position x="300" y="200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Grey Promenade">
    <description>Glints of light are visible in the distance, reflecting off the High Altar's smooth surface in the center of this cavernous room.  The tall pale granite walls seem to meld into the smooth grey marble underfoot that extends towards a mahogany arch to the northwest and the altar to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="280" y="180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Grey Promenade">
    <description>The grey stone walls rise to an immense height, dwarfing anyone who stands between their massive countenance.  The murals etched into the walls that depict the neutral emblems of the Thirteen take on an almost overwhelming presence upon the tall slabs of granite, their gaze constant upon all who pass.  In contrast, a mahogany arch beckons silently to the northwest, the wood heavily polished and carved with images of shields overlaid one atop another.</description>
    <position x="260" y="160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Light Promenade">
    <description>The white marble passage continues between the tall grey granite walls.  On both sides, images have been carved into the stone, creating an elaborate but elegant mural.  Sconces line the walls, casting a soft glow upon both the etchings and the marble underfoot.  Above, row upon row of mahogany benches lines the great stairways, curving upwards along the sloping granite.</description>
    <position x="380" y="200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Light Promenade">
    <description>Drifting gracefully from the great skylight above, pale beams of starlight fall upon the marble tiles and stream across the tall granite walls, lending subtle warmth to the coolness of stone against stone.</description>
    <description>Drifting gracefully from the great skylight above, pale beams of sunlight fall upon the white marble tiles and stream across the tall granite walls, lending subtle warmth to the coolness of stone against stone.</description>
    <position x="400" y="180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Light Promenade">
    <description>The promenade ends at a mahogany arch, bordered by row upon row of mahogany benches lining the sloping edge of the granite walls.  In the distance, the metallic gleam of the temple's High Altar is visible near the center of the sphere, illuminated by the great skylight high overhead.</description>
    <description>The promenade ends at a mahogany arch, bordered by row upon row of mahogany benches lining the sloping edge of the granite walls.  Moonlight streams through the skylight to bathe the temple's High Altar in a soft glow.</description>
    <position x="420" y="160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The hallway continues its curved passage leading to each of the Eyes of the Thirteen.  A narrow wooden staircase, recessed into one wall, is visible as it curves gently downward toward the lower portions of the temple.  To the northwest within the curving passage, sprinkles of some kind of shimmering purple dust are visible on the floor, adding a remarkable contrast of color against the white plaster walls.</description>
    <position x="461" y="107" z="3" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" hidden="True" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The lacquered mahogany borders that ornament the hallway arc over a break in the curving walls.  Recessed slightly, a staircase curves and vanishes from vision as it gently slopes downwards, faint beams of light visible as they reflect off the surfaces below.</description>
    <position x="219" y="107" z="3" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" hidden="True" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>Warm textured layers of rich dark mahogany frame an archway, beckoning towards a golden-hued marble platform.  The faint glow from within the shrine cascades across the stark white plaster walls, lending its warm glow to this stretch of hallway as it curves its way around the temple.</description>
    <position x="275" y="72" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go framed archway" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The lily-white plaster walls gently curve along the corridor, following the spheriform shape of the temple itself.  Through a bleached ash archway along the inner wall, a pale alabaster platform extends out over the High Altar area.</description>
    <position x="340" y="60" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ash archway" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>Lacquered mahogany trim streaks across the bottom of the white plaster wall as it meanders its way around the gentle curvature of the hallway.  A set of wolf prints sprinkled with deep purple alexandrite dust is sculpted into the floor, leading the way into the shrine which lies beyond the polished black granite archway.</description>
    <position x="405" y="72" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black archway" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>Matte black marble rises in a graceful arch leading to the entrance to a shrine.  Steel dagger hilts, their blades buried in the stone, radiate outwards along the curve of the arch, while the keystone is carved with the image of a snarling amber-eyed panther.</description>
    <position x="501" y="160" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble arch" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>Finely carved mahogany borders hug the curves of the archway which serves as entrance to the shrine.  A faint corona of ruddy light flows through the arch, bathing the pale paster with a pale reddish tint.</description>
    <position x="519" y="223" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The pale walls of the hallway curve to each side, reflecting on floors of polished marble tile.  Set into the tiles before the entrance to the Shrine of Mortals is an intricate mosaic crafted from multicolored glass.  Diffused blue light pours through the silver-inlaid mahogany archway, setting the glittering mosaic afire with color.</description>
    <position x="513" y="289" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany archway" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The scent of incense from somewhere nearby wafts through the air, filling the space with a mild, sweet aroma.  Revealed by a narrow arch within a section of the curving walls, a narrow staircase flows upwards and disappears above as it arcs up toward the uppermost areas of the temple.</description>
    <position x="484" y="348" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The curving white plaster walls are tinted a rich luminous green as light flows beneath a gem-encrusted satinwood archway.  Beyond the archway, a silver platform leads out into the Eye of the Serpent.</description>
    <position x="435" y="393" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go satinwood archway" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The hallway continues its circular path within the white plaster walls of the temple.  Perfect mirror images, two cresting waves have been inlaid into the tile floor before a narrow archway leading toward a blue crystal platform.</description>
    <position x="373" y="417" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow archway" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The cool white walls of the hallway are broken by two pillars of ivory -- a pair of carved mammoth tusks forming an archway to a shrine bathed in amber light.</description>
    <position x="307" y="417" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ivory arch" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>The gentle glow of candlelight emanates from beneath a lacquered oaken archway, causing fickle figures to dance across the delicate white plaster walls.</description>
    <position x="245" y="393" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken archway" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>A faint flickering of color and luminescence cascades along the white plaster walls, drifting from the nearby shrines dedicated to the gods and their aspects.  The path of the play of light is broken momentarily as it crosses a narrow archway curving over a staircase leading upwards, deeper into the temple's structure.</description>
    <position x="196" y="348" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>Rosy light flows into the hallway from a carved white crystal archway, casting a gentle pinkish tint over the white plaster walls.  The faint sound of music echoes through the air.</description>
    <position x="167" y="289" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white archway" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>Curving along pristine walls of white plaster, a reflection of light, emanating from a translucent jade archway, creates a striking contrast between subtle shadow and dominant light.  Claws, carved with a remarkably realistic effect, stand at the base of the archway, warding off some unseen attack.</description>
    <position x="161" y="223" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go jade archway" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hallway">
    <description>This portion of the hallway is dominated by a polished ebony archway that leads into the Shrine of the Void.  Nothing is visible beyond the arch, as the only light which streams out on to the platform is the weak ambient light from down the hall.</description>
    <position x="179" y="160" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebony archway" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Kertigen's Shrine" note="Divyaush|Zachriedek">
    <description>Flecks of platinum and gold embedded in the marble floor shimmer softly in the warm serene glow of light filling the area as it seeps through the sunlight-colored dome.  Resting quietly on the end of the platform, a scintillating statue of glimmering crystals and precious metals stands in reverence to the god of riches.</description>
    <position x="282" y="91" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glittering platform" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Kertigen" note="Kertigen">
    <description>Gazing out over the temple floor, a statue atop the altar rests protected by a fine crystalline dome covering the end of the platform.  The light from the temple, shaded to a rich golden yellow, washes over the heavily adorned sculpture.  Its wealth of gems and precious metals splash tiny reflections on every surface, a sea of shining stars across a sunlit sky.</description>
    <position x="289" y="109" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hodierna's Shrine" note="Asketi|Berengaria">
    <description>The platform is surrounded by a large opaline crystal dome.  Leading out to the hallway of the temple, a bleached ash archway stands as noble sentry, guarding this sacred shrine.  Faint etchings have been made in the pale alabaster floor, leading inward toward the end of the crystal half-sphere.</description>
    <position x="340" y="80" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ash archway" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster platform" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Hodierna" note="Hodierna">
    <description>The air itself seems to glow here as the light from beyond the dome filters through in a luminous blur.  At the end of the platform, nestled up against the crystal, stands a low white marble altar which rises seamlessly upward into a magnificent triptych statue, basking in the nimbus of pearly light that permeates this place.</description>
    <position x="340" y="100" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Meraud's Shrine" note="Firulf|Kerenhappuch">
    <description>Carved alexandrite-dusted wolf prints continue their trek over a black onyx platform, making their way towards a polished granite altar set at the darkened far end.  On either side of the dome are black steel braziers that are lit with eerie purple flames, setting a surreal ambience in the room.  The lighting caresses its way across the four intricate carvings lined on either side of the tracks set into the platform.</description>
    <position x="398" y="91" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black archway" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go onyx platform" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Meraud" note="Meraud">
    <description>The gem-kissed wolf tracks end their journey at an inscription carved before a polished black granite altar veined in deep purple alexandrite.  Sitting on top of the structure is a stunningly detailed statue sculpted from polished granite as dark as the stone from which the altar is made.  Encompassing the platform is a faceted dark crystal dome that refracts the incoming light with the glow coming from the braziers into a dimly hued array of color and shadow.</description>
    <position x="391" y="109" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Damaris' Shrine" note="Phelim|Dergati">
    <description>Walls draped entirely in black silk fill the length of this platform with shadows that shift from ebon to deep azure as light falls from the dome of midnight-blue glass above.  Barely silhouetted in the gloom is the lithe form of a life-sized obsidian panther depicted in full stalk, the great cat seeming to lead the way towards the room beyond.  Someone has placed a garland of scarlet nightshade around its neck, the blossoms gone fiery against the dark, glassy stone of the sculpture.</description>
    <position x="483" y="169" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble arch" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go onyx platform" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Damaris" note="Damaris">
    <description>Filtering through crystalline stars circling the apex of the midnight-blue dome, beams silvered like moonlight edge a graceful obsidian altar at the end of the platform.  Countless bas-relief nightingales swirl up its sides, wings flared and heads flung back in eternal nightsong.  Encircling its base is a ring of shrike skulls, each polished to the warm glow of old ivory and gleaming with opulent rows of tiny jet and lapis beads.</description>
    <position x="465" y="178" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Everild's Shrine" note="Kuniyo|Trothfang">
    <description>Fiery shades of red blaze within the confines of this stark chamber, the light from the temple shining smoothly through the warmth of the crystal resting over the far end the platform.  A gentle tapping whispers throughout the room as a barbed spear suspended from the ceiling strikes softly against a battered shield that hangs above the archway.  Resting silently at the edge of the platform, a statue set in pure silver gazes outward, its vigil over the temple floor below constant and unending.</description>
    <position x="499" y="225" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crimson-covered platform" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Everild" note="Everild">
    <description>Streaks of red tint the fine crystal dome, cascading over the surface of the altar and down to the lip of the platform.  A single white beam of light pokes through a tiny fracture in the crystal, reflecting brightly upon a polished silver statue.</description>
    <position x="479" y="227" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Truffenyi's Shrine" note="Alamhif|Huldah">
    <description>A silvery blue dome erupts from the wall above, creating a hemisphere to enclose the shrine in hues that mimic the summer sky.  Sunlight filtering through the crystal from the chamber beyond fills the room with a steady glow that sparkles where it touches silver specks in the dark granite platform beneath you.  Sitting near the archway, an obsidian stand is tipped slightly beneath the paws of an impish agate weasel, leaving a silver magpie on top to backwing as its perch is pushed out from under it.</description>
    <description>A silvery blue dome erupts from the wall above, creating a hemisphere to enclose the shrine in hues that mimic the summer sky.  Starlight filtering through the crystal from the chamber beyond fills the room with a wan glow that glitters where it touches silver specks in the dark granite platform beneath you.  Sitting near the archway, an obsidian stand is tipped slightly beneath the paws of an impish agate weasel, leaving a silver magpie on top to backwing as its perch is pushed out from under it.</description>
    <position x="495" y="285" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany archway" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite platform" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Truffenyi" note="Truffenyi">
    <description>The granite platform sparkles slightly where touched by the diffused light shed by the silvery blue dome.  Silver feathers inlaid in the crystal dapple the surface of a polished granite altar with tiny shadows that almost blend into the stone's already mottled surface.  Rising from the altar's center is an ornately carved triptych statue crafted so seamlessly as to appear an extension of the same stone of the altar.</description>
    <position x="475" y="278" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Hav'roth's Shrine" note="Peri'el|Ushnish">
    <description>The silver platform below you gleams as a sea of liquid emerald, the light striking it tinted by a green crystal half-sphere that encases this small shrine.  Tiny people bustle in and out of the seats in the High Altar chamber below, some likely waiting for the next sermon to begin under the Eyes of the Thirteen.</description>
    <position x="424" y="376" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go satinwood archway" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver platform" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Hav'roth" note="Hav'roth">
    <description>A faceted green crystal dome encases the end of the smooth silver platform, giving the shrine the appearance of being trapped within the delicate crystalline structure of an emerald.  The green glow casts itself throughout, as if the only color ever known to this place.  At the edge of the platform, just against the dome, a bejeweled silver triptych statue rests upon a low altar.</description>
    <position x="414" y="359" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eluned's Shrine" note="Lemicus |Drogor">
    <description>Glistening like cool water, a blue crystal platform leads toward a coral statue resting deeper within the Shrine of the Ocean Mother.  Fashioned from the same material as the passage underfoot, a great oval dome curves down to cradle the shrine in the deep blue light found within the heart of the sea.  An indigo glaze marks the center of the colored half-sphere above the far statue, as though this were the eye of Eluned herself, gazing down upon the High Altar below.</description>
    <position x="369" y="397" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crystal platform" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow archway" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Eluned" note="Eluned">
    <description>A rose coral statue rises from its altar base as seamlessly as a wave, silhouetted against a large blue crystal dome that juts out toward the center of the temple.  Filling the space with a bluish glow, faint streams of light accent the ridges and valleys along the carving, granting it a sense of motion despite its lifeless structure.</description>
    <position x="366" y="378" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Glythtide's Shrine" note="Saemaus|Smaragdaus|Be'ort">
    <description>The arch leading to the hallway is flanked by two large murals depicting key moments in divine history.  They are bathed in a warm amber glow coming from the direction of the platform.  The wash of golden light makes the room seem as if one were viewing it through a mug of pale beer.</description>
    <position x="311" y="397" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ivory arch" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platform" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Glythtide" note="Glythtide">
    <description>A huge ale-brown crystal dome bows out into thin air, providing an amber-tinted view of the chamber below.  Golden light washes over an altar crafted from thick, twisted grapevines sitting at the end of the platform.  A three-part statue rises seamlessly from the top of the altar.</description>
    <position x="314" y="378" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Tamsine's Shrine" note="Albreda|Harawep">
    <description>A pale golden crystal dome extends outward from the wall to surround the amber platform which stretches out from beneath the lacquered oaken archway.  Two rows of Halfling-high candles line either side of the platform, casting an inviting glow throughout the entire shrine.</description>
    <position x="256" y="376" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken archway" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go amber platform" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Tamsine" note="Tamsine">
    <description>The amber platform ends here, both rows of candles curving around to meet each other behind a low yew altar that stands just before the end of the pale golden crystal dome.  The candlelight gleams brightly against the sloping window, creating an illuminating halo about a yew triptych statue that rests upon the altar.</description>
    <position x="266" y="359" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Faenella's Shrine" note="Murrula|Idon">
    <description>Mirrored panels line the reflective glass of the platform, echoing the image of the altar located at the front of the shrine from innumerable different angles.  Light ripples in through the ruby-colored dome that arcs over the shrine, casting everything in the room with a pink hue.  An elaborately carved crystal archway leads into the hallway.</description>
    <position x="186" y="284" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white archway" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crystal platform" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Faenella" note="Faenella">
    <description>Bathed in a pale rose hue from the light flowing through the moonlight ruby colored dome, the mirror-paneled chamber reflects multiple images of the carved rosewood statue upon the altar at the edge of the platform.</description>
    <position x="205" y="278" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Chadatru's Shrine" note="Rutilor|Botolf">
    <description>Walls of jade edged in mahogany line the shrine, creating the feel of a clouded atmosphere.  Finely carved from mahogany and possessing startling lifelikeness, lions peer out beyond their posts with an eyeless gaze.  Translucent jade forms a platform that extends outward, towards a muted dome, while an archway leads back toward the hallway.</description>
    <position x="181" y="225" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go jade archway" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go jade platform" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Chadatru" note="Chadatru">
    <description>Formed out of seamless translucent jade-colored crystal, a dome extends out beyond the platform that supports it, drawing in an eerie reflection of light from the exterior of the dome.  Sculpted from jade is a simple altar that extends outward, upon which rests a translucent triptych statue that stands as mute sentry to its surroundings.</description>
    <position x="201" y="227" z="3" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Urrem'tier's Shrine" note="Eylhaar|Aldauth">
    <description>A sea of inky shadows is all that is visible deeper within the black glass dome.  The glossy jet platform gleams with what little light filters through the polished ebony archway that leads back into the temple halls.</description>
    <position x="197" y="169" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebony archway" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go jet platform" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Eyes of the Thirteen, Eye of Urrem'tier" note="Urrem'tier">
    <description>The artificial light brought into this chamber seems feeble and choked, as if struggling for its own life amidst the blackness that saturates this small shrine.  A giant obsidian dome envelops the glossy jet platform, trapping the chamber in eternal darkness.  Resting flush up against the dome on the edge of the platform is a low onyx altar upon which rests a strange statue.</description>
    <position x="215" y="178" z="3" />
    <arc exit="none" move="pull silver candlestick" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>The scent of fresh baked bread and a multitude of herbs wafts from a narrow arch as the cramped hallway continues its curved path leading from one section of the monks' quarters to the next.  A niche in one wall leads to a staircase that provides access to the lower sections of the temple.</description>
    <position x="185" y="199" z="4" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" hidden="True" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow arch" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>A panel of glass between the white plaster walls blocks the northern end of the passage.  Various plants growing heartily are visible beyond, the heavy scent of dirt managing to waft its way through and filling the hallway with a metallic, earthy scent.</description>
    <position x="495" y="199" z="4" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" hidden="True" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>A bleached pine door stands silently on the east side of the curved hallway, the scent of amber emanating slightly from the room beyond.  The white plaster ceiling slopes in a gentle curve above the door, bringing attention to a watercolor mural.</description>
    <position x="495" y="281" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>A bleached pine door, surrounded by a molding carved to depict sirese flowers in full bloom, stands to the east toward the rim of the sphere while a highly polished ebonwood door blocks passage at the southern end of the hallway.  The light scent of amber wafts within the walls from two oil burners mounted into the white plaster, filling this otherwise confining space with a sense of warmth and welcoming.</description>
    <position x="453" y="353" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Monks' Quarters, Library" note="Tamar|Library">
    <description>Glass-covered bookcases hug the walls, protecting the various tomes from the rough hands of time and dust.  Small cushioned chairs fill the center of the room and provide a comfortable space for monks, scholars or those simply filled with curiosity to read the treasure of stories, histories and accounts that fill the shelves.  Carefully tended by the monks to guard against fire or smoke damage, candles have been lined along the mahogany molding.</description>
    <position x="381" y="395" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebonwood door" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>Small sconces line the walls.  Maintained by the temple's monks, they provide ever-present light within the passages.  A mahogany door stands proudly at the end of the hallway, the gentle glow from the candles making the polished wood glisten with a reddish hue.</description>
    <position x="299" y="395" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Monks' Quarters, East Dormitory">
    <description>Warm light drifts from four tall candle holders placed in each corner of the room, casting a gentle glow upon a watercolor painting on the east wall.  A wooden desk is cramped between two small bunk beds, each draped with a red wool blanket.</description>
    <position x="439" y="339" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Monks' Quarters, Meditation Room">
    <description>Ten willow-reed mats circle a single oil lamp which gives off the faint, wafting scent of burning amber.  The aroma induces a feeling of calm and serenity, creating the perfect environment in which to spend hours in prayer and meditation.  A large plaque is centered above a tall fern on the far wall.</description>
    <position x="475" y="276" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>The plaster walls are accented with red mahogany borders at both the ceiling and floor as the hallway continues its circular path.  A small wooden door carved with a tiny trail of vines along each of its four sides stands welcoming against the southern wall while an ebonwood door blocks further passage in a clockwise direction.</description>
    <position x="227" y="353" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebonwood door" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Monks' Quarters, Dining Room">
    <description>A silver plaque, adorned with the stylized rendition of a rearing unicorn, hangs on the wall above a circular oak table that fills most of this room.  Torcheres line the walls and fill the small space with a gentle light and the everpresent mild scent of smoke.  A narrow red rug lines the barely passable space between the fixtures and the chairs that surround the table.</description>
    <position x="185" y="281" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebonwood door" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Monks' Quarters, Kitchen">
    <description>This small kitchen is as warm and full of wonderful scents as a Halfling grandmother's.  A pine sideboard is draped with a cheery red tablecloth, and a large iron stew pot sits atop a simple wood stove.  Sconces cover the walls between narrow cupboards, filling the windowless room with a soft glow and the scent of smoke mixed with herbs and fresh baked bread.  A crowd of pots and pans hangs from the ceiling, making it impossible to pull one object down without sending all the others toppling to the floor.</description>
    <position x="227" y="127" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow arch" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Monks' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>A door formed from bleached pine wood and another of frosted glass stand on either side of this short hallway.  Near the uppermost portion of the sphere, this passage is remarkably constricted, every amount of space having been preserved for the monks' living areas.</description>
    <position x="299" y="85" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" hidden="True" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Monks' Quarters, Garden">
    <description>The floor of this room has been structured to extend further toward the center of the sphere.  Panels of glass surround it, allowing sunlight to filter through the skylight on the top of the temple and feed the ever-hungry plants and herbs that grow here.  Rows of shelves fill the semi-circular room, permeating the space with color and the scent of growth.</description>
    <description>The floor of this room has been structured to extend further into the sphere, below the temple's great skylight.  Panels of glass surround the space and function like a greenhouse, keeping this room ever warm and moist.  Small candles burn in between the pots of plants, flowers and herbs, complementing the multitudes of stars above.</description>
    <position x="381" y="85" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Monks' Quarters, Gardener's Room">
    <description>This entire room is filled in every nook and cranny with flowers, plants and herbs.  Some have been carefully wrapped with thin cotton cloth as one would a fresh wound.  A tiny cot just fits between two large potted ferns whose leafy tendrils cascade down and drape across the floor.  In one corner, a large wicker basket is filled with dirt-stained garden tools.</description>
    <position x="453" y="127" z="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="High Priestess' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>Granite benches provide a place to sit for those waiting to hold audience with the High Priestess of the temple.  The door to her office is fashioned from mahogany, carved with the crest of the guild of clerics which is encircled by two palm leaves.  Tendrils of smoke carrying the scent of exotic incense float lazily through the archway, drifting up from the monks' quarters below.</description>
    <position x="340" y="120" z="5" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" hidden="True" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="High Priestess' Quarters, Hallway">
    <description>Each step echoing from the cool marble floor of the hallway reverberates against the temple's plaster walls, intruding upon the monastic silence.  A faint breeze, redolent with the sweet fragrance of flowers and the spicy aroma of herbs, drifts down a narrow winding staircase, while the muffled sounds of distant chanting floats up from the temple below.</description>
    <position x="454" y="203" z="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding stairway" hidden="True" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="High Priestess' Quarters, Private Chambers">
    <description>Comfortable furnishings clutter this cramped bedchamber, the need for function competing with the limits of the space.  A flickering pool of light plays over a tiny writing table near the mahogany door, cast by a tallow candle.  In the center of the room, a mahogany bed nestles amidst teetering stacks of books and parchments fallen from a shelf along the wall.</description>
    <position x="411" y="337" z="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="High Priestess' Quarters, Defense Control" note="Defense Control Room">
    <description>Two large cambrinth-framed mirrors -- one oval, the other rectangular -- seem out of place as the only attempt at decoration in this chamber.  A rounded marble console emerges fluidly from the wall as though part of the same stone, or sculpted by magic.  Atop the console, a series of unusual gems are arrayed on the surface of a bronze panel.</description>
    <position x="269" y="337" z="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron-bound door" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="High Priestess' Quarters, Office" note="Tallis|High Priestess" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A dark wooden desk sits before a small window that looks over the temple below.  Bronze braziers stand to either side of an iron-bound door, their glowing embers providing light and warmth to the office of the key religious leader of the province.  Two wooden chairs provide a place to sit for those who would seek advice or counsel with the High Priestess of the great temple.</description>
    <position x="226" y="203" z="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron-bound door" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>Well-tended rows of herbs and flowers stretch in leafy array over the convex surface, reined in by a sturdy railing that guards against a perilous drop from the steepening curve of the dome.  A gravel path trails between the rows and rises gently toward a spire that juts from the center of the roof.  The fire from the top of the nearby watchtower flares faintly against the warm light of day.</description>
    <description>Well-tended rows of herbs and flowers stretch in leafy array over the convex surface, reined in by a sturdy railing that guards against a perilous drop from the steepening curve of the dome.  A gravel path trails between the rows and rises gently toward a spire that juts from the center of the roof.  The fire from the top of the nearby watchtower flickers brightly against the night sky.</description>
    <position x="320" y="260" z="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go winding stair" hidden="True" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>Sturdy, thick planks of wood curve around the perimeter of the garden.  A small streamer of ivy has wound around the railing and swings gently with every gust of wind.  The breeze bears with it the reeking scents of the Segoltha River mingled with the sharp tang of smoke from the nearby watchtowers.</description>
    <position x="340" y="280" z="6" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>When the wind shifts, smoke from the watchtower directly southeast drifts through the slats of the railing and across the path.  The flourishing plants appear not to suffer for it, however, and thrive in the rays of the sun.</description>
    <description>When the wind shifts, smoke from the watchtower directly southeast drifts through the slats of the railing and across the path.  The flourishing plants appear not to suffer for it, however, and thrive in the light of the stars.</description>
    <position x="360" y="260" z="6" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>A curious sculpture in the shape of a plant with clear leaves stretches low to the ground, taking up much of this patch of soil and swaying gently near the edge of the gravel path.  Sparkles of sunlight dance along the structure, which radiates in thirteen points from its center stalk.  The leaves chime faintly when they brush against the stones and the railing.</description>
    <description>A curious sculpture in the shape of a plant with clear leaves stretches low to the ground, taking up much of this patch of soil and swaying gently near the edge of the gravel path.  Sparkles of starlight dance along the structure, which radiates in thirteen points from its center stalk.  The leaves chime faintly when they brush against the stones and the railing.</description>
    <position x="380" y="240" z="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>The scent of rich loam rises from a mounded heap of dirt from which the monks replenish the garden.  Ivy has gained a foothold in the soil and drapes thickly over the wooden slats, stretching toward the skylights and the curve of the temple below.  One tenacious strand crawls along the gravel path, slowly making its way toward the beacon spire.</description>
    <position x="360" y="220" z="6" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>Here at the northernmost point of the roof garden, a massive watchtower rises beyond the wooden railing, mostly blocking the view of the city below.  The expanse of smooth slate on the tower is mirrored in the metallic beacon spire opposite it at the center of the garden.  A gravel path leads toward the spire and stretches through the rows of leafy plants.</description>
    <position x="340" y="200" z="6" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>A small rosebush clings to the railing, swooning gracefully against its strong support.  Other, better behaved flowers nestle in the thin soil surrounding the gravel paths and flourish among the herbs.  Their blooms follow the sun on its course through the sky's dome, halting only when the shadows of the watchtowers and beacon spire fall across them.</description>
    <description>A small rosebush clings to the railing, swooning gracefully against its strong support.  Other, better behaved flowers nestle in the thin soil surrounding the gravel paths and flourish among the herbs.  Their blooms are quiescent beneath the night sky, lit only by the fires atop the watchtowers that jut beyond the roof.</description>
    <position x="320" y="220" z="6" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, Gardens">
    <description>City sounds rise as a complex melody from the Crossing's teeming streets, drifting aimlessly before fading into the breeze like the smoke that rises from the vents beyond the railing.  The crunch of the gravel path underfoot, the vibrancy of the plants, and the silent spire of the beacon at the center of the roof all contribute to the sense of remoteness from the busy world below.</description>
    <position x="300" y="240" z="6" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel path" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="High Priestess' Sanctuary, The Beacon" note="Beacon|Temple Beacon" color="#00FF00">
    <description>At the center of the dome's surface is a thick metallic spire that rises into the sky, the conjunction of the paths from the edges of the roof and the focus of the three watchtowers.  It is to here, in times of trouble, that the greatest defenses of the temple -- and the city -- are summoned.  The silvery surface of the beacon is cool to the touch, even on the sunniest of days.</description>
    <position x="340" y="240" z="6" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, North Stairway">
    <description>Divided only by these steps of pale granite, a vast sea of mahogany benches lies methodically staggered into the sloping walls of this cavernous room, each seat providing a clear line of sight to the altar below.  Further up the slightly rough stairs, a thick metallic pillar stands proudly, sunk into the granite foundation as if it were required as some fundamental means of support.</description>
    <position x="340" y="185" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, The Pillar" note="cambrinth orb">
    <description>Thick and unyielding as an ancient oak, a steel-like pillar rises from deep within these granite steps, its surface skillfully etched with the nightingale of Phelim and the great wolf of Meraud.  Constructed of the same material as the altar below, the formidable column is capped with a halved sphere of an opalescent mineral whose milky interior swirls with a lazy power.  Seating areas rest on either side of this great marker, each perched in silent vigil high above the sacred altar.</description>
    <position x="340" y="150" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, North Stairway">
    <description>From this landing poised just beneath the Iris Rim, a sweeping granite stairway ascends to the circular ledge above, providing access to the six arches that line the equator of this spherical space, and drawing one toward the watchful Eyes of the Thirteen.  The stairs continue downward in a gentle curve toward the metallic altar, their progress as fluid and graceful as water streaming down a rough face of rock.</description>
    <position x="340" y="115" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>Just below this granite ledge, a steep staircase sweeps down toward the metallic High Altar.  The descending steps are lined on either side by countless mahogany benches, the clean scent of oiled wood drifting upward to fill this airy space.  A black marble arch breaks the smooth wall of plaster to the north, granting access to one of the six shrines located around the Iris Rim.</description>
    <position x="340" y="80" z="2" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairway" hidden="True" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black arch" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>Far below, marble tiles of grey, black and white stream outwards from the base of the High Altar, their motley arrangement growing monochromatic as they begin to define the entrances to their respective promenades.  The broad granite ridge underfoot continues its circular progress around the lofty circumference of Ve Aevan Gaenan, granting access to shrines that wait in either direction.</description>
    <position x="420" y="100" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>A dark marble arch stands patiently to the northeast, its base melding seamlessly with the granite that comprises this curving passage.  Any who dare skirt the rim's inner edge risk a cliff-like fall through open air, only a slight breeze standing between this ledge and the white marble tiles below.</description>
    <position x="480" y="160" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey arch" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>From the edge of the Rim, myriad mahogany benches begin their graceful procession down into the bowl of Ve Aevan Gaenan, every seating area intent on the High Altar.  Appearing for a moment like the delicate sheen of a silken fabric, lines of pale yellow light trace shifting patterns over the white plaster walls, wavering in time with a slight breeze that tickles over the sconces circling the ledge's perimeter.</description>
    <position x="500" y="240" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>Along the outer wall, a lapis-edged arch stands vigil over the entrance to one of the temple's shrines, hints of incense wafting from within to mingle with the mild scent of smoke that drifts along the ledge.  Opposite the shrine's arch, a massive stairway descends toward the interior of the sphere, approaching the nadir of this holy chamber where the High Altar stands in quiet splendor.</description>
    <position x="480" y="320" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lapis-edged arch" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairway" hidden="True" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>The dulcet sound of chanted devotions fills this space, its steady rhythm keeping time with the quiet footsteps that circle the granite Rim.  Cradled within the cauldron of Ve Aevan Gaenan, the temple's High Altar rests beneath the watchful gaze of the Thirteen.</description>
    <position x="420" y="380" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>A red granite arch parts the delicate wall of white plaster, stone meeting stone as the grey passage underfoot continues to circle the inner perimeter of the temple sphere.  Two silver sconces frame the arch, their pale yellow light casting shadows that disappear into the valley of mahogany benches below.</description>
    <position x="340" y="400" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red arch" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>Visible from the edge of this lofty ridge, the High Altar stands proudly upon a raised platform far below, its metallic surface bathed in the soft light that streams down from the watchful Eyes of the Thirteen.  The Iris Rim continues its circular path around the circumference of this massive chamber, both directions leading toward one of the six arches that line this level of the Temple.</description>
    <position x="260" y="380" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>The circular rim underfoot seems to flow toward the graceful cascade of a pale granite stairway, its procession of worked stone streaming down around a steel-like pillar below.  Opposite the stairway, a pale-green chalcedony arch beckons silently toward the shrine that waits within.</description>
    <position x="200" y="320" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go chalcedony arch" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>The wide granite walkway of the Iris Rim curves around the interior of the temple sphere, its circular path visible across the vast expanse of the bowl-like chamber.  Six stone archways are spaced evenly along the entire circumference of the ledge, each poised in silent dignity before the shrine that waits within.</description>
    <position x="180" y="240" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>The edge of the walkway marks a perilous drop to the marble of the Grey Promenade that divides the northeast seating areas of Ve Aevan Gaenan.  Toward the center of the chamber below, grey tiles mingle with those of white and black, uniting to form an elegant mosaic around the High Altar.  An alabaster arch beckons in the opposite direction, providing access to one of the six shrines that line the Iris Rim.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="The Iris Rim, Hallway">
    <description>Following the inner circumference of the Temple, the Iris Rim provides an uninterrupted view of both the High Altar below and the vigilant Eyes of the Thirteen above.  From those thirteen iris-shaped panes of glass, thirteen different colors of cool light touch the chamber below, illuminating with a pale grace.</description>
    <position x="260" y="100" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go clockwise" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go widdershins" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="The Iris Rim, Shrine of Destruction" note="Shrine of Destruction|Destruction">
    <description>The walls of this room are formed of smooth black trachyte, the reflective surface carved with images of Gorbesh soldiers ransacking and pillaging the former temple.  Resting in the center of the shrine, a dull iron altar leans awkwardly, its base cracked and broken.  A fierce depiction of the power of destruction, this room is an eerie reminder that nothing is eternal.</description>
    <position x="444" y="180" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey arch" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="The Iris Rim, Shrine of Outwardness" note="Shrine of Outwardness|Outwardness">
    <description>Dedicated to spirit manifested outwardly, one wall of this room is dominated by a rich tapestry.  Its opulent stitchery depicts a kneeling, plate-clad warrior humbly offering his blade to an Alfar whose blazing, unearthly beauty surrounds him with radiance.  A stained glass roundel depicting Elanthia graces the ceiling, traced in gold with the major trade routes of land and sea.  A bright flicker in one corner reveals an extraordinary sculpture -- a crystal phoenix rising amidst real flames.</description>
    <position x="444" y="300" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lapis-edged arch" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="The Iris Rim, Warrior's Shrine" note="Warrior's Shrine">
    <description>This room is faced with polished deep red porphyry and is dedicated to those whose burden in life is blood and battle.  Burning steadily, two torches frame a small steel altar forged from broken weapons, and cast long finger-like shadows across the shards of glistening metal.  A simple porcelain bowl rests in the middle of the altar, its white surface stained copper by the many offerings of blood droplets the temple monks provide during their vigils.</description>
    <position x="340" y="360" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red arch" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="The Iris Rim, Shrine of Thought" note="Shrine of Thought|Thought">
    <description>To free the mind for journeying along the pathways of thought, this room is bare of ornamentation, the bustle and din of the outside world held at bay by thick marble walls draped in blue-black velvet.  Deep silence reigns here, and soft darkness surrounds all.  Suspended near the apex of the high arched ceiling is a luminous crystalline sphere, its silvery light falling upon a single white lotus blossom centered on a little sandalwood altar.</description>
    <position x="236" y="300" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go chalcedony arch" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="The Iris Rim, Shrine of Healing" note="Shrine of Healing|Healing">
    <description>Designed to honor those who devote their lives to the salvation of bodies and souls, this shrine is decorated with a profusion of flowers and medicinal herbs.  Fresh flowers adorn the wall next to the alabaster arch leading into the hallway, and a collage of dried flowers protected by glass looms over the altar in the back of the room.</description>
    <position x="236" y="180" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="The Iris Rim, Shrine of Foresight" note="Shrine of Foresight|Foresight">
    <description>This shrine is possessed of a dreamlike ambiance, watery illumination emanating from the core of a delicate crystal bowl resting upon the central altar.  Faint streaks of colored light meet walls obscured by sheer curtains of smoke and shadow around the circumference of the room painted constellations and moons tease at the edge of recognition before again slipping behind the cloak of satin darkness.</description>
    <position x="340" y="120" z="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black arch" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Southwest Stairway">
    <description>Rows of mahogany benches blend into a continuous sea of darkly stained wood, the wedge-shaped seating area bisected by the clean lines of these granite steps.  Further up the stairs, a thick metallic pillar stands firmly, rooted deep into the foundation as if it had been built around rather than added to the structure.</description>
    <position x="300" y="280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="stairs down" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, The Pillar" note="cambrinth orb">
    <description>Rising from deep within the pale granite, a steel-like pillar stands with regal dignity, its surface carefully etched with the horned owl of Firulf and the great wolf of Meraud.  Its composition strikingly similar to the altar below, the formidable column is capped with a halved sphere of an opalescent mineral whose milky interior swirls with a tamed power.  Spacious seating areas rest on either side of this great marker, each perched in silent vigil high above the sacred altar.</description>
    <position x="280" y="300" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Southwest Stairway">
    <description>From this landing poised just beneath the Iris Rim, a sweeping granite stairway climbs onto the annular ledge above, providing access to the six arches that line the equator of this spherical space, and drawing one toward the watchful Eyes of the Thirteen.  The stairs continue downward in a gentle curve toward the metallic altar, their progress as fluid and graceful as water streaming down a rough face of rock.</description>
    <position x="260" y="320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Southeast Stairway">
    <description>Individual rows of darkly stained benches blend into a continuous sea of mahogany, the wedge-shaped seating area bisected by the sharp lines of these pale steps.  A thick metallic pillar stands further up the stairs, buried deep into the foundation as if it had been present far before the stone that currently surrounds it.</description>
    <position x="380" y="280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, The Pillar" note="cambrinth sphere">
    <description>From deep within these granite steps a great pillar rises proudly -- its surface skillfully etched with the unicorn of Hodierna and the great wolf of Meraud, its strength unassailable and without equal.  A halved sphere of an opalescent mineral caps the pillar, its milky interior swirling with a lazy power.  Spacious seating areas are perched on either side of this great marker, resting in silent vigil high about the sacred altar.</description>
    <position x="400" y="300" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Ve Aevan Gaenan, Southeast Stairway">
    <description>From this landing poised just beneath the Iris Rim, a sweeping granite stairway ascends to the circular ledge above, providing access to the six arches that line the equator of this spherical space, and drawing one toward the watchful Eyes of the Thirteen.  The stairs continue downward in a gentle curve toward the metallic altar, their progress as fluid and graceful as water streaming down a rough face of rock.</description>
    <position x="420" y="320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Temple Grounds, Grand Stairway">
    <description>Below to either side, paths curve around in between the main temple and the east and west towers.  The monoliths stretch upwards and lean slightly toward the temple itself, as if grasping out toward the beacon area atop the structure, above the Eyes of The Thirteen.  Smoothly cut granite steps lead upward to the north, climbing toward the massive temple.</description>
    <position x="340" y="460" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Temple Grounds, Grand Stairway">
    <description>The grand stairway continues its ascent to the north, approaching the looming orb of the temple.  Ornate silverwillow banisters curve down from the entrance, polished to a lustrous sheen and carved to resemble flowing streams, trickling serenely to the bottom of the stairs.</description>
    <position x="340" y="440" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="182" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Grand Stairway, Temple Entrance" note="Temple Entrance">
    <description>The stairs descend to the south providing a spectacular view of the meandering Segoltha river.  The grand orb-like temple yawns open directly to the north, its massive double doors sure to ward off any foolish invaders who may besiege this religious fortress.  Two massive bronze sconces protrude above the entryway, each shaped like an outstretched feline's paw clutching an eternal flame -- surely a blessing from the goddess of civilization who aided in the reconstruction of this monument.</description>
    <position x="340" y="420" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt down" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Wedding Glade, Outdoor Chapel">
    <description>A smooth cobblestone path meanders its way from under a whitewashed latticework archway to the southeast, leading beneath the gentle shade of a gazebo to the north.  Lush green modwyn vines reach up from the ground, coiling about the gazebo's posts to intertwine atop it, creating a picturesque canopy to shield any would-be wedding parties from the elements.  Festive streamers of a myriad of colors weave a sweeping rainbow before the small chapel's entrance.</description>
    <position x="160" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go latticework archway" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb brass ladder" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Outdoor Wedding Chapel, Reception Plaza">
    <description>A thick carpet of pale golden-brown leaves covers the ground of this small plaza, barely allowing one to see the concealed cobbled road beneath.  Festive golden streamers lazily dance about, tied to small wooden posts that hold the pruned hedges at bay.  A large nearly-naked cherry tree rises in the center of the plaza, shedding its crisp golden feathers, having borne its children for the year.</description>
    <description>The fresh, wintry crunch of the crisp white snow beneath each footstep heralds the arrival of the late months.  A large cherry tree stands dormant, barren of leaves and sporting only a few small, frozen buds.  The dulled daylight shines off the snow, casting an ambient glow upon everything in sight.  The hedges appear as snowbanks, buried beneath the frosty white carpet that drapes over all in this small cul-de-sac.</description>
    <position x="140" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Beneath the Wedding Glade, Sundering Chapel" note="Shrine1-05|Sundering Chapel" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Fresh dirt walls have been packed in crudely, a thin tunnel in the ceiling leading up to the wedding chapel above.  The faint laughter of a joyous party is heard in the distance, muffled and given an eerie quality tinged with sorrow in this small hovel within the earth.  A crude obsidian slab has been smoothed into a makeshift altar, littered with shattered crystal shards -- the remnants of former scission blades, and the only physical trace of the sundered wedding vows made by countless people before.</description>
    <position x="160" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb brass ladder" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Temple, North Tower" note="Map2d_Crossing_Escape_Tunnels.xml|Escape Tunnels|Tunnels">
    <description>Diffuse golden light falls from somewhere above, its honeyed beams drifting down the length of the tower.  Matched flagstones of deep grey slate create a broad landing that punctuates the staircase as it continues its gradual climb.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Reception Hall, Stage">
    <description>Smooth walnut boards underfoot and rich blue velvet curtains along the walls make this an elegant nook where minstrels and performers can share their music with those in the ballroom.  Wooden chairs sit in neat rows facing the north, each with a silver stand set in front shaped like a lyre.  A cleared space made in front of them is framed by multicolored silk streamers that flutter onto the stage.</description>
    <position x="160" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go velvet curtain" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Eye of Urrem'tier, Warding Chamber">
    <description>Concave walls of pitch black obsidian carve out a small spherical chamber.  Etched into the walls are strange sigils and warding runes that glimmer every so often with a white radiance.  The chamber is bare save for a simple black ironwood stand in the center and an ebony rack on one wall.</description>
    <position x="240" y="190" z="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small hatch" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <label text="Resurrection Creche - Level 0">
    <position x="280" y="250" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to Hallway (1) --">
    <position x="120" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to Hallway (1)">
    <position x="440" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to Resurrection Creche (0) --">
    <position x="20" y="150" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to Eyes of the Thirteen (3) --">
    <position x="30" y="310" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to Eyes of the Thirteen (3)">
    <position x="480" y="310" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Eyes of the Thirteen - Level 3">
    <position x="254" y="-8" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Iris Rim - Level 2">
    <position x="289" y="2" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to Hallway (1)">
    <position x="460" y="100" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to Monks' Quarters (4) --">
    <position x="40" y="340" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to Monks' Quarters (4)">
    <position x="490" y="340" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to eyes of the thirteen (3) --">
    <position x="-2" y="192" z="4" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to Eyes">
    <position x="505" y="192" z="4" />
  </label>
  <label text="MONK'S QUARTERS - Level 4">
    <position x="262" y="-2" z="4" />
  </label>
  <label text="SANCTUARY GARDENS - Level 6">
    <position x="254" y="-2" z="6" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to sanctuary gardens (6)">
    <position x="459" y="195" z="5" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to monk's quarters (4)">
    <position x="352" y="111" z="5" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stairway">
    <position x="100" y="300" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text=" to Ve Aevan Gaenan (1) --">
    <position x="60" y="310" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stairway">
    <position x="530" y="300" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- to Ve Aevan Gaenan (1)">
    <position x="490" y="310" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stairway">
    <position x="335" y="44" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="v  to Ve Aevan Gaenan (1)">
    <position x="335" y="56" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to Hallway (1) --">
    <position x="100" y="100" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="HIGH PRIESTESS' QUARTERS - Level 5">
    <position x="233" y="-2" z="5" />
  </label>
  <label text="go stair to high prestess' quarters (5) --">
    <position x="86" y="235" z="6" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hallway - Level 1">
    <position x="279" y="-5" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="-- go stair to Resurrection Creche (0)">
    <position x="480" y="150" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="To The Crossing">
    <position x="298" y="591" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="favor altar">
    <position x="320" y="360" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wedding Chapel">
    <position x="140" y="340" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="orb">
    <position x="260" y="280" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Grand Stairway">
    <position x="300" y="470" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="sphere">
    <position x="400" y="280" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="orb">
    <position x="320" y="150" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Foresight">
    <position x="320" y="120" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="Healing">
    <position x="220" y="180" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="Thought">
    <position x="220" y="280" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="Warrior's Shrine">
    <position x="300" y="340" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="Outwardness">
    <position x="410" y="280" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="Destruction">
    <position x="410" y="180" z="2" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hodierna">
    <position x="320" y="100" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Kertigen">
    <position x="270" y="110" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Meraud">
    <position x="380" y="110" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Urrem'tier">
    <position x="220" y="170" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Chadatru">
    <position x="210" y="220" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Faenella">
    <position x="210" y="270" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tamsine">
    <position x="250" y="340" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Glythtide">
    <position x="290" y="360" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Eluned">
    <position x="350" y="360" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hav'roth">
    <position x="390" y="340" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Truffenyi">
    <position x="420" y="270" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Everild">
    <position x="440" y="220" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Damaris">
    <position x="420" y="170" z="3" />
  </label>
  <label text="Southeast Tower">
    <position x="530" y="470" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Southwest Tower">
    <position x="40" y="470" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="North Tower">
    <position x="310" y="-10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cemetery">
    <position x="320" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bathing Pool">
    <position x="40" y="380" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Entry Gates">
    <position x="320" y="560" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Triage Hall">
    <position x="450" y="230" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="triage">
    <position x="230" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hearth Chamber">
    <position x="160" y="230" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dispensary">
    <position x="390" y="340" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text=" of the Thirteen (3)">
    <position x="510" y="210" z="4" />
  </label>
</zone>