<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Throne City Thief" id="35a">
  <node id="1" name="Drainage Channel" color="Blue">
    <description>Bits of broken cobblestones and pieces of shattered statues redirect the route of a stream of rather dirty water, sending it spiraling in little eddies against the curving sides of the channel.  On the other side of the debris pile, the water resumes its steady course, gaining speed until it hurtles through an opening and into the outside world.</description>
    <position x="420" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go a gap" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Drainage Channel" color="Blue">
    <description>A dark mildew stain covers the lower half of the wall, indicating precisely where the levels of runoff water rise when forced through this passage by rains or floods.  Only a small river of murky liquid gurgles through currently, sloshing against the stones and joyously creating echoes in the otherwise drab and dreary channel.</description>
    <position x="380" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Drainage Channel" color="Blue">
    <description>Six large pipes protrude from beneath a massive stone dais, each spilling their own gallons of water into the collection basin on the floor.  Somewhere behind, overflow from the Faldesu river must regularly fill ditches and channels, only to have its waters diverted here and away from the streets where a flood would be disastrous.</description>
    <position x="360" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze pipe" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Underground, Beneath a Barricade">
    <description>Though numerous cobblestones are worked into the ceiling, implying that a road is above, it is obvious by the concave sagging of the rocks and dirt that something much more massive presses down.  As further evidence, rows of ironwood supports jut out of the ceiling.  Some of these beams have been wrenched free and now prop up the very mass they once belonged.</description>
    <position x="0" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go of stone" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Underground, Beneath Jares Row">
    <description>More a hollow beneath the roadway than any sort of real passage or drainage channel, this tunnel shows indication of sentient purpose.  Broken masonry and other debris that have slipped down from the overhead streets lay cluttered all about, but a simple, narrow path through the mess remains.  A number of thick roughly hewn timbers shore up the ceiling in an attempt to keep more rubble from collapsing.</description>
    <position x="20" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large crack" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Seven Star Exchange and Pawn, Storage Room">
    <description>Long rows of shelves, oddly empty for the backroom of a pawnshop, cover three of the four marble walls.  Only a handful of small boxes and barrels are kept here, though the upper shelves are filled with dust and cobwebs.  Interestingly, none of the lower and more accessible rows show signs of similar disuse.  The wall devoid of shelving has a door-sized panel with obvious hinges.</description>
    <position x="40" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine crate" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="none" move="push switch;#event 2 go panel" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Imperial Palace, Dungeon" note="Map35_Throne_City.xml|dungeon">
    <description>An odd assortment of implements and clumsy devices clutter this shadowed edge of the Imperial dungeon.  The forefront of the army of devices is led by the easily recognizable guillotine and rack.  Many of the other mammoths, ranging from mechanical to magical, appear rusted over but still functional.  A glance up a blockaded staircase reveals its destination as the famed Death Hall that contains solitary confinement cells used for the Empire's political prisoners.</description>
    <position x="330" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze pipe" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy" note="Map35_Throne_City.xml|dahl">
    <description>The echo of sloshing water rises from beneath a flat stone fitted into the cobblestones.  Pierced by small, almost delicate vents, this grate stretches completely across the street and is most likely part of a drainage system of some kind.  Richly decorated troughs of flowering plants and an elevated aqueduct run perpendicular to the stone, abutting the front of a magnificent tiled structure.</description>
    <position x="440" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" />
    <arc exit="south" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Old Throne City, Entertainment District" note="Map35_Throne_City.xml|district">
    <description>A massive wall looms to the north, high and reinforced, though not nearly as tall as the colosseum to the east.  Large, dangerous-looking spears jut upward from the ramparts of the city's barricade as it nears the old sporting complex, and a similar set of sharp implements aims back from the complex as if the two structures were cautiously keeping each other at bay.  Though some strands of ivy manage to curl around the stonework, this dead end is desolate and unused.</description>
    <position x="0" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Seven Star Exchange and Pawn" note="Map35_Throne_City.xml|pawn">
    <description>The walls are white marble, though this is difficult to tell since there is such an abundance of what most people would term junk.  Most of the items have a nautical theme, if one could give randomness such a unifying concept, but it is just as likely it was all simply salvaged from a ship wreck.  Buried among the rubble of the assorted goods is a large iron safe.</description>
    <position x="60" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Old Throne City, Vagabond's Row">
    <description>Rubbish and blankets are strewn across the alleyway, possibly left by littering hands or blown by the wind.  A tarp-covered statue stands near the street.  Between this marble monstrosity and the empty crates stacked nearby, it is unlikely that passers-by would notice this area at all.  Serving as one side of this man-made canyon is the wall of the nearby museum, a makeshift wooden scaffolding ascending its surface.</description>
    <position x="320" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden scaffolding" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Museum of Imperial History, Rooftop">
    <description>By day, the view would certainly be a commanding one, but now consists only of the distant twinkling lights of passing boats on the Faldesu.  Much closer, a makeshift wooden scaffolding peaks at the edge of the wall, very nearly matching the height of the museum itself.</description>
    <description> The view is a commanding one.  From here even hazy glimpses of the Lesser and Greater Fists are visible to the far west while the blue horizon of the east indicates the presence of the Reshal Sea.  Much closer, a makeshift wooden scaffolding peaks at the edge of the wall, very nearly matching the height of the museum itself.</description>
    <position x="280" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden scaffolding" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Museum of Imperial History, Northern Rooftop">
    <description>Though the ornamentation on the roof's edge effectively forms a parapet, the street below can be surveyed easily by quick glances between the stone alfars and soldiers.  Anyone on Dahl Aeliy would be hard pressed to spot a lurker hiding on this building, and such a task would be even harder for those living in the luxurious residential areas further north.  From the rooftops, leisurely study of Throne City's layout can be taken for granted.</description>
    <position x="295" y="125" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Museum of Imperial History, Rooftop">
    <description>Shady figures move along other rooftops, their faces hidden by deep cloaks of various sullen hues.  Luckily for anyone at this vantage point, the forms take no notice of other rooftops as their attentions are aimed downward and south.  They blink in and out of view, appearing on other buildings, moving in utter silence like ghosts, their goals equally ethereal.</description>
    <position x="295" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Museum of Imperial History, Southern Rooftop">
    <description>The mingling, contrary scents of roses and horses arise from below, drifting from private gardens nestled behind the Palace as well as the nearby palatial stalls.  Though ivy and flowering vines cover the stone, the walls of the Palace are notably unrestored, bearing centuries of chips and marks.  Those who did the restoration certainly never intended to impress anyone who might be on the rooftop of the museum.</description>
    <position x="295" y="155" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy" note="Map35_Throne_City.xml|Dahl Aeliy|Throne City">
    <description>As the road straightens, spaces between the buildings reveal a rich residential area a mere stone's throw to the north.  Even such small glimpses extoll the exotic parks and shrubbery surrounding those homes, but a slight scent of horses carried on occasional breezes indicates the closeness of the Palatial horse stalls.  Along the southern side of the street, stately shops and elaborate structures of aristocratic content only partly block the view of the Palace's domed roof.</description>
    <position x="320" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" />
    <arc exit="west" />
  </node>
</zone>