<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Throne City" id="35">
  <node id="1" name="Colosseum Ruins, Upper Tier" note="Fade" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Wide openings in the walls of the colosseum were once passages and solid stone, through which spectators hurried to now vanished seating areas.  Now, these shattered windows reveal the grandest urban schemes and designs of the Seven Races lie in ruins to the south, having crumbled and fallen to the ravages of time.  Northward, the structures are by far more dignified and repaired.</description>
    <position x="20" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Colosseum Ruins, Upper Tier">
    <description>Planks of wood make a serpentine pattern on the floor, snaking around the many holes that were formed as portions of the lower tier collapsed.  In the places where the footing looks most stable, rows of scaly husks are piled, though many of the larger ones are instead nailed onto the walls.  Between the holes, planks and husks, splatters of red and black paint freckle the stone.</description>
    <position x="40" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Colosseum Ruins, Upper Tier">
    <description>Signs of residents abound, from the empty trunk and chests stacked in a disorganized heap to the pitted canvas stretched overhead.  Most obvious of some group's claim to these previously abandoned ruins is the large sign hanging from rusted chains.  These squatters are not a cleanly group, as a layer of grey filth from dirty boots tracks from the makeshift ladder toward the northwest.</description>
    <position x="60" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb makeshift ladder" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Colosseum Ruins, Northern Tier">
    <description>This was never the best seating in the colosseum, since massive structural supports made of stone obstruct large swathes of the combat theater from view.  Well removed from the better seats, this was probably considered by the rich to be an excellent place for the hordes of ragged commoners and the less-than-aristocratic to gather and chant for their heroes -- at least what they could see of them.</description>
    <position x="60" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb makeshift ladder" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Colosseum Ruins, Northern Tier">
    <description>The brick and mortar barricades that partition the various seating areas have collapsed, allowing access directly to the shattered top of the arena wall.  Hung overhead are a multitude of tattered tapestries, obviously recent additions as there is no way something so fragile as cloth would have survived centuries of exposure and abandonment.</description>
    <position x="40" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb arena wall" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Colosseum Ruins, Northern Tier">
    <description>Piles of fragmented stone and block from the partial collapse of the upper tiers show signs of having been purposely cleared, as if to make movement along the northern tier more convenient.  Through the splits created as the rubble fell from above, the outside streets are visible and choked with bits of the foundations of shops and stalls.  A lone tangled vine snakes its way through one of these triangular holes, twitching in the breeze like an anxious spectator awaiting entry.</description>
    <position x="20" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tangled vine" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Colosseum Ruins, Northern Tier">
    <description>The ravages of time and aimless vandalism have combined forces to weaken the faulty walls, leaving the above areas all the more weakened.  Red bricks and grey rubble lie scattered among piles of dust, all trailing down a now partially blocked stairway.  What memories this place could share of spectators cheerfully filling the seating areas in anticipation of a gladiatorial bloodshed, if only stone could speak.</description>
    <position x="0" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb blocked stairway" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Colosseum Ruins, Combat Theater">
    <description>Once the center point of the combat yard, this part of the arena is now the northernmost section due to the collapse of the seating areas above.  Protecting the spectators from the wind, rain and sun, poles supporting heavy canvas and leather now lean and hang in dreary, tattered condition.  The grand view of the sky is still available, ringed on all sides by the stone of the colosseum.</description>
    <position x="40" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb arena wall" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Colosseum Ruins, Combat Theater">
    <description>Boulders of broken stonework lay strewn about on the ground, fallen from the massive arch that once loomed high above.  Long granite pillars lay across one another like exhausted combatants, too tired to maintain the struggle against the pull of gravity, and the slowly decaying stone floor.  A decaying stairway, partially blocked by crumbling stone, offers a perilous climb to the arena wall above.</description>
    <position x="20" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb blocked stairway" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Colosseum Ruins, Combat Theater">
    <description>Once covered by a thin layer of sand on rock, the floor of the combat theater is now little more than a massive pit with sparse areas of green grass growing in and around sink-holes and deep depressions left in the ground.  Nothing remains of the large granite columns that arose from the arena floor, their crumbling stonework now vanished into the gloomy darkness below.</description>
    <position x="40" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone wall" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Old Throne City, Entertainment District">
    <description>The shimmering veil of illusion which hides Throne City from the rest of the world allows those within to see out, but from here only the encroaching woods of Therengia can be seen.  Those forests overflowing the city's walls prove that nature is a patient planner, desiring to engulf man's fragile works completely.  Even the colosseum is not completely spared from the lush greenery as a lone tangled vine trails up its surface.</description>
    <position x="0" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tangled vine" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Colosseum Ruins, Lower Tier">
    <description>The remains of heavy iron bars divide this large open area into small holding cells, where warriors once waited for their time to fight.  Despite the scent of dust and rock that pervades the area, a lingering aroma of blood and sweat can still be caught on the passing breezes as they wind in and around the stonework arches and broken walls.  Partially blocking access to the combat theater stands a crumbling stone wall, the jagged edges making for difficult passage to the arena above.</description>
    <position x="60" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Colosseum Ruins, Lower Tier">
    <description>Crumbling stonework and shredded tapestries are all that remain of the grand architecture that once honored those who fought and died for the enjoyment of the crowd, and the honor of battle.  Lost in the decay and destruction are the grandly carved engravings and flowing banners, now little more than fragments of memories from times long past.  Beyond an immense cracked archway lies a city in ruins, victim of the ravages and constant abuse of the elements.</description>
    <position x="40" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Colosseum Ruins, Lower Tier">
    <description>Ruddy brown stonework columns climb their way to the distant curving arches high overhead sheltering the large chunks of stone and marble that now litter the floor.  A testament to the ravages of time, iron sconces that once held brightly lit torches now hang in rusted pieces of twisted metal and tattered fragments of detailed tapestries dangle by mere threads along the cracking and broken walls.</description>
    <position x="20" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go decaying arch" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Old Throne City, Entertainment District">
    <description>The giant stone arch to the colosseum looms overhead like a god, concealing shadows within its massive maw.  High above are the second tier arches, which are mostly intact, and the fragmented remains of a third and fourth tier.  Curving toward the nearest wall of the colosseum is a makeshift barricade, assembled obviously to create a single line of defense against some threat.</description>
    <position x="40" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone arch" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb makeshift barricade" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Old Throne City, Entertainment District">
    <description>Poles stretch over the remnants of the cobbled roadway, a small reminder of the canvas awnings and street vendors that once served throngs of anxious spectators.  A wide stone arch leads inside the colosseum proper, flanked on one side by a crumbling gladiator statue from days past.  Even now, he continues to salute the sky with weapon in hand, a memorial not only to those who died within but to the memory of Throne City's grander times.</description>
    <position x="20" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone arch" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Old Throne City, Entertainment District">
    <description>A massive wall looms to the north, high and reinforced, though not nearly as tall as the colosseum to the east.  Large, dangerous-looking spears jut upward from the ramparts of the city's barricade as it nears the old sporting complex, and a similar set of sharp implements aims back from the complex as if the two structures were cautiously keeping each other at bay.  Though some strands of ivy manage to curl around the stonework, this dead end is desolate and unused.</description>
    <position x="0" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Old Throne City, Entertainment District">
    <description>Rising high above all the intervening vacancies of building shells, the massive colosseum dominates the skyline of Throne City's ruins.  With years of neglect and seasons of weather slowly destroying the abandoned remains, it still manages to dwarf all nearby structures.  Even the tallest of the decorative pillars that still linger along the streetsides are buried in the shadow of the mammoth.</description>
    <position x="100" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb makeshift barricade" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Old Throne City, Garden District">
    <description>A row of seven columns have abandoned only three of their number to the efforts of time, though the ones sacrificed have been wholly destroyed and now remain only as powder and fragments on the street.  The wind occasionally picks up, swirling the dust and shrilly whistling through the overturned pottery and debris.  Footprints track through the ruin, destination and source unclear due to their hectic and seemingly random placement.</description>
    <position x="100" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble stairs" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Old Throne City, Garden District">
    <description>Several statues have fallen down the stairs and now lay in a large heap, most of them rolled against the wall of the nearest tier.  Oddly, there is less randomness to their placement than the surrounding ruins, as if these had been moved out of the way under direction of some sentient power.  For what purpose they were moved remains unknown.</description>
    <position x="140" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble stairs" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Old Throne City, Garden District">
    <description>The lower tiers of the Garden District are cluttered with shops and small residences which have slid partially down towards the streets below.  It is possible that this area of the ruins will be among the last to be restored, as the work would be far greater than in other sections.  As testament to the extremes of time, a small fountain is shattered, the statue in its middle broken completely in half.</description>
    <position x="160" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Old Throne City, Magic District" note="WM Quest Tower" color="#FF8000">
    <description>A lone tower stretches skyward, its blackened husk charred by an inferno.  Perhaps started by a careless mage fleeing Throne City or by some act of vengeful arson, nature is doing its best to reclaim the burnt structure by wrapping thin green tendrils around its form.  All around, the other buildings have been hollowed by their own catastrophies, though these have not been so unfortunate as to be ravaged by an ancient conflagration.</description>
    <position x="120" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Old Throne City, Southern Gate District">
    <description>Normally, passage to the southwest would have been possible through the wide ruined streets, but a series of tall columns and statues have collapsed, making the route impassable.  The debris has fallen on top of several small buildings to completely engulfs the area.  This must have occurred years ago, since a wide variety of grasses and weeds root on top of the piles in whatever sparse clumps of dirt the vegetation can find.</description>
    <position x="140" y="580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Old Throne City, Magic District">
    <description>Even in ruination, the buildings are distinctly more utilitarian here than to the north, blending into the militant Southern Gate District.  Likely, this was once where Warrior Mages gathered to swap tales and scrolls, a choice spot to indulge in both arcane magics and combat prowess.  Precisely which building such gatherings occurred is a mystery, as all have had untold centuries of damage dealt by the passage of time.</description>
    <position x="100" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Old Throne City, Southern Gate District">
    <description>Arching slightly upward before suddenly dropping off, the remains of a ruined bridge head toward the south.  The supports have collapsed outward from beneath this behemoth structure, sending what was once an elevated and ornate walkway crashing into the forest to be consumed by seasonal growth.  An iconic pedestal stands near the spot where the travelers of years gone by would have begun their journeys to places now blocked by rubble.</description>
    <position x="100" y="580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Old Throne City, Southern Gate District">
    <description>A massive wall of debris cuts the road in half, blocking any further progress.  Something uses this dead end as a makeshift lair, evidenced by the wide selection of bones and deep burrows beneath the mound.  Many of the remains appear to be of the Seven Races, stripped of all flesh in much the same way as the surrounding buildings have been stripped of decorum and color.</description>
    <position x="120" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Old Throne City, Magic District">
    <description>The walls of the old city are nearby, though some sort of oddly shimmering, transparent field of subtle colors blurs the woods beyond.  Like viewing river stones beneath clear water, the world outside of Throne City shudders and ripples.  Yet within, there is no water, only the dusty remains of libraries and magical repositories, student dorms and wizards' towers.</description>
    <position x="80" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Old Throne City, Magic District">
    <description>Towering over the ruins is the colosseum to the north, impressively bulky and mostly standing while all the tallest remains of wizard towers are mere slivers pointed skyward.  Several small trenches run parallel with the abandoned roadway, some cordoned off with small posts and yellow-dyed string.  A few rusted and useless tools remain, abandoned next to the excavation site.</description>
    <position x="80" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Old Throne City, Baralibas Bridge">
    <description>Ancient flower holders and the remains of gardens and ponds abound still on the roofs and terraces of the ruined buildings.  Below, a long roadway stretches southward, split into sections by the untamed growth of weeds and the shattered remains of fallen columns.  Once upon a time, this would have been the best vantage point to watch parades and processions heading to the Imperial Palace.</description>
    <position x="180" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Old Throne City, Baralibas Bridge">
    <description>The bridge rises in the middle, a convex curve formed by the sagging outer edges as the years take their toll on the aging stonework.  This elevated spot enhances the view all around, which would be magnificent if not for the terrible state of the surrounding buildings.  Northward, the contrast in ruin and repair is clearly divided by a reinforced boundary, by the backs of shops and residences with barred or sealed windows, and by the appearance of mysterious figures along the balconies and rooftops.</description>
    <position x="320" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Old Throne City, Garden District">
    <description>Man-made steppes where lush gardens long ago bloomed are now nothing more than crumbling masonry and untamed weeds.  The staggering of these large open blocks implies that the entire roadway was sheltered by greenery and the current open view to the south was once not so clear.  If not for the darkness of night, visibility would easily extend for miles.</description>
    <description>Man-made steppes where lush gardens long ago bloomed are now nothing more than crumbling masonry and untamed weeds.  The staggering of these large open blocks implies that the entire roadway was sheltered by greenery and the current open view to the south was once not so clear.  Distantly to the west and slightly south, a tiny plume is the only thing visible of the Greater Fist, at least a hundred miles away.</description>
    <position x="400" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Old Throne City, Merchant District">
    <description>Merchant stalls separated by short granite walls line both sides of the rough cobblestone street.  Broken pottery and the occasional forgotten copper still litter the confines of the open-air shops, and tattered scraps of canvas suspended by rusting metal poles sway quietly in the errant breeze.</description>
    <position x="400" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow alley" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Only some renovation has taken place along this narrow stretch of street, seen by the missing cobblestones as well as the general decrease in the amount of ornamentation.  Few vendors market their wares here in this man-made canyon of partially white-washed buildings and half-restored statues, most likely due to the lack of regular foot traffic rather than any missing pretty sculptures.  Atop a brown brick shop, a figure occasionally appears, surveys the area, then vanishes again.</description>
    <position x="400" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow alley" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick shop" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Old Throne City, Merchant District">
    <description>Standing as solidly as the day it was erected, the front wall of a large storehouse is all that remains of the once great structure.  Deep ruts left behind by the constant passage of delivery wagons have been worn into the decrepit stonework of the road, a lingering reminder of the flourishing industry that once thrived along these now dark and silent avenues.</description>
    <position x="440" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Old Throne City, Merchant District">
    <description>A column of deep blue lapis rises from the center of the road, supporting the weight of a rough-hewn marble sign suspended by rusting iron chains.  Around the pedestal, broken pieces of a glazed clay cistern lay shattered beneath a heavily dented brazier, the chains that once held the bronze bowl aloft snapped from the subtle touch of the elements and the passage of time.</description>
    <position x="460" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Old Throne City, Merchant District">
    <description>Laid out like a giant piece of checkercloth, alternating tiles of dark and lightly colored marble fill the breadth of the arched walkway, the once polished surface lost beneath layers of dust and crumbling rock.  Ascending from the center of the covered path, a fountain carved from deep blue lapis sits quiet and empty, save for the heavy layers of dried leaves deposited by the passing winds that blow freely through the deserted expanse of forested granite and crafted stonework.</description>
    <position x="480" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Old Throne City, Merchant District">
    <description>Decaying granite columns march down each side of the dusty marble walkway, capped by tottering lancet arches that threaten to collapse at the mere exhalation of nature's breath.  Sprigs of hardy grass and bracken push their way up through gaps between the dark stone blocks, the vigorous patterns of scattered greenery seeking to eclipse the dense shadowed ruination that thrives around the decaying footpath.</description>
    <position x="480" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Old Throne City, Church District">
    <description>Clouds of dust and dried leaves blow freely across the cobblestone streets, the rustling whisper of their sporadic dance filling the otherwise deathly quiet.  Lining empty walkways like stoic guardians, marble pillars support the chipped sculptures that served as reminders of the gods' ever-watchful eyes upon the once bustling thoroughfare.  The crumbling walls of a majestic church rise high above the soil, laid waste by the passage of time and the silence of the faithful who no longer dwell here.</description>
    <position x="480" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ruined church" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Old Throne City, Church District">
    <description>Cold grey cobblestones and short marble pillars are all that remain of the once proud structures that inhabited this part of the city.  Swirling clouds of dust rise up from the empty road, snatching up bits of debris and refuse littering the ground and depositing them in tiny piles scattered around the area.  To the north, the ruins of a once magnificent cathedral dominate the silent skyline of the city, the high bell tower rising above the crumbling granite walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Hodierna's Cathedral Ruins, Basilica Foyer">
    <description>Crumbling columns and piles of rubble left by the now shattered marble ceiling are all that remain of the detailed craftsmanship that once paid homage to the goddess of life.  The tall lancet arch leading outside leans precariously, as though even a small breeze could send it crashing to the ground.  To the west, a pale glow rises softly from a raised pedestal, lending an air of peace in contrast to the ruins that fill the area.</description>
    <position x="520" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lancet arch" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Hodierna's Cathedral Ruins, Basilica Foyer">
    <description>Scattered leaves dance lazily across the floor, pushed quietly by an errant breeze blowing in through a breach in the ruined granite wall.  Set on its side, a short marble stand lays cracked and broken beneath the remains of a shattered porcelain font.  The scent of corroding iron wafts down through an opening in the ceiling, the trapdoor wedged open by a rusting metal ladder hanging down from the bell tower above.</description>
    <position x="540" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb metal ladder" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ash-filled brazier" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Hodierna's Cathedral Ruins, Unicorn Pedestal" note="Hodierna|shrine" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Rising above the cold surface of the granite floor, delicately polished pearl-white marble bricks form an altar surrounded by a wide circular pedestal.  In contrast to the dilapidated architecture surrounding it, a sculpted ivory unicorn stands proudly atop the marble platform, defying the passage of time that has so completely set its home in ruins.  A faint peaceful glow fills the air -- a reminder that Hodierna still smiles upon this place, despite the level of solitude the church now inhabits.</description>
    <position x="500" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Hodierna's Cathedral Ruins, Basilica Foyer">
    <description>Piles of broken rock and fragments of polished marble litter the cold granite floor, vestiges of a roof long since given to the testament of time.  Dust-ridden remnants of fine tapestries lie strewn around the room, the once colorful detail now lost under layers of dirt and mold.  A large ash-filled brazier rests between the remains of two massive support columns, the scorched bronze and crumbling supports partially blocking passage to the north.</description>
    <position x="540" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ash-filled brazier" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Hodierna's Cathedral Ruins, Bell Tower">
    <description>Despite the constant breezes blowing through the lancet windows in the tower wall, the sluggish acrid smell of rusting metal hangs heavily in the air surrounding an immense iron bell.  Thick growths of fungus and lichen cling to the pitted granite walls, nurtured by the elements that wander freely within the confines of this once masterful architecture.  A decaying metal ladder hangs down through an opening in the floor, its braces twisted and loose from corrosion.</description>
    <position x="540" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb metal ladder" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Centered in the street is a large fountain with a majestic, lifesized sculpture of a horse drawing a chariot.  Birds and pigeons nest on the equine's back, oblivious to the fact that this area is heavily fortified as if the residents were awaiting an attack at any moment.  The few vendors that peddle their merchandise here do so from push carts and other temporary stalls lined along the spike-topped walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Despite being obviously fortified, the buildings are still beautifully constructed, bearing cream-colored frescos of men wrestling horses, stone waves along the bases, and dancing women along the pilasters.  Even the ends of the alleys are home to marvelously realistic statues, though this is apparently an attempt to disguise the blocks that seal the opposite end of each.  Rising to the road above is a series of wide steps, its low banisters equally adorned with decorum.</description>
    <position x="540" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crooked alleyway" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Old Throne City, Faldesu Overlook">
    <description>Just to the south, the ruins of the old merchant district lie, but here at the boundary between the ancient and the restored, many of the buildings have been reclaimed.  Warehouses and trader stalls have been created by rebuilding ceilings and walls, or in some cases by securing thick canvas between towering columns.  While the division is apparent by the obvious restorations, it is also well-defined by a massive stone wall clearly designed to stop access to the ruins.</description>
    <position x="580" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas-covered stall" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Old Throne City, Faldesu Overlook">
    <description>Stacked doubly high, a forest of pillars rises to the sky, holding up no ceiling nor structure.  Between their stony cylindrical forms, the cobblestones yield to a decorative but sturdy pattern of blue and white tiles.  The passage from untold ages of merchants and horses have left trails of dirt and cracks along the tiles, especially near the marble gate leading to the docks.  Aside from this portal, the buildings here are tightly clustered and fortified.</description>
    <position x="580" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble gate" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>The oversized steps leading up to Dahl Aeliy end here at an equally massive archway, its entrance completely bricked over.  Even the tallest of men or Gor'Tog are dwarfed by the monumental structures the same way a child would be in a sky giant's playground.  All of the buildings here, stained a dull brown from the slow weathering of time, are sealed, and the cobblestones lie beneath a fine layer of dirt.  Both are indications that this place is purposely neglected.</description>
    <position x="320" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Beyond the age-browned stones of partially abandoned shops and half-restored residences rise the great walls of the old colosseum.  The large arches of that structure are broken, drooping like the angled head of a tired multi-eyed beast.  Even from this distance, clinging vines can be seen covering the walls much as they do to the buildings along this street.</description>
    <position x="240" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>In striking contrast to the buildings just south and east, those here are blessed with all the benefits that come with nearly complete restorations.  Flowering greenery drapes down from rooftop gardens, delicate bas relief are etched along elegant marble walls, and even the cobblestones have recently been repaired.  Only a few chips and cracks indicate that this portion of the city was ever in ruin.</description>
    <position x="160" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go circular edifice" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>The massive ruins of the colosseum loom nearby, segregated from this street by an impressively reinforced wall.  All the buildings along the southern side of the street apparently use this strengthened barrier as a backwall, and even the ends of the alleys are blocked by its solid surface.  Whatever lurks in the remains of the colosseum is clearly not wanted here.</description>
    <position x="100" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white pavilion" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ornamental trellis" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Rows of small businesses line the street, some little more than simple wooden stands while others are the more elaborate products of detailed restorations.  Tendrils of ivy grow up the building walls, twisting and coiling around every ledge and windowsill with tenacity.  The street slopes slightly to the south, but the vantage from here offers a hazy view of the ruined majority of Throne City.</description>
    <position x="100" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble house" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Flanked by small, elegantly trimmed shrubs, a rotund limestone dome rises skyward, its importance clear by its immaculate restoration job.  Near the dome's top, a massive and dark telescope peeks out, aimed at the broad sky.  Across the street from the building, a small alleyway slants up to the next highest street, Dahl Aeliy.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small alleyway" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go limestone dome" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>The tendrils of garden plants hang from nearly all the rooftops, dangling and curling along supports and pillars in cascades of flowering green.  A mixture of apartments, libraries, residences, and research facilities line the street, each framed in similar stonework and remarkable statuary.  One particularly large statue of an Elven warrior, mostly unrestored, stands in the center of a wide granite fountain.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vaulted hall" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite building" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>The palace does not seem quite so dominating from this section of street, perhaps due to the pleasant columned atrium that breaks up its foreboding westernmost walls.  Merchants have packed the area beneath the atrium with item-heavy tables and simple stalls.  While this would have been highly illegal at best during the height of the Empire, this is apparently overlooked by the local authorities now.</description>
    <position x="200" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey stall" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brown tent" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>A great colonnade branches off from the street and tucks in toward the palace, its columns covered in waving flowery plants.  Behind the iron gates of the colonnade, the sound of horses echoes strangely against the granite walls.  Wide rose beds on either side are an obvious effort to mask the strong scent of the animals.</description>
    <position x="200" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>Not far to the west rises Ponthilas IV Observatory, the tip of the Emperor's Eye telescope within stretching majestically to the sky.  Large parks abound on all corners, each filled with sweet flowering plants and carefully trimmed hedges.  These delicate smells fail to disguise a distinctive but faint scent of nearby horses.</description>
    <position x="260" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small alleyway" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>As the road straightens, spaces between the buildings reveal a rich residential area a mere stone's throw to the north.  Even such small glimpses extoll the exotic parks and shrubbery surrounding those homes, but a slight scent of horses carried on occasional breezes indicates the closeness of the Palatial horse stalls.  Along the southern side of the street, stately shops and elaborate structures of aristocratic content only partly block the view of the Palace's domed roof.</description>
    <position x="320" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide steps" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alley" hidden="True" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>Dingy water stains left by rain spot the framework box formed from the ornately topped columns of the bank.  A curving flat of deep crimson marble arches over the doorway, spared the obvious signs of water marks due to its dark color.  Like all the buildings in Throne City, the bank is massive, but even it is dwarfed by the taller dome of the Palace library beyond.</description>
    <position x="380" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wagon" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble shop" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bank" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>The echo of sloshing water rises from beneath a flat stone fitted into the cobblestones.  Pierced by small, almost delicate vents, this grate stretches completely across the street and is most likely part of a drainage system of some kind.  Richly decorated troughs of flowering plants and an elevated aqueduct run perpendicular to the stone, abutting the front of a magnificent tiled structure.</description>
    <position x="440" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiled structure" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>A slight tilt is noticable in the road as it bends around the domed library wing of the Imperial Palace, angling toward the wide steps leading down to Mir'Aevar Jegu.  As is the case with other roads in Throne City, the descent is flanked by oversized statues and carvings of grandiose images.  This elevated position gives a grand view over the roofs of the homes and buildings along that other street, and reveals the partially reclaimed ruins of the old merchant district.</description>
    <position x="440" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched building" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>Columns line the outer edges of the street, spaced far enough apart so as not to hinder the inhabitants of the homes and businesses located here.  Ivy clings to some of the pillars and buildings, adding a touch of rich green to the otherwise unimaginative blend of white, ivory and cream stone.  Most of the structures are kept clean, but one in particular -- a columned granite building -- is immaculate.</description>
    <position x="380" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite building" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>The massive facade of the Imperial Palace dominates the street, overshadowing all the nearby buildings, structures and columns with its towering yet elegant bulk.  Wide, long steps stretch between two immense stone dragons, leading up to the Palace's foyer.  Each of the dragons is a mirror twin of the other, and both have their snake-like heads turned to observe those trekking up the steps, ever frozen in watchful guard.</description>
    <position x="320" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Old Throne City, Dahl Aeliy">
    <description>The rooftop gardens of western Mir'Aevar Jegu can be seen through the alleys, the greenery spilling over the sides of the white marble dwellings like waterfalls.  Beyond, the ruins and crumbling towers of the magic district lie, neglected and nearly buried in their own cascades of rubble.  A grey mist clouds details from this distance, much as the bulk of the nearby palace obscures the buildings in its shadow.</description>
    <position x="260" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Between two buildings, an artificial stream flows, spilling from a stone channel on the road above and down a rocky slope.  The gurgling water churns along a small but serpentine course, splattering the blue marble of one of the buildings with dirty drops as it rushes beneath the bridge that splits the street.  A few trees cling to the shores, growing untamed but lending a tranquil, natural shade as they bend over the roadway.</description>
    <position x="540" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go framed door" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble building" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Old Throne City, Mir'Aevar Jegu">
    <description>Thin dogwood trees cluster between expensively restored homes and speciality stores, their upper branches filling the spaces with a canopy of flowering greenery.  Many of the structures also have rooftop gardens, and overflowing vines and plants dangle over marble edges to gaze at passerby on the street below.  Further north, even wealthier homes peek out from behind parks and buildings.</description>
    <position x="500" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go four-story residence" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Sanyrsen Hall, Goldcap Application Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Designed for purpose and function over aesthetics, the furniture in this office is arranged with calculated precision.  A large set of shelves fills one wall while an immense map of the known world covers another.  Despite the utilitarian placement of the larger fixtures, tattered papers and thick tomes are scattered over every available flat surface.  Muffled sounds of people shuffling about come from behind an oaken door set into a granite archway.</description>
    <position x="560" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Old Throne City, Palatial Grand Steps">
    <description>Halfway up the mighty grey steps, a view to the street below is unobstructed except by the bodies of the stone dragons flanking either side.  Over these rocky behemoths, the city's buildings are clearly visible, resembling an architect's vignette in miniature.  Only from here does the impressive scale of Throne City come into its own, and all of it hidden for so long by the surrounding forests of southern Therengia, even now seen in the far distance to the south and southwest.</description>
    <position x="320" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Imperial Palace, Palatial Grand Entrance">
    <description>The dull waterstains that streak the smooth ivory marble of the main palace discolor the backgrounds of the frescos and bas-relief, but serve only to enhance the incredible beauty and detail.  Far above, the ceiling is decorated with seven-pointed stars repeated in an array of stone squares, but lower down upon the wall is the chiseled mantra Together, we shall create triumphs of the magical arts.</description>
    <position x="320" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze doors" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Imperial Palace, Columned Atrium">
    <description>An errant whispering breeze whisks along the tops of the pilasters, failing to entirely mask the echoes of daily life upon the street below.  The dark squares of silver-veined marble and the yellowed fluted columns have witnessed the passing of untold centuries, outliving ancient emperors and generals, and now bearing a sort of refuge from the gods and politicians of the past.  Such is the scale of time and this structure that man is an insignificant presence.</description>
    <position x="310" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Imperial Palace, Columned Atrium">
    <description>For lack of better terms, a highly detailed statue of Jares Braun is tucked away in this side of the foyer.  Nothing could seem cozy about the giant columns since even the natural flaws in the marble easily dwarf most men, and the spaces between are wide enough to drive carriages.  Still, there is a strange sense of unexposure, despite the marvelous view afforded of the street and from the street to here.</description>
    <position x="330" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Imperial Palace, Grand Foyer">
    <description>Massive bronze doors guard the entryway into the foyer, the faint flickering candlelight adorning each of the huge stone columns reflecting softly in the polished bronze surface.  Veins of twinkling gold-streaked lapis frame the granite ceiling resting atop the columns, lending purchase to every echo that abounds within the spacious vestibule.</description>
    <position x="320" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze doors" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Imperial Palace, Grand Foyer">
    <description>A richly stained oak bench covered in blue plush cushions hugs the gold-flecked lapis stonework of the wall.  Threatened with being extinguished in a steady yet gentle draft, flickering flames dance atop candles adorning the stone columns that support the ceiling.  Above the bench, a tiny niche rests partially hidden in the dim light, a finely carved statuette standing quietly within its confines.</description>
    <position x="310" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Imperial Palace, Grand Foyer">
    <description>Deep black-veined marble frames the curve of the archway.  Two identical bronze statues rest on either side of the opening, each with a glowing orb held aloft in its outstretched hands.</description>
    <position x="310" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Imperial Palace, Grand Foyer">
    <description>Casting a rich glow, a large chandelier made of lapis and crystal hangs majestically from the great stone roof, lending its powerful luminance to the beautiful mosaic spanning the breadth of the ceiling.  The huge columns supporting the roof glow softly in the light, the highly polished marble reflecting faintly upon the lavish artwork set into the rich marble floor.</description>
    <position x="320" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Imperial Palace, Grand Foyer">
    <description>Rich lapis surrounds the archway leading from the foyer, its deep golden veins pulsing with the flickering candlelight filling the area.  Gentle grey and black shadows frozen in the thick marble of the floors and walls cast their watchful gaze over all within the ancient halls.</description>
    <position x="330" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lapis archway" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Imperial Palace, Grand Foyer">
    <description>Resting against the deep blue lapis adorning the foyer walls, a sturdy high-backed chair made from dark lustrous ebonwood sits in the shadow of the flickering candlelight that dances against the huge stone pillars and the high granite roof.  Above the chair, a small niche set into the wall displays a slender robed statue cast in gleaming bronze.</description>
    <position x="330" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Imperial Palace, Zohkhalo Hall" note="RS Moon Mage">
    <description>Displayed upon a platform of dark night-blue lapis, a huge marble throne fills the center of the room, its intricate carvings and faintly glowing runes brought to life in the flickering light of the crystalline chandelier that is suspended from the polished granite ceiling.</description>
    <position x="320" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble arch" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Imperial Palace, Western Wing">
    <description>Twin rows of columns run down either side of the lengthy wing, pressed closely against the marble walls and leaving little space for anything behind them but dust.  Between every few columns, suspended from the vaulted ceiling, are great chandeliers of bronze, their gaethzen orbs dark while torches -- no doubt much easier to maintain -- provide illumination.</description>
    <position x="300" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vaulted archway" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Imperial Palace, Council Chambers">
    <description>With arms outstretched to the stylized images of the heavens inset into the ceiling dome, two huge white marble statues flank the vaulted archway.  Shuddering in the gentle draft that comes through the arched opening, a large red tapestry brushes lightly against the nearest statue as if attempting to mask the stone form's presence.  The lapis lazuli of the artistic constellations above sparkle in polished grandeur, indifferent and out of reach of any attentions from tapestries and statues.</description>
    <position x="285" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vaulted archway" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Imperial Palace, Council Chambers">
    <description>A row of polished columns circles the chamber, each holding a ring of elegant sconces and made of an unusual crimson marble.  Between each pair of columns is an alcove, having varying items of interest within them such as dusty paintings or white stone statuettes.  The most outstanding objects appropriated in this way are two large, red tapestries.</description>
    <position x="295" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Imperial Palace, Council Chambers">
    <description>A tremendous oak window overlooks the city streets, though the view is mostly obscured by a large red tapestry that covers the wall.  Wooden trim and crown molding edge between the window and where the domed ceiling meets the wall, disguising what few imperfections might exist in the white stone.  The excellent craftsmanship of ages past is still intact and well-maintained, and only the slightest of wear mars the construction.</description>
    <position x="285" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Imperial Palace, Council Chambers">
    <description>Covering a set of windows are a pair of majestic red velvet tapestries, flowing along the contours of the intricately carved stone walls and lending the area a subtle crimson glow.  Reflecting their light off the gold inlay of the chamber's vaulted ceiling, ornate braziers stand guard against darkness, positioned carefully to enhance the tapestries' color with flickering illumination.</description>
    <position x="275" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze doors" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Imperial Palace, Council Chambers">
    <description>An exotic pattern circles through the gold-trimed panels of the ceiling's high dome, accurately portraying the constellations with inlays of lapis lazuli and precious stones.  Four orbs representing the moons hang from golden bars, their places indicative of their real counterparts' places in the sky.  Positioned almost exactly beneath the center of the faux display is a massive gold-veined marble table, surrounded by thirteen chairs, one more ornate than the others.</description>
    <position x="285" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Old Throne City, Open Air Atrium">
    <description>Grand stone pillars rise skyward, flanking a granite walkway which still bears the scars of ancient wars and the collapse of the Empire.  Atop a pair of massive bronze doors remains a chipped seven-pointed star, inset with lapis lazuli and jade.  While dusty, some work has been done to restore the nearby dome of the council chamber, and flecks of gold still shine brightly even in the dullest of illumination.</description>
    <position x="275" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze doors" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Imperial Palace, Eastern Wing">
    <description>The walls are not only scalloped to better accommodate the massive columns, but also broken by square niches which hold decorative jars and vases.  Running the length of the wall is a wide gold-flecked slat of marble set roughly the height of a tall Halfling, its existence clearly an attempt to break up the untinted monotony of white marble columns on white marble walls.</description>
    <position x="340" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fluted arch" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Imperial Palace, Archives">
    <description>A fluted limestone arch, flowing script deeply carved into its smooth surface, serves as the sole entrance to this circular chamber.  Covering the dark almhara walls are book-lined shelves of polished black walnut reaching to the painted dome ceiling high above.  Oak ladders and a narrow stairway lead to the upper reaches of the walls as well as a large catwalk circling the room.</description>
    <position x="355" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stairway" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fluted arch" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Imperial Palace, Archives">
    <description>A large obsidian tabletop set over walnut legs dominates this corner of the room, its surface carved with an elaborate seal.  The table rests atop fine burgundy carpeting covering much of the smooth almhara floor.  Across from the table sits a small display case, secured by a bronze lock bearing a crest identical to that affixed to the table and filled with several ancient texts which are cradled upon crimson velvet cushions.  On the other side of the room, more shelves loom over the domed chamber.</description>
    <position x="345" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sealed door" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Archive Storage, Main Hall">
    <description>Thick, heavy scents of wood and dust fill the air, a reminder of the densely packed crates and boxes that remain obscured by the darkening shadows and sparse luminescence that inundates the interior of the storage area.  Despite the gloomy darkness, the golden archway framing the door still glows with its own faint inner light, making the exit much easier to see for those who wish to leave quickly.</description>
    <position x="345" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sealed door" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Archive Storage, Main Hall">
    <description>Crates both small and large obscure every inch of the thick granite walls from view, having been stacked all the way to the ceiling in precarious columns of mismatched shapes and sizes.  Barely perceptible in the faint light filtering in from the west, an opening in the rocky floor betrays a darkened stairwell, its winding steps descending into the gloomy darkness below.</description>
    <position x="355" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb darkened stairwell" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Archive Storage, Lower Level">
    <description>Musty wooden shelves layered in thick dust and yellowing tattered scrolls line the walls, each one bowing under the tremendous weight and the toll time has taken on the old oaken supports.  Breaking through the gloomy darkness of the room, a darkened stairwell rises through an opening overhead, providing access to the main storage area above.</description>
    <position x="365" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb darkened stairwell" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Archive Storage, Vault Entrance">
    <description>This narrow room is devoid of any furnishings or adornment except for the massive granite vault door that makes up the entire back wall, and the two Y'Shai Guardians standing as sentries.  A dull yellow glow illuminates the chamber though the exact source of the light remains hidden from view.</description>
    <position x="375" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Imperial Palace, Above the Archives">
    <description>A tight and narrow spiral staircase leads from the elegant wooden catwalk back to the floor.  With the height of the room, one is granted a perfectly unobstructed view of the picturesque scenes painted upon the palace archives' dome.  The ebony and walnut shelves here are lined with Guild registers and financial records, each embossed upon their covers with the Moon Mage crest.  At either side of the staircase stand metal poles, one holding a sphere of luminous gaethzen, the other an orb of tzgaa.</description>
    <position x="365" y="290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Imperial Palace, Above the Archives">
    <description>This cramped, burgundy-carpeted catwalk allows access to books held high atop the floor of the archives on the sprawling upper reaches of the shelves.  Hanging over the side of the catwalk railing are brightly glowing tzgaa orbs, providing needed light to every shadowy nook of the chamber, without placing the precious texts in the danger flames would.  Looking out over the archives grants a clear view of an obsidian table below, its pitch surface seeming to absorb any light that touches it.</description>
    <position x="355" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Imperial Palace, The Lapis Hall">
    <description>To one side of the columned hall looms a smooth and lifelike statue of a winged man, young in face and garbed in flowing robes and cracked sandals, clutching a tall staff capped by a softly glowing tzgaa orb of a gentle green hue.  Across from the alfaric icon, a pirouetting S'Kra is frozen midway through her motions, the stony dancer eternally locked in the graceful sarhhtha.  Brilliant lapis lazuli bracelets adorn her rock wrists, each larger than a Gor'Tog waist.</description>
    <position x="330" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lapis archway" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Imperial Palace, The Lapis Hall">
    <description>Waves of lapis tile surge around several granite blocks placed precisely between staggering columns of dark green-flecked black marble.  The hunks of drab granite are bedecked with golden plaques upon their faces, each metal plate engraved with large lettering of exacting quality in the common language, and various items enclosed in glass cases rest atop the rock.</description>
    <position x="330" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Imperial Palace, Hall of Lapis and Marble">
    <description>Through a spiraling archway of half glistening white marble and half deep blue lapis, the darkened recesses of a stairway are partially visible as most of the light from the magical tzgaa and gaethzen orbs fails to pierce the shadows' furthest reaches.  To the east and west stretches a long corridor filled with exotic treasures, Imperial decorations of fabulous wealth, and marble columns, all upon a dark blue and green tile floor.</description>
    <position x="320" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Imperial Palace, The Marble Hall">
    <description>Even gentle shuffles and cautious footsteps echo throughout this section of the palace, reverberating between the towering white columns and bouncing off of the walls.  Few items are displayed here, but in the center of the hall is a solid block of granite decorated with blue and green marble tiles.  A single glass box rests on this, padlocks of brass clearly keeping the item within secure while matching the brass plaque inset into one side.</description>
    <position x="310" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Imperial Palace, The Marble Hall">
    <description>Blue and green squares run down the length of the hall, forming a repeating checkerboard pattern that is broken only by the dark flecks of black veins within the marble surface.  Between the massive columns which support the ceiling are nestled a vast assortment of objects and curiosities, arranged as if in a museum's display.  Most notable are a bleached skull resting on a table, a faded diagram carefully arranged in a wall frame, and a brittle parchment set upon a stone pedestal.</description>
    <position x="310" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Imperial Palace, Dungeon">
    <description>Muted light filters through the gaze of a dimmed gaethzen wall plate, barely illuminating the large circular chamber of drab granite slabs.  A metal desk flanks the stairway leading back to the palace proper.  Opposite the stair, a row of steel bars blockades a dreary cell.</description>
    <position x="320" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Imperial Palace, Dungeon">
    <description>An odd assortment of implements and clumsy devices clutter this shadowed edge of the Imperial dungeon.  The forefront of the army of devices is led by the easily recognizable guillotine and rack.  Many of the other mammoths, ranging from mechanical to magical, appear rusted over but still functional.  A glance up a blockaded staircase reveals its destination as the famed Death Hall that contains solitary confinement cells used for the Empire's political prisoners.</description>
    <position x="330" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Museum of Imperial History, Outside Atrium" note="Musuem of Imperial History" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Low, wide granite steps lead down to the street, partitioned off into three sections by long rows of greenery filled troughs.  A pair of monstrously sculpted lions perches atop tight clusters of quadruple columns, gazing down upon museum-goers with impassionate stony stares.  Two small plaques, one of ruddy brass and the other a patina-coated copper, are bolted to the bases.</description>
    <position x="320" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze doors" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Museum of Imperial History, First Floor Foyer">
    <description>On either side of the entrance, the walls are filled with restored tile mosaics depicting life in Imperial times.  The hues of blue, gold, and green, all framed by lustrous white marble, extend from the floor to nearly the ceiling, a sharp contrast to the otherwise beautiful yet unadorned museum walls.  A few ivory-colored stone benches give rest for the weary, allowing them a relaxing pause after a day of exhibit browsing.</description>
    <position x="280" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze doors" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Museum of Imperial History, Theories on Pre-Empire Life Exhibit">
    <description>Vaulted arches connect the tops of alabaster white columns, giving this curving museum hall the sensation of being framed in a marble cage.  Between the first and second columns is a large section of sandstone wall, embellished with a scene of myriad colors.  This piece of stone nearly blocks access to an acanth door.  As if studying the wall section, a stuffed cloth mannequin stands opposite in an unmoving pose.</description>
    <position x="265" y="155" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb alabaster staircase" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Museum of Imperial History, The Young Empire Exhibit">
    <description>Propped up by a wooden frame to appear as stoic as a dedicated guardian, the rusty top portion of an elaborately detailed set of plate armor watches over the area.  Just beside this metal faux-warrior is a brittle parchment in a firm wooden frame, while on its other side is a steel-trimmed case.  Large tapestries hang from the marble columns on all sides, their surfaces either damaged by passing years or pristinely restored by museum staff.</description>
    <position x="280" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Museum of Imperial History, The Fall of the Empire Exhibit">
    <description>Nestled between two elegant columns is a tabletop diorama, its surface covered with tiny model ships on an ocean of blue velvet.  A sweeping alabaster staircase ascends to the upper floor just behind the diorama, giving those coming up or down a bird's eye view of the miniature naval arrangement.  Furthering the area's ship-going theme is a worm-eaten wooden heketel'tegreis, strategically placed in front of a nearby acanth door.  A brass plaque explains the relevance of the various exhibits.</description>
    <position x="295" y="155" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb alabaster staircase" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Museum of Imperial History, Glory Days of the Empire Exhibit">
    <description>The white marble columns of the central octagon of the museum soar majestically to support the arched ceiling and second floor balconies.  Numerous cases and displays are artistically arranged around the spacious room.  This extra space is put to good use featuring furniture exhibits of a fire damaged rug and a darkly stained acanth chair.</description>
    <position x="280" y="155" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Museum of Imperial History, The Might of the Empire Exhibit">
    <description>A massively thick-beamed ironwood trebuchet reinforced with rust-plagued iron supports dominates the room.  Opposing forces were likely intimidated by the sheer size of towering siege engines like this one, and it must have been an equally impressive task for the museum staff to set it up.  A sweeping alabaster staircase arches down in the opposite direction, surely because the weight would be too much to rest near a fragile descent.</description>
    <position x="265" y="110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb alabaster staircase" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Museum of Imperial History, Ancient Magic Exhibit">
    <description>A quadruple set of marble columns rise towards the vaulted ceiling, each adorned with majestic restored tapestries and proud signs extolling the archaeological finds of Throne City.  One massive cloth tapestry stands out from its kin, the bottom edge partially draped over a framed chart.  In a position of obvious importance, a jewelry case rests in front of the balcony railing.</description>
    <position x="280" y="125" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Museum of Imperial History, Dragon Priest Exhibit">
    <description>Guarding the banister of a sweeping alabaster staircase is a S'Kra Mur statue, its form made completely of colored wax.  The placement is likely no accident, as this dominating simulacrum is the first thing those ascending the staircase see.  Across from the S'Kra Mur, a white-edged purple banner hangs from one of the marble columns, although the waxen Dragon Priest looks none too happy with this arrangement.</description>
    <position x="295" y="110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb alabaster staircase" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Museum of Imperial History, Modern Throne City's Restoration">
    <description>The exhibitions here are devoted to the modern day and age, ranging from the stuffed head of a decapitated angiswaerd to the large parchment map of the city.  A white banner stretching between two marble columns indicates advertisement and soliciting are not beneath the staff of the museum.  Confirming this is a cherry wood donations box, situated neatly in the center of the exhibits.</description>
    <position x="280" y="95" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Baravor's Wagon" note="Baravor's Wagon|Jumpy Jewelry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Resembling more of a traveling disaster area than a workroom, a myriad of pouches, canisters, tools and various items in need of repair lie strewn about what can only be considered a work bench.  Spools of gold, silver and platinum chain sit precariously atop a long wooden shelf, and a mahogany display stand leans unevenly against the back wall.  Ashen smudges and faded burn marks of all shapes and sizes dot the walls and floor, the products of a less than fastidious mage.</description>
    <position x="340" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas flap" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Xathvier's Curios and Oddities" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Magnificent marble columns stretch toward a spacious ceiling area, their scalloped surfaces masked closer to the floor by numerous stacks of baubles and goods.  Such is the density with which the shelves are packed that the various layers are exposed like the side of a cliff, giving clues through the strata as to the time each item has lain untouched.</description>
    <position x="380" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Xathvier's Curios and Oddities, Backroom">
    <description>Despite being equally as large as the store proper, the backroom is far more cluttered.  Stacks of dusty boxes and satchels of unknown content are piled in precarious placements, and an overabundance of shelving is covered with a two- and three-layer high menagerie of trinkets.  Everything from quills, scrolls and tomes lie next to disorganized heaps of cloth, metal and leather.  In the midst of this chaotic mix is an ornate marble desk.</description>
    <position x="380" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone archway" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Faldesu Exchequer, Foyer">
    <description>Merchants and city patrons alike create a constant stream of traffic into the bank, their voices rising in a cacophony of sound that echoes loudly off the vaulted ceiling high above.  Several guards stand at key locations throughout the area, keeping a careful watch on all those who enter through the steel double doors.  On the marble floor just inside the entrance is an intricate tile mosaic, displaying a seven-pointed star pattern.</description>
    <position x="420" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Faldesu Exchequer, Atrium">
    <description>Checkered designs and patterns cover the polished marble floor, marking off a deliberate path south that leads toward the exchange booths beyond.  Painted upon the south wall, and somewhat faded by the passage of time, is a stunningly detailed mural of the God Kertigen.</description>
    <position x="420" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Faldesu Exchequer, Currencies and Restitutions" note="Exchanger" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Ringlets of gold filigree polished to a lustrous shine, swirl along the black-veined marble walls of this chamber.  Hasty repairs have been made to the ceiling above, where whitewashed paint scarcely hides the water stains that lie beneath.  Oblivious to the surroundings are the moneychangers behind the hardwood counter, quickly counting out and exchanging each patron's coin.</description>
    <position x="420" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Faldesu Exchequer, Lounge">
    <description>Light streams down through the frosted-crystal skylight above, bathing everything in an ambient glow.  Soft music also fills the air, and together they create a soothing backdrop for the business deals being conducted at each table.  Off to one side rests a small sideboard of refreshments, ready to serve the merchants' and patrons' needs.</description>
    <position x="430" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Faldesu Exchequer, Atrium">
    <description>Ornately carved marble columns rise from the highly polished floor towards the vaulted ceiling, supporting white plaster beams that stretch the length of the structure.  Two rather large exotic plants stand to either side of the passage that leads to the Teller windows beyond, creating the appearance of an archway.  Dominating the eastern wall through which the passage travels is a massive mural portraying many raven-drawn caravans as they make their arduous journey over the lands of the Empire.</description>
    <position x="430" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Faldesu Exchequer, Teller" note="Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Iron bars circled by rings of brass and gold comprise the grills through which the clerks conduct the financial transactions.  Merchants and city patrons crowd this tiny area, hoping to complete their business quickly and make their leave.  In the corner stands a lone guard who watches everything in silence, anxiously waiting a moment in which to be of assistance.</description>
    <position x="440" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="The Gilded Atrium, Lobby" note="Bathhouse">
    <description>Vast statues of beautiful Eluned support the ceiling, strategically clothed with shells and seaweed, and accompanied by schools of dolphins, fish and other sea life.  A desk made of polished granite sits near the entrance, apparently for the custodian to use as she greets visitors, but the fact that only a wet towel remains on guard indicates that she's most likely abandoned her post for a swim with the customers.</description>
    <position x="380" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hot pool" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="The Gilded Atrium, Salt Baths" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Some distance above, a tile mosaic runs along the edge of a stone balcony, flanked by statues of nymphs and nyads dancing carefree in liquid glee.  A sparkling waterfall cascades from the ledge, churning the bath with flowing currents and froth.</description>
    <position x="400" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble steps" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="The Gilded Atrium, Salt Baths" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Tucked beneath the balcony, this section of the pool swirls with strong, foamy eddies that rush to the southeast.  Filled by the channels and grooves along the backwall, the current is powerful, and few swimmers linger in this area, prefering to splash playfully in the waters that do not flow so quickly.</description>
    <position x="390" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="The Gilded Atrium, Balcony">
    <description>A curving set of colorfully tiled stairs descends to the ground floor, its banisters littered with towels, cloaks and shoes of those now swimming in the soothing waters.  From here, a spectacular view of the bath hall opens up, revealing that the building is quite large indeed, and putting one at roughly eye level with the massive Eluned statues standing in the lobby.</description>
    <position x="380" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hot pool" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="The Gilded Atrium, Balcony Pools">
    <description>The bath is trapezoidal in shape, presumably to better channel the water over the lip of the balcony's edge and into the pools below.  A number of square openings along the backwall keep a steady stream flowing and splashing over the stone faces of fish and nymphs lying just beneath the surface.</description>
    <position x="380" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble steps" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive waterfall" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Groeshum Marbleworks, Furniture Atrium">
    <description>Large and obviously heavy works of marble are lined up in what would otherwise be a spacious atrium.  Several Dwarven clerks wiggle their ways between the massive merchandise to catalog the pieces, pausing occasionally to pull out hammer and chisel and repair minor chips.  Their work is neverending, as contractors and wealthy customers apparently always desire these powerfully carved marble products.</description>
    <position x="480" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Groeshum Marbleworks, MAMAS Services" note="MAMAS" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Precisely fitted slats of slate grey stone alternate with similarly shaped pieces of pure white, creating a sidewise checkerboard pattern along every wall.  An impressive white wolf pelt is stretched near the top of one of the walls, but the shop is otherwise unadorned with decor.  While aesthetics are neglected, function is not, and the entire area is filled with unshaped blocks, carved statues, and ornate trim awaiting their use in Throne City's restoration.</description>
    <position x="480" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Heritage House, Columned Foyer" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tall granite columns run in parallel lines down the middle of the chamber, partially blocking the light from an oversized brazier burning brightly in the heart of the foyer.  Small bowls filled with scented water surround the glowing fire, the warmth of the flame causing the scent of rose petals to rise high into the air.</description>
    <position x="340" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Heritage House, Secretarial Post">
    <description>Heavily polished and immaculately clean, the gold-veined white marble walls shine brightly in the light of the glowing chandelier above.  Fine tapestries depicting various historical events hang along the walls, retelling the tales of times long past.  Covering the smooth granite floor, a plush rug constructed of soft fur stretches from wall to wall.  An oak door leads deeper into the chapter house, where only members of this scholarly sect can pass unhindered.</description>
    <position x="340" y="410" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Vermadian's Exotic Pelts" note="Furrier|Tanner" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Thick stitching binds the canvas walls of the stall securely, but not enough that the sounds of street traffic or the tugging of random breezes is even partially blocked.  Crates of animal products and salts are stacked in the corners, most of which are sealed and labeled with unusual and faraway locations.  The floor is nothing more than the dirty road surface, giving Throne City's only furrier a sense of being merely temporary.</description>
    <position x="160" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Dahl Aeliy Provisions and Wares" note="General Store" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Well insulated from both the stifling heat of summer and the chill touch of winter, this tent has multiple linings of canvas between its interior and exterior.  Less attention has been paid to the dynamics of aestheticism, and the ceiling, propped up on the corners by reed shoots, droops sloppily down in the center.  Splitting the tent is a low mahogany table with a bound set of bark sheaves resting atop it.</description>
    <position x="160" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Atrium" note="Observatory" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The off-white limestone of the walls is broken by the deep grey of fluted columns supporting an overhanging mantle of similarly dark stonework.  Beyond the columns is the bottom of a monumentally sized device which angles upward out of view, its purpose obscured by the atrium's lower ceiling and walls.  Just beside the entrance, a parchment starchart is set behind a panel of glass.</description>
    <position x="120" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Base of the Emperor's Eye">
    <description>A mammoth telescope consisting of an assortment of metals, gears and stone structural supports rises at an acute angle toward the domed ceiling far above.  Easily dwarfing the size of typical shops and homes, the hulking construction is surrounded by a network of metal catwalks and smaller lenses.  The main viewing port at ground level is sealed, but an iron ladder provides access to the higher telescopes.</description>
    <position x="130" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Ascending Catwalk">
    <description>Creaking as it shifts, the catwalk is made of overlapping hammered flats of iron that form a supportive grill, which in turn is attached to several stone arches.  A tremendous number of beams rises from underneath the platform, criss-crossing and straddling the larger and lower portion of the Emperor's Eye.  Far more delicate than the beams, thousands of copper, bronze, and brass gears are exposed upon the back of the monster to facilitate focusing.</description>
    <position x="130" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Catwalk on the Emperor's Eye">
    <description>The catwalk curls slightly as it heads underneath the angled form of the Emperor's Eye then ends abruptly at a drop off with only a simple railing stopping a nasty fall.  A large amount of supports rise from the floor far below like skeletal fingers, looking too frail to hold up what must be an intense amount of weight.  Not only are they successful in this endeavor, these smaller supports also somehow manage to orient the telescope when the appropriate gears and counter-weights are set into motion.</description>
    <position x="120" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Catwalk on the Emperor's Eye">
    <description>The domed ceiling is so close that the astonishing carved details along the ledge of dark rock at the dome's base are clear.  Cooing pigeons nestle along this lip, yet none seem audacious enough to sully the polished surface of the upper telescope.  A gaethzen orb provides illumination for an assortment of levers designed to focus the giant sky-watching lenses.</description>
    <position x="120" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Lens of the Emperor's Eye">
    <description>The lens for the beast is high above, visible from here only due to a complex array of mirrors, their purpose to allow attendants to spot obstructions on the glass and direct light to areas otherwise too difficult to see.  A long focusing scope runs the length of the larger telescope, complete with its own focusing arrangement, no doubt set up for preliminary sightings before committing to the effort of moving the Emperor's Eye.</description>
    <position x="130" y="170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Ponthilas Observatory, Private Observation Platform">
    <description>An alcove is carved into the limestone of the dome, and one end of this scaffolding is supported on the lip of that while the other end is attached to the iron web of catwalks surrounding the Emperor's Eye.  Centered on a pedestal of ornate stone is an exquisite enameled telescope, specifically positioned in this lofty perch to allow private viewing of the skies to honored guests of the city and persons of import.</description>
    <position x="130" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="The Celestial Forum, Atrium" note="Celestial Forum" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A compass rose is set in the floor, its deep blue ceramic tile contrasting the white marble of this sprawling atrium.  At the points of the cardinal directions, wide pillars stretch into flying buttresses from which drape streams of flowing silk.  Sparkling crystal stars connected by silver thread trace constellations across each of the deep-blue silken banners.  Further up, where the walls meet the ceiling, the text of the Lunar Accord is carved into slabs of marble encircling the chamber.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble arch" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="The Celestial Forum, Assembly of Yavash">
    <description>A mahogany banister guards the edge of the balcony, overlooking the amphitheater below.  Descending rows of padded benches, upholstered in crimson leather, provide seating for the gallery.  Small gaethzen orbs held aloft by black marble shadowlings with spinel eyes cast a dim red light from above.  In the corner of the room, a small buffet is attended to by a quiet steward.</description>
    <position x="230" y="150" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="The Celestial Forum, Assembly of Katamba">
    <description>A mahogany banister guards the edge of the balcony, overlooking the amphitheater below.  Settees of ebony with sable cushions provide seating for the gallery.  Small gaethzen orbs held aloft by black marble shadowlings with onyx eyes cast a dim light from above.  In the corner of the room, a low counter is attended to by a quiet steward.</description>
    <position x="240" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="The Celestial Forum, Assembly of Xibar">
    <description>A mahogany banister guards the edge of the balcony, overlooking the amphitheater below.  A row of high-backed chairs, cushioned in light blue velvet, provide seating for the gallery.  Small gaethzen orbs held aloft by black marble shadowlings with eyes of blue-white diamonds cast a dim azure light from above.  In the corner of the room, a wide sideboard is attended to by a quiet steward.</description>
    <position x="230" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="The Celestial Forum, Amphitheater">
    <description>Two marble columns rise from the center of the room, reaching up to the vaulted ceiling far above.  Rows of padded benches are arranged in a semi circle around an elevated dais between the columns.  A wide balcony overlooks the amphitheater, providing more seating for onlookers and the rare petitioner awaiting his or her turn to speak to the assembled crowd.  The back of the room is marked by a tall stained glass window depicting Jares Braun signing the Lunar Accord.</description>
    <position x="220" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Maginius Kaentao Maous, Spell Library" note="Maginius Kaentao Maous|Spell Library" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tall, elegant columns carved like intermingled two-headed serpents rise to the ceiling, which itself is a dizzying distance above.  Circular shelves contain thousands upon thousands of books, most of which are off-limits to the casual browser.  Scribes constantly scurry here and there, cataloging and arranging the contents.  Near the entrance is a red velvet partition, where those visitors interested in viewing books up close have to register.</description>
    <position x="180" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Maginius Kaentao Maous, Exclusive Library">
    <description>Tremendous ladders set on top of low, wagon-like constructs fill the aisles between the towering shelves of books, allowing scribes access to the volumes at the highest and most precarious perches.  A single oaken door, massive in its own right but dwarfed by the immensity of the books stored here, is set into the farthest wall.  Thousands of candles in glass-cages and gaethzen spheres illuminate the tomes for those allowed to seek knowledge in this place.</description>
    <position x="170" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken door" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Maginius Kaentao Maous, Rare Books Room">
    <description>Four unusual statues hold up the ceiling of this fairly small room, each face blackened and doglike, and covered by gilded mesh helms.  A wide ironwood case holds a series of large, foreboding tomes, each lit by a single, off-colored gaethzen sphere.  Empty shelves fill the rest of the space, awaiting their own uncommon tomes and careful readers.</description>
    <position x="160" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken door" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Seven Star Exchange and Pawn" note="Pawnshop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The walls are white marble, though this is difficult to tell since there is such an abundance of what most people would term junk.  Most of the items have a nautical theme, if one could give randomness such a unifying concept, but it is just as likely it was all simply salvaged from a ship wreck.  Buried among the rubble of the assorted goods is a large iron safe.</description>
    <position x="60" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Imperial Stargazer's Medical Pavilion, Healing Chamber" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Pristine white walls adorned with frosted crystal sconces enclose the chamber, surrounding a floor composed of blue and green tiles.  Nestled under an oak-framed painting is a large, whitewashed cabinet, smelling of freshly harvested herbs.  Tinted skylights overhead lend an airy feeling to the room, bathing the area with muted illumination.</description>
    <position x="80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wood door" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Imperial Stargazer's Medical Pavilion, Treatment Chamber">
    <description>Pale azure panels line the walls of the chamber, edged with ornately carved midnight-blue molding.  Frosted crystal sconces cast pools of gently flickering light, making the faint silvery lines embellishing the darkly-stained floor appear to float above the glossy finish of the wood.</description>
    <position x="80" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wood door" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Imperial Stargazer's Medical Pavilion, Treatment Chamber">
    <description>Pale red panels line the walls of the chamber, edged with ornately carved dark crimson molding.  Frosted crystal sconces cast pools of gently flickering light, making the faint golden lines embellishing the darkly-stained floor appear to float above the glossy finish of the wood.</description>
    <position x="70" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Imperial Stargazer's Medical Pavilion, Treatment Chamber">
    <description>Silvery panels line the walls of the chamber, edged with ornately carved charcoal-grey molding.  Frosted crystal sconces cast pools of gently flickering light, making the faint coppery lines embellishing the darkly-stained floor appear to float above the glossy finish of the wood.</description>
    <position x="90" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="The Durgaulda Chamber, Research and Lore Division" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A trio of sandstone dragons carved in bas-relief circle the domed ceiling, looking down from their lofty perches upon all who seek to peruse the facility's texts.  The wings of each dragon are chisled craftily to appear as if they were blending into the wing of the next, forming as a whole an intricate textured pattern.  The focus of the creatures' stony stares are the rows and rows of shelving, all filled with hundreds of crimson and rawhide tomes.</description>
    <position x="160" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Chelwick's Glassworks" note="Glassworks" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Burlwood paneling sheaths the walls, banded by gently rounded black ironwood molding and baseboards.  Attached to the wall behind a low counter is a small shelf holding an assortment of books and other items, while just below it rests a multi-drawer cabinet.  A single gaethzen lamp hangs overhead casting a blue-white light around the room, muted by the quantity of dust floating around freely.</description>
    <position x="440" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Old Throne City, Mahkra Alley" note="Mahkra Alley" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Cracked paving stones underfoot are bordered with lines of withered, yellow weeds.  One section which has partly sunken into the ground holds a shallow pool of scummy water, filled with desiccated leaves and other debris.  Buildings on either side make the available light sketchy at best, casting the entire alley in an eternal and miserable gloom.</description>
    <position x="560" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crooked alleyway" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Old Throne City, Mahkra Alley" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Thin, climbing ivy frames the stout oak door which grants entrance to an imposing two-story building, breaking the monotony of weathered red brick with faded pastel greens.  Shallow puddles of scummy water blight the ground underfoot, filling depressions in the cracked and weed-strewn paving stones.</description>
    <position x="580" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Old Throne City, Mahkra Alley" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Scraggly bushes and withered, brown-tipped weeds clog the area, implying a sense of desolation.  Dried leaves dance on the occasional breeze around piles of decaying rubble and garbage, their movement contrary to the stillness that pervades.  A rotting cart leans against the side of the building, abandoned as food for enterprising termites.</description>
    <position x="600" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Elanai's Delicate Tastes, Cheese and Bread Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>For a mere stall, the interior is elegant, ordered, and very clean.  Wicker baskets are arranged in neat circles around a deobar counter, each container overfilled with a variety of cheeses and breads.  Most are covered with soft blankets with a lone sample of their contents lying on top.  Near the center of the area, a delicate paper menu is tacked to a support beam.</description>
    <position x="620" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Elanai's Delicate Tastes, Wine Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rows of wine bottles are lined along the backwalls, nearly disguising the fact that this is a streetside stall with the appearance of some wealthy aristocrat's cellar.  Straw batting is stuffed around some of the more precious samples.  A wine list, placed carefully atop an upside-down oak cask, notes the inventory for potential buyers.</description>
    <position x="630" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Old Throne City, Shakoepi Bridge">
    <description>A wall of crates lines the stone railing of the bridge, reducing the expansive view southward to one of occasional unobstructed glimpses.  This bridge, whatever its original purpose, is now used as a way station for cargo and deliveries into Throne City.  All things passing through the gates of the city are subject to inspection, whether they be man, beast or mineral, and as such, those inanimate things that can not hurry their journey inside wait the longest.</description>
    <position x="600" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble gate" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb muddy slope" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Old Throne City, Shakoepi Bridge">
    <description>Not far to the east, the elegant spires and massive columned homes of the Arcadius residential sector rise skyward in all their exotic and rich splendor.  These buildings are cordoned off by a long high wall of stone, leaving Shakoepi Bridge the only access into the sector.  Below, the waters of the Faldesu inlet gurgle and splash around the remains of one of the ancient Imperial Navy's ship hulls.</description>
    <position x="620" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Old Throne City, Beneath Shakoepi Bridge">
    <description>The sandy beach of a Faldesu inlet surrenders to thick vegetation and plant-life, which rises on a gentle incline to cover the solid walls protecting Throne City.  Pounded into mud by ascending and descending travelers, a slope angles up this hill and to the bridge above.  Nearby, several crates rest at the edge of the water, covered with tarps and canvas until they can be delivered to their destinations.</description>
    <position x="600" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb muddy slope" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Old Throne City, Beneath Shakoepi Bridge">
    <description>As much like a cave as anything, this portion of the trail is sheltered on the sides by thick foliage and above by the bridge.  The nearby inlet is barely visible through a screen of reeds and bamboo, but what brief glimpses can be had also reveal the remains of a ship's hull.</description>
    <position x="620" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Outside Throne City, Forested Trail">
    <description>The top of the covered stone dock which subtly feeds Throne City with supplies and exotic goods is visible to the north.  Oddly, the air between here and there shimmers slightly, reminiscent of the rippling of heat on stone during a hot summer's day.  A nagging sensation of being under close scrutiny hangs over the area, but the gently waving fronds of wide-leafed plants appear to be the only observers.</description>
    <position x="580" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Forested Trail, Cobblestone Ruins">
    <description>Heavy foliage presses in on the trail, a nearly irrepressible tide of nature that is awash with leaves, stems, and branches.  Crooked cobblestones poke up from the dirt, betraying the original nature of this pathway as a road.  These are mostly barren of the weeds that choke the trail's edges, as if something regularly bore them down beneath passing feet.  Where such travelers would go is unclear, since a wall of vegetation has turned this path into a dead-end.</description>
    <position x="560" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="none" move="southeast" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Stone Docks, Covered Shore" note="Riverhaven|barge|Kraelyst start point|travel start point" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Barely extending from the shore, the dock is little more than a short series of solid blocks of weather-battered stone.  Thick sheets of canvas are lashed in a tent-like fashion around this port, keeping the onslaught of the skies and winds at bay while also serving to mask its presence from passing ships.  With the excessive vegetation that creates yet another disguising layer outside the canvas, it's clear that many boats could pass along the Faldesu without ever knowing this place exists.</description>
    <position x="560" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brushy break" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Along the Faldesu, Forested Shore">
    <description>A tent of stretched canvas is visible just over the edge of wide, elephant-eared plants, though movement further west would quickly eliminate even these glimpses behind a curtain of greenery.  Tangled vines and nettles cascade over muddy banks, forming a natural wall southward, but the patches of sand and shoreline make passage west possible.</description>
    <position x="500" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brushy break" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Along the Faldesu, Forested Shore">
    <description>Heavy, thick clumps of reeds rise like miniature citadels, their sides curving bowl-like toward the muddy center of the sandy path.  Beetles and birds occasionally peek out from their homes in these fortified plants to spy on passersby, curious but too cautious to breach their safety.  Dangling vines reach down over many of the clumps, some so far as to make solid columns of vegetation from ground to overhead tree.</description>
    <position x="480" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Along the Faldesu, Forested Shore">
    <description>Odd and out of place, a row of petite white flowers peeks out from behind a wall of sharp grasses and nettles, adding a touch of delicate grace to an otherwise unremarkable tangle.  A constant swarm of insects hums and buzzes around this rare delight, uncaring of the razor-edged plants nearby.  Some of the small petals are caught in the breezes, sent swirling into the air to finally touch down upon the softly lapping waters of the river.</description>
    <position x="460" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Along the Faldesu, Sandy Shore">
    <description>As if inviting visitors, arches of thick branches and hanging vines route explorers toward this small opening and, further, to a long sandy trail.  Flat, open areas of dirt and sand are marked by multitudes of clawed footprints, also following the course of the arching vegetation as well as making their own paths to the water's edge.  If not for the hungry predators in the area, the scene would be nearly idyllic.</description>
    <position x="440" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandy trail" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Along the Faldesu, Sandy Shore">
    <description>The branches of intermingling water oaks create a thick canopy overhead, nearly as tangled and wide as the ground level vegetation.  Stumps and waterlogged trunks provide the basis for hundreds of varieties of mosses and mildew, behind which spring a curtain of high reeds.  This tiny cul-de-sac is a dead end for all but the smallest of birds and creatures.</description>
    <position x="420" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="The Faldesu River, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Leading away from this small, reed-cluttered shore, a long sandy trail winds its way through clumps of vegetation toward somewhat drier land.  The water here is merely ankle deep, though the mud beneath the surface makes movement difficult -- too shallow to actively swim, but too wet to actually walk.  Arboreal creatures, such as the occasional squirrel, have a much easier time traversing this area through the overhanging branches.</description>
    <position x="440" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandy trail" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="The Faldesu River, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Curving out into the water is a small, muddy extension of the bank, so choked with reeds that only the smallest of birds could find passage through it.  Eternally, the water laps away at this feature, sucking away the black mud to expose stubborn roots.  Though eventually the river may win, the tiny outlet of land will not go quietly into that dark water.</description>
    <position x="420" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="The Faldesu River, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A sandbar humps out of the Faldesu's waters, making it impossible to approach the shore by boat.  Driftwood jutting out of the mud is a tell-tale sign that at some point, at least one captain tried to beach a vessel here, though to what goal is impossible to guess.  In the time it took for nature to reduce the wreck into fragments, it would appear that no others lacked the sanity enough to try.</description>
    <position x="400" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="The Faldesu River, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Something has made several nests in the muddy banks, each spaced out some distance from one another and only partially excavated.  Broken reeds and brush kneel down around each indent, but aside from a scant few clawed footprints leading to and fro, there is no indication that any of these river-front residences are actively used -- or at least actively accessed from anywhere but the water.</description>
    <position x="380" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="The Faldesu River, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Reeds and cattails clog the shallow water, providing shelter for an assortment of small, wide-eyed fish that dart energetically just below the surface.  A steady rustle of wind off the Faldesu sets the thick tops of the cattails into motion, drumming off one another in the air's invisible caress and revealing glimpses of woodland vegetation further to the west.  From here, there is no access -- only knee-deep mud and nettles.</description>
    <position x="360" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Outside Throne City, Faldesu Inlet">
    <description>Wide-leafed plants fill the edges of the inlet like the spectators at a parade, waving their fronds as if in admiration of the gurgling waters.  Flowing on its course, the water is indifferent to this constant wind-driven attention, content to be the source of life for so much vegetation and then to offer it nothing more.  If adoring gazes are what the plants give, then stoic resistance is the only gift from a series of stone pillars, half submerged in the liquid.</description>
    <position x="620" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go inlet shallows" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Outside Throne City, Faldesu Inlet">
    <description>Where once ancient feet trod upon interlocked cobblestones, now thickened grass and choking weeds grow, narrowing the remains of a major trade road to a mere footpath.  Rocks and light rubble lie buried in the thorny vegetation, an indication of a long-ago structure stretching toward a distant wall far into the woodland.  All this abandoned ruin is of no concern to nature, her attention spent in the years since to grow a particularly large tree that leans over the nearby waterway.</description>
    <position x="640" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Thayergraben, Faldesu Inlet">
    <description>A twist of thorns and spiny plants hinders passage north but fails to block it completely.  Dragonflies dart in and out of the tangle, back and forth between it and the neighboring reeds choking the inlet.  Not all obstacles here are natural, as a large granite block lies in the water as well, and almost completely buried in vegetation along the shore is a granite marker of some kind.</description>
    <position x="660" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite block" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Faldesu Inlet, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Narrow rows of reeds and cattails rise in anything but oppressive numbers, and certainly not in quantities large enough to alter the course of the inlet.  The water is merely shallow and relatively easy to traverse, though the silt and mud does its best to impede.  Jutting up from these measly depths are several stone pillars, all in a row.</description>
    <position x="640" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go muddy bank" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Faldesu Inlet, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Clouds of silt drift beneath the surface of the shallow water, spinning and twirling like the tumultuous motion of a submerged storm.  The water is not intensely powerful against anything more weighty, though the steady pressure has forced the brown and green reeds to angle downstream.  Foam nestles at the stems of these bent aquatic plants, occasionally pulling free to sail unfettered with the current.</description>
    <position x="640" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="182" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Faldesu Inlet, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thick trees from the shore hang languidly over the inlet waters, drooping their willowy limbs down as if drinking.  Perhaps they seek vainly to reach the large squarish stone beneath the surface, slicked with strings of submerged algae.  The water itself is clear but dark, shaded by the mass of Shakoepi Bridge overhead.  Small fish dart along the bottom, dancing from reed to reed in search of tasty leeches or insects.</description>
    <position x="620" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Faldesu Inlet, Churning Waters" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Significantly stronger here than the water just a few steps westward, the forceful current pushes far too hard for any thick vegetation to take hold.  This is not the case on the far eastern shore, as immense trees and wide swaths of reeds and cattails clog the inlet waters.  To reach that land from here would require crossing the deepest water of the inlet while risking a quick death by drowning.</description>
    <position x="640" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="182" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Faldesu Inlet, Churning Waters" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Flowing with such rapid force that swimming directly northward is impossible, the inlet's waters are far easier to manage at an angle.  Bits of floatsam are carried swiftly by, lost and swirling until deposited upon some muddy bank.  Some of this debris falls from the branches of a large, overhanging tree directly overhead.  South, a pair of immense stone blocks squeezes the rushing waters into an even more hectic speed.</description>
    <position x="660" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Faldesu Inlet, Granite Block">
    <description>This granite block provides a stable if somewhat slick perch in the middle of the inlet's flowing waters.  Several paces wide, it doesn't even slightly tilt nor tremble with the passage of rushing water.  The size and resilience indicates it may have been from a particularly massive structure.  An equally large granite rock lies in the calmer water to the east, although it looks extremely slippery and wet.</description>
    <position x="680" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite rock" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shore" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Faldesu Inlet, Slick Granite Rock">
    <description>Though the inlet waters are not particularly rough here, foamy white splashes soak the surface of this large rock every few seconds.  Years of this action have worn the granite smooth, and slippery green slime maximizes its slickness, providing a possible but hazardous crossing to the eastern bank.  Perhaps once this rock was part of a larger structure, but the vanquished features are long since gone.</description>
    <position x="700" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go eastern bank" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite block" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Faldesu Inlet, Eastern Bank">
    <description>Thick water oaks cluster a short distance from the shore, growing with abandon in this rich, moist soil.  Despite the packed reeds, grasses, and undergrowth, several criss-crossing paths divide and conjoin, generally heading southward.  Someone or something regularly beats the vegetation into submission while passing.</description>
    <position x="740" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slippery rock" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Faldesu Inlet, Eastern Shore">
    <description>Oak and willow trees spread their greenery overhead in a heavy umbrella of tangled branches and drooping limbs.  In this shade, the shoreline is covered with layers of hairy moss, thriving in the dank dirt and drinking in the occasional spray of mist.  Though this moss may provide a soft bed for tired beasts, the sharp reeds lining the inlet are a hazard for thirsty snouts.</description>
    <position x="760" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Faldesu Inlet, Eastern Shore">
    <description>Amidst the rough-barked trees, clusters of thin, wiry vines dangle from the upper limbs and wrap around the trunks.  Some tinged with red along the leaves, others merely rough and cordlike, the vines belie the increasingly feral nature of this shore.  Further south, the woodland becomes so choked with hearty plant life that only subtle signs indicate the presence of humanity.</description>
    <position x="760" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Faldesu Inlet, Eastern Shore">
    <description>Patches of elephant grass and clumps of dagger-like reeds part just enough to reveal easy access to the inlet shallows, though what may lurk in those dark waters could be worse than anything hiding in the vegetation.  Through this vacancy can be seen swifter waters to the north and in the middle of the inlet, but close to the shore it slogs along slowly, churning up mud and leeches.  The nearest ground is waterlogged, blurring the line between land and liquid.</description>
    <position x="780" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go inlet shallows" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Faldesu Inlet, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Clusters of brown cattails clog the water, leaving scant few spaces available for wading explorers to trudge.  The current beneath the surface is routed and rerouted, forced between the shoots of these water-dwelling reeds, but nonetheless black and thick with swirling mud.  Strong, deadly, and deep water lies further to the west, beckoning but cordoned off by rows of hardy plants.</description>
    <position x="740" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go southern shore" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Faldesu Inlet" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Slowing somewhat as it approaches the shore, the inlet takes on a distinctive, lazy-river feel, though the undercurrent remains a continual risk.  The water is murky, churned mud along the bottom rising nearly to the surface.  What hungry things might lurk in this cloudy flow can only be guessed, but there are plenty of hiding spaces for who knows what.</description>
    <position x="720" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Faldesu Inlet" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Though the water is quite deep and the current rather strong like a small pony, masses of aquatic vegetation manage to thrive.  For the most part, the long tendrils of algae-coated grasses cling to the sheltering sides of two massive blocks in the course of the inlet, but a few manage to survive just fine along the sticky sludge on the bottom.</description>
    <position x="700" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Outside Throne City, Boggy Pit">
    <description>Grey mud slides down the sides of this muck-filled pit, dripping off of roots and fallen tree limbs in great clumps.  Though the water isn't particularly clean or clear due to this, it is transparent enough to see animal bones beneath the surface.  Small worm-like things dart beneath the surface, apparently stirred into activity by any motion of falling mud or beast. </description>
    <position x="640" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb root-covered wall" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Phelim's Sanctum, Walk of Pillars">
    <description>Columns made of a dark blue, almost ebony marble line the wide hall, stretching from the floor to nearly vanish in the darkness far above.  Constellations of gold inlay dot the ceiling, visible despite the shadow, lending the illusion of a star-filled summer sky.  Near the end of the hall, a powerfully sculpted statue of Phelim stands, head cast upward as if admiring the tribute to the heavens.</description>
    <position x="540" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Phelim's Sanctum, Tear of Grazhir" note="Tear of Grazhir|Turtle|Grazhir|Astral Plane|Theren|Ways|Mintais" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A sprawling mosaic of bright colors has been tiled into the floor and spirals outwards in a tremendous sunburst shape from the center of the room.  Though this may be a design feature solely to further enhance the remarkable brilliance of the design, nothing else here displays such shades and hues, as the walls and ceiling are a drab blue.  A tiny white shard of mineral lies in the center of the mosaic.</description>
    <position x="540" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go moongate" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Jewel of the Faldesu, Gems and Fine Metals" color="#FF0000">
    <description>What is most striking about this home-turned-business is the true elegance and refinement of the decor.  From the delicate mother-of-pearl animals inlaid into the rich rosewood of the crown molding to the ornamental framed portrait behind the counter, this is a high class establishment.  Appearing somewhat out of place, a number of surly guards constantly linger, each keeping a cautious eye always turned to the customers.</description>
    <position x="500" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Gealeranendae College, Tear of Grazhir Exhibit" note="Map42_Therenborough_and_Keep.xml">
    <description>Rising and vanishing into darkness, the circular walls are home to four marble gargoyles that stare balefully from their perches at the silvery-white shard imbedded deeply into the floor's center.  A single plaque of brass and silver is fastened in the stones near the exit.  Otherwise unadorned, the room is thick with shadows, no sconces or torches to help shed illumination.</description>
    <position x="540" y="220" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Salt Yard, Barge Dock" note="Map30_Riverhaven.xml">
    <description>The end of the dock is reinforced with heavy timbers and rusting iron plates, no doubt to compensate for the extreme weight of the high piles of salt sacks.  Strategically hidden between the stacks are crates and leather satchels, their shipping labels designating their contents as decidely non-salty in origin.  None of the items appear to be black-market goods, so why such lengths were taken to disguise their transport is not clear.</description>
    <position x="560" y="20" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Tower Ruins, Ancient Military Post">
    <description>Frail fingers of crumbling stone rise toward the sky, marking the places where once fortified walls held against threats of war and attacks.  Near the tops of these half-collapsed piles, square-shaped vacancies remain as the only indication that this place ever had a roof or higher floors.</description>
    <position x="460" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Garden Rooftop, Medical Pavilion">
    <description>Branching vines of ivy creep outward from their tenacious hold on an ornamental trellis jutting up into view from below and wind through the elegantly beveled banisters of a low railing that borders the edge of the rooftop.  Small clay pots nestle against the tendrils of green ivy, harboring carefully tended herbs that perfume the air with a faintly medicinal scent.  Watching over the garden are three odd little statues, their ivory, jade and amber bodies mingling with the surrounding colors.</description>
    <position x="80" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ornamental trellis" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Garden Rooftop, Medical Pavilion">
    <description>Occupying the center of the garden is a clear crystal dome enclosing a swirling mass of greenish mist.  As though observing from on high, a lone figure carved from snow-white marble stands on its translucent perch, the long flowing tresses cascading towards the ground in sculptured smooth curves from an upward-tilted head, lost in contemplation.  Bordering the edge of the roof is a low railing supported by elegantly beveled banisters, framing the tops of the high pillars lining the street below.</description>
    <position x="60" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Garden Rooftop, Medical Pavilion">
    <description>Sheltering a bed of roses the colors of the moons is a low railing resting atop elegantly beveled banisters.  Tiles of green marble alternate with patches of springy heather and gildleaf shrubs, creating a verdant frame that compliments the blue and green of the serpents rising from within a marble fountain carved in bas-relief.  Gazing toward a cobalt blue telescope from its perch in the water is a wooden duck, its wings partially extended as though for balance.</description>
    <position x="40" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Imperial Palace, Conference Chambers">
    <description>Hanging from the center of the vaulted ceiling is a massive gold and crystal chandelier, its gaethzen orbs glowing with a muted light.  Below it, a large marble table stretches down the length of the room, accompanied by a full compliment of velvet-cushioned chairs.  Portraits line the walls, most showing signs of water damage or minor ruin but all set in elegant wood frames.</description>
    <position x="320" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Old Throne City, Vagabond's Row">
    <description>Rubbish and blankets are strewn across the alleyway, possibly left by littering hands or blown by the wind.  A tarp-covered statue stands near the street.  Between this marble monstrosity and the empty crates stacked nearby, it is unlikely that passers-by would notice this area at all.  Serving as one side of this man-made canyon is the wall of the nearby museum, a makeshift wooden scaffolding ascending its surface.</description>
    <position x="240" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden scaffolding" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Museum of Imperial History, Rooftop">
    <description>By day, the view would certainly be a commanding one, but now consists only of the distant twinkling lights of passing boats on the Faldesu.  Much closer, a makeshift wooden scaffolding peaks at the edge of the wall, very nearly matching the height of the museum itself.</description>
    <position x="265" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden scaffolding" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Museum of Imperial History, Northern Rooftop">
    <description>Though the ornamentation on the roof's edge effectively forms a parapet, the street below can be surveyed easily by quick glances between the stone alfars and soldiers.  Anyone on Dahl Aeliy would be hard pressed to spot a lurker hiding on this building, and such a task would be even harder for those living in the luxurious residential areas further north.  From the rooftops, leisurely study of Throne City's layout can be taken for granted.</description>
    <position x="280" y="45" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Museum of Imperial History, Rooftop">
    <description>Shady figures move along other rooftops, their faces hidden by deep cloaks of various sullen hues.  Luckily for anyone at this vantage point, the forms take no notice of other rooftops as their attentions are aimed downward and south.  They blink in and out of view, appearing on other buildings, moving in utter silence like ghosts, their goals equally ethereal.</description>
    <position x="280" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Museum of Imperial History, Southern Rooftop">
    <description>The mingling, contrary scents of roses and horses arise from below, drifting from private gardens nestled behind the Palace as well as the nearby palatial stalls.  Though ivy and flowering vines cover the stone, the walls of the Palace are notably unrestored, bearing centuries of chips and marks.  Those who did the restoration certainly never intended to impress anyone who might be on the rooftop of the museum.</description>
    <position x="280" y="75" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <label text="Bank">
    <position x="420" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Enchanting">
    <position x="340" y="120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Shops">
    <position x="340" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bathhouse">
    <position x="360" y="210" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Heritage">
    <position x="350" y="390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="House">
    <position x="350" y="400" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gem">
    <position x="480" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="MAMAs">
    <position x="460" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Shop">
    <position x="480" y="160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bakery">
    <position x="620" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Imperial Palace">
    <position x="280" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="General Store">
    <position x="170" y="330" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tanner">
    <position x="130" y="240" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Spell Library">
    <position x="110" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Celestial">
    <position x="200" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Forum">
    <position x="200" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Observatory">
    <position x="70" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pawnshop">
    <position x="30" y="200" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Musuem of">
    <position x="300" y="80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Imperial History">
    <position x="290" y="90" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Glassworks">
    <position x="430" y="420" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Grazhir Shard">
    <position x="510" y="190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Turtle">
    <position x="520" y="200" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Alley Thugs">
    <position x="50" y="390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="King Fade">
    <position x="10" y="320" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Marbled Angiswaerds">
    <position x="150" y="570" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Angiswaerd Hatchlings">
    <position x="120" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Angiswaerd Hatchlings">
    <position x="480" y="470" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="River Caiman">
    <position x="430" y="10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blue Belly">
    <position x="650" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crocodiles">
    <position x="650" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="River Boas">
    <position x="700" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Heggarangi Boars">
    <position x="660" y="170" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Riverhaven">
    <position x="570" y="10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Barge Dock">
    <position x="580" y="50" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>