<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Therenborough and Keep" id="42">
  <node id="1" name="Therenborough, Town Gate" note="Town Gate">
    <description>The imposing turreted towers of Theren Keep dominate this inland town, standing proud against the sky and seen plainly from every vantage point in the area.  Walls of massive stone surround the small, but bustling community, and beyond the open gates to the south are rolling pastures and distant farmsteads.  The pedestrians milling around the gate are periodically forced to step aside as paladins in gleaming plate armor ride by on magnificent steeds, heading north toward the castle.</description>
    <position x="222" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town gate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="North Road, Barony Pass" note="Map40_Langenfirth_to_Therenborough.xml|Ker'Leor|Langenfirth|Mistwood Forest|Town Gate|Gate">
    <description>With one final sweep, the road straightens out from the hilly pastures in the south to stop at a walled village.  Looming above the stone boundary is the majestic Theren Keep, its battered towers still an imposing sight to behold.</description>
    <position x="222" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town gate" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Therenborough, Horseman's Run" note="First Land Herald|Herald|newspaper|news stand" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This wide dirt pathway borders the southern end of the town, providing riders with easy access to the main streets.  A vast square, paved with granite and filled with milling people, opens up to the north.  To either side of it, smaller buildings made from dusty red bricks and quaint thatched cottages are scattered between impressive marble structures.</description>
    <position x="222" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Therenborough, Horseman's Run" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Quiet backstreets lead off from this bridle path, overlooking gardens, old courtyards and a pleasant clutter of pink and white cottages with thatched or tiled roofs.  Several horses stand sedately at hitching posts, patiently awaiting their owner's return.</description>
    <position x="162" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Therenborough, Arbalest Row">
    <description>This shop-lined pedestrian thoroughfare travels around the western side of the towering keep that survives still in all its granite magnificence.  Passersby occasionally stop to gape up at the looming tower with its circlet of ferocious stone gargoyles.</description>
    <position x="122" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carousel square" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Therenborough, Arbalest Row" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A large cottage made from honey-colored stone faces the street, its open doors emitting a savory aroma of roasted meat and herbs.  Climbing rose bushes intertwine over the front, the pure white blossoms enhancing its elegant appearance.</description>
    <position x="122" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large cottage" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Therenborough, Arbalest Row">
    <description>A red-tiled roof with flared eaves hangs over a stylish stacked-stone building.  Its bay windows show off colorful displays of fashionable clothing, attracting appraising glances from passing pedestrians.</description>
    <position x="82" y="700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Therenborough, Arbalest Row">
    <description>Gleaming marble columns of the palest pink and blue support a veranda that circles a spacious structure.  An engraved bronze plaque is mounted on one of the front columns.</description>
    <position x="22" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go spacious structure" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Therenborough, Arbalest Row">
    <description>Arbalest Row ascends up the slope of a hill where it ends at the doors of a small brick theatre.  Bronze comedy and drama masks look down from their position above the doors, welcoming those who enter.  From this high point, the town of Therenborough spreads out to the south, watched over by the towering keep.</description>
    <position x="22" y="640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small theatre" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Theatre, Lobby" note="Theatre">
    <description>Memorabilia from former performances decorates the walls and fills a glass case.  Tucked in the corner, a small bar offers a selection of liquid refreshments to thirsty theatre-goers during the intermission of the performance.  An empty marquee propped near the door waits to announce the next performance.</description>
    <position x="62" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go paneled door" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hallway" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="The Rose of the Theatre, Instruments" note="Rose of the Theatre|Music" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Bright plaid fabric hangs against one wall of the shop, serving as a backdrop for a harp whose strings are entwined with white silk roses.  Tables and baskets around the perimeter feature instruments and tools for their care.  A simple curtain, drawn back and tied out of the way of shoppers, leads to another room of the store.</description>
    <position x="82" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go paneled door" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple curtain" destination="318" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Theatre, Audience Seating">
    <description>The theatre is large and impressive with or without an audience.  The pale blue and yellow marble walls and columns are offset by the earthtones of the seats.  Affordable seating is available to all -- from the orchestra to the balcony and loges above -- to the dress circle and boxes below.  The semi-circular design and the high loft of the balcony tiers allows excellent viewing and hearing from all locations.</description>
    <position x="62" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rows" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rows" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rows" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Theatre, Balcony">
    <description>Beautifully stitched cushions in muted shades of autumn grace the chairs, while columns of blue and yellow marble elegantly frame this balcony.  A tastefully engraved sign placed within the balcony area reads, Quiet, please, when performances are running.</description>
    <position x="32" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Theatre, Floor Seating">
    <description>Upright chairs made from fine pine offer seating at floor level.  A clear view of the stage is given to all with no need to shift around to see performers.  A small notice on the back of the chair in front of you reads, Quiet, please, when performances are running.</description>
    <position x="32" y="610" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Theatre, Loge">
    <description>Columns of blue and yellow marble frame the loge.  Its seats are covered with soft cloth in shades of autumn.  An engraved golden sign placed within the loge reads, Quiet, please, when performances are running.</description>
    <position x="32" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Theatre, Backstage" note="Backstage">
    <description>Brightly lit and bustling with activity, this huge room is the hub for performers, stagehands, scenery designers, prop handlers, costumers, wig and make-up artists, all rushing to and fro.  There is always a rehearsal or performance to get ready for.  Large cabinets stand open spilling their contents on the already cluttered floor.  Costumes hang from a wooden rack and a large mirror is propped against the wall allowing for that last minute check.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go backstage door" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained doorway" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Theatre, Wings">
    <description>Used for storage, as well as providing a workspace for current projects, the wings are the focal point for the more physical aspects of the production.  Here, carpenters, painters, builders and designers can work together on such items as scenery, set decor, tableaus and backdrops.  During performances, the wings are just as busy, as performers quietly rehearse their lines one last time and stagehands rush to change sets between acts.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go backstage door" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Theatre, Stage" note="Stage">
    <description>A semi-circular stage is surrounded by rows of elegant seating while silver and blue embroidered curtains hang along the sides.  Crystal sconces placed around the stage flicker with bright candlelight.</description>
    <position x="22" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Theatre, Dressing Room" note="Dressing Room">
    <description>A large common space in the center of the room separates the men's and women's private dressing areas.  Sewing tables wait for costumers to work on new creations and make alterations as fitters bring garments by.  Tall chairs stand ready for perfomers to take a seat as make-up artists and hairdressers work their magic.  Production assistants and stagehands are often seen coming and going with script changes, food deliveries, props and accessories.</description>
    <position x="-38" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Public Baths, Foyer" note="Public Baths|Bathhouse">
    <description>The foyer is a study in restrained elegance.  Bronze statues line the ivy covered walls and marble columns rise to meet a domed skylight.  The baths are well-patronized by those who like to take advantage of both its therapeutic and social benefits.  An enormously fat Human waddles in from the Calidarium.  He takes a deep breath before heading over to the Frigidarium.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Public Baths, Frigidarium">
    <description>The most invigorating of the baths, many choose to finish up their visits with a dip into the cold water.  A huge relief, depicting an epic battle between heroic knights and a force of undead, covers all four walls.  Perhaps because she has seen it so many times, the Halfling attendant takes no notice of the painting as she waits to hand towels to shivering patrons when they climb out of the bath.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bath" destination="348" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Public Baths, Natatio">
    <description>The swimming pool is the most popular spot in the baths, especially for children.  Its immense size easily holds the largest number of patrons and seems filled to capacity.  Just as many people lounge along the polished wooden deck as are in the water.  A group of youngsters of various races scamper past, competing to see who will be first to the diving platform.</description>
    <position x="-28" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb platform" destination="336" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pool" destination="337" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Public Baths, Calidarium">
    <description>Steam rises out of the oval shaped bath causing the tiled floors, marble benches and mosaic lined walls to sweat.  Instead of entering the water, most patrons choose to sit on the benches or talk in small groups at the tables as they soak up the the sauna-like effect.  The bathers who do brave the boiling water jump in to get a quick dip before moving on to another room.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bath" destination="347" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Tarsha's Emporium" note="Tarsha's Emporium|Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The tinkling of door bells and the rich scents of dried flowers and leather fill this fashionable shop.  The walls, covered with a pale blue silk, are offset by dark wood furniture and reflected back through the massive framed mirror that stands at the far end of the shop.  Gold gilded cherubs posed above the mirror look down on the room below.</description>
    <position x="122" y="700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="The Baron's Table, Dining Room" note="Baron's Table" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The dark polished wood of the paneling and tables provides a warm glow to the elegantly furnished dining room.  Throne-like chairs with pale yellow silk damask seats are arranged around each table.  Glazed windows look out over the town walls, the milky rippled glass turning the surrounding hills and groves into waves of rainbow images.  The susurration of quiet conversations rises and falls as diners linger over their meals.</description>
    <position x="82" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Therenborough, Carousel Square">
    <description>A massive conical building rises from the cobbles at the square's center, its snowy alabaster surfaces gleaming brilliantly.  A bejeweled mosaic set above an oval doorway reads THE CAROUSEL.</description>
    <position x="122" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oval doorway" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="360" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Therenborough, The Carousel" note="Carousel|Vault" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Exotic tapestries of every possible description drape the wall ringing the Carousel's core.  A circular roof supports a vast framework of iron and timbers rising to the building's apex.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights within the structure form the strikingly complex and beautiful mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="122" y="830" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go desk" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="349" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Therenborough, Carousel Desk" note="Lost and Found" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A white marble desk spans the width of the western wall.  Highly polished brass lanterns hang from the ceiling, and the floor behind the desk is covered in sparkling white tile.</description>
    <position x="132" y="830" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Therenborough, Carousel Booth">
    <description>A polished steel lever protrudes from the eastern wall of the small, lunat-panelled room, flanking a steel door to the north.</description>
    <position x="112" y="830" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Therenborough, Carousel Chamber">
    <description>A sturdy vault, set in the back wall, stands ready for your use.  The floor is covered in a thick burgundy carpet, and the walls are paneled in polished lunat.  Looking at the back wall, you notice a tiny gap between it and the rest of the room.  On the wall to the left hangs a colorful tapestry.</description>
    <position x="102" y="830" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Therenborough, Claymore Court">
    <description>Beneath the spreading branches of an old chestnut tree stands a small cottage, its timbers bursting through whitewashed wattle and daub.  Densely cultivated gardens surround the dwelling, and bunches of hulnik grass and plovik stems hang in the front windows.</description>
    <position x="162" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small cottage" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Therenborough, Horseman's Run">
    <description>Tall structures of marble, sparkling in various pale hues, can be seen off to the northeast.  Although these magnificent buildings are imposing on their own, they are dwarfed by the towering castle walls that they surround.  The murmur of friendly conversation and the shout of a successfully bartered deal can be heard from beyond a high hedgerow that separates the Market Square from this bridle path.</description>
    <position x="259" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hall" destination="351" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Therenborough, Quadrangle" note="Quadrangle">
    <description>The vast quadrangle is paved with blocks of silver-speckled granite and bordered by rows of marble columns interspersed with matching benches.  Throngs of people congregate in this popular gathering spot.  Every so often an animated speaker addresses the crowds from the public orator's stand.</description>
    <position x="222" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Theren Keep, Approach" note="Theren Keep|Keep|drawbridge">
    <description>A timeworn gatehouse rises to the north, its twin towers bearing conspicuous scars from a long-standing siege.  The stone and mortar look patched in key places where catapult stones bombarded the stout facade, but there's no indication the gates have ever been breached.  A stagnant semi-filled moat impedes further progress towards the Keep, and the sickly-green slime bubbling inside looks and smells like it dates back to the Old Empire.</description>
    <position x="222" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood drawbridge" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Therenborough, Claymore Court">
    <description>Alabaster marble columns designate the entrance to the busy Market Square.  The throngs of people moving in and out of the square represent all walks of life.  Fledgling paladins, still awkward in their heavy plate armor, mingle with weathered farmers wearing cloth caps, stout boots and tweed jackets.  A silk banner, decorated with paintings that depict items sold in the marketplace, ripples and flutters in the gentle breeze.</description>
    <description>Pale marble columns stand out against the night sky, designating the entrance to the Market Square.  The thriving marketplace remains open all night, with noble knights mingling with young couples walking hand in hand.  A silk banner, decorated with paintings that depict items sold in the market, ripples and flutters in the night breeze.</description>
    <position x="282" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go market square" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Therenborough, Horseman's Run">
    <description>The bridle path connects the elegant business district along Rutilor Boulevard with the more rustic Lower East Way with its compacted dirt surface and whitewashed fences.  Several hitching posts provide a convenient spot for travelers to leave their horses while they attend to business along either pedestrian thoroughfare.</description>
    <position x="342" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Therenborough, Tournament Lane">
    <description>Connecting the town's center with the massive stone wall that surrounds it, this rustic patch slices through a landscape lush with flowering shrubs and small trees that help to muffle some of the noise wafting from the nearby cosmopolitan streets surrounding Theren Keep.  Roughly carved from stone, a water trough sits off to the side waiting to slake the thirst of paladins and their mounts as they travel in search of jousting competitions.</description>
    <position x="322" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Therenborough, Tournament Lane">
    <description>Branching off from the main thoroughfare, this hoof-beaten path is wide enough to accommodate the mounted squads patrolling the town's border.  Wild rose bushes climb the front of a whitewashed stable, their pink petals not only decorating the building's stark exterior but also perfuming a variety of natural odors wafting from animals resting within its close quarters.  Off in the distance, equestrians wearing uniforms of the Therengian Cavalry march in and out of a stacked log outpost.</description>
    <position x="342" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go whitewashed stable" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Therenborough, Tournament Lane">
    <description>Crowning the widened path is an arch carved from alabaster, its somewhat translucent white stone standing out against the rural landscape.  Planted at the base of a brightly colored sign, large mounds of blue-green hosta hold their formal shape despite the occasional trampling by mischievous children hiding behind the thick leaves in an attempt to get a peek at their favorite champion riding by.</description>
    <position x="362" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="182" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Therenborough, Rutilor Boulevard">
    <description>The wide boulevard paved with granite slabs stretches northeastward, providing a home for the town's official buildings.  The overall impression here is of elegance with beautiful marble structures that are graceful and well-proportioned in appearance.  The tall, leafy trees planted along the street enhance the gleaming expanses of pale marble.</description>
    <position x="342" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office" destination="322" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Therenborough, Rutilor Boulevard">
    <description>As the granite thoroughfare curves through this part of the city, it passes in front of the Alliance of Exchange building.  Created of serene blue marble, the aura of dignity surrounding it is somewhat disturbed by the constant throngs bustling in and out of a pair of towering acanth doors.  Knots of traders stand together quietly talking under the shade of neighboring trees while others make their way inside, eager to sell their pelts and goods.</description>
    <position x="342" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth doors" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Therenborough, Lower East Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Skinny homes of rough-hewn wood crowd each other for space along this narrow earthen streetfront.  An occasional granite cobblestone from the paving farther to the west lies embedded in the ground, ready to trip the unwary.  From the east comes the slightest hint of smoke to tickle the nostrils of those who pass.</description>
    <position x="382" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go thatched cottage" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Therenborough, Shop Yard">
    <description>The pressure of countless boots, hooves and sandals has beaten the dirt yard of a shingle-roofed general store to a hard packed finish.  Two squared wooden pillars frame a heavy pine door leading into the shop.</description>
    <position x="382" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Therenborough, Lower East Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A low-lying stone wall surrounds a wide, grassy yard shaded by a large oak tree.  Underneath the tree stands an anvil and forge which mark the nearby building as the home of the local blacksmith.</description>
    <position x="402" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Therenborough, Lower East Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>An unpaved circular plaza lies to the east, dominated by a two-story chapel surrounded by a low wall of rough-hewn stone.  The wooden homes, stuffed one against another here at the edge of the plaza, thin somewhat to the west.</description>
    <position x="422" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Therenborough, Chapel Plaza West" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A small two story chapel, surrounded by a rough-hewn stone wall, rises here in the midst of a circular dirt plaza.  A double iron gate, swung wide and pegged open with two wooden stakes, beckons visitors to enter the confines of the walls to worship.  Several side streets meet at this central point to meander off to other parts of the town.</description>
    <position x="442" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Therenborough, Chapel Plaza South" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The stone wall surrounding the town chapel has crumbled in one corner.  Many of its stones appear to be missing, most likely carried away by peasants to be used elsewhere.  A sloppy patchwork of mortar has been slapped to the wall, but much of that has fallen too and lies scattered about the ground.</description>
    <position x="502" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Therenborough, Narrow Alleyway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A sharp bend in the street offers passage to a narrow alleyway which stretches off to the south and beyond.  A teeming mob of ramshackle homes have gathered along the way, jostling each other for space in what is obviously the poorer section of town.  To the northeast rises a small chapel surrounded by a low stone wall.</description>
    <position x="482" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Therenborough, Narrow Alleyway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The street takes a sharp bend here, turning east into a narrow alleyway and widening to the north before disappearing around a bend to the northeast.  Most of the homes here are of mud brick and thatch rather than the more precious wood plank in evidence elsewhere in the village.</description>
    <position x="482" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Therenborough, Alley's End">
    <description>Dominating this end of the alley is a looming pile of boards which could only be called a building by the most optimistic of persons.  Nailed together at almost every angle imaginable, the motley assortment of timber used to build the place looks as if it could be blown over by the sneeze of a sickly Halfling.  What seems to be intended as the building's door lies ajar at a bizzare angle, as if it were never really meant to be closed but instead was added as an artistic afterthought.</description>
    <position x="502" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rickety door" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Therenborough, Chapel Plaza East" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The main thoroughfare of the city merges here with a wide earth plaza, in the midst of which stands a wall of rough-hewn stone.  The second story of the Therenborough chapel peeks over the top of the wall, as if eager to escape its stony confines.</description>
    <position x="562" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Therenborough, Pikeman Lane">
    <description>A cheery two-story building of sturdy oak stands tall here at the far eastern reaches of the city.  Grey smoke wafts pleasantly from a red brick chimney rising above the roof at the north wall, and in the glass windows of the second story can be seen curtains of simple white linen.  Thick double doors of smoke-stained wood stand swung wide at the south wall, welcoming travelers to enter from the street.</description>
    <position x="602" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Therenborough, Chapel Plaza North" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A neatly-trimmed hedgerow abuts the stone wall surrounding the chapel here in the town center.  To the northwest runs a small side street lined with houses of mud brick and thatch, while to the south and southeast one can rejoin the main city thoroughfare.</description>
    <position x="502" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Therenborough, Alabaster Road" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Nestled here among simple homes of wood and thatch is a slightly larger building of worked stone.  Wide steps lead up to a porch of virgin pine boards.  Hanging over the porch is a small sign which marks the place as the home of the local midwife.</description>
    <position x="482" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide steps" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Therenborough, Alabaster Road" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Neat rows of small country homes line both sides of the street.  A building of dark pine squats in the dusty cul-de-sac at the end of the lane, well-ordered displays of wooden furniture gracing its porch.</description>
    <position x="462" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark building" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Therenborough, Rutilor Boulevard">
    <description>The Bank of Therenborough sits at precise right angles to the street here.  The once sharp edges of its steps have been muted by the footfalls of countless customers, and time has weathered the marble walls to a faded blue.  A towering statue of Kertigen stands in a welcoming pose at the entrance, forever fastening his gaze upon the crowds hurrying beneath his feet.  The building thrums to the pulse of commerce as people arrive to settle their financial affairs.</description>
    <position x="382" y="640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble entrance" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Therenborough, Rutilor Boulevard">
    <description>The august walls of Telomin Hall rise before you.  Formed of massive limestone blocks joined without the aid of mortar, the building boasts slim colonnades supporting a grey slate roof.  A shining silver sword has been mounted over the hall entrance in honor of an unknown paladin hero.  Sounds from the nearby commercial district are strangely muted as if afraid to disturb the serious matters taking place behind these walls.</description>
    <position x="402" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go telomin hall" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Therenborough, Rutilor Boulevard">
    <description>Tangled vines of honeysuckle embrace the garden gate while low-growing maugwort bushes line either side of the avenue.  Shaded by tall oak trees, a low garden bench invites passersby to sit and enjoy the fragrances of sirese flowers and honeysuckle wafting through the air.  A white gate leads into the depths of the garden.</description>
    <position x="402" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandstone building" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garden gate" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Therenborough, Rutilor Boulevard">
    <description>Abruptly, the boulevard comes to a halt, its granite paving making way for the cobblestones of the plaza facing the Amphitheatre.  Large enough to almost hold its own against the bulk of the nearby Keep, the Amphitheatre is where warriors test their prowess, create a reputation or lose their lives.  People hurry towards its marble arches, eager to fight or watch blood spill on the sand.  The cool marble sides and columns contradict the conflict that has been its livelihood for generations.</description>
    <position x="462" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble amphitheatre" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Theren Keep, Gatehouse">
    <description>Buttressed towers stand to either side, housing the drawbridge mechanisms and a half-raised portcullis rusted in place from years of disuse.  The main keep looms to the north beyond an open courtyard, stretching northwest toward some exterior buildings and east where a small grove of trees brightens the landscape.</description>
    <position x="242" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood drawbridge" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Theren Keep, Sicle Grove" note="Sicle Grove">
    <description>Lush grass and tiny wildflowers blanket the ground beneath a small grove of sicle trees, offering a pleasant diversion from the stark backdrop of Theren Keep.  A well-branched young sicle tree is securely rooted beside an old gnarled stump, a symbolic motion by the Baron and his garrison to reestablish the honorable name of Theren and restore the keep to its former glory.</description>
    <position x="262" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Theren Keep, Bailey">
    <description>While the walls of Theren Keep bear telltale scars of siege and war, a newly-constructed ballista assumes the charge of her inner defenses.  Skeins of twisted cord notch the weapon's deadly ammunition -- a half score of long, razor-sharp arrows aimed southward should the mighty gatehouse fall to attackers.  A tall wooden rack contains more lethal shafts beside a crumpled tarpaulin, used to protect the ballista during inclement weather.</description>
    <position x="242" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Theren Keep, Bailey">
    <description>An aging heavy catapult lies abandoned at this junction in the courtyard, with only a broad, wooden frame and broken crossbeam to distinguish it as a siege engine.  A junk pile near the outer rampart reveals the splintered catapult arm and its water-logged skeins, useless now, but at one time capable of raining death far beyond the barony's walls in the form of massive boulders or fiery concoctions.</description>
    <position x="222" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Theren Keep, Bailey">
    <description>The persistent sounds of hooves clomping on solid earth and of neighing signals the presence of the Baron's stables.  A deep-rutted path leads north through patches of dry grass, and a small tower hovers to the east, guarding the stone entryway.</description>
    <position x="182" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go baron's stables" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Lasa Morit Livery, Stable Yard" note="Lurellan">
    <description>A slight haze of red dust coats the split rails of the small paddock connecting a long thatch-roofed stable to a squat red brick office.  Standing in the shadow of a lone tree, a small herd of horses of varying shade and size patiently whisk away flies with their tails.  One battle-hardened horse remains alone near the water trough, stomping imperiously as he glances repeatedly toward the gate.</description>
    <description>Shadowy forms moving restlessly near the split rails of the small paddock connecting a long thatch-roofed stable to a squat red brick office bear little resemblance to horses, until one of them whickers a soft greeting.  A stray beam of light cast through the stable's open door rests on the form of a battle-hardened horse keeping a lonely vigil through the night.</description>
    <position x="162" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rail gate" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stable" destination="326" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Theren Keep, Bailey">
    <description>The dirt trail gradually turns to mud as it passes a small shed protruding from the western parapet, and a tall, fractured rampart lingers to the north, opposing the parapet's even crenellations with jagged edges that bruise the daytime sky.</description>
    <description>The dirt trail gradually turns to mud as it passes a small shed protruding from the western parapet, and a tall, fractured rampart lingers to the north, opposing the parapet's even crenellations with jagged edges that bruise the nighttime sky.</description>
    <description>The dirt trail gradually turns to mud as it passes a small shed protruding from the western parapet, and a tall, fractured rampart lingers to the north, opposing the parapet's even crenellations with jagged edges that bruise the nighttime sky.  Towards the east caravan tracks lead to the Trader stables.</description>
    <description>The dirt trail gradually turns to mud as it passes a small shed protruding from the western parapet, and a tall, fractured rampart lingers to the north, opposing the parapet's even crenellations with jagged edges that bruise the daytime sky.  Towards the east caravan tracks lead to the Trader stables.</description>
    <position x="182" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small shed" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="320" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Theren Keep, Storage Shed" note="Storage Shed|Shed">
    <description>Boxes, crates and barrels of all sizes line the walls from corner to corner midst a thick layer of dust and unsightly rat droppings.  An uprooted floorboard reveals a possible underground passage, but the opening is far too small for even a Halfling.</description>
    <position x="162" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Theren Keep, Bailey">
    <description>The outer wall runs diagonally from the northwest parapet, turning southward as it skirts the main courtyard.  Here, the upper rampart has fallen into complete ruin -- first weakened by enemy bombardment, then broken off in the final assault and toppled into the moat.  In spite of the damage, a rickety wooden ladder still leans against the crumbling wall-walk.</description>
    <position x="182" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Theren Keep, Ruined Wall-Walk">
    <description>Crumbled stone shifts underfoot with granulated mortar, but the rampart's sheer width makes it safe enough that a drunken bard would have trouble slipping over the side.  An awful stench rises from below, and glancing into the moat you'd guess this is where most of the Keep's refuse is discarded.</description>
    <position x="162" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="none" move="jump moat" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Theren Keep, Entrance">
    <description>A squat drum-tower overlooks the forebuilding, warding the entrance with ruthless crossbow fire from arrow loops along its battle-scarred walls.  Ascending through engraved marble arches, a series of chiseled stone steps leads into the Baron's resurging stronghold.</description>
    <position x="222" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone steps" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Theren Keep, Forebuilding" note="Forebuilding">
    <description>At first glance, this chamber appears quite innocuous.  Grey stone steps lead down to the courtyard, and huge, black walnut doors welcome guests like lethargic watchmen.  However, machicolations disguised as lion's gullets and cleverly concealed murder holes reaffirm this stronghold shall always be prepared to defend itself.</description>
    <position x="222" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go huge doors" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Theren Keep, Entry Hall">
    <description>Twin rows of gleaming plate armor stand along the lengthy hallway, resplendent in shimmering surcoats of blue and gold.  A heavy wooden beam protrudes from a nearby pedestal, placed so that it won't disrupt the pristine view, but still close at hand should the entrance need to be barred.  The polished marble floor radiates a soft, blue luminescence as it ripples northward into flickering shadows, like moonlight on the open water.</description>
    <position x="222" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go huge doors" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Theren Keep, Gallery">
    <description>A row of evenly spaced torches burns brightly to illuminate the way along this long gallery that stretches to the east.  A large tarpaulin, nailed to the wall, has replaced the old tapestries.  Blue-marbled tiles lead southward through a well-lit entry hall.</description>
    <position x="222" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Theren Keep, Gallery">
    <description>Voices and laughter echo throughout the gallery, originating from a granite archway and the keep's central hall beyond.  A majestic standard hangs upon the wall in plain view, so that all who enter or exit the Baron's court shall know who it is that offers them hearth and hospitality.</description>
    <position x="242" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go side passage" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite archway" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Theren Keep, Gallery">
    <description>The corridor halts before a drystone wall, recently constructed in a manner unlike that of the surrounding masonry.  A broken shovel litters the ground, quite out of place considering the rich tapestries and extravagant weapon displays to either side.  Southwards, a crude stairway leads down to the lower levels.</description>
    <position x="382" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crude stairway" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Theren Keep, Corridor">
    <description>Spanning roughly ten feet across, this dim corridor ranges southward to a guard's antechamber.  Thousands of opaque tiles form a vivid mural illustrating the keep before it was razed, silhouetted against a clear blue sky and the rising sun.</description>
    <position x="242" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gallery" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Theren Keep, Ward" note="Ward">
    <description>Light and heavy crossbows hang from a convenient rack, each weapon accompanied with a score of deadly quarrels.  A simple table and chair are the only other furniture in this spartan guard post, yielding to a lengthy corridor northwards.</description>
    <position x="242" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone arch" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Theren Keep, Garrison Hall" note="Garrison Hall">
    <description>This expansive bay accommodates a score of professional soldiers, though ample space remains for twice that number if needs be.  Judging from the perfectly aligned cots and footlockers, the Captain of the Guard keeps his charges orderly and well-disciplined -- even mattresses reserved for infrequent mercenaries lay neatly in the corner.</description>
    <position x="242" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Theren Keep, Armory" note="Armory|Tad Deshon" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Greatswords, battle axes and maces join an immense inventory of weapons staged around the room, and elaborate suits of plate and chain await champions bold enough to don them in Theren's name.  Somehow, a small writing desk littered with scrolls and ledgers squeezes midst the armaments, where a scribe reluctantly logs every piece of equipment.</description>
    <position x="262" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Second Floor, Hallway">
    <description>Thin sunlight strays through a rough, cross-shaped arrow loop, betraying a flurry of dust stirred up by your movements.  A sturdy oak door leads out to the parapet, and a spiral staircase winds downward to the first floor.</description>
    <description>Thin moonlight strays through a rough, cross-shaped arrow loop, betraying a flurry of dust stirred up by your movements.  A sturdy oak door leads out to the parapet, and a spiral staircase winds downward to the first floor.</description>
    <position x="322" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Second Floor, Hallway">
    <description>Dull, featureless stone marks this interminable hallway, and a glimpse in either direction promises little if nothing better.  A flight of short steps ascends to the keep's upper echelons, straining half the corridor's length just to reach the next floor.</description>
    <position x="322" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb short steps" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Theren Keep, Hall of Knights" note="Hall of Knights|Knights">
    <description>Heads, horns and furs from beasts both mundane and monstrous decorate the freshly-painted walls of the Hall of Knights, where the Baron's warriors congregate when not feasting in the Great Hall or sparring in the courtyard.  The castellan's office looms beyond an acanth table strewn with local maps and games of strategy, and the keep's chapel lingers to the east like a dull afterthought.</description>
    <position x="322" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go castellan's office" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small closet" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Theren Keep, Chapel" note="Chadatru|pilgrim's badge|altar|shrine-2-03" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Sunlight is welcomed into the Chapel of Chadatru by the rainbow colors of a stained glass window set in the eastern wall.  A richly embroidered tapestry serves as a backdrop to a polished ash altar carved with the image of a golden lion upon its surface.  Simple oak benches have been placed here so the devout can come and observe the first rays of dawn blaze into existence across the face of the window, casting its fiery light across the altar of the god of justice.</description>
    <description>A polished ash altar has been placed here so the devout can come and observe the god of justice.</description>
    <description>Tapered candles provide a warm light for the Chapel of Chadatru despite the dark of night.  Even in the dim light the stained glass window can be viewed.  A richly embroidered tapestry serves as a backdrop to a polished ash altar carved with the image of a golden lion upon its surface.  Oak benches have been placed here so the devout can come and observe the first rays of dawn blaze into existence across the face of the window and cast its fiery light across the altar of the god of justice.</description>
    <description>A polished ash altar has been placed here so the devout can come and observe the god of justice.</description>
    <position x="342" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk curtain" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Southwest Tower, Castellan's Office" note="GL Paladin|Cleworth|RS Paladin|tithe box" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Everything in this room speaks of a sharp, well-organized mind.  Not a yard of floor space goes unoccupied, and the castellan wastes no effort on frivolous artwork or tapestries.  Instead, books and ledgers line the shelves, all neatly aligned according to size, and a wide desk bears a detailed floor plan of the Keep.</description>
    <position x="302" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Theren Keep, Garderobe">
    <description>The knights enjoy a private latrine reserved for their use.  Fresh herbs are scattered about the floor that give up their scent when crushed underfoot.  Bundles of straw lay handy and a half-filled wooden bucket of water stands to one side of some overturned chamber pots.  While the narrow chute has been scrubbed as far as is possible, the rest is mercifully obstructed from view.</description>
    <position x="322" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Southeast Tower, Aumbry">
    <description>Once used as a storage place for ceremonial vessels, the aumbry now serves as a home for rats and other vermin.  Dusty cobwebs flutter in every corner, anchored by dessicated husks of spider's prey, and in a few instances, the spiders themselves.</description>
    <position x="342" y="270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Second Floor, Barricade">
    <description>Sturdy wooden planks nailed across the northern wall of this room block off all access to the ruined Northeast tower.  A large tarpaulin stretches across the wooden barricade to keep the worst of the wind and moisture out.</description>
    <position x="362" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Third Floor, Hallway" note="Third Floor|3rd Floor">
    <description>Colorful frescos beautify the walls with bright pastels and soft earthtones, quelling the drab ambience of a stairwell angling down to the second floor.  An assortment of gold and indigo curtains introduces a broad balcony to the east, overlooking the great hall but largely concealed from the occupants below.</description>
    <position x="382" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go broad balcony" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark stairwell" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Third Floor, Hallway">
    <description>The southwest tower harbors a solid, steel-bound door, bolted shut with broad bands of metal.  Its dark grey fixtures pulse in and out of shadow as if suffused with a restless spirit, foregoing the Starry Road to fulfill a tragic life.  Eastwards, the hallway ventures through the infamous guest quarter, while blithe embellishments illuminate the north.</description>
    <position x="382" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Third Floor, Guest Hall">
    <description>A fine oil painting distinguishes the quaint foyer to one of several apartments reserved for honored guests.  Despite slender arrow loops housed in the embattlement, the trappings here look every bit as comfortable as the finest inn in Riverhaven.</description>
    <position x="402" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth door" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Third Floor, Guest Hall">
    <description>The scent of recently painted wood lingers where a restored architrave has replaced a severely damaged doorway.  The sturdy door is made of carved deobar, graced with a shiny, new brass doorknob.  Fresh rush matting muffles every footstep ensuring that guests are not disturbed as bustling servants go about their daily chores.</description>
    <position x="422" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Third Floor, Guest Hall">
    <description>Woven rush matting cushions your footsteps as the hallway veers past the southeast tower and west beyond the common guest suites.  Framed paintings of charming pastoral scenes line the walls and a fine porcelain vase, complete with fresh flowers stands on a marble pedestal.</description>
    <position x="442" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sana'ati door" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Third Floor, Hallway">
    <description>A side balcony to the west provides a lofty perch for spying on the great hall, visible through a tasseled silk curtain fluttering from a burnished brass rod.  The sconces along the wall remain empty for one reason or another, throwing the walkway into near darkness.</description>
    <position x="442" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go side balcony" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Third Floor, Barricade">
    <description>Sturdy wooden planks nailed across the northern wall of this room block off all access to the ruined Northeast tower.  A large tarpaulin stretches across the wooden barricade to keep the worst of the wind and moisture out.</description>
    <position x="442" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Third Floor, East Balcony">
    <description>The damp of the stone wall is somewhat mollified by the vivid tapestries that grace this balcony.  The flickering light of a single torch sheds a pool of feeble light onto the gleaming mahogany deck.  A handsome banister gleams with freshly applied polish, the smooth lines of its curved posts testifying to its newness.  Down below, the hall thrives with newfound effervescence.</description>
    <position x="422" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Southeast Tower, Royal Guest Suite" note="Royal Guest Suite">
    <description>More queen's parlor than baron's guest chamber, this comfortable apartment could kindle a romantic spark between the most frigid couple.  Rich blue-gold curtains frame a shuttered window, and an exquisite sandalwood dresser offers sumptuous edibles fresh from the kitchen.  Lush floral carpets shroud the stone floor embellished with soft pink rose petals, while a comfy loft lounges below a skylight of crystalline glass polished to a breathtaking sheen.</description>
    <position x="442" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go comfy loft" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sana'ati door" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Southeast Tower, Loft">
    <description>Sunlight filters through panes of shimmering crystalline glass, spanning the entire roof of this secluded loft.  A sloping bedframe swept with layered down comforters provides guests with a luxuriant cradle for romantic diversions or a simple hideaway to enjoy the pristine skyward view.</description>
    <description>The night sky is visible through panes of shimmering crystalline glass, spanning the entire roof of this secluded loft.  A sloping bedframe swept with layered down comforters provides guests with a luxuriant cradle for romantic diversions or a simple hideaway to enjoy the pristine skyward view.</description>
    <position x="452" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Theren Keep, Guest Chamber">
    <description>Smelling of lavender and polish, this room bears the hallmarks of refurbishment -- fresh paint and obviously new furniture.  The four-poster bed is resplendent with satin covers, plump pillows, freshly laundered bed linen, and small petal-filled muslin satchels tied with a silk ribbon.  An elegant high-backed chair stands in one corner next to a small glass case.  A candelabrum with tall candles stands on a glossy cabinet with brass hinges and handles.</description>
    <position x="422" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Theren Keep, Guest Chamber">
    <description>More honeymoon suite than common guest room, the romantic ambience tantalizes your senses.  Freshly laden herbs cover the floor, their sweet scent mingled with jasmine and lavender, and a cozy fireplace contributes to the heady aroma, crackling at the foot of a large canopied bed.  Soft satin pillows shimmer in the light, awaiting their lover's embrace.</description>
    <position x="402" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth door" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Third Floor, West Balcony">
    <description>This elegant balcony stands midway between the tiled ceiling and marble floor of the great hall.  Seasoned mahogany enhances the decor with its deep, reddish brown hue, and luxurious chairs offer the hospitality one would anticipate in a prince's theatre, much less a stone-walled keep.  Nestled in shadow, you have an excellent view of the hall below.</description>
    <position x="402" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Third Floor, Hallway">
    <description>The passageway halts before a reinforced ironwood door with elaborate figures etched around the frame.  Faint scuffmarks blemish the door's threshold, and a stout lock ensures the northwest tower remains offlimits to all but the Baron himself.</description>
    <position x="382" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Theren Keep, Moat" note="Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A mound of slimy-green refuse coagulates here, providing a shaky foothold and limited view beyond the moat's filthy walls.  The gatehouse looms overhead like a gaping maw, and a narrow ledge leads upwards through a patch of slippery moss.  Brackish water oozes east and west, shallow enough that even a Halfling could wade through without much difficulty.</description>
    <position x="222" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Standing well over twice the height of a Human, the moat's stone walls muffle all sounds except the faint trickle of water.  The mildewed waterlines reflect the barony's decline and seep lower with each passing year, falling into decay and corruption like the wizard-kings of the Seven Crown Empire.</description>
    <position x="422" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thriving stoneworts nestle amongst hardened lime deposits against the wall, their whorly stalks striving forth in defiance of the brackish water.  Intermittent splashes disturb the silence, and darkness blankets the channel which curves around the southeastern edge of the Keep.</description>
    <position x="462" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A nearly imperceptible current flows from north to south, bringing with it a nagging infestation of hungry mosquitos.  Bobbing along the surface, a discarded chamberpot teeters to one side, revealing a dark, foul-looking liquid.</description>
    <position x="462" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thick vines entangle this portion of the keep, from the topmost parapet to the murky waters swirling afoot.  The long, twisted tendrils obscure the stonework completely, gathering at the waterline where striders and beetles skitter between the leaves.  Oddly, the temperature seems somewhat cooler in this location.</description>
    <position x="462" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The moat halts abruptly, obstructed by remnants of what was once the northeast Keep.  Even from this poor vantage point, the devastation is frightening.  The northeast tower lies sideways across the moat, as if uprooted from the ground by a wrathful god and abandoned like a child's toy.  Undoubtedly, no conventional army wrought this awful destruction.</description>
    <position x="462" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A massive catapult stone protrudes from the water like the bald pate of a Gor'Tog giant.  Its unsavory green hue pales in comparison to the blackened mildew that plagues the embattlement, spreading upwards through imperfections in the stonework and fractures left by siege missile fire.</description>
    <position x="122" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Frothy white globules erupt from an unknown source beneath the muck and drift slowly in all directions, tainted with grime and residue.  An underwater current sucks them under near a curve in the wall, but they pop right up with stubborn buoyancy.</description>
    <position x="62" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A luminescent gel-like substance coats the stone embattlement along its roughly-hewn face, pulsing softly with an eerie glow.  The mass tapers off southward, but appears much more prevalent northward where garbage chokes the passageway to just a few feet.</description>
    <position x="62" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Theren Keep, Moat" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Discarded rubble, lumber and common trash compose a daunting heap to the northeast, blocking the moat entirely in that direction.  The combination of filthy garbage and stagnant water elevates the stench here to heights no mortal should ever experience, and the narrow, slime-ridden passage southwards looks like it offers little, if any, relief.</description>
    <position x="62" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb pile of debris" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Theren Keep, Rubble" note="Moat">
    <description>Broken masonry and trash clog the moat at this junction, forming a makeshift dam that prevents stagnant water from spoiling the northern Keep.  The upper ramparts stand in ruin, clearly the source of all the rubble, but still high enough to thwart intruders despite its dilapidated condition.  Unlike the dank, water-logged channel southwards, the moat looks dry and solid to the east.</description>
    <position x="62" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Theren Keep, Dry Moat" note="Dry Moat">
    <description>Long iron spikes line the moat's bottom, spaced far enough apart that a nimble thief could walk between them, but sure to impale any fool falling from above.  Gazing upwards, a dark tower pierces the nighttime sky, soft torchlight flickering from its windows.</description>
    <description>Long iron spikes line the moat's bottom, spaced far enough apart that a nimble thief could walk between them, but sure to impale any fool falling from above.  Gazing upwards, a dark stone tower pierces the skyline like a lance, culminating in a majestic standard of royal blue and gold.</description>
    <position x="79" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb pile of debris" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Theren Keep, Dry Moat">
    <description>The moat descends through a gap in the foundation, the site of a massive cave-in where attackers undermined the castle's embattlements.  Ramparts once thought impenetrable lie about in shambles, blocking further progress beyond the exposed mining tunnel.</description>
    <position x="99" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Theren Keep, Mining Tunnel" note="Mining Tunnel">
    <description>Crumbling stone slabs rise from the earth like misshapen gravemarkers, lamenting their downfall from what was once a mighty bastion.  Other fragments choke the very mining tunnel that induced their ruin, as a final act of defiance in a war the descendants of long-dead soldiers can't even recall.</description>
    <position x="119" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slender gap" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Roughly carved stone walls meet the hand cut blocks of the keep's outer wall to the south.  Moisture creeps down the tunnel walls to gather in a pool on the floor and begin its journey deeper into into the darkess.  An opening, half-heartedly covered up, appears to have led out at one time but is now sealed.</description>
    <description>Roughly carved stone walls meet the hand cut blocks of the keep's outer wall to the south.  Moisture creeps down the tunnel walls to gather in a pool on the floor and begin its journey deeper into the darkess.  An opening, half-heartedly covered up, appears to have led out at one time but is now sealed.</description>
    <position x="262" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slender gap" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Northwest Tower, The Old Study">
    <description>Untouched since the days of the late Baron, the room and its furnishings preserve the shape of a life.  A portrait depicts a noble couple, and their clear affection has an appeal that aging canvas and dustry frame cannot dim.  Some shelves stand near a great oaken desk at which the Baron spent many a day, week, month, and year.</description>
    <position x="402" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Northwest Tower, a Bedchamber">
    <description>Although stately in proportion and design, it seems a lonely forgotten corner of the Keep, hung with yellowing dust covers and stripped of its former glory.  Faded patches on the floor and walls hint at tapestries, pictures and rugs that once clothed the room.  All that remains of the old furnishings is a large brass bed and some carved sana'ati dressers, too bulky for easy removal.</description>
    <position x="402" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden hatch" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Northwest Tower, Spire">
    <description>From this lofty vantage point, the Baron oversees nearly all of Therengia -- from the craggy western mountains to the banks of the Faldesu River where the towns of Riverhaven and her smaller sister, Langenfirth, ply their fish and pelts.  City rooftops dot the landscape like tiles on a strategic boardgame, undisturbed by the moat's putrid stench far below.</description>
    <position x="402" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden hatch" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Theren Keep, Parapet" note="Parapet">
    <description>This particular corner of the parapet sulks below the northwest tower, rising overhead with all the majesty of an emperor's palace compared to the outer ramparts.  Unlike the weathered stone deck, the tower shows signs of half-hearted maintenance where mud and grime was scraped away by either reluctant servants or guards caught sleeping at their post.</description>
    <position x="342" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Theren Keep, Parapet">
    <description>The sound of boots striking stone echoes across the parapet whether you step or stand still.  Perhaps a despondent ghost or lone watchman, the source remains obscure though a clear line of sight bares the passageway in both directions.</description>
    <position x="342" y="190" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Theren Keep, Drum-Tower" note="Drum-Tower">
    <description>Disjointed boarding provides a makeshift roof over this squat drum-tower, the ancient wood half-charred to a brittle crisp.  Safeguarding the entrance and western courtyard, the embattlement provides fields of fire ranging beyond the outer ramparts, and machicolations to hinder assailants below.  If not for the keep's warlike implications, the picturesque view of the surrounding countryside might even be considered romantic.</description>
    <position x="342" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Theren Keep, Parapet">
    <description>A tiny bird's nest rests between two square-cut merlons, protected by a wooden shutter still dangling from a few arrow-riven splinters.  Almost laughable in this place of war, the nest's owner has gathered shreds of hay, cloth and fletching to build its new home, now an old souvenir of long-dead men and forgotten battles.</description>
    <position x="352" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Theren Keep, Ruined Parapet" note="Ruined Parapet">
    <description>Ages ago, the parapet encircled the northeast tower and continued south to protect the vulnerable flanks.  But now the walkway greets empty space where the tower once stood, its pitiful remnants strewn across the landscape a thousand times over by unfathomable powers.  Even time takes its toll in the aftermath, slowly eating away the weakened embattlements year after year.</description>
    <position x="362" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Theren Keep, Great Hall" note="Great Hall">
    <description>Seven columns span the chamber in a vast semi-circle of burnished black marble, the middle three curving around a broad dais while the outer pairs brace high, spectacular balconies.  Striking blue-gold banners and silken tapestries proclaim the royal colors of Therengia, but these minor ornaments pale before the tiled dome ceiling and a massive, seven-sided table which dominates the great hall.</description>
    <position x="202" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go well-lit corridor" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Theren Keep, Servant's Quarters" note="Servant's Quarters">
    <description>Modest but comfortable, the servants enjoy excellent quarters considering the restricted capacity of the keep.  Woven rush mats blanket the cold floor, and soft bedding comforts the hand-picked personal staff who retire here after toiling in the yards or kitchen.</description>
    <position x="202" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small closet" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Theren Keep, Garderobe" note="Garderobe">
    <description>Nothing more than a recess in the exterior wall, the latrine's cleanliness speaks well of the servants who attend it.  Sweet-scented jasmine mollifies the air, and a bucket of wash water stands prepared to flush out the chute.</description>
    <position x="182" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Theren Keep, Pantry" note="Pantry">
    <description>Barely large enough to accommodate the deobar table and matching cabinets for which it was built, this modest room serves as a staging area for elaborate feasts before their presentation.  Southwards, master chefs prepare renowned culinary recipes foretold by the mouth-watering aromas wafting from that direction.</description>
    <position x="242" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deobar door" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Theren Keep, Kitchen" note="Kitchen">
    <description>If the victuals taste as good as they smell, the current Baron follows his predecessor's tradition and keeps a lavish table.  Fresh fruits and vegetables garnish shelves along the wall, and strings of garlic, dried peppers and sausage dangle from handy hooks overhead.  A scarred cutting board proudly displays an array of dishes ranging from poultry to exotic seafood imported from the Eastern Seaboard.  Each dish bears the hallmark of the chef's culinary brilliance.</description>
    <position x="242" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Theren Keep, Buttery">
    <description>Deft craftsmen have fitted massive blocks of new stone, rebuilt cabinets, and added several shelves to these kitchens.  Only faint smudges of indelible black and mild bubbling at the edges of some of the old masonry show that these kitchens were anything other than pristine.  Large kegs of ale and tapped barrels of wine now line the eastern and northern walls.  Pitchers and ladles hang from long brass hooks, and the wide shelves are crammed with preserves and bottles.</description>
    <position x="282" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy ladder" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Theren Keep, Basement" note="Rutilor|Shrine2-15">
    <description>This end of the basement remains bare of supplies, excluding a dusty barrel tethered against the wall.  A trail of footprints marches back and forth between a storeroom door and a sturdy ladder, but seems loath to proceed north any further than necessary.</description>
    <position x="322" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy ladder" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Theren Keep, Storeroom">
    <description>Multiple levels of shelves expand the storage capacity here at least twofold, accommodating a stockpile of iron rations which could probably support the keep beyond a thirty-day siege.  Casks of low-grade wine settle in a far corner, as tasteless now as they'd be in a hundred years.</description>
    <position x="322" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Theren Keep, Basement">
    <description>Bricks, shovels, lime and mortar are piled near a bench with other mason's tools, and a stack of smoothly-cut blocks eclipses the basement's rusticated facade.  Additional space opens to the south, and a crude stairway climbs upward on dimpled steps which look like a blind man attacked them with a pick.</description>
    <position x="322" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low crack" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crude stairway" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Theren Keep, Sloping Tunnel">
    <description>Distorted sounds echo down this pock-marked tunnel, carried on a frigid draft whipping around your legs like a disgruntled poltergeist.  Flickering torches maintain a somber light as the passage descends sharply to the west.</description>
    <position x="302" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Theren Keep, Dungeon" note="Dungeon">
    <description>Chilling darkness permeates the chamber despite a glowing firepit, churning sparks like a mage's bungled spell.  A long wooden rack replete with chains and manacles awaits traitorous thieves or murderers, and heavy tongs, branding irons, and leather whips round out the torturer's modest collection.</description>
    <position x="282" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Theren Keep, Storeroom">
    <description>Sealed crates and pallets cram the room from floor to ceiling, most marked as one sundry item or another.  From lumber to furs to perfume, you can bet it's here if traders find it worth the journey to Riverhaven.</description>
    <position x="302" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>As you crawl along this passage, sharp rocks and gravel give way beneath your hands making it difficult to stay on all fours.  The low ceiling traps your breath and makes it hard to breathe, as you fight the sweat that runs off your brow and into your eyes.</description>
    <position x="322" y="50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low crack;stand" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice;stand" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Your knees ache with the pain of supporting the weight of you and all your gear.  Your clothing and other items snag on the razor-like edges created through the impact of metal picks on hard stone.  The passage sweeps from a northern darkness into a western darkness.</description>
    <position x="332" y="50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>As you move through this tunnel your mind pauses to reflect on the workers that dug it.  Just moving through them is difficult, the thought of having to chisel and pick inch by inch and then haul the debris out boggles the imagination.</description>
    <position x="332" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Ants seem to have taken up housekeeping in this part of the tunnel.  As they crawl about and over your hands you can't help but wonder how they could build a nest in what appears to be almost solid rock.  Light makes its way across the stone floor from a low opening to the west where the area on the other side offers an opportunity to stand and stretch.</description>
    <position x="332" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low opening" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>The rough stone walls of the tunnel are covered with a sticky substance that would seem to be spider's silk, were it not so inordinately thick and heavy.</description>
    <position x="322" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite arch" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low opening" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Dim light seeping through the gloom from the south provides a welcome alternative to navigating through these dark, web-riddled passages by touch.</description>
    <position x="312" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Weblike threads dangle in artistic patterns from the ceiling and walls.  The scent of dust, trapped in the sticky strands, hangs heavy in the air.  To the south an arch, now bricked up, silently tells of a time when this passage was part of the Keep's floorplan.</description>
    <position x="312" y="50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>To the northeast is the view of a richly decorated room that is quite out of place in these deep, dank tunnels reeking of wet soil and stone.  A glow of light filters through the iron door but reveals only darkness on the other side.</description>
    <position x="322" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble arch" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Time and abandonment have not destroyed the beauty of the lavish tapestries and thick carpets that adorn this underground room.  Designed to be self contained, the room contains a four poster bed, a pair of well cushioned chairs, a dining table and a polished mahogany dresser.  A bookcase large enough to hold several month's worth of reading material stands empty against the furthest wall of the room.</description>
    <position x="332" y="10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken door" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Gravel and rock piled about the floor almost hide the expensive tile laid on beneath the rubble.  A shredded tapestry hanging on the wall makes a feable attempt to hide a hole carved out of the rock near the floor.  Studying the tapestry for any indication of what it might have depicted in its better days, your eyes follow it to the ceiling where you notice another hole that is definitely out of reach.</description>
    <position x="342" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>High in the ceiling, troughs have been carved and a low burning fire finds residence there.  Obviously fed by some type of fuel, the light makes it very easy to see in what would normally be a pitch dark area.  Interestingly, there is a small opening in the lower portion of the north wall.</description>
    <position x="282" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Any movement to the west would require stepping on an odd looking slab embedded in the floor of the tunnel.  A large tapestry depicting a scene from a battle hangs on the wall.  A soft glow of light winds its way down the tunnel from the eastern end.</description>
    <position x="272" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Any movement to the east would require stepping on an odd looking slab of rock embedded in the floor of this passage.  A large tapestry depicting a battle of archers versus horsemen hangs on the wall of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="262" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>A caved-in section of the ceiling allows light and air to enter this section of the tunnel.  Sporadic patches of moss growing along the stone walls glisten with moisture in the dim illumination.</description>
    <position x="252" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Although not visible in the darkness, a steady dripping can be heard as water makes its way from the ceiling to the floor.  A slippery slime covers the floor, requiring each step to be made with caution.</description>
    <position x="252" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Broken strands of cobwebs lifted by an almost imperceptible current of air brush against mildewed walls.  A splintered oak door hangs precariously against the inner wall of a tunnel that splits to the east.</description>
    <position x="252" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>An oak door hangs in ruins against the stone wall, held in place by one twisted iron hinge.  A collection of rubble has been piled up against the tunnel wall to form what looks like a battle barricade.</description>
    <position x="262" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>A few weapons and armor lie on the floor, rust and decay being a testament to the years that have passed since they were last used in a battle.  A garrison banner, still attached to its staff, lies buried under rubble and mud.</description>
    <position x="272" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Brewer's vats and barrels reveal the past purpose of this room.  Crossbeams still support the pulleys once used to move barrels from the racks to transportation carts.  Tired and frayed ropes hang from the crossbeams, dangling just out of reach.</description>
    <position x="282" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Empty burlap sacks, long ago robbed of their grain by the smaller vermin that run these tunnels, lay rotting in the moisture of the floor.  The storage racks where the bags were once stored are now little more than splinters tossed about recklessly.</description>
    <position x="272" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Light seeps through small holes in the ceiling of the tunnel and reflects dimly off the stone walls.  Thin rivulets of water trickle along the rough passage floor, flowing slowly to the north.</description>
    <position x="252" y="50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>An old single hole privy fills the majority of this room.  A mirror frame with no mirror inside hangs crookedly on the wall.  Stone and pebbles are piled about the floor making it difficult to find a comfortable place to stand.  A large gaping hole in the ceiling is well out of reach.</description>
    <position x="342" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken door" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Old meat kegs, now empty, fill this room.  Still present on the stone floor is the salt that was once used to pack the meat.  Now dirty and caked, the salt has managed to keep the room completely dry which in turn has made this part of the tunnels one of the few areas without a mildew smell.  In a divot carved into the wall, sits a wooden box.  A hole, about three feet off the floor, has been bored in the stone wall.  The tunnel continues to the east but gets very low.</description>
    <position x="352" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>A low ceiling makes standing impossible in this section of the tunnel and the sharp edged stones of the roughly chipped passage makes crawling particularly uncomfortable. </description>
    <position x="362" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Sticky cobwebs cling to everything that passes through this tight space.  Faintly glowing patches of lichen provide the only source of natural light.</description>
    <position x="362" y="90" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>You find you must twist and turn your body to to maneuver through here.  There will be no turning around at this point, you must ever continue forward or back your way out.  So close are the walls that you can feel the heat of your own breath.  The cold stone is almost welcome as sweat drips from your brow.</description>
    <position x="362" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Any effort to stand in this portion of the tunnel would be futile.  Movement further north will require a bit of twisting and turning.  The passage to the south, just a few squirms away, appears to be a little more spacious.</description>
    <position x="352" y="110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Faint tracks of white ash run from the north and into a hole in the east wall.  A make-shift iron plate which once covered the small opening is now pryed up and allows entry.  Occasionally a slight whisp of fresh air floats in from the south cooling your face just briefly.</description>
    <position x="382" y="110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>Several bones and skulls lie scattered about the floor along with remnants of armor and weapons.  A fire to the northeast has scorched the walls about half way into this section of the tunnel.  White streaks of ash reveal something was drug across the floor and to the south.</description>
    <position x="382" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>A fire raged in this room at some time in the past.  A fire hot enough to turn the surrounding rock to a molten slag now cooled to glassy smoothness.  A few inches of grey ash on the floor is all that remains of whatever objects were once contained here.</description>
    <position x="372" y="90" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Cobwebs trail from shelf to box to rotting bag in this underground storage room. Several old chairs are stacked against one wall, and a pile of splintered crates blocks a portion of the exit to the north.</description>
    <position x="382" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small opening" destination="345" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>This portion of the tunnel has been converted into a storage area for the furniture of the keep that no longer has a home.  A good size hole now covered by a tapestry at one time must have provided access to the keep itself but it is now sealed.</description>
    <position x="372" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Estate Home Exteriors" note="Estate Home Exteriors|Exteriors" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Siding strips of fine woods adorn the walls of this elegant salesroom in a gleaming spectrum of colors and finishes.  An appealing scent of lemon oil imparts a sense of careful maintenance to the shop despite its unusual decor, and a thick tapestry rug underfoot contributes warmth and comfort to the atmosphere of refined elegance.</description>
    <position x="422" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Estate Entrances" color="#FF0000">
    <description>An expanse of glossy cedar floorboards spreads across the room, and heavy tapestries adorn the pristine white plaster walls.  Arranged on sturdy wrought iron racks in the center of the showroom, an assortment of magnificent doors invites the eye, their gleaming surfaces and polished fittings promising a stylish entrance to any country estate.</description>
    <position x="432" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Bank of Therenborough, Lobby" note="Bank">
    <description>The lobby seems dead compared to the constant crowd of the day.  A chandelier hanging from the center of the vaulted ceiling provides a great deal of light.  Shadows dancing with the flicker of the flame seem to make the few customers nervous, all glancing around and holding their coin purses tightly.  The daytime guard has been replaced by a pair of guards who look more nervous than any of the customers.</description>
    <description>A steady stream of people wander in and out, some beaming, others far from happy.  Oak floors squeak with age under the weight of the customer's strides.  The vaulted ceiling makes the room seem airy and spacious reinforced by sunlight flowing in through windows looking onto the street.  A guard roams around the room, peeking in others, watching for the slightest hint of trouble.</description>
    <position x="402" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Bank of Therenborough, Teller" note="Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A small line of people waits in front of a small booth, many looking at strangers with a hint of distrust.  The teller stationed behind the booth talks shortly to each one counting money or flipping through a large ledger book.  A barred door behind the teller allows a glimpse of a corridor leading to vaults and safes.</description>
    <position x="402" y="650" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Bank of Therenborough, Foreign Exchange" note="Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A desk is littered with papers that are scratched with notes and numbers.  An abacus clicks loudly as a man slams the beads around muttering to himself.  Locked boxes marked with metal and currency sit within reach of the desk.  Some chairs lining a wall serve as relaxation for customers.</description>
    <position x="392" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Bank of Therenborough, Debt Collector" note="Debt" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The small office is barely large enough to hold the desk and chair for the clerk.  As each customer pays their debts the clerk smirks and secures the money in a drawer.  A tapestry behind the desk has the symbol of Therengia embroidered on it. </description>
    <position x="402" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Alliance of Exchange, Main Hall" note="Alliance of Exchange">
    <description>Dominating the center of this great hall is a granite sculpture of a Human in full plate armor.  A small engraving adorns the bottom of the statue.  Traders and other ilk flow through an elaborate door near the center of the north wall.  A large plaque is inset in the yellow marble walls near an arched opening which leads into a rather prosperous business.  A short passage leads deeper into the exchange.</description>
    <position x="322" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go short passage" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elaborate door" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched opening" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Alliance of Exchange, Hallway">
    <description>A nondescript wooden door stands directly across from a marble archway here.  Upon the door is tacked a white wolf pelt.</description>
    <position x="322" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Alliance of Exchange, Traders' Center">
    <description>The yellow marble walls here have swirls of blue and grey flowing through them.  To the east you hear the low rumble of many people talking.  A large portrait dominates one wall.</description>
    <position x="332" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Alliance of Exchange, Traders' Pit" note="Traders' Pit">
    <description>Traders move about this room, talking and haggling.  The chatter in here is rather low, and tension can be felt in the air as deals are made and goods are traded.  Two large boards listing the commodities for trade are suspended from twin chains bolted to the ceiling.  A lithe Elf covered with chalk stands ready to change the boards at a moment's notice.</description>
    <position x="342" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Alliance of Exchange, Dorsot's Collectables" note="Dorsot's Collectables|Pawn" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shelves line the walls here, most of them stacked high with various merchandise that at one time was valuable.  Dorsot, a potbellied Halfling, is busy behind a counter, counting a large bag of beads.  Standing in one corner of the shop is a gigantic stuffed cave bear.</description>
    <position x="312" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Alliance of Exchange, Fur Trade" note="Fur Trade|Bundles|Dartrise" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Fur-covered walls act as a backdrop to the shelves pressed against them, which are overflowing with various pelts, skins, claws, hooves, and horns.  Uncommonly tidy for a furrier's shop, each group of skins is neatly tied, stacked, labeled and ready for shipping.  The Elven fur buyer, Dartrise, stands behind a metal counter in flowing robes, waiting for her next transaction with eagerness.</description>
    <position x="312" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Alliance of Exchange, Gruk's Stones" note="Gruk's Stones|Gems" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Piles of rock and rubble stand in each corner of this shop.  From behind a granite slab stands a huge Gor'Tog with a large metal mallet in one hand and a steel chisel in his other hand.  A sign appears to be mounted on the stone slab.</description>
    <position x="322" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Arcade">
    <description>Under the cloak of night, stray footfalls of a lone guard on patrol break the eerie silence before fading as he walks toward Theren Keep.  Evening light reflects off fragments of silver lacing the granite cobblestones that pave the road passing beneath the majestic alabaster arch, creating a curiously illuminated path to the fields of competition.</description>
    <description>Granite cobblestones laced with flecks of silver pave the arcade passing beneath a majestic alabaster arch leading the way towards the Barony's Tournament Field.  Brightly colored pennants, magnificently flapping in the slightest breeze, sport the blue and gold colors of Therenborough artfully interspersed with the crests of famous champions of the Morzindaen.</description>
    <position x="402" y="900" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Arcade">
    <description>Off in the distance flickering lights dance through the darkness of night, casting shadows that appear to breathe life into the white stone of a large alabaster statue that rises up from its hedged corral.  Watered down after the day's activities, the aroma of the practice field's dampened soil intermingles with the lush scent of pine, creating an earthy perfume that wafts through the cooled evening air.</description>
    <description>Set to one side of the cobble-stoned arcade, a large alabaster statue pays homage to the animals that have brought their riders fame in the joust.  Boxwood forms a ring at its base, the green hedge softening the stark white of the stone as well as discouraging children from attempting to climb its smooth surface.  Periodically, a melodic chirping can be heard from songbirds playfully hiding their identities amongst the frilly-needled pines growing together to form a screen in front of the practice field.</description>
    <position x="422" y="900" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Arcade">
    <description>Standing guard through the evening, a pair of tall steel braziers contain blazing fires that wage war against the darkness.  Crickets hide from view, forming an audience that cheers on a battle between night's nocturnal veil and the raging sword-like flames determined to defeat it.  Shadows dance between a wide wooden arch leading to the royal gallery and a dimly lit tent, where overworked pages socialize while they finish off chores assigned to them by their champions.</description>
    <description>Heralding the end of the granite-floored arcade, a pair of tall steel braziers proudly introduces the jousting field's entrance.  Carefully tended by the Barony's groundskeepers, the flames are never allowed to die out as they stand to welcome local and visiting participants to the competitions.  Flags wave atop a nearby tent, welcoming those in search of relief.  Through a wide, wooden arch the royal gallery provides tiers of gaily decorated boxes, offering comfortable seating for attending audiences.</description>
    <position x="442" y="900" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go knight's pavilion" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden arch" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Jousting Field of Honor" note="Jousting Field of Honor">
    <description>The occasional call of a lonesome owl breaks the stillness of night as flames from tall braziers at the field's entrance cast a formidable shadow over the double fences of the jousting lists.  Stray ribbons flutter and tumble across the ground, their once vivid colors now pale reminders of the day's victories.  Young squires pass silently through the darkened field gathering up the few discarded lances that are repairable before shuffling toward the armory with their night's workload tucked under one arm.</description>
    <description>During tournaments, the strident ring of shod hooves rises above the clink of the steel plated armor encasing hopeful combatants.  Dominating the center of the field, the double fences of the jousting lists stand unadorned and chillingly businesslike in the festive surroundings.  Brightly colored ribbons lie strewn haphazardly about the field.  Several bloodstained rosettes, unfortunate enough to be trampled into the hard packed earth, give mute testament to the dangers of this noble sport.</description>
    <position x="462" y="900" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Practice Field" note="Practice Field">
    <description>Well-beaten dirt paths still damp from the evening's cleaning routine encircle the field, flowing in an oft-traveled route between fence, pole, wall and post.  Angled slightly from its most recent attack, a battered quintain dressed to resemble a rather tipsy looking marauder stands in the middle of the course awaiting the next day's activities.  The shadowy outline of neatly trimmed hedges hems the edge of the field.</description>
    <position x="402" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Feat of Archery" note="Feat of Archery|Archery">
    <description>Broken bow strings and pieces of shattered arrows lie strewn across a field trampled to hardened clay from countless displays of battle prowess with various ranged weapons.  One side of the field is dedicated to archery competitions, while the other is flat and devoid of any obstacles except for a long bench peeking through the shadows.  Flickering light from torches softly plays across the ground, revealing occasional snippets of colorful ribbons left crushed and pounded into the soil of the arena.</description>
    <position x="422" y="920" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone arch" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Archery Practice Field">
    <description>Rough-hewn poles form a tall stockade fence that surrounds the field, keeping curious nocturnal animals who may wander in search of food from the adjoining woods safely outside its boundaries.  Torches from the nearby competition range cast a soft flickering light that dances across the ground like playful fairies in the darkness of night.  Peeking through the shadows is a wooden table surrounded by what appears to be a ring of low growing stools, smelling faintly of pine in the cool evening air.</description>
    <position x="402" y="940" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Archery Viewing Stands">
    <description>Several tiered benches extend upward from a waist high balustrade that surrounds the edges of the viewing stands.  Banners hanging from the railing flutter gently, causing shadows to dance in the evening light on the stark field of competition below.</description>
    <position x="442" y="940" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Knight's Pavilion" note="Knight's Pavilion">
    <description>Amidst the clamor of competition, this spacious tent provides a place to rest and recoup between bouts.  Several field chairs await the champions whose souvenirs of competition need delicate tending, while refreshments for keeping up one's strength and spirits are provided on a cloth-covered sideboard.  Near the entrance flap, a small collapsible table stands on rickety legs, bearing the Field Marshall's thick book of cheques.</description>
    <position x="442" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entrance flap" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Therenborough, General Store" note="General Store|Keth Lavatt" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The interior of the small general store is neatly ordered and clean.  Well-crafted knotty pine shelves display a carefully selected inventory of dry good supplies.  The proprietor of the store, Keth Lavatt, is a thin, wrinkled sort of human with a pleasant expression.  He sits in a rocking chair behind a somewhat battered display counter nodding a smiling greeting to each customer who enters the shop.</description>
    <position x="382" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Krrish's Home, Front Room">
    <description>Great heaps of garbage and broken furniture lie scattered about the floor of this tiny room.  Torn star charts drape mournfully from the walls, competing for space with dark stains of dried blood.  Several rat-size holes have been chewed through the mouldering floorboards, and the whole place smells as if it had just been disgorged from the belly of a troll.</description>
    <position x="522" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go string of beads" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rickety door" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Krrish's Home, Back Room" note="Krrish's Home" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sagging wooden shelves covered with a potpourri of mouldering books, dessicated animal parts, and jars filled with the crusts of unidentifiable liquids loom from every wall of this claustrophobe's nightmare of a room.  A tiny space on the rear wall holds a small wooden sign and a framed set of coins.</description>
    <position x="532" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go string of beads" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Therenborough Inn, Common Room" note="Therenborough Inn|Inn">
    <description>A sense of welcome pervades the atmosphere of the common area of the inn.  Sturdy pine benches and tables provide seating for customers and a long serving bar extends along most of the wall to the east.  Exposed oak beams angle sharply up the slant of the vaulted ceiling to the second story and the tops of several doors can be seen above the railing of the balcony.  Steps lead down to a sunken fireplace that beckons with a promise of peaceful warmth.</description>
    <position x="602" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go straight staircase" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steps" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Therenborough Inn, Hallway">
    <description>The sturdy pine railing extending along the open second-story landing provides a view of the common room below.  Both walls are lined with a series of doors, each leading to a room belonging to one of the inn's long-term residents.  A curtain covers the eastern end of the passage.</description>
    <position x="602" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go straight staircase" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Therenborough Inn, Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Small, evenly spaced doors line the pine walls of this passage.  The floor underfoot, of a slightly lighter grain of pine, has been polished smooth by the passage of many slippered feet.  A light scent of cinnamon tickles the air, though its source is not readily apparent.</description>
    <position x="582" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Therenborough Inn, Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The hallway ends here, a large oil painting covering the west wall from floor to ceiling.  Doors to some of the inn's many private rooms line both walls, most bearing a placquard indicating they are currently being rented.</description>
    <position x="562" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Therenborough Inn, Bedroom">
    <description>This room looks cool and fresh, with a bed constructed of trim bleached pine, coverlets of soft light blue and crisp white cotton curtains.  A comfortable couch of white leather positioned between two reading tables completes a picture of relaxed tranquility.</description>
    <position x="582" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Therenborough Inn, Bedroom">
    <description>A red and blue quilt covers the thick mattress of an oversized brass bed that fills the far end of the room.  Tucked between the bed and the wall is a nightstand of whitewashed pine.  White linen curtains with blue embroidered edges decorate the windows, and a rag rug covers the smoothly sanded floor beams.</description>
    <position x="602" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Therenborough Inn, Bedroom">
    <description>Tucked into the western corner of the second story of the inn, this cozy room has a warm playful atmosphere. A bouncy-looking feather bed positioned against the west wall is covered with a yellow cotton bedspread.  Fresh flowers are arranged in a clay pot on the pine nightstand and a tall brass clothes rack sits in one corner of the room.</description>
    <position x="622" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Therenborough, Church Courtyard" note="tithe box" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A simple church of crumbling brick and dark, aged pine stands here surrounded by walls of rough-hewn stone. The bare earth leading to its entrance has been pressed flat by the passing of countless generations of worshipers, leaving not even a hardy weed to break the brown vista underfoot.  Despite the poverty of the building, a warm, inviting glow beckons through its open doors.</description>
    <description>A simple church of crumbling brick and dark, aged pine stands here surrounded by walls of rough-hewn stone.  The bare earth leading to its entrance has been pressed flat by the passing of countless generations of worshipers, leaving not even a hardy weed to break the brown vista underfoot.  Despite the poverty of the building, a warm, inviting glow beckons through its open doors.</description>
    <position x="462" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go church doors" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Therenborough Chapel, Interior" note="Depart|pilgrim's badge|altar|shrine-2-04" color="#400040">
    <description>The city's tiny chapel is a simple square room furnished with polished oak pews facing a raised altar.  The small stained-glass window over the entry door casts a subdued light upon the altar, causing the embroidery on the altar cloth to sparkle with a silky bluish glow.  A single brass candlestick rests in the middle of the cloth.</description>
    <description>The city's tiny chapel is a simple square room furnished with polished oak pews facing a raised altar.</description>
    <description>The city's tiny chapel is a simple square room furnished with polished oak pews facing a raised altar.  The small stained-glass window over the entry door sparkles with candle light and casts a subdued light upon the altar, causing the embroidery on the altar cloth to glow with a silky bluish tint.  A single brass candlestick rests in the middle of the cloth.</description>
    <description>The city's tiny chapel is a simple square room furnished with polished oak pews facing a raised altar.</description>
    <position x="502" y="780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained opening" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Church, Rear Garden">
    <description>A profusion of delicate lacy vines grows over the rough stone wall that separates the chapel from the rest of the town.  Tall, fragrant evergreen bushes have been grown and shaped to form a deep bower on the east side of the garden.  A white cobblestone path bordered with sweet-smelling flowers leads from the chapel to the bower.</description>
    <position x="502" y="800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Chapel, Bower">
    <description>The branches of the evergreens curve and arch about above, as welcoming as a loved one's embrace.  Maiden's Breath vines twine in delicate patterns through the dark green foliage of the bushes, filling the bower with the sweet, heady perfume of their blossoms.</description>
    <position x="482" y="800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Church, Cleric's Room">
    <description>A humble cot spread with meticulously clean linen sheets dominates this tiny room.  At the foot of the cot is a large iron bound chest.  In one corner is a hearth with a neatly stacked assortment of food preparation utensils sitting to one side and a pile of firewood at the other.  A table pushed close to the bed seems to serve as a desk as well as eating area for the room's occupant.</description>
    <description>Dim light filters through a round window placed near the ceiling, casting faded shadows about the room.  Open-beamed and devoid of partitions, the attic has a feeling of spaciousness missing in the chapel below.  Except for a small bookcase and a few storage trunks the place is empty, and noises bounce around the room in faint, hollow echoes.</description>
    <position x="502" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety ladder" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Chapel, Attic" note="Attic">
    <description>Hazy, yellow light filters through a round window placed near the ceiling, casting an eerie glow about the room.  Open-beamed and devoid of partitions, the attic has a feeling of spaciousness missing in the chapel below.  Except for a small bookcase and a few storage trunks the place is empty, and noises bounce around the room in faint, hollow echoes.</description>
    <description>Dim light filters through a round window placed near the ceiling, casting faded shadows about the room.  Open-beamed and devoid of partitions, the attic has a feeling of spaciousness missing in the chapel below.  Except for a small bookcase and a few storage trunks the place is empty, and noises bounce around the room in faint, hollow echoes.</description>
    <position x="522" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety ladder" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Therenborough Inn, Sunken Fireplace" note="Fireplace">
    <description>A brightly snapping fire of cedar logs burns in the red brick fireplace.  Recessed below the level of the common room, the fireplace hearth provides a quiet spot for rest and conversation.  Thickly furred animal pelts spread across the floor in front of the fire allow the weary traveler to recline in comfort.  Steps lead back up to the common room.</description>
    <position x="582" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steps" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Piny Pleasures, Foyer" note="Piny Pleasures|Housing">
    <description>A strong scent of fresh-cut pine permeates the air, so pungent it almost makes the eyes water.  Sawdust covers the entire floor in a layer at least a hand deep, most of it white in color, though a strip emanating from the shop's entrance has been packed flat into a discolored brown.</description>
    <position x="502" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Piny Pleasures, Tables" note="Tables" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tables of all shapes and sizes, all of them crafted from various types of pine, line the walls.  All of the pieces appear newly-created, their surfaces dust-free.</description>
    <position x="492" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Piny Pleasures, Odds-n-Ends" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Large piles of wooden blocks, only the occasional piece recognizable as furniture, squat upon every inch of the floor.  Everything has a price tag, though it's not entirely clear all the items in the room were originally intended to look the way they do.</description>
    <position x="492" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Piny Pleasures, Floors" note="Floors" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Long stripes of pine paneling hang from the walls, samples of flooring which Piny Pleasures has available for installation.  Each piece sports a small tag denoting its price.</description>
    <position x="502" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Piny Pleasures, Beds" note="Beds" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dozens of pine bed frames sit in neat, ordered rows, each awaiting an owner.</description>
    <position x="512" y="670" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Piny Pleasures, Walls" note="Walls" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The walls of this room are divided into neatly ordered sections, each paneled in a different type of pine.  A sales clerk waits expectantly in one corner, eyeing patrons carefully as they enter and exit his domain.</description>
    <position x="512" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Piny Pleasures, Doors" note="Doors">
    <description>Large piles of sawdust cover the floor of this obviously unused room.</description>
    <position x="512" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Piny Pleasures, Chairs" note="Chairs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The ever-present fragrance of freshly-stripped pine mingles in the air with a faint scent of amber polishing oil in this cluttered display area.  Stacks of chairs and stools lean against the walls, balanced carefully behind rows of sturdy pine benches which barely manage to contain the tangle of carved pine arms and legs.</description>
    <position x="502" y="690" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Midwife's Cottage, Porch">
    <description>A swing of smoothly sanded honey pine sways gently at the end of the covered porch.  Near the front door of the cottage, a padded rocker beckons with promises of a comfortable rest.  Wide steps lead down to the village road.</description>
    <position x="462" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide steps" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Midwife's Cottage, Front Room" note="Midwife's Cottage">
    <description>The stringent smell of crushed herbs pervades the front room of the cottage.  Shelves positioned above a large, well-scrubbed pine table hold a neat assortment of jars and bottles that seem to be the source of the smell.  Across from the table is a tall white cabinet, two chairs, and a cot spread with clean white sheets, standing ready for use.</description>
    <position x="442" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hallway" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Midwife's Cottage, Hallway">
    <description>A thick rag rug runs down the hallway, coming to a stop at an arched opening at the end of the passage.  Wooden doors, each the home of an Empath or midwife-in-training apprenticing to the building's owner, line the walls.</description>
    <position x="422" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white curtain" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Midwife's Cottage, Storage Closet">
    <description>Long cedar planks form shelving along both sides of this small closet.  Neat stacks of blankets and linen sheets cover most of the storage space but a few large portable basins are stacked on the bottom shelves.</description>
    <position x="422" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Smithy, Front Yard">
    <description>A large oak tree looms tall here in the yard of one of the town's smithies, providing shade for a small work area built into one corner.  A simple brick forge is built up against the low-lying stone wall, and nearby stands a sturdy anvil and a heavy oak worktable.</description>
    <position x="422" y="800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Smithy, Storage Shed" note="Smithy|Dagul|Repair Metal" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This long, narrow building appears to be a storage area for the Blacksmith's tools and finished projects.  Wide metal shelves running along two opposite walls of the shed frame a narrow aisle down the center of the room.  Several larger implements have been hung from hooks nailed to the rafters above.  To the south lies a door.</description>
    <position x="422" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Therenborough Town Stable, Barn" note="Stable" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Thin barred windows raised high on exterior walls do little to illuminate this darkened shelter, securely built from thick wood planks.  Parallel rows of narrow stalls, split by an aisle covered with a blanket of fresh straw, provide safe haven for all manner of beasts of burden.  Off to the north is the corral, housing animals in need of exercise while boarded.</description>
    <position x="362" y="920" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Therenborough Town Stable, Corral" note="Corral">
    <description>A pair of buildings face each other across an expanse of hoof-packed earth.  Encircling the area is a split rail fence enclosing a large corral that secures any animals left behind by equestrians going about their chores.  The larger of the two buildings, an outpost for the Therengian Cavalry, is built from stacked logs, while the second more modest structure houses the stable's business office, where deals are made and goods of all kinds can be purchased.</description>
    <position x="362" y="900" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go business office" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cavalry outpost" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Therenborough Town Stable, Business Office">
    <description>Whitewashed walls do little to brighten up the small space whose haphazard decor suggests it's used for all sorts of random deals.  Cradling the corner, a sturdy desk is piled high with ledgers, doing little to hide the chipped finish of the surface and that of the chair neatly tucked behind the desk.  A collection of straw-lined boxes, crates and chests are casually stacked across the room, keeping all edible treasures safe from hungry rodents.</description>
    <position x="342" y="900" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Therenborough Town Stable, Cavalry Outpost">
    <description>This rustic outpost is spacious enough to house the regiments that form the Therengian Cavalry, allowing boisterous meetings to be held outside the Keep so as not to disturb the Baron's day-to-day activities.  Silk banners representing each troop adorn the wall behind a podium, adding a colorful background.  Benches, chairs and unclaimed saddles perched on stands offer seating near a table filled with refreshments, set out to fortify hard-working patrols that wander in at all hours.</description>
    <position x="362" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Therenborough Town Stable, Cavalry Barracks">
    <description>Precisely furnished for the comfort of the Baron's horsemen, this long chamber is kept neat despite signs of frequent use.  Horsehair mattresses pad field cots lining the length of one wall, each one fitted with a standard issue blanket and pillow.  Small mirrors hang behind serviceable dry sinks, meticulously set with washbasins, pitchers and a variety of toiletries.  Ending the wide aisle splitting the room, a table and chairs await any guardsmen unable to sleep who choose to relax with a game of cards.</description>
    <position x="342" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Baronial Tournament Arena, Royal Gallery">
    <description>Safe and secure from the crush of competition on the jousting field below, royal blue and gold cushions adorn the benches gathered in small groupings along the tiered boxes of the viewing gallery.  A slight curve in the highly polished banister prevents excited spectators from tumbling out of the stands while cheering on their champions of choice.  Banners emblazoned with the crests of several noble houses of Therengia lend a sense of regal festivity to the thrill of competition.</description>
    <position x="462" y="920" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Therenborough, Gizgo's Engraving" note="Gizgo's Engraving|Engraver" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A short pine counter divides Gizgo's work area from the rest of his shop. Bleached animal hides, upon which are drawn carefully crafted engraving patterns, are nailed along the back wall of the shop.  Near the front is a menu board listing all the patterns that Gizgo currently offers to potential customers.</description>
    <position x="382" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Empath Home" note="Healer|Hospital|Empath Home|Srela" color="#00BF80">
    <description>The cottage has an air of peacefulness, though sounds of weeping and the occasional scream conquer other sounds.  Cushions and rugs cover the floor offering much appreciated comfort to the patients.  Bloody bandages piled in a corner show how many people depend on this empath's services.  Blood-spattered walls mount paintings of empaths on battlefields healing the wounded.  A young woman glides across the room examining each patient in silence, occasionally touching one lightly and moving on.</description>
    <position x="162" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Therenborough, Market Square" note="Market Square">
    <description>Blue and white canopied stalls displaying bountiful baskets of produce nestle between quaint shops with flower-filled window boxes.  The square is crowded with people and filled with the noise of conversation and the shouts of merchants hawking their wares.  Hearthwives ladened with mesh shopping bags push aggressively forward as they vie with each other for the best produce.</description>
    <description>Blue and white canopied stalls, shuttered closed for the night, nestle between quaint shops with flower-filled window boxes.  The square is much quieter in the evening hours, with only murmurs of quiet conversation breaking the silence.</description>
    <position x="282" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple shop" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sky-blue cottage" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Therenborough, Market Square">
    <description>Granite cobblestones line the lane, making travel easy for shoppers strolling by as well as traders delivering their wares.  Merchants display their specialties in the windows of small shops, painted in an array of candy-like pastel colors, hoping to attract customers as they engage in the daily battle for business in the competitive market.  Songbirds flit about the branches of a large cherry tree, entertaining the local children, as they remain safely hidden by its abundant leaves.</description>
    <description>Throughout the evening, ambitious merchants bathe their window displays in golden candlelight, hoping to attract customers too busy to shop during the day.  An occasional click of heels echoes off the cobblestones, breaking through the dark's silence as a lone guard strolls by on his nightly patrol, stopping only to duck behind the trunk of a large cherry tree for a quick smoke before resuming his rounds.</description>
    <position x="282" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick store" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go painted store" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Therenborough, Market Square">
    <description>A tall cherry tree shades the lane on summer days, its trunk scarred from the shoes of local children who've climbed it just to see if they can.  Mixing with the everyday scents of the busy marketplace, a lingering aroma of freshly baked goods drifts through the air, drawing customers further along the lane.</description>
    <description>Shops lit to fight off the dark cast a golden glow, bouncing off a tall cherry tree to create a parade of shadows dancing across the lane that continues throughout the evening.  An occasional rustle of leaves indicates that not all visitors to the marketplace go home at night to sleep.</description>
    <position x="322" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go yellow shop" destination="314" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Fit for a Baron, Display" note="Fit for a Baron|Armor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Hanging high from the opaque ceiling are bright lights that glint off the armor displays.  Tapestries and heavy curtains cover the ironwood walls while plush snowbeast fur rugs line the marble floor.  Stands line the walls and mannequins fill the corners of the room.</description>
    <position x="262" y="740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go carved door" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Elanthian Travel Tours, Gift Shop" note="Elanthian Travel Tours|Travel Tours|Gift Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Poles hold up a brightly covered canvas awning that can be lowered when the shop is closed.  An oversized tower shield with a small plaque is in a roped area in the corner.  Hooks loaded with wares hang near a counter that blocks customers from rifling through the unopened boxes and crates piled in the shadows.</description>
    <position x="282" y="700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Gretchen's Hats, Workshop" note="Gretchen's Hats|Hats" color="#FF0000">
    <description>An array of silk flowers, satin and grosgrain ribbons, wooden berries and chiffon scarves spread across the polished granite slab that covers a row of maple cupboards.  The hatmaker Gretchen Abernathy sits at the workspace, a fanciful hat adorned with bright wooden strawberries and green silk leaves in her hand.  Boldly patterned rugs crisscross the floor below her, and handpainted flowerpots cluster in the corners.</description>
    <position x="262" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Sweet Delights, Front Room" note="Sweet Delights" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A comfortable, homey clutter fills this pleasant shop giving it a relaxed, lived-in atmosphere.  Mismatched pitchers and jugs cover the shelf-lined walls, and rows of tapered candles hang from the top of the window frames.  The pale blue of a magnificent wisteria growing outside the back window is reflected in the sky blue walls of the shop.  Several regular patrons sit over endless cups of coffee discussing other people's love lives.</description>
    <position x="322" y="760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Therenborough Gardens, Blue Garden" note="Blue Garden">
    <description>The initial impression here is one of flowerbeds lavishly planted with brilliant blue, but on closer examination the artful blending of mauve, purple and varying shades of blue can be seen.  Midnight blue clematis climb through the cheerful blue globular blossoms of giant thistle, while pale mauve geranium and purple-leafed plantain cover the ground.  A marble statue stands in the center, overlooking the floral display.</description>
    <position x="422" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garden gates" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Therenborough Gardens, Yellow Garden" note="Yellow Garden">
    <description>Sunny yellow jonquils and orange marigolds grow around a small pond where large goldfish swim, their long trailing fins creating golden shimmers just below the water's surface.  A group of stone nymphs frolic at the edge of the pond.</description>
    <position x="432" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Therenborough Gardens, White Garden" note="White Garden">
    <description>A higher elevation sets off this tranquil garden planted with simple patterns of lilies, white roses and pale feathergrasses.  A charming white trelliswork pavilion stands open at the far end.  The subdued planting of pale flowers high above the other gardens gives this area an ethereal feeling.</description>
    <position x="442" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garden pavilion" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Pavilion" note="Pavilion">
    <description>Neatly trimmed trellises dripping with honeysuckle surround a lush lawn on which roses are grown in elaborate, knotted circles.  Bees trek merrily about the colorful blooms, oblivious to everything but the task at hand.  At each corner of the pavilion, junipers sway majestically with the wind.</description>
    <position x="452" y="590" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Amphitheatre, Entrance" note="Amphitheatre">
    <description>These hallowed halls are where the brave come to prove their worth to their gods and peers.  The sounds of combat and cheering crowds filter in from the nearby entrance.</description>
    <position x="482" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arched entrance" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Amphitheatre, Hall of Champions">
    <description>The highly polished oaken walls are covered with heroic crests of the brave knights who have won honors in the arena.  In each corner stands a lance with multi-hued streamers attached to them.</description>
    <position x="482" y="530" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken doorway" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Amphitheatre, Viewing Stands" note="Viewing Stands">
    <description>The many rows of seats encircle and gradually slope downwards to the arena.  Most seats are occupied with the local townfolks here to enjoy the combat games.  The amphitheatre's design gives each seat a clear view of the entire arena while the perfect acoustics permit even the slightest whisper to be heard from below.  Colorful banners drape gracefully from overhead and reach towards the arena below.</description>
    <position x="492" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Amphitheatre, Waiting Room">
    <description>While designed to be a staging area for combatants of the arena, this room has been converted into a makeshift triage station to keep from having to rush the bleeding wounded through the streets.  The pounding excitement of the arena pervades the room.</description>
    <position x="492" y="530" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tall doorway" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Amphitheatre, The Arena" note="Arena">
    <description>This open space provides ample room for many combatants to do battle at the same time.  Clean white sand covers the hard-packed ground and most of the blood from prior battles.  Many multicolored banners trail down from the viewing stands above.</description>
    <position x="502" y="530" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Therenborough, Kaudric's Gateway">
    <description>An alabaster arch stretches over the roadway, its smooth surface carved with elegant words.  A brass plate attached to the arch gives directions to various sites in the capital.  Nearby can be heard the sound of rushing water.</description>
    <position x="462" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster arch" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Therenborough, Lirum Square">
    <description>A small stucco building with a red-tiled roof lies along the outskirts of the massive city square.  Displayed in the shop's window are several pieces of clothing, most of which bear the trappings of Therengian court.  The bustling square boasts a newly paved roadway, and is named after one of the Barony's idols.</description>
    <position x="442" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stucco shop" destination="293" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Therenborough, Lirum Square">
    <description>Surrounded by several sets of stained oak benches is a marble fountain filled with clear water pouring from three twin lion's heads.  The sounds of children's laughter always present in the days is noticeably absent under the moonlight.  Every now and then young lovers stop by the splashing waters of the fountain.</description>
    <description>Surrounded by several sets of stained oak benches is a marble fountain filled with clear water pouring from three twin lion's heads.  A few children amuse themselves by running along the edge of the fountain, careful to avoid falling in while laughing at each other.</description>
    <position x="462" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gates" destination="329" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="Therenborough, Lirum Square">
    <description>A magnificent limestone building with double doors flanked by marble columns stands proudly before the square.  The Gealeranendae College of Magical History, famed throughout the five provinces, welcomes students, visitors, and teachers within its revered halls.  Hanging above the walnut doors is a blue banner with gold edging.</description>
    <position x="442" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="274" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Therenborough, Lirum Square">
    <description>Pigeons circle over the marble fountain, some landing and skittering across the ground pecking for food, only to flee back to the air when anything larger than a bug approaches them.  To the side of the fountain, a weathered oak tree stretches outward to cosset the clouds, occasionally dropping an acorn as an offering.</description>
    <position x="422" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shop door" destination="317" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Therenborough, Mercantile Street">
    <description>A round little shop stands beside the street, its windows bearing several finely crafted tapestries made from imported Rathan silk.  The building's oak door is open, welcoming customers inside.  A few birds can be seen flying through the air around the crouching gargoyles of the great keep's towers.</description>
    <position x="402" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go little shop" destination="296" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Therenborough, Mercantile Street">
    <description>A paved roadway runs through a collection of small houses topped with red clay tiles.  A sturdy metal gate holds a wooden sign with elegant words scrawled in black paint.  The wind blows through the colorful acacia trees lining the boulevard, scattering purple and yellow flowers about.</description>
    <position x="422" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go metal gate" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alabaster pavilion" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="Therenborough, Mercantile Street">
    <description>The broad boulevard passes by a tiny building, its windows tightly shuttered, a sign proclaiming it the home of the mysterious sister Nongwen.  Piled outside of the home are rows of wooden crates, all nailed shut.  A pile of rubble has been pushed off the side of the roadway.</description>
    <position x="342" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny building" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="Therenborough, Telomin Lane">
    <description>A small lane edges between the large edifices of the town's commercial district to halt before the doorway to a limestone building.  The rear entrance to the stately Telomin Hall, lights can be seen from within it at all hours, and a careful observer can detect the sounds of discussion and silver clinking against glass.</description>
    <position x="342" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go alley" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doorway" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="Therenborough, Escutcheon Boulevard">
    <description>The long Escutcheon Boulevard ends at a massive steel gate breaching a large rock wall.  Upon the wall is a gold plaque bearing the crest of Trigomas, one of the wealthier Therengian Houses.  In the center of the road is a bronze statue of a young Human male holding a longsword in one hand and a scale in the other.  Encircling the statue is a ring of shrubs.</description>
    <position x="302" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="Therenborough, Mason's Circle" note="Mason's Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A painted gateway marks the boundary between paved road and dirt track.  Alongside the path stands a weatherbeaten but sturdy stable, a few bundles of hay stacked by the door and a rusted steel pitchfork tossed carelessly to the side.</description>
    <position x="462" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go metal gate" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="Therenborough, Mason's Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Small cottages cling to the stone walls of the city, the ominous shadows of the giant keep looming over them all.  The roadway, little more than a dust trail, wanders aimlessly through the homes like a snake, slithering around well-tended gardens and plots of trees.</description>
    <position x="462" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Therenborough, Mason's Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Outside one two-story dwelling dozens of children's toys are scattered, with striped red and blue balls, ornate hobbyhorses, and wooden wheels strewn across a fenced-in patch of grass.  A sign bearing methodically painted script hangs beside the whitewashed door.</description>
    <position x="442" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Therenborough, Mason's Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Off of the packed dirt track, solid brick steps supported by a wooden railing lead up to a noisy building, the sounds of wood being sawed and hammered coming from within.  Thick letters engraved on the door proclaim the spot a carpenter's residence.</description>
    <position x="422" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go building" destination="312" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Therenborough, Well" note="Well" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>In the midst of tile-roofed houses spewing grey smoke from stone chimneys stands a brick well surrounded by a cobbled walk.  Atop the well rests a knotted wooden bucket tied to a thick, worn rope, and a few decorative ceramic pots and vases are placed neatly by the side.</description>
    <position x="442" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Therenborough, Escutcheon Boulevard">
    <description>A proud bronze lion rears up over the street from the marble pedestal it stands upon, his clawed paw slicing at the air.  A small cobbled path leads east from the main roadway, heading into a collection of quaint tile-roofed houses.</description>
    <position x="382" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Therenborough, Escutcheon Boulevard">
    <description>Stone gargoyles loom above a large building, their faces frozen in snarls or grimaces.  Carved into the granite facade of the building are images of ancient heroes of Therengia and the Empire.  A massive lancet arch leads within, and above the arch a swan is depicted in meticulous stained glass.</description>
    <position x="402" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lancet arch" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Therenborough, Mason's Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The cobbled path to the west circles large and elaborate houses, dwindling to a packed dirt road to the east.  In the center of the road stands a shining pole clutching a blue banner depicting a seven-pointed star above a tower.  Tall hedges line the sides of the road, animal shapes carved into their mass at even intervals.</description>
    <position x="402" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Ibec Hall, Foyer">
    <description>Broad oak double doors, flanked by a phalanx of fine green marble pillars, lead from the reflectively spotless floors of the austere civic building to the paved streets of Therenborough outside.  Walls of brilliant lapis blue marble, marked by tessellated flecks of black and white, offset the promenade of green columns marching from the doors to a long corridor northward.  To one side of the entry chamber, a crystalline staircase leads up to the hall's rooftop.</description>
    <position x="302" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak doors" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Ibec Hall, Walk of Heroes">
    <description>Lifelike and elaborate statues formed of alabaster, plaster, and bronze stand upon ornate cerulean marble pedestals.  Proudly displayed upon each pedestal is a plaque of platinum, gold, or some other valuable material proclaiming the name of the hero and the bold and honorable deeds that earned them an eternal place in this hallowed hall.  Bringing a bit of uniqueness to the frozen guardians, each holds something in their right hand.</description>
    <position x="302" y="390" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Ibec Hall, Walk of Heroes">
    <description>Honored heroes, many now shrouded in the mystery of myth and legend, stand guard along the main passageway of this ancient hall, once a Paladin Guild, as though to repel any invader that would attempt to reach the inner sanctum just ahead.  Though silent and still, the sculptures are so expertly crafted as to appear ready to leap from their marble pedestals.  An elaborate shield mosaic of white and gold embellishes the tile floor.</description>
    <position x="302" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="265" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Ibec Hall, Sanctum" note="Ibec Hall">
    <description>The building opens up into a large, circular chamber.  Radiant rays of starlight shine through the domed ceiling's glass skylights, exposing the goings-on of the beautiful sanctum to the vigilant eyes of the gods above.  The heart of the hall, two arches lead from this chamber to other rooms.  Displayed upon the floor in tile mosaic is a black tower with a golden star suspended above it.</description>
    <position x="302" y="370" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go black arch" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go golden arch" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Ibec Hall, Licensing Offices" note="Licensing Offices" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Inamicable and surly clerks clad in livery plod about this cramped room leadenly, some delivering documents to the corner of the room, while some march their wards out of the room through a walnut door.  A few of the more engaging workers sit at unremarkable desks from which they issue various licenses, writs, and permits.  The corner of the room contains a dusty desk occupied by a cadaverous old scribe diligently recording in a massive tome every detail of the lives of the province's populace.</description>
    <position x="302" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cherrywood door" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go golden arch" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Ibec Hall, Homes Licensing Office" note="Homes Licensing Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>This small room is dominated by a walnut table, around which stand two clerks, heavy in their own discussion.  Upon the table is a small model of the city, with marks for future expansion, and special attention given to residential areas.  A large pile of documents rests beside the model, the scrolls within containing information on citizens and home occupants.</description>
    <position x="292" y="350" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Ibec Hall, Passport Office" note="Passport Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A finely crafted desk serves as the work space for a bedraggled licenser.  On one side of the desk wobbles a stack of documents, each bearing the wax seal of the Baron, granting travel rights throughout the province.  A mural of Lake Gwenalion decorates one wall of the room.</description>
    <position x="312" y="350" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Ibec Hall, Genealogy Office" note="Genealogy Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Forming a counter that divides the small room is a desk long enough to accommodate additional employees when things get hectic.  Everything is kept neat and tidy, from the stacks of record books to the genealogy charts hung along the walls, showing the resident clerk's attention to detail.  A padded bench sits near the door, encouraging citizens to sit and wait their turn instead of pacing around the office in hopes of hurrying the bureaucratic process along.</description>
    <position x="312" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Ibec Hall, Registrar's Office" note="Registrar's Office|citizenship" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Opposite the cherrywood door that leads within this semi-circular room, a red cherrywood desk serves as the seat of the Chief Registrar.  Papers are precisely and neatly arranged upon the surface of the work area, illustrating the northerner's belief in the importance of order, and beside the stacks is an opaline frosted glass bottle filled with some jet liquid.</description>
    <position x="292" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cherrywood door" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="273" name="Ibec Hall, Registry Records Office" note="Registry Records Office|Item Registration|Gilbair" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Highly polished wooden filing cabinets line the walls of this tiny office, leaving no room for frivolous decoration.  Piles of neatly stacked papers cover the top of a cherrywood desk that has been positioned to immediately catch the attention of anyone entering the room.  The cramped waiting area intentionally lacks furniture, encouraging citizens to take care of business as quickly as possible and be on their way.</description>
    <position x="292" y="370" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plain curtain" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Gealeranendae College, Entry Hall" note="Gealeranendae College">
    <description>The polished wooden floors of this large foyer shine with a permanent luster, remaining glossy and unscuffed even by the many pairs of feet which have passed through over the years.  A glass display case sits prominently to one side, exhibiting the prestigious certificates and awards of past graduates.</description>
    <position x="502" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth door" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Gealeranendae College, Hallway">
    <description>This wide hallway is decorated on both sides with polished wooden cases containing books and manuscripts.  A collection of magical artifacts is displayed in a cabinet under protective glass.  Nearby, a well-lighted stairwell leads to the academy's lower floor.</description>
    <position x="502" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go chestnut door" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone stairs" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Gealeranendae College, Hallway">
    <description>Conservative off-white walls, devoid of any decoration, surround you.  Thick, lush carpeting covers the floor and provides a damper on outside noise.  While starkly functional, there is nevertheless a feeling of security.  A thick oak door leads to the college's library.</description>
    <position x="502" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Gealeranendae College, Instructors' Office" note="Instructors' Office">
    <description>The musky scent of fine pipe tobacco permeates this small office, which is blanketed with richly woven Ilithi carpets.  Across from the doorway sit a sturdy cherrywood desk and polished leather chair, and a stuffed owl with glass eyes perches on an engraved shelf to one side.</description>
    <position x="482" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go acanth door" destination="274" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Gealeranendae College, Lecture Hall" note="Lecture Hall">
    <description>A cavernous lecture hall stretches outward from a set of huge double doors with glossy curved handles.  Rows of seats extend down the aisles to a high stage platform at the front, each chair with a small wooden table resting on the arm for ease in taking notes.</description>
    <position x="502" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="274" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Gealeranendae College, Recitation Room" note="Recitation Room">
    <description>This small classroom looks to have been designed for a modestly sized recitation class.  Several desks cluster in the center of the room and a large white ash rack hangs on the far wall.  Across from it is a slate board covered with arcane scribblings in various colors of chalk.</description>
    <position x="482" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go chestnut door" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Gealeranendae College, Registrar's Office">
    <description>Every available flat surface in the office has been piled high with stacks of forms.  Along one wall is a row of large cabinets with several drawers pulled haphazardly open, spilling more paper into the chaos of the room.  A harried-looking clerk works busily behind the desk.</description>
    <position x="522" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Gealeranendae College, Library" note="Library">
    <description>Tall oaken book cases line the walls of this enclosed room, giving off a pleasant woody scent which permeates the air.  Worn leather chairs are set at a large oak table, providing a place to read in comfort.</description>
    <position x="502" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="276" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Gaeleranendae College, Dormitories" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The wood panel floors are polished to a lustrous shine, their surface unblemished by any marks.  Decorating the blue wall is an oak-framed painting of the city of Therenborough, and beneath the painting hangs a wooden sign.  A carpeted staircase leads to the rest of the school.</description>
    <position x="522" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="276" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Gaeleranendae College, Dormitories" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The hallway, painted in pale blue hues, is dimly lit by candles held in wall sconces.  Along the walls hang portraits of notable figures from the college's history.  By one of the doors, there is some faint scuffing of the paint, as if scratched at by something.</description>
    <position x="522" y="390" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Gaeleranendae College, Dormitories" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Outside one dormitory room rests a glass tray, an earthenware jug and bowl and some silver utensils piled neatly on top of it.  An oil painting of the Zaulfung Stones hanging from a brass hook in the wall is slightly tilted at an odd angle.</description>
    <position x="522" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="285" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="283" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="Gaeleranendae College, Dormitories" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Muffled sounds come from behind one door.  Harsh whisperings, the metallic jingle of coins, and the rattle of dice in a cup can all be heard, though the noises cease after a brief shuffling every time rapping footsteps pass down the hallway outside.</description>
    <position x="522" y="370" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="286" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="Gaeleranendae College, Dormitories" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>At the hallway's end stands a gold pedestal bearing a bust of the college's founder, and a blue tapestry bearing the Gaeleranandae crest covers the wall above the bust.  Like a cloak, a thick rug made from the fur of an island desumos lies on the floor.</description>
    <position x="522" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Gealeranendae College, Downstairs">
    <description>The small room is bare save for a series of hooks lining the plain whitewashed walls, from which hang various-sized drab smocks stained by unknown substances for academy students to borrow.  A tall scuffed cabinet in one corner contains several emergency medical kits and various pieces of safety equipment.  An unlit staircase leads below.</description>
    <position x="522" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone stairs" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dusty staircase" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="291" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="Gealeranendae College, Magic Lab" note="Magic Lab">
    <description>Scrolls and grimoires containing detailed descriptions of myriad spells fill the cabinets of this stone-walled lab, enclosed behind thick glass doors layered for protection against magical accidents.  A large cambrinth sphere rests atop a stone pillar in the center of the room, and several unfinished runestones are scattered across a small bench to one side.</description>
    <position x="522" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Gealeranendae College, Alchemy Lab" note="Alchemy Lab">
    <description>The walls of this spacious laboratory are lined with large cabinets containing empty jars, mixing bowls, and various alchemical supplies.  A huge worktable dominates nearly half of the room, providing ample space for students and professors to work safely side by side.  In the corner a small water bin rests beside a pile of stacked unlonchai buckets.</description>
    <position x="542" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Gealeranendae College, Storage Room" note="Firulf" color="#800080">
    <description>Dust blankets this cramped underground storage space like the snowy quilt of winter upon a pale field.  Wooden crates, securely nailed shut and decorated with vivid red paint, clutter the basement and make moving about difficult.  Nestled between two wobbling stacks of yellow and faded books, an obviously once-ornate altar shows the effects of brutal age and underground damp.</description>
    <position x="542" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Gealeranendae College, Tear of Grazhir Exhibit" note="Grazhir Exhibit|Dinegavren|turtle|Ways|Astral Plane" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Rising and vanishing into darkness, the circular walls are home to four marble gargoyles that stare balefully from their perches at the silvery-white shard imbedded deeply into the floor's center.  A single plaque of brass and silver is fastened in the stones near the exit.  Otherwise unadorned, the room is thick with shadows, no sconces or torches to help shed illumination.</description>
    <position x="542" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go moongate" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Phelim's Sanctum, Tear of Grazhir" note="Map35_Throne_City.xml|Throne City">
    <description>A sprawling mosaic of bright colors has been tiled into the floor and spirals outwards in a tremendous sunburst shape from the center of the room.  Though this may be a design feature solely to further enhance the remarkable brilliance of the design, nothing else here displays such shades and hues, as the walls and ceiling are a drab blue.  A tiny white shard of mineral lies in the center of the mosaic.</description>
    <position x="542" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" />
  </node>
  <node id="293" name="Courtly Styles, Main Sales Room" note="Courtly Styles|Frahnz" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Velvet draperies on the walls have been pulled back to frame luxurious tapestries.  Plush burgundy carpet muffles the footfalls of customers and sales staff.  Racks and stands have been neatly lined in front of a long mahogany counter with a marble top.  Platinum-based candelabras stand in each corner of the room, shedding a soft light on the wares.</description>
    <position x="442" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Courtly Styles, Women's Parlor" note="Women's Parlor" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted in a soft rose and edged with a moss-green ivy border, this room is decidedly feminine.  Chairs with chintz-covered pillows and lace doilies are a resting place for weary shoppers or bored spouses.  Racks of clothing have been placed about the room, showing off the fine fabrics and colors to their best advantage.</description>
    <position x="452" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="293" />
  </node>
  <node id="295" name="Courtly Styles, Men's Study" note="Men's Study" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dark stained paneling and thick velvet drapes make the lanterns in the corners of the room necessary.  Plush leather chairs and a solid brass spittoon in the corner are signs of the masculine customers this room caters to.  A large bloodwood armoire and clothes racks are refilled by silent clerks as the wares are bought.</description>
    <position x="452" y="510" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Paintings and Tapestries for the Distinguished" note="Paintings and Tapestries for the Distinguished" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The drab stone walls of the shop are given dazzling color by an assortment of tapestries and banners hanging throughout.  Resting to one side, a solid table displays a loom alongside bolts of smooth, regal silk and a bundle of thick wool.  Carefully arranged near the material on the wooden tabletop are glass jars of oils, paints and dyes.</description>
    <position x="382" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="251" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Theren Cleric Shop" note="Cleric Shop|Nongwen" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sturdy oaken shelves, wicker baskets, and a wooden counter display a variety of clerical wares and necessities in the shop of Sister Nongwen.  The air is heavy with smoke from sputtering oil lanterns and incense burners that flicker eerily, casting dark shadows on the shuttered windows.  Bundles of herbs and wild grasses hang from exposed rafters, partially obscuring a dimly lit corner of the store.</description>
    <position x="342" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beaded curtain" destination="298" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small storeroom" destination="321" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Sister Nongwen's Back Room">
    <description>Neatly kept, this tiny room serves as both living quarters and an additional storeroom.  A small cot and a cooking stove designate one corner as the home, while the rest of the room is stacked to the ceiling with boxes and crates placed here in storage.</description>
    <position x="352" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="299" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beaded curtain" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="Sister Nongwen's Garden" note="Sister Nongwen's Garden">
    <description>Several troughs filled with colorful herbs and flowering plants growing from rich soil are aligned in orderly rows.  A weather-worn wooden bucket filled with well water rests on the cobblestone walkway next to one of the troughs.  A sturdy oak door marred by the elements leads to the back room of the shop.</description>
    <position x="362" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Sister Nongwen's Garden">
    <description>A whitewashed wooden fence encases the small back yard, with muffled sounds from the surrounding buildings and homes of the city drifting in over the painted enclosure.  The herbs growing in the troughs in this area have thick stems with sharp thorns.</description>
    <position x="372" y="410" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="299" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Sister Nongwen's Garden">
    <description>Wicker baskets bearing rare and precious herbs hang from a tall oak tree shading the cobbled path.  Encircling the large trunk are several racks filled with tiny glass bottles of pastes, powders, and dried herbs.</description>
    <position x="382" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Sister Nongwen's Garden" note="Sister Nongwen's Garden|Sirese">
    <description>Off to the side of the cobblestone walkway stands a low brick wall protecting the jewel of Sister Nongwen's garden, a plot of dirt containing several different varieties of sirese flowers.  Wooden poles around the wall support a cloth roof that protects the fragile buds from damage due to inclement weather.</description>
    <position x="372" y="430" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="299" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Therenborough, Derelict's Alley">
    <description>Uneven and disheveled from irregular settling, the cobblestones are certainly in need of repair, or at least a good flattening to make the alley passable for delivery carts.  By the look of the surrounding buildings and homes, however, few if any deliveries are made here, and the ever present shadows -- which a cutpurse could easily make use of -- may be partly to blame.</description>
    <position x="382" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go telomin lane" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Therenborough, Alley's End" note="Alley's End">
    <description>Waves of some heady scent ripple through the alleyway, and though no drafts or breezes are apparently the cause of such an olfactory undulation, the street debris and discards of Therenborough life are obviously the source of odor.  The proximity of this alley to the north end of the moat also most certainly has something to do with the assault on the nostrils, but sight of it is hidden by the backs of buildings, shops and homes, their windows and doors sealed to this seedy back street.</description>
    <position x="362" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Telomin Hall, Sitting Room">
    <description>The mellow smell of woodsmoke permeates this mahogany-paneled room, coming from the massive limestone fireplace that dominates the far wall.  Flames dance around the large oak logs that pop and crackle behind the hearth's mesh screen.  Tall chairs with plush velvet seats are arranged in groupings around the hearth.  A stunning tapestry covers the length of wall above the roaring fire.  A large burgundy couch sits back away from the fire somewhat, giving the room a slightly cooler spot to sit.</description>
    <position x="322" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go massive doors" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Telomin Hall, Conference Chamber">
    <description>The deep luster of the wood-paneled walls is accented by the rich hues of the burgundy and blue tapestries hung about the room, creating a tasteful and sedate atmosphere.  A thickly padded burgundy rug mutes the conversations taking place here.  Several mahogany sitting tables and chairs run down the center of the room, providing a place for the elite to rest and discuss the events of the day.  Dozens of candles in wall sconces and silver candelabra cast a soft glow across the chamber.</description>
    <position x="322" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go massive doors" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Telomin Hall, Foyer" note="Telomin Hall">
    <description>Twin silver candelabra flank the heavy oak door leading outside, beside viridescent stone pillars.  Plush burgundy carpeting covers the floor from wood-paneled wall to wood-paneled wall.  A noticeable hush hangs throughout the vestibule, as if the slightest whisper would disturb the hanging blue tapestries.  A polished wooden table, small but ornate, rests near the doorway, a leather-bound register and frosted glass ink pot upon it.</description>
    <position x="322" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hallway" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Telomin Hall, Dining Hall">
    <description>A broad table in the center of this restrained room is covered by a fringed white cloth, food and drink arranged neatly and precisely upon it for the perusal of guests.  The smells of the freshly baked breads and cooked meats and sauces waft through the air.  Several antique suits of armor stand to one side of the room atop a burgundy rug, where groups of people occasionally stop to chat about current events, and an opulent blue chair is provided for comfort.  A narrow hallway leads out.</description>
    <position x="322" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hallway" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Telomin Hall, Ballroom">
    <description>Brilliant gold chandeliers hang from the ceiling, light from the candle flames reflecting off of the myriad crystals decorating the fixtures.  The floor shines with a lustrous glow, polished enough to be ideal for dancing.  A broad set of double oak doors leads from the ballroom to the hall's foyer.  In the corner, a harper and flutist stand aside nondescriptly, playing gentle melodies.</description>
    <position x="302" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Konezu's Lenses, Foyer">
    <description>Pure white alabaster offsets a striking multihued fresco dominating the rear walls of this majestic foyer.  Thirteen shimmering gaethzen lamps dangle from the edge of a circular opening midway between a naturally formed pool and the expansive dome overhead.  A crystal weer telescope sits amid a framework of ironwood beams and brass machinery.  The telescope's tremendous tube angles upwards, providing it access to the heavens.</description>
    <position x="422" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="311" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Konezu's Lenses, Darkened Room" note="Konezu's Lenses|Lenses" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Hanging from a chain attached to the ceiling's center beam, a crude votive lamp of murky wine-colored glass spills muted illumination upon a low rosewood table.  Charcoal woolen curtains and a padded bench draped with purplish-black felt enhance this shadowy atmosphere.  As if escaping the darkness, an occasional draft flees whistling up a wide circular staircase.</description>
    <position x="412" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="310" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb circular staircase" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Vori's Fine Carpentry" note="Vori's Fine Carpentry|Carpentry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Neatly cut pieces of lumber are piled in the far corner of the room and wood shavings almost completely conceal the smooth floor.  The shop's wares, elaborately carved racks and stands, are stacked upon a large oak table, the remainder cluttering the floor, making navigation difficult without toppling over the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="442" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Konezu's Lenses, Atop the Catwalk" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Encased in a web of interlocking panes of golden glass, the amber tinted dome affords a wide-angled perspective of the heavens.  Three crescent-shaped lanterns of amber glass emit soft golden light, throwing into shadows lush plants placed about a stone staircase in large earthen pots.  Crystallized in mid-game, a litter of gnome-sized shadowlings cavort amid a pile of cases.  Caught in a costly game of keep-away, an extensive collection of telescopes remains in their paws.</description>
    <position x="412" y="410" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb circular staircase" destination="311" />
  </node>
  <node id="314" name="The Cupcake Cafe, Front Porch">
    <description>Multi-hued flagstone covers the floor, adding a splash of color to the glassed-in room.  Bistro tables and chairs are spaced apart, just far enough so customers can sit and sample their purchases while still enjoying a private conversation.  At the end of the porch, a white wicker swing hangs from the ceiling complete with extra cushions for those in need of a comfortable rest.</description>
    <position x="322" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="315" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glass door" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="315" name="The Cupcake Cafe, Salesroom" note="Cupcake Cafe" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Whitewashed walls are decorated with whimsical paintings of dancing cupcakes, candies and herbs to amuse shoppers as they wait in line for their purchases.  Bakers in white coats and tall, puffy hats rush out from the kitchen with trays of freshly decorated baked goods trying to keep up with the day's orders.  The aroma of freshly brewed coffee and tea emanates from a small cast iron stove in the corner that keeps the complimentary pots hot for customers to enjoy.</description>
    <position x="312" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="314" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained doorway" destination="316" />
  </node>
  <node id="316" name="The Cupcake Cafe, Specialty Sales" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Mixed in with the aroma of baking cake, the scent of assorted liquors helps to perfume the air, indicating that the confections displayed here were created with the adult customer in mind.  The bakers working this area seem particularly happy with their jobs, although not very steady on their feet.  Despite looking as if they've been sampling some of the special ingredients for quality control, they keep the counter constantly stocked.</description>
    <position x="302" y="720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtained doorway" destination="315" />
  </node>
  <node id="317" name="Chispin's Handbills" note="Chispin's Handbills|Handbills" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Elegant in its simplicity, the print shop is filled with tables which are set against the bare brick walls.  Fine, handwoven mats have been laid upon the floor, protecting the granite from the heavy furniture.  Beyond a stone counter lies a small printing press, fairly new-looking and well cleaned.  Bottles of ink are lined up nearby, their acidic smell heavy in the air.  A reinforced ironwood door provides the only entrance.</description>
    <position x="422" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="318" name="The Rose of the Theatre, Attire" note="Theatre Attire" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Bright plaid fabric hangs against one wall of the shop, serving as a backdrop for a theatrical mask decorated at the base with white silk roses tucked into small glass vials.  Shelves and chests around the perimeter feature clothing and accessories.  A simple curtain leads back out to the front of the store.</description>
    <position x="92" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple curtain" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="319" name="Theren Keep, Cell">
    <description>Roughly five paces long and three wide, this barren cell is intended more as a holding area than a dwelling for long-term guests.  This knowledge provides no solace, however, as stories abound of the infamous Cage of Death, reserved for the Baron's most "favored" prisoners.  Useless chains hang from a granite wall where rust-colored stains scar the dull rock, and a sturdy cell door oversees the only passage in or out.</description>
    <position x="342" y="240" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="320" name="Theren Keep, Caravan Stables" note="Caravan Stables" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Not a single horse graces the empty stables -- no saddle or harness hangs upon the wall.  If chargers or warhorses ever paced these dusty grounds, they are long gone with the stalwart knights who bridled them.</description>
    <position x="199" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="321" name="Sister Nongwen's Small Storeroom">
    <description>The contents of stacked boxes and opened crates surround a young sales clerk who is busily categorizing the items in a large parchment binder before placing them on sturdy storage shelves.  A polished brass lantern hangs from the ceiling, affording ample light to display the wares that are available for sale.</description>
    <position x="332" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="322" name="Therenborough Orders Office, Lobby" note="Orders Office">
    <description>The flickering flames of a multitude of lit candles reflect in the polish of the desk tucked into the corner.  They light up this room that is both parlor to guests and the Therenborough Regional office for the Administrator of Orders.  A pair of stools is pushed up against the smooth plaster wall where various documents hang to either side of a small oval window.  Narrow hallways spanning east and west flank a wide staircase whose curve leads to the upper floors.</description>
    <position x="312" y="800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="323" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="324" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go heavy door" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="323" name="Therenborough Orders Office, Recruitment Hall">
    <description>Simplicity seems to be the decorating order of the day in this hallway.  The walls are soft grey-white and rather plain, bare of any decoration save a single mirror hanging from a small, inscribed picture hook.  Reflecting the world around, the etched circle only emphasizes the elementary decor.  Notwithstanding the artistry of the mirror, the dominant feature here is the set of ornate archways each of which boasts a pair of heavy curtains and a small plaque indicating the Order within.</description>
    <position x="322" y="800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="322" />
  </node>
  <node id="324" name="Therenborough Orders Office, Recruitment Hall">
    <description>Simplicity seems to be the decorating order of the day in this hallway.  The walls are soft grey-white and rather plain, bare of any decoration save a single painting hanging from a small, inscribed picture hook.  Notwithstanding the elementary decor, the dominant feature here is the set of ornate archways each of which boasts a pair of heavy curtains.</description>
    <position x="302" y="800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="322" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flamewood arch" destination="325" />
  </node>
  <node id="325" name="Therenborough Orders Office, Theren Guard Recruitment Room" note="Theren Guard Recruitment Room|OTG">
    <description>Placed above the archway is a massive gold and black shield etched with the vivid image of a mighty dragon and loosely draped with a banner of scarlet silk.  Against the far wall, a heavy wooden stand supports a box fastened with a polished lock.  Above a nearby table hangs a brass plaque shimmering softly in the available light.</description>
    <position x="292" y="790" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flamewood arch" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="326" name="Lasa Morit Livery, Stable">
    <description>Muffled by a thick bed of straw, the sound of stomping hooves echoes from several of the roomy box stalls extending along both sides of the spacious stable.  The overwhelming musk that is pure horse mingles with the scent of saddle soap, warm leather, and hay dust to create the distinctive atmosphere that is common to all well run stables.  Soothing reassurances follow in the wake of a young stable hand attempting to escort a high-strung stallion to the stable yard.</description>
    <position x="162" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stable yard" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open doorway" destination="327" />
  </node>
  <node id="327" name="Lasa Morit Livery, Tack Room" note="Lasa Morit Livery|Tack Room|Stablemaster Raedams|Raedams" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Large hooks supporting tack in various stages of construction and repair line the walls of this bright and airy room.  A low-slung rail runs between two worn benches, creating an easy spot to sling saddles while giving them a proper cleaning.  Occasional breezes filter through the open window overlooking the paddock outside.  Tucked behind the open door, several shelves hold an overflowing array of grooming tools.</description>
    <position x="152" y="230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="326" />
  </node>
  <node id="328" name="Lasa Morit Livery, Broker's Office" note="Broker's Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A large framed map of Elanthia's trade routes overshadows the presence of a small tidy desk situated in the center of the room.  Carefully filed documents fill the oak cabinets lining the wall behind the desk, each with a large locking mechanism that is kept secured at all times.  Hushed voices deliberate over the finer points of a contract before the scritching sound of quill being put to document indicates yet another sale to be recorded.</description>
    <position x="162" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="329" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, Courtyard" note="Theren Guard Headquarters">
    <description>Wild grape vines spider the base of the battlement-capped walls that surround the sprawling, well-tended grounds.  Amid neatly trimmed hedges, alabaster statues of armored knights line the broad flagstone walkway that traverses the courtyard and encircles a sunken marble pool, a towering gryphon sculpture at its center.  A pair of semi-circular marble benches provides a leisurely place to chat or to simply take in the beauty of the landscape.  Built within the eastern wall is the two-story riverstone Order house, it's ironwood double doors bearing ornately crested shields, while a nearby arbored archway leads further into the area.</description>
    <description>Wild grape vines spider the base of the battlement-capped walls that surround the sprawling, well-tended grounds.  Amid neatly trimmed hedges, alabaster statues of armored knights bearing gaethzen swords light the broad flagstone walkway that traverses the courtyard and encircles a sunken marble pool, a towering gryphon sculpture at its center.  A pair of semi-circular marble benches provides a leisurely place to chat or to simply enjoy the evening stars overhead.  A soft glow is cast from the windows of the two-story riverstone Order house built within the eastern wall, it's ironwood double doors bearing ornately crested shields, while a nearby arbored archway leads further into the area.</description>
    <position x="492" y="490" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gates" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="330" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arbored archway" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="330" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, Kenman Hall" note="Kenman Hall">
    <description>Polished ivory sandstone surrounds the spacious hall with ornate blind arcades set within the walls, one highlighting a tall statue of an Elven knight, the others displaying suits of armor.  Flanked by a pair of satin standards, a broad chandelier hangs overhead, its soft glow drawing attention to the dramatic mosaic worked within the marble floor.  Surrounding the intricate design are a trio of walnut-framed settees and a decorative tea table, all overlooking the grand fireplace upon the southern wall.  A spiraling stone stairwell in a nearby corner leads to the upper rooms of the house.</description>
    <position x="502" y="490" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go soulstone archway" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone stairwell" destination="333" />
  </node>
  <node id="331" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, Baron Jeladric Theren Memorial Arena" note="Baron Jeladric Theren Memorial Arena|Memorial Arena">
    <description>Highlighted by the glow of the gaethzen orbs, a towering memorial statue stands outside the Order House, overlooking the vast landscape with its colorful pennants fluttering from atop the enclosing riverstone walls.  Along the northern side of the grounds stands two, ringed targets while the opposing side bears a full jousting arena with a set of double-sided bleachers separating the two and allowing an excellent view of either tournament's fanfare.  In the distance, a small stable is enclosed within a large paddock where several of the Order's stock graze leisurely.</description>
    <position x="482" y="490" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooded path" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron-banded door" destination="332" />
  </node>
  <node id="332" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, The Lion's Den Lounge" note="Lion's Den Lounge" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Richly-grained mahogany surrounds the spacious lounge, the full-length windows that overlook the arena flanking the grand marble fireplace where several tufted leather armchairs invite a relaxing chat by the fire.  Rich oil paintings, vibrant tapestries and a colorful dartboard adorn the walls while delectable aromas mingle throughout the area from the kitchen door tucked behind the polished flamewood bar spanning the southern wall.  A massive chandelier overhead creates a soft glowing ambience to the area, highlighting the statued pedestal tables below and etched glass display case nearby.</description>
    <position x="492" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go soulstone archway" destination="330" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go back door" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="333" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, Gathering Hall" note="Gathering Hall">
    <description>A soft woolen rug patterned with an intricate design runs the length of the spacious room underfoot, while burgundy satin brocades drape the walls beneath the ornate acanth leaf moldings.  Highlighted by the gaethzen chandelier overhead, a grand marble fireplace crackles with a warm fire at the far end of the room, while a large mural detailing the Order crest hangs on display on a nearby wall.  Tufted velvet settees surround a low table at the center of the room, overlooking the ornately-framed paintings and gracefully-arched windows that provide a stunning view of the aerial meditation garden beyond.</description>
    <position x="502" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="334" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mural" destination="335" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone stairwell" destination="330" />
  </node>
  <node id="334" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, Aerial Meditation Garden" note="Aerial Meditation Garden">
    <description>The daylight sky radiates through the glass dome overhead, creating an ideal year-round environment for the abundance of trees and redolent blossoms that teem throughout the massive atrium.  Surrounding the garden is a multi-hued fieldstone parapet bearing gryphon-shaped piercings that overlook the surrounding community.  In a quiet area along the far side of the atrium is a silver telescope, while a central fountain is encompassed by a pair of semi-circular benches, a frequent stop for those perusing the volumes on the nearby bookshelf.</description>
    <position x="512" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="333" />
  </node>
  <node id="335" name="Theren Guard Headquarters, Commander's Office" note="Commander's Office">
    <description>Rich crimson brocades drape the polished copperwood walls at measured intervals, highlighting the towering built-in bookcases and elaborate sconces that surround the expansive office.  Against the far wall, a majestic gryphon's head fireplace burns with a warm fire, overlooking the semi-circular tables that radiate from either side of a large Commander's desk, nearly making a complete circle around the tasseled rug that blankets the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="492" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bookcase" destination="333" />
  </node>
  <node id="336" name="Natatio, Diving Platform" note="Diving Platform">
    <description>The diving platform is made of a roughened stone surface which extends over the lip of the pool.  The water seems a very long way down.</description>
    <position x="-41" y="667" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive pool" destination="337" />
  </node>
  <node id="337" name="Natatio, Sunken Pool" note="Natatio|Swimming Pool">
    <description>The water is alive with activity.  Some are swimming laps in cordoned off lanes.  The younger children of the Therenborough, with their mothers nearby, play in the shallow end while the slightly older boys and girls take turns jumping from the various heights of the diving platforms.  A dwarven lifeguard scowls at everyone from his chair and one wonders how exactly he got his job.</description>
    <position x="-41" y="680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="338" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>A rusted pick finds itself married to the rock by time and age in this section of the tunnel.  Left in haste by its former owner, the handle broken off, it provides a legacy to the assault that led to the creation of these tunnels.  A small hole in the east side of the rock wall reveals a deep secret darkness.  Fire burns in troughs cut along the walls close to the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="322" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="341" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble arch" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flat opening" destination="339" />
  </node>
  <node id="339" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Puffs of dust rise up with every movement in this low compartment.  A strange writing is barely visible on the wall to the south, and so faded any effort to read or decipher it would be fruitless.</description>
    <position x="282" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flat opening" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small crevice" destination="340" />
  </node>
  <node id="340" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Sharp cornered rocks extending from the wall of this roughly cut, narrow tunnel make movement difficult.  Pale moonlight seeps into the area from an exit to the north.</description>
    <position x="379" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="343" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low crevice" destination="339" />
  </node>
  <node id="341" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>In the darkness you find it difficult to keep your eyes adjusted either to see in the shadows or to keep them open to the brightness of the fire troughs along the ceiling at the bottom.  A faint skittering sound emerges from the deep reaches of the tunnel causing you to hesitate just momentarily.</description>
    <position x="322" y="-10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="342" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="338" />
  </node>
  <node id="342" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>This portion of the tunnel is very dark and cold.  Without light, it is difficult to tell what the rubble sealing the tunnel is made of.  As the tunnels decends down, it is a quick assumption that this is the top of the tunnel and therefore a way out, but for the time being that will have to remain an assumption.</description>
    <position x="322" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="341" />
  </node>
  <node id="343" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Anyone with a fear of closed in spaces would find themselves very uncomfortable in this section of the tunnel.  The claustrophic atmosphere of the narrow passage is heightened by the eerie silver moonlight seeping in from the north.</description>
    <position x="379" y="50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="344" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="340" />
  </node>
  <node id="344" name="The Breech Tunnels" color="#993300">
    <description>This end of the tunnel would continue north were it not for a tremendous amount of boulders and other rubble blocking any further passage.  A slight puff of air drifts in with the light once in a while, alerting you to the fact you must be close to the outside.</description>
    <position x="379" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="343" />
  </node>
  <node id="345" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Movement and occasional skittering noises from the shadows suggests that there is something living in these darkened passages.  You can only hope that whatever it is, it isn't hungry.</description>
    <position x="419" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="346" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flat opening" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="346" name="The Breech Tunnels">
    <description>Light drifts up from a hole in the floor of this section of the tunnel.  Wide enough to crawl through, you approach the hole cautiously, not knowing if the surrounding area can hold your weight or not.  The smell of something aweful seems to be carried up with the light.  The scent causes you to look around briefly in the shadows to see if something has died up here.</description>
    <position x="419" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="345" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large hole" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="347" name="Calidarium, Sunken Bath" note="Calidarium|Hot Bath">
    <description>The water is almost scalding hot and most who jump in get out just as quickly.  A Gor'Tog relaxing in a corner shows no signs of discomfort.  He watches with a puzzled and amused expression the antics going on around him.  A young Human paladin sits across the way.  He is in obvious discomfort, but for some reason chooses to remain in place.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble steps" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="348" name="Frigidarium, Sunken Bath" note="Frigidarium|Cold Bath">
    <description>The temperature can only be a little above freezing.  While it is difficult to keep from shivering uncontrollably, the water does feel both invigorating and cleansing.  These must be the reasons why a large group of paladins sit chest-deep along the limestone steps.  Many in fact don't look to be the slightest discomforted.</description>
    <position x="-18" y="660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb limestone steps" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="349" name="Therenborough, Carousel Family Services">
    <description>A series of guarded arches line the southern wall.  The complicated framework of iron and timbers spans across the ceiling.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights form the strikingly complex mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="122" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="350" />
  </node>
  <node id="350" name="Therenborough, Family Vault">
    <description>A Dwarven attendant stands near the entry, doing his best to ignore you but seeming anxious.  A wooden platform sits in the middle of the room, and a complicated series of gears, rope and other mechanisms are focused around it.</description>
    <position x="122" y="850" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="349" />
  </node>
  <node id="351" name="Theren Meeting Hall, Entrance">
    <description>Made out of polished mahogany and white marble, the Theren meeting hall is pristinely clean, with columns that support an arched roof.  Long golden chains hang downward to support lanterns burning gaethzen orbs, giving the hall's interior a look of burnished sunlight.  Banners hang on the walls and in even intervals along the length of the long corridor, emblazoned with Therengian crests.</description>
    <position x="279" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="352" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="353" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="354" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platinum door" destination="359" />
  </node>
  <node id="352" name="Theren Meeting Hall, Eastern Wing">
    <description>Torches in golden sconces illuminate the hallway, set into the marble columns set into the walls and scattering bright light through the wing.  Bright ash paneling covers the walls, and on them, several weapons of various types hang proudly on display.  A set of narrow banners frame an arched window that looks out onto the city streets.</description>
    <position x="299" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="351" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver door" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go golden door" destination="358" />
  </node>
  <node id="353" name="Theren Meeting Hall, Western Wing">
    <description>The western end of the meeting hall opens up into a large circular room, lined with pedestals that display relics of battles long past.  The ceiling is made from several arches that converge in the center, and the keystone supports an elegant chandelier.  Pure white marble makes up the floor, with narrow strips of gold separating the perfectly square tiles.</description>
    <position x="259" y="860" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="351" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze door" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go copper door" destination="356" />
  </node>
  <node id="354" name="Theren Meeting Hall, Baronial Conference Room">
    <description>Vibrant tapestries depicting historical moments in Therengian history are hung at measured intervals along the richly grained mahogany walls, further emphasizing the towering built-in bookcases and ornate lion's head sconces that cast a warm glow throughout the expansive lounge.  Against the far wall, polished suits of armor flank a carved mahogany podium.  A settle bench rests nearby, providing the ideal spot for a peaceful chat.</description>
    <position x="279" y="880" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="355" name="Hall of Power">
    <description>Carved wooden panels cover the low walls of the meeting room, and a small arrangement of Therengian roses grows in a bronze vase in one corner.  Several rows of high-backed benches are arranged in the center of the room, each finely carved from sturdy mahogany and decorated with elaborate ivy vines.  Large violet banners cover the walls, embroidered with images of filled pieces of cambrinth.</description>
    <position x="259" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bronze door" destination="353" />
  </node>
  <node id="356" name="Hall of Justice">
    <description>Carved wooden panels cover the low walls of the meeting room, and a small arrangement of Therengian roses grows in a copper vase in one corner.  Several rows of high-backed benches are arranged in the center of the room, each finely carved from sturdy mahogany and decorated with elaborate ivy vines.  Large white banners cover the walls, each embroidered with an image of a judge's gavel.</description>
    <position x="259" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go copper door" destination="353" />
  </node>
  <node id="357" name="Hall of Honor">
    <description>Carved wooden panels cover the low walls of the meeting room, and a small arrangement of Therengian roses grows in a silver vase in one corner.  Several rows of high-backed benches are arranged in the center of the room, each finely carved from sturdy mahogany and decorated with elaborate ivy vines.  Large blue banners cover the walls, embroidered with images of brilliant gold sunrays.</description>
    <position x="299" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver door" destination="352" />
  </node>
  <node id="358" name="Hall of Triumph">
    <description>Carved wooden panels cover the low walls of the meeting room, and a small arrangement of Therengian roses grows in a golden vase in one corner.  Several rows of high-backed benches are arranged in the center of the room, each finely carved from sturdy mahogany and decorated with elaborate ivy vines.  Large red banners cover the walls, embroidered with images of raised shields.</description>
    <position x="299" y="880" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go golden door" destination="352" />
  </node>
  <node id="359" name="Hall of Virtue">
    <description>Carved wooden panels cover the low walls of the meeting room, and a small arrangement of Therengian roses grows in a platinum vase in one corner.  Several rows of high-backed benches are arranged in the center of the room, each finely carved from sturdy mahogany and decorated with elaborate ivy vines.  Large yellow banners cover the walls, embroidered with images of pristine soulstones.</description>
    <position x="279" y="840" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go platinum door" destination="351" />
  </node>
  <node id="360" name="Therenborough, Rundmolen Post Office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tucked up against the stone block wall is an low stone counter showing many dings and chips.  Fretwork screens carved from dark woods surround the counter, sectioning it off from the rest of the square.  Vast, countless rows of differently sized shelves are behind the counter, and complex Dwarven mechanisms can be heard as they rearrange the package-covered storage.  Clerks shuffle endlessly back and forth between the counters and shelving as they assist patrons with their packaging and mailing needs.</description>
    <position x="112" y="820" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <label text="Bank">
    <position x="1510" y="-1310" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Town Gate">
    <position x="169" y="870" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Theren Keep">
    <position x="130" y="21" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="wolf spiders">
    <position x="248" y="-2" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="wolf spiders">
    <position x="378" y="124" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dungeon">
    <position x="246" y="83" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Great Hall">
    <position x="142" y="90" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Stables">
    <position x="115" y="235" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Paladin">
    <position x="283" y="284" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Armory">
    <position x="244" y="244" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gov't Offices">
    <position x="276" y="331" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Racks and Stands">
    <position x="441" y="323" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gealeranendae">
    <position x="525" y="375" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="College">
    <position x="539" y="388" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Astral Plane">
    <position x="552" y="440" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dinegavren">
    <position x="552" y="450" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Turtle">
    <position x="552" y="460" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Lenses">
    <position x="402" y="390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cleric Shop">
    <position x="332" y="390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Paintings">
    <position x="352" y="460" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Clothing">
    <position x="407" y="525" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Amphitheatre">
    <position x="455" y="545" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Telomin Hall">
    <position x="250" y="519" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bank, Debt">
    <position x="382" y="680" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Piny Pleasures">
    <position x="472" y="650" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Exteriors">
    <position x="404" y="624" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gardens">
    <position x="457" y="580" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pawn, Bundles">
    <position x="282" y="630" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gems">
    <position x="282" y="640" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Inn">
    <position x="592" y="700" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Chapel">
    <position x="502" y="780" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Krrish's Bones">
    <position x="496" y="885" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Engraver">
    <position x="357" y="740" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Midwife's">
    <position x="412" y="745" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="General">
    <position x="360" y="843" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Metal Repair">
    <position x="384" y="824" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hats">
    <position x="232" y="750" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Sweets">
    <position x="282" y="742" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Armor">
    <position x="232" y="720" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gifts">
    <position x="262" y="680" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cupcakes">
    <position x="284" y="702" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Empath">
    <position x="142" y="740" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Vaults">
    <position x="79" y="840" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Stable">
    <position x="339" y="930" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tournament Area">
    <position x="452" y="930" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Food">
    <position x="70" y="747" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Clothing">
    <position x="102" y="680" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Public Baths">
    <position x="-12" y="705" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Theatre">
    <position x="22" y="570" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Handbills">
    <position x="392" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Orders">
    <position x="295" y="805" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Theren">
    <position x="496" y="495" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Guard">
    <position x="498" y="507" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Third Floor">
    <position x="384" y="260" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>