<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<zone name="Langenfirth and Surrounding Areas (to Therenborough)" id="40">
  <node id="1" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path" note="Bin" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The rustic town is nestled in the Danduwen Forest, on the shore of a sheltered cove on Gwenalion Lake.  The fir and pine trees grow very tall and in thick stands, with a few birch and oak finding room to spread under the lower limbs of the taller firs.  The streets, more like paths, wind and twist past the huge tree trunks, obviously an effort to avoid cutting down any tree.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deer trail" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak tree" destination="344" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb pine tree" destination="345" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The streets, nothing more than wide footpaths, thread their way in and out of the majestic old fir and pine trees.  It appears that the founding residents objected to the cutting of the trees, and simply followed woodland and animal trails as a guide to where streets should be.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Langenfirth, Lomar Road">
    <description>Under a canopy of pine branches and birch trees sits a small cabin with an open door.  Piles of untanned hides sit on a wooden platform near the building, and those still curing are stretched on racks scattered about in a small cleared sideyard.  A small shingle swings in the breeze to one side of the door.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go leather goods" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path">
    <description>The overhead foliage is so thick it blocks all but the merest glimpse of the sky.  Dappled sunlight occasionally dances on the ground, but for the most part, the town lays in the shadows of the giant trees.  To one side of the path sits a small cabin, built in the one-story, peaked-roof architecture common to the area.</description>
    <description>The overhead foliage is so thick it blocks all but the merest glimpse of the sky.  The rustle of underbrush and the distant call of an owl reminds one that the forest is as awake at night as it is during the daytime.  To one side of the path sits a small cabin, a faint glow of light falling from its windows.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="319" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path">
    <description>Trappers loaded down with piles of pelts and hides make their way through the twisting streets, brushing shoulders with Rangers on brief returns from their sojourns to the northern hills.  Langenfirth, originally a mere Ranger outpost, thrives now as a center for trapping and trade, having grown popular with woodsmen after the opening of the Ranger Guild.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path">
    <description>Most of the town's structures are built in a rustic manner, from solid logs with flag-stone chimneys and deeply-sloped roofs.  Heavy snows during the winter months would collapse a flatter roof, and the residents found logs best to keep out drafts and dampness.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path">
    <description>As the street wends its way through the trees, now and then a glimpse of a side of a building or cabin can be seen.  The thick foliage and dense underbrush make staying on the wandering paths the only practical way to reach a destination.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-156" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Langenfirth, Blufe Path">
    <description>The street forks here, between the two paths standing the only multiple-story building in the town.  Built of logs with a steep roof like all the other buildings and cabins, Telgar Inn is a popular place with travelers, traders and the local populace.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go telgar inn" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Langenfirth, Polwich Street">
    <description>Most of the buildings along the road have high, small windows with heavy wood shutters to be closed against the night or cold or wet weather.  Panes of leaded glass are rarely used in town.  The expense of shipping glass this far north, and the beating glass windows would take from the wind, make wood shutters much more practical.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Langenfirth, Polwich Street">
    <description>Several modest cabins line this street.  The buildings are well-kept and sturdy, although there is nothing remarkable about them.  The tightly shuttered windows and closed doors suggest that the occupants must be away working their traps or tending the forest.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="317" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Langenfirth, Polwich Street">
    <description>The street forks here but continues along in both directions.  A few small cabins line the path making this seem to be the most residential area of the town.  Several larger structures have small yards cleared of underbrush and one or two even have gardens planted in the loamy earth.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu" note="Langenfirth">
    <description>The northern forests rise up into the hills gouged out by the retreating glaciers of a long ago ice age.  The town ends as the street widens into a road that travels up the forested slopes in a northerly direction.  Only a lone dilapidated cabin huddles here, the underbrush obscuring any trail that might lead to it.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-236" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go faint trail" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Outside Langenfirth" note="RTT27|RT-LB-GF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Rustic wooden cabins peek out from the lush growths of trees and bushes that almost manage to hide the fact that there is a small community just to the south.  The North Road picks up again at this point, heading straight north through the deep Danduwen Forest.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-256" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="North Road, Feathergrass Grove">
    <description>The North Road is very narrow at this point, hardly wider than a lane.  Tall growths of feathery grasses lean inward over the road, brushing at passersby with their reddish fronds.  The passageway opens up to the north, where the sound of babbling waters can be heard.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-276" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="North Road, River's Edge">
    <description>The southern shoreline of the Gwenalion River is strewn with smooth pink pebbles, accented by tufts of deep purple river moss.  An elegantly constructed bridge of white stone arches across the water heading north.  Judging from the chorus of throaty calls, an abundance of toads and frogs reside here.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-296" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone bridge" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu">
    <description>The street meanders towards Gwenalion Lake.  The dirt underfoot is looser and damper than in other parts of the town, but still of the rich, peaty quality of soil enriched by years of forest decay.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu">
    <description>Along the edge of the street the earth falls away, cliff-like, into the lake. The lake water is stained a murky brown from years of run-off through the peaty soil of the forest.  Even the shallow bottom of the lake shore is obscured.  The water has acquired an odd taste making it impalatable for drinking but excellent for brewers.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-156" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu" note="Ranger Cache|Cache|RTTCache|RT-L-LCR" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The street twists as it edges around a sheltered cove and away from the residential part of the town.  Along the shore bob small canoes, and several green-clad figures are fishing with long spears from the water's edge.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-136" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Langenfirth, Shuri Road">
    <description>The streets twist into one another to avoid the trunks of large trees.  There is very little wind through the lower branches, so close to the town center, and sheltered by the surrounding hills.  The wind off the lake can be heard high overhead tossing the tops of the giant firs.  A large log building near the street houses the local fur exchange.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fur exchange" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Langenfirth, Mir Mod">
    <description>Sheltered from the wind by the ancient tree and its smaller cousins, the street continues to circle the small park-like clearing around the trunk. Now and then it seems like voices can be heard calling to each other from high up in the branches.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go peltry" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb langenfirth tree" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Langenfirth, Mir Mod">
    <description>The street circles around an ancient fir tree whose top seems lost in the clouds.  Several huge branches droop near the ground, here and there affording a place for townspeople and travelers to sit and rest.  The tree is a focal and gathering point for all, and a great deal of care seems to be taken to keep it healthy.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-136" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb langenfirth tree" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Langenfirth, Mir Mod">
    <description>Under the shade of the giant firs stands a tidy cabin with Town Hall painted on the door.  A bronze gong hangs nearby, green with age and weather.  The building appears to be one of the oldest ones in the town, but it has either had excellent care or very little use.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb langenfirth tree" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town hall" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Langenfirth, Mir Mod">
    <description>Pleasant little nooks about the lower branches provide secluded areas for private discussions between friends and business people.  One section of the trunk seems marred by huge claw marks, perhaps that of a very large bear.  Most of the scratches appear very old and weathered, yet a few seem to be quite recent.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb langenfirth tree" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Langenfirth, Shuri Road" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Narrower, but heavily traveled, this street serves as a shortcut for the locals trying to get through town quickly but avoid the more congested areas.  The forest is thick with fir, pine and evergreen trees, and the ground is covered in dense underbrush.  The dirt of the path is so hard packed it appears to be paved.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Langenfirth, Lomar Road">
    <description>The street twists through the trees and past a well cared for workshop with a small forge in the side yard.  Tinker's End is the only place in town to have items repaired if one cannot do their own work.  Whether it is a cook pot or a breastplate, if it is damaged, it comes here.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small workshop" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Langenfirth, Lomar Road" note="Stock Pens">
    <description>The grunt of pigs and low of sheep drift out of a nearby pen in a small clearing near several shops.  The smell of pig slop and fresh manure mixes with the peaty smell of the forest floor, the dust of the street and the tang of the nearby pines.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stock pen" destination="311" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Langenfirth, Lomar Road">
    <description>Meandering between the trees, the street veers from the cove towards the town center parting the thick underbrush.  Small squirrels scurry up and down the trunks of the trees scattering the pine needles and leaves on the ground while searching for berries and nuts.  There is a small piece of parchment nailed to the door of a small, thatch-roofed shop.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go herbalist shop" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Langenfirth, Modren Roade">
    <description>A short, narrow side street slips along between several large fir trees and some spindly oaks.  The underbrush has been cut back near the road to allow for passage of larger carts and wagons, but off the road the forest is so thickly overgrown movement would be impossible.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Langenfirth, Modren Roade">
    <description>The street ends in a small cul-du-sac at the door of a modest shop.  While no sign identifies the goods sold there, a very large, hand-carved longbow hangs from the cabin eaves.  The trees have grown right up to the structure, and the underbrush seems never to have been thinned.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bowyer shop" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Langenfirth, Lomar Road">
    <description>Small sparrows flutter about from branch to branch, and squawk in fright as squirrels scampers out on their branches.  Several streets twist into each other around the trunks of the trees, wending towards the cove and back towards the hills.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak cabin" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu">
    <description>Nearer the docks, Langenfirth is a bit busier.  Wheeled carts and mules strapped with packs of pelts are moved towards the wharf, while wagons with crates of sundries and staples are brought to local merchants.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu" note="Fish Buyer">
    <description>The overwhelming odor of fresh fish emanates from the open door of a small cabin that sits between the street and the shore of the cove.  It mingles with the smells of decaying catches at the shore line and day-old leftovers dumped behind the market.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fish market" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu" note="Portal" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Wheels and hooves clatter on the wood as they move on and off the platform of the landing.  Heavy foot traffic joins the carts and wagons to add to the general turmoil of arriving goods and departing trades.  Through the general commotion can be heard chimes from a nearby temple and the occasional call of a lake bird frightened from its perch.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go waldroth landing" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meeting portal" destination="375" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Langenfirth, Waldroth's Landing">
    <description>The landing is constructed out of solid trunks of large trees driven into the soft bottom of the lake.  More stout trunks frame and floor the structure, while some have been split in half to lay across the rough wharf to provide a smooth surface for feet and wheels.  Here and there a duck sits huddled on a piling watching the more daring pigeons swoop down and grab scraps dropped by passersby.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Langenfirth, Waldroth's Landing">
    <description>Several large pilings jut out into the lake supporting a somewhat worn-down wharf.  Crates and barrels are stacked about waiting for loading or pick-up by the local tradesmen.  A duck waddles between the stacks looking for tidbits of food and scaring a large rat out from behind a barrel.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Langenfirth, Wharf" note="Wharf|Riverhaven|Barge|First Land Herald|Herald|newspaper|news stand" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Nothing about this tattered replica of a wharf would instill confidence in the wary traveler.  Broken planks strafe the pier to which massive barges are tied on listing mooring rails which might tumble over at any moment.  The aged wood buckles easily beneath your feet, but apparently is tough enough to withstand the heavy cargo off-loaded each day.  Several bystanders mill about, checking their precious shipments as they wait for the next barge.</description>
    <description>The waters of the Gwenalion lap gently against the pilings beneath this rickety pier.  Huge gaps in the broken wood let up tangy scents of damp peat mixed with a distinctively colorful yet indeterminate odor.  Swathed in silence and darkness, the wharf seems derelict and abandoned, hardly suggestive of the activity which takes place upon it when the sun touches the sky.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go barge" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go barge" destination="377" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Gwenalion Marina, Seord Dock" note="Marina">
    <description>Neatly coiled ropes lie next to highly polished anchors on this well tended dock.  Sailors hurry about their daily business, lugging cargo and moving briskly from ship to shore.  Shouting is heard from the ships as they make their passage safely to shore.</description>
    <description>Lanterns flicker in the night with their flames dancing against the waters below.  Sailors lounge about at their leisure, done with their daily chores of lugging cargo and swabbing decks.  Singing is heard from the ships as they make their way back after a few drinks at the nearby taverns.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Gwenalion Marina, Zelka Dock">
    <description>Heavy waves lap against the docks, often splashing water on its new wooden structure.  Families stroll around the area, gazing at the different ships, looking for fresh fish to buy, and stopping to feed the little birds nearby that call the sea their home.</description>
    <description>Dark seas stir, lapping against the dock with a slight lulling tune.  Lanterns bring soft lighting, their flames flickering against the water below.  Seagulls rest among piles of rope and gear till the next day's dawning.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Gwenalion Marina, Fulmi Dock">
    <description>Barrels of fish are neatly stacked by boxes of cargo that are ready to be delivered to market.  Seabirds squawk as they argue with one another over a piece of dropped fish or a favored stoop to land on.</description>
    <description>Barrels of fish are neatly stacked by boxes of cargo that are ready to be delivered to market.  Guards roam the area making sure nothing is disturbed, including quelling the fights that occasionally break out among sailors.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Langenfirth, Kilth Street" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The wind off the lake dissipates the smell of the fir trees and the nearby fish market.  The stiff breeze rushes through the tops of the tall fir trees, whistling through the branches, occasionally scattering pine needles and pine cones across the street.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Langenfirth, Kilth Street">
    <description>The street quiets here as it passes the local temple.  The only stone building in town, it appears to be ancient in design and has seen very little upkeep since that time.  Mortar has long since aged and fallen away, leaving gaps in the walls, many of which have become the roosts and nests of the local wildlife.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go temple courtyard" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Langenfirth, Kilth Street">
    <description>The branches of the trees hang far out over the street and droop low, brushing the ground in spots.  This makes it about impossible for carts or pack animals to pass this way, but there are still a great many pedestrians dodging the limbs and making their way through.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine cabin" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu">
    <description>The path widens here into that of a true street as several other trails intersect.  The dark, peaty dirt is packed hard from the wheels of many carts and the trample of many hooves.  The smell of the damp shore mingles with the twang of the fir trees and a definite odor of fish.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak shack" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Langenfirth, Shuri Road">
    <description>Meandering between the trees, the street veers from the cove towards the town center parting the thick underbrush.  Small squirrels scurry up and down the trunks of the trees scattering the pine needles and leaves on the ground while searching for berries and nuts.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pawnshop" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Langenfirth, Jalgelvjegu">
    <description>The street meanders along the cove towards a cluster of small wooden docks.  The dull brown water of Gwenalion Lake laps the shore gently, although outside the shelter of the land the water is speckled with white-caps from the stiff breeze out of the northern hills.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lake shore" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Langenfirth, Polwich Street" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The street narrows to not much more than a footpath where it disappears into a larger trail running along the shore of a small cove.  The tall firs and dense underbrush are thicker than in most areas of the town.  The occasional rustle in the brush notes the almost silent passing of someone or something.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-136" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Langenfirth, Polwich Street">
    <description>A large cabin sits behind a high log fence with a solid wood gate.  Nowhere else in town, except for the stock pens is a gate or fence used, and no other cabin has one.  It is built of thick branches woven between the naturally growing trees.  The structure is higher than a man's head, making it impossible to see anything but a large, steep green roof sticking up over the top.  A small notice on the gate reads Ranger Guild.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Langenfirth, Lake Shore">
    <description>The dull brown water of Lake Gwenalion is shallow at the shore.  Rippling waves lap the dark loamy earth giving the water its odd hue.  The gentle swells toss small sticks and dead leaves against the beach and carry them away again.  Up and down the lake various geese and ducks paddle back and forth in the tepid shallows, while further out over the lake herons circle lazily watching the surface for a glint of scales.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Langenfirth, Lake Edge" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The wind blows steadily off the lake tossing white caps across the center of the lake.  In the shelter of the cove the breeze barely ripples the surface of the knee-deep water.  The shallows serve as a safe haven for fry, young fish and a family of mallard ducklings.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Langenfirth, Lake Gwenalion" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The water deepens farther from the shore, but the shelter of the cove calms the wind and lulls the lake into calmness.  The dark waters, colored brown by the decaying matter of the Danduwen Forest, obscure the lake bottom but small fish occasionally bump into whatever or whomever wades their way.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Langenfirth, Lake Gwenalion" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Outside the shelter of the cove the lake bottom drops off sharply, and the water is rougher.  The waves break now and then into small white caps as a strong wind blows off the lake.  The chill of the water is not uncomfortable, but is very invigorating.  Nearby the silver slash of a fin creases the surface followed quickly by a diving heron seeking its dinner.</description>
    <description>Outside the shelter of the cove the lake bottom drops off sharply, and the water is rougher.  The waves break now and then into small white caps as a strong wind blows off the lake.  The chill of the water is not uncomfortable, but is very invigorating.  Nearby the silver slash of a fin creases the surface followed quickly by a diving heron seeking its dinner.  </description>
    <position x="200" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Langenfirth, Lake Gwenalion" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Chilled brownish water laps about, tossed by the strong westerly wind off the lake.  Back near the shore, fisherman ply their lines in the comfort of the sheltering cove.  A little ways further into the lake is the structure of the landing and the barge wharf.  The lake seems to teem with fish, many breaking the surface and then diving back into the dark waters.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Langenfirth, Lake Gwenalion" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The rocky lake bottom was long ago covered with silt washed off the beach, providing a silky cushion and a rich home for hermit crabs.  Now and then a small fish breaks the surface quickly, attracting the attention of a duck paddling nearby.  The water is quiet, and the surface smooth, as the wind off the lake is gentled by the sheltering cove formed by the trees and hills of the surrounding Danduwen Forest.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Lake Gwenalion, Near the Landing" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Near the wharf the lake laps roughly against the pilings, tossing odds and ends dropped by those on the Landing back and forth on the waves.  Ducks paddle about the structure, but not out into the open water of the lake, afraid to brave the stronger current and the wind swept surface.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Deobar trees tower high overhead, their soft green needles bringing a sharp, fresh scent to the air.  Songbirds twitter as they dart rapidly in and out among the branches, carrying twigs and assorted pieces of grass with which to build their nests.  Tiny log cabins nestle amidst the foliage in this idyllic wilderness, blending into the shadows cast by the great trees.</description>
    <description>Deobar trees tower high overhead, their soft green needles bringing a sharp, fresh scent to the air.  An occasional rustle in the branches overhead combines with the low twittering of woodland birds, home to roost for the night in the thick canopy.  Tiny log cabins nestle amidst the foliage in this idyllic wilderness, blending into the shadows cast by the great trees.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deobar tree" destination="320" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The path meanders this way and that as it snakes its way through the thick trunks of close-growing deobar trees.  Log cabins huddle beneath the branches, their split cedar shingles darkened by exposure to the weather.  Soft patches of moss stop up gaps between the logs, giving the tiny buildings a charming, rustic appearance and smudging their outlines gently into the surrounding greenery.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A rough-hewn log bridge arches lazily over a nearby burbling stream.  Fuzzy brown cattails sway amidst bright green leaves in the chilly water, caressed by a gentle breeze.  Moss-covered rocks line the banks of the stream, their pillowy cloaks sprinkled with tiny wildflowers which flourish in the cool dampness.</description>
    <description>A rough-hewn log bridge arches lazily over a nearby burbling stream.  Fuzzy brown cattails sway amidst bright green leaves in the chilly water, caressed by a gentle breeze, and moss-covered rocks line the banks of the stream.  A rumbling chorus of bullfrogs mingles with the melody of crickets in the night air, serenading local residents.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden bridge" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Sturdy cabins nestle amidst the undergrowth which lines the path.  Moss-covered slate roofs blur the outline of the structures, blending them softly into the shadows cast by the massive deobar trees.  Nearby, a rough log bridge arches over a swift-flowing brook.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden bridge" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brook" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The path wends its way through the forest, roughly parallel to a nearby stream.  The packed dirt surface is cushioned by dead leaves and deobar needles which fall from the trees overhead.  Log cabins are scattered here and there, not too far from the path, but far enough to create a sense of isolation for each resident.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Shelf lichen clings to the rough-textured bark of a nearby tree, the creamy surface marred by a roughly scratched sigil.  Deep green ferns and an occasional burdock surround the path, extending wafting tendrils across the narrow, winding trail.  Somewhere overhead, the ceaseless chatter of a flock of mockingbirds fills the air with strange conversation, their voices alternately strident and melodic.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A sharp, musky fragrance fills the air, and deep scratches in the earth suggest the proximity of an animal's lair.  The forest floor is shaded by the leaves overhead, allowing only a faint dapple of light to filter through.  Nearby, log cabins nestle unobtrusively in the shadow of the trees, their outlines blurred by moss growing on their roofs and in the chinks between the wood.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Water splashes down a fast-running brook to tumble into a deep pool at the end of the trail.  Small cabins surround the clearing, half-hidden in the shadows of the forest's embrace.  A wide variety of animal tracks, among them deer, raccoon and wolf, cover the mud at the water's edge.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deep pool" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Langenfirth, Daelfa Seord'telgi" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A small clearing in the dense growth of trees provides a peaceful location for a group of good-sized cabins.  Fat log walls and sloping, moss-grown roofs typify the comfortable homesteads which dot the clearing, their sturdy chimneys breathing purplish wisps of peatsmoke into the overhanging branches.  Occasional trills of birdsong echo around the canopy overhead.</description>
    <position x="-280" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Langenfirth, Falban Seord'telgi" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A rough wooden bridge arches overhead, casting deep shadows across the slow-flowing stream.  Water weeds cling to the slowly rotting pilings and blend into a heavy moss which coats the underside of the bridge.  The nearby stream bank offers an easy scramble back to shore.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stream bank" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Langenfirth, Falban Seord'telgi" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Smooth, slick pebbles line the streambed, polished to a dull gleam by the water's flow.  Willow trees grow along the shore, their pale green withies reaching down to sway gently in the current.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steep embankment" destination="378" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Langenfirth, Falban Seord'telgi" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A narrow gap between several squatting boulders forces the water into a frothing rush.  Twigs and cattails, fallen from overhanging branches into the smoother waters upstream, ride the waves in a merry, turbulent tumult.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Langenfirth, Falban Seord'telgi" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Large boulders line the streambed, breaking the mad turbulence of the upstream waters into fiercely swirling eddies.  A small pond downstream offers a glimpse of calmer waters, in stark contrast to the semi-rapids which tumble down from above.</description>
    <position x="-240" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Langenfirth, Seord'telgi teorn" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Water from the nearby stream makes a final splash over rocks and jutting tree roots before tumbling into the waters of this small, deep pond.  Cattails sway near the bank, revealing brief glimpses of the cottages and cabins lining the clearing around the pond.</description>
    <position x="-260" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shore" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Gwenalion Fens" note="Fens">
    <description>Dismal and dreary, gnarled oak trees sway in the dense woods which run along the edge of the field, twisted limbs stretching down toward the ground.  A narrow deer trail winds through the trees before vanishing into the depths of the forest.  Rolling ridges of wildflowers and bog rosemary stretch out to the southeast, interspersed with sullen hollows filled with brackish water.  The surface of Lake Gwenalion glimmers in the distance.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="4" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deer trail" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>The spongy surface of the fen squelches underfoot as water slowly oozes out of the ground to fill the prints left by travelers.  A steady breeze blows off the lake, carrying with it the watery scents of fish and seaweed.  Delicate orchids in pale shades of pink and lavender bow their heads before the wind, bobbing and swaying like dancers in nature's ballroom.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="24" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Crickets chirp their mating call from within the protective layer of sedge that blankets the ground.  Tiny catkins surround one of the pools that dot the fen, home to frogs and birds as well as the long-legged insects that skitter quickly across the water's surface.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="24" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>The land dips suddenly, becoming soggier as it skirts a small pool.  Slick and muddy, even the most agile traveler must work hard to keep their balance on the slope.  The incline is eagerly embraced by otters or other small creatures who have left behind a smooth slide of glistening black mud leading from the bank down into the water.</description>
    <position x="0" y="44" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Gwenalion Fens" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Poised atop a rise, the fens stretch out in all directions.  The green of sedge and grass is broken by glimmering pools of water and colorful mounds of wildflowers.  In the distance, glittering reflections dapple the dark surface of the lake.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="64" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Gwenalion Fens" note="RTT28|RT-GF-LB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The path twists and winds through the fen, skirting sodden depressions which fill with water after each rainfall, sullenly draining in better weather.  Mounds of wildflowers thrive in the damp soil -- vibrant patches of pink, red, yellow, purple and blue swaying amidst the deep green ground cover.  Over it all, the forest looms, dark and secret, the thorny thicket that guards its borders an impenetrable barrier.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="64" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>A stunted oak grows by itself, away from the dark mass of underbrush that marks the edge of the forest proper.  Half-uprooted by wind or water, the gnarled tree is canted toward the forest, its limbs crushed against the ground, its roots exposed to the air.  Yet it survives, clinging to life with tenacious determination as its roots stretch out to take hold again in the fertile soil of the fens.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="44" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Gwenalion Fens" note="RTT24|RT-GF-MF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>A fallen log blocks the path to the south and forces travelers to skirt around the puddle at its base.  Many years dead, its branches are chewed off, its trunk is split, and old char marks near a split limb hint at fire or lightning as a contributing factor in its demise.  But life springs from death in the fens as in the forest, and graceful orchids and bromeliads have turned the fallen trunk into a nurse tree on which they feed.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="84" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>A downward dip in the path leads through a shallow water-filled hollow.  Rain and flood keep the low-lying fens damp in all but the most prolonged droughts, attracting the tiny pale blue butterflies no bigger than a Gnome's finger which fan their wings as they rest on floating twigs.  Other insects skitter across the water's surface leaving widening circular ripples for footprints.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="104" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Gwenalion Fens" note="RTT25|RT-GF-HF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Wood chips litter the ground around a low stump.  The surface is smooth and slightly curved, making a perfect seat on which to rest before continuing on the way, and the pile of broken sticks and snapped limbs tossed into the nearby underbrush suggests that a youngster just learning to carve wood has done just that.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Spongy moss cushions the feet as you make your way through the gentle, rolling fens.  Day and night, birds warble from their perches in the forest to the west, shaded from sun and moon alike by the dense canopy of leaves.  The tangled thicket separating forest from fen marks an impenetrable barrier to hunter and hunted alike.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch copse" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Feathery sprays of curling ferns in various shades of green and brown nestle in the shadow of the thicket that divides the fens from the nearby forest.  The plants sport faint yellow streaks, but seem to be thriving eagerly in the moist soil and shade.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Tight pellets of fur and bone litter the ground beneath an ash tree.  Moles, shrews, mice and other small rodents thrive in the sedge and reeds of the fens, providing a good hunting ground for owls.  An occasional bushy red tail prancing gaily through the grass or the harsh call as a raptor circles overhead is mute testimony of the area's popularity as a feeding ground.</description>
    <position x="0" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Waist-high stalks of sedge and statice cover the spongy ground of the fens.  The wind from the lake sends rustling waves of green and purple across the landscape's rolling ridges and carries with it a faint, lemony fragrance that tickles the senses.</description>
    <position x="0" y="204" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Gwenalion Fens, On the Shore">
    <description>Clusters of catkins sway to and fro with a faint whisper as the velvety heads brush against each other.  Beyond, dried reeds carried by the currents drift together to be bound by thick ropy strands of moss.  While not overly stable, the resulting hummocks are big enough to support several people as they bob gently in the water, some close to the shore, others further out.</description>
    <position x="20" y="224" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Alive with movement, the fen is a tapestry of colorful threads being woven at a measured and unchanging pace.  Iridescent-winged insects swarm and buzz, glinting like jewels in the unfiltered light.  Birds fly low through the area and occasionally catch a plump bug as they wheel and swoop from the sky.  Even the vegetation shifts, the reeds and stunted trees bending in the wind and flowers bobbing with each ripple in the water.</description>
    <description>Alive with movement, the fen is a tapestry of colorful threads being woven at a measured and unchanging pace.  Iridescent-winged insects buzz through the darkness.  Birds fly low through the area and occasionally catch a plump bug as they wheel and swoop from the sky.  Even the vegetation shifts, the reeds and stunted trees bending in the wind and flowers bobbing with each ripple in the water.</description>
    <position x="0" y="244" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Solid ground stretches out to the west, far more solid, at least, than the somewhat wobbly surface of the reed hummock on which you currently perch.  The water between here and the shore is narrow enough to leap, though perhaps not without risk of a wetting in the process, and other hummocks bob in the water nearby.</description>
    <position x="40" y="224" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>The hummock rocks gently underfoot as the current carries it on its stately progression around the fens.  Unstable at best, the floating islands shift in the wake left by the passage of the creatures who dwell in the depths of the lake.  In the distance, the doleful cries of marsh birds echo across the water.</description>
    <position x="60" y="244" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Deep green tendrils wind in among the weeds and cling tenaciously to the reeds.  Perhaps dropped by some passing bird or caught in the claw or coat of one of the creatures which frequent the hummocks, the lyrandia has taken hold, sending up a handful of sweetly scented golden blossoms among the twining vine.</description>
    <position x="60" y="204" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>The packed reeds underfoot yaw and pitch with the shallow waves near the shore as they drift with the currents across the water of the lake.  Jostled by adjacent hummocks, the relative position of each individual islet rarely changes, but the distance from one island to the next seems to vary from day to day.  Dark shadows glide beneath the surface of the water around you, and an occasional cry of a nesting gull echoes mockingly from the shore.</description>
    <position x="40" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go log" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go animal trail" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Gwenalion Fens, On the Shore">
    <description>Hunters plodding along the muddy shoreline find that the fens cling to paws, feet and boots with an impartial affection.  The air is filled with the dank scent of rotting vegetation and the sickly sweet stench of decaying fish, their bellies raked by claws or fangs.  A dried reed hummock, one of many that bob in the still water of the lake, is probably close enough to reach to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="20" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go animal trail" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>The remains of a tumble-down cottage squat beside a small birch coppice, still sporting a few dried strands of thatch clinging to the fallen ridgepole.  A few whitewashed bricks still stand one atop the other, but for the most part the dried mud has long since melted back to the soil from which it came.  Blackened wooden support piles driven deep into the peat are barely visible beneath the rubble piled around the building.</description>
    <position x="0" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Conical russet-spotted mushrooms grow in a colorful faerie ring nestled at the bottom of a hollow.  The ring encircles a dark pool, no more than a pace across, its water black from the peat in the soil.</description>
    <position x="20" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mucky trail" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>A cool breeze blows in fitful spurts off the lake, bringing with it a breath of fresh air.  The wind gives only momentary relief from the pervasive miasma of dead fish and decaying plant life that hangs over the still water near the shore.</description>
    <position x="40" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Gwenalion Fens, On the Shore">
    <description>The ground is wetter and the watery patches seem deeper as the land rolls down to the nearby lake.  Dried reeds carried by the lake's currents wash in near the shore to be bound together by tangled masses of water-weed, forming mounded hummocks that bob precariously on the surface of the water.  The floating mats are home to beavers, herons and other animals, and are probably sturdy enough to support your weight, assuming you can manage to leap over the gap between shore and hummock.</description>
    <position x="60" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Close to shore, the reed hummock jostles restlessly on slow, curling waves as half-seen creatures roll through the lake's dark waters.  The floating mat, only about fifteen paces across, is home to long-legged pipers and other marsh-dwellers who build their nests or dens in the hollow spaces between the dead reeds.  Drier ground stretches out to the northwest across a rippling band of muddy brown water.</description>
    <position x="80" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>The grass ripples as an unseen creature prowls through the fens in search of water or of prey.  Streaks of blue and red, yellow and brown all dart through the air as songbirds warble cheerfully in the sunlight, scratching for grains fallen from the wildflowers which mass on the fen's rolling landscape.</description>
    <description>Hoarse croaks fill the air as frogs join their voices with the shrill chirr of crickets in a nightly symphony of the reeds.  Fireflies sparkle in the darkness -- short flashes, long flashes, complicated patterns of light designed to attract just the right mate.</description>
    <position x="40" y="104" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>A musky odor wafts through the air, concentrated around a dark hole about a handspan in diameter that opens in the side of a spongy tussock.  The portal, too small for the blood and bone wolves which haunt the local forests, is half hidden behind a fallen log which shelters it from the elements.</description>
    <position x="0" y="104" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mucky trail" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Dappled patches of sunlight dance across the grassy fens beneath the leaves of a cluster of birch trees.  A weathered bench leans against one tree.  The waist-high brush which covers the field is lower here, and an oddly tranquil aura lingers.  Sweet-scented lemon balm grows with lavender and bog myrtle attracting butterflies and thumb-sized bumble-bees that drone drowsily as they fly about.</description>
    <description>Shimmering moonbeams dance across the dark grass beneath the leaves of a cluster of birch trees.  A weathered bench leans against one tree.  The waist-high brush which covers the field is lower here, and an oddly tranquil aura lingers.  Sweet-scented lemon balm, lavender and bog myrtle fill the night air with a compelling fragrance, redolent of incense.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trail" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Gaily colored butterflies flit from blossom to blossom, alighting briefly to sip nectar before floating aimlessly on to the next flower.  A few linger to fan their wings on the edges of water-filled footprints left by those who travel the fens.  The air is humid, hanging heavily on skin and clothing, and filled with the cloying, sweet stench of death and decay.</description>
    <position x="20" y="84" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Gwenalion Fens">
    <description>Dense thickets border the fens to the north and east making the forest beyond impassable.  In the distance, sparkling reflections dance about as the sunlight reflects off patches of water visible through the mounds of sedge and other plant life.</description>
    <description>Dark thickets border the fens to the north and east making the forest beyond impassable.  In the distance, a gentle glimmer of moonlight reflects off patches of water visible through the mounds of sedge and other plant life.</description>
    <position x="20" y="64" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Time, wind and rain wash the reeds, sweeping clean the dirt and mud of the shore and leaving behind a weathered greyish-tan coating.  Each hummock lasts but a year or two before winter storms batter it to pieces, but those same storms sweep in more reeds to take their place.  Through it all, the otters, beavers and water voles which occupy the hummocks placidly adapt, moving their homes as needed.</description>
    <position x="60" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>The faint tang of wood smoke drifts across the water but the source cannot be seen.  Long-legged waterbugs skitter across the lake near the hummock, their feet causing momentary ripples which disturb the glassine surface.  Once in a while a fish darts to the surface to implement the lake's revenge or, to the more pragmatic, collect its own dinner.</description>
    <position x="100" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Rocking dizzily with each footstep, the hummock floats low in the lake.  Water oozes up between the reeds and trickles unevenly from an abandoned otter's den, foreshadowing the eventual dissolution of the structure.</description>
    <position x="120" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>The cool water of the lake glimmers softly in the sunlight, inviting observers to dive in and swim.  But dark shadowy figures are faintly visible beneath the surface like unseen monsters lurking beneath a child's bed.</description>
    <description>Moonlight glimmers softly against the cool water of the lake, inviting observers to dive in and swim.  But dark shadowy figures writhe beneath the surface, barely visible beneath the blanket of night, like nightmarish monsters lurking beneath a child's bed.</description>
    <position x="120" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Like amber beads scattered against a glimmering silver tray, the islets bob in the darkened waters, shifting and rolling with the current.  Sunlight glistens brightly against the shallow waves, making it necessary to squint in order to see clearly.</description>
    <description>Fireflies float lazily over the water, each wink of light reflecting against the darkened surface, distorted by the slight ripple of waves.  Surrounding hummocks glimmer faintly as tangles of phosphorescent mosses glow amidst the weeds, floating like luminous jewels in the dark waters of the lake.</description>
    <position x="120" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>The hummock creaks and crackles underfoot, but the tangle of moss which binds the reeds seems to be holding.  In the water, fish rise to the surface.  Birds swirl overhead.  And in the fens, life goes on, nature looking neither ahead nor behind, but simply living for the moment.</description>
    <position x="100" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>A cool wind blows off the lake, ameliorating the sun's heat trapped in the reeds underfoot.  At night, the heat is released, maintaining a relatively constant temperature on the hummock.</description>
    <position x="80" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Occasional flashes of blue near the shore mark the activities of a family of kingfishers plying their trade on the lake's fish.  From time to time, one of the birds will circle over the reeds, suddenly diving into the water to hopefully rise with the family's dinner.</description>
    <position x="80" y="224" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Close examination of the floating mound reveals a high proportion of bladderweed tangled amidst the dried reeds.  Whether by accident or design, the air trapped in the bladders helps support the island in the water.  Eventually a storm or time will dissolve the bindings, and the fens will gain a bit more area as this islet becomes part of the shoreline and more dried reeds drift in to take the place of the outer isles.</description>
    <position x="80" y="244" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Despite the surrounding water, the dense-packed reeds retain the heat from the sun, making the hummocks warm underfoot.  A gap between the branches marks the opening to a beaver's den near the leeward side of the islet.</description>
    <description>Vague tendrils of fog coil and curl around the island's surface as the dense-packed reeds slowly release the sun's warmth.  In the nearby water, a fish or small insect rises to the surface, sending concentric rings of reflected moonlight rippling outward before being absorbed into the placid calmness of the lake.</description>
    <position x="80" y="264" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Reeds shift underfoot as they work loose from the weeds which hold them tangled together.  The quiet lap of water against the reeds is broken from time to time by a hoarse roar or a shrill whistle as some unseen predator seeks out his prey.</description>
    <position x="100" y="244" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>A sour smell reminiscent of spoiled milk lingers near a patch of oily black mud.  Closer examination reveals claw marks on the surrounding reeds, as if something had tried to tear the hummock apart beneath its feet.</description>
    <position x="100" y="204" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Gwenalion Fens, Dried Reed Hummock">
    <description>Sunlight sparkles painfully against the rippling surface of the surrounding lake making it a strain to distinguish details against the glare.  Several small hummocks float near this one, just a brief jump away over the water.</description>
    <description>Moonlight, cool and soothing, glimmers gently against the rippling surface of the lake.  The mist rising from the water makes it hard to distinguish details about the surroundings, but several small hummocks not much different from this one float in the nearby water.</description>
    <position x="120" y="224" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="North Road, Stone Bridge">
    <description>The stone bridge arches over the water toward the north, where it descends into the dense trees of the Danduwen Forest.  A glistening white balustrade borders the bridge, protecting the many caravans that cross it from straying off its sides.  Undulating forms of several river trout lie in the shadowy water below.  The southern shore extends toward the wooden dwellings of Langenfirth, almost hidden in the trees.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-316" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go southern shore" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="North Road, Stone Bridge">
    <description>Below the stone bridge the water gurgles pleasantly as it meanders over rocks and branches.  Natterjack toads croak their mating calls with throaty rattles that provide a percussive accompaniment to the river's song.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="North Road, Stone Bridge">
    <description>Ripples show on the surface of the water below, where occasional brown water rats swim silently to their homes among the gnarled tree roots that grow on the sandy banks.  The stone bridge ends at the northern shore which is bordered by a dense woodland.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go northern shore" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="North Road, River's Edge">
    <description>Wild orchids grow along the northern bank of the Gwenalion River, their nodding purple heads mirrored in the still water below.  The road penetrates the Danduwen Forest to the north, and a stone bridge leads back toward the small community of Langenfirth to the south.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone bridge" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" note="RTT16|RT-LB-MF|Danduwen Forest|Forest" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The melancholy cry of a riverbird comes from the south, where the Gwenalion River meanders past the rustic dwellings of Langenfirth.  Dense woodlands to the north press up against the waterway's coastline, and judging from the array of twitters and rustling branches, they provide shelter for a rich variety of wildlife.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-396" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The road travels at a fairly steep slant over inland hills, meandering through the thick woods of old eucalyptus trees with drooping long leaves, tattered bark and heady fragrance.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-416" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go twisting trail" destination="287" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#008000">
    <description>Sweet rush bushes line the roadway, their crinkled leaves emitting a fruity scent.  The fragrance has attracted a multitude of purple emperor butterflies that flutter over the bushes in a graceful dance.</description>
    <description>A sweet, fruity scent fills the night air, radiating from the dark bushes that line the roadway.  Large moths flutter past you occasionally, their pale wings shimmering in the moonlight.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-436" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shaded path" destination="299" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" note="RTT15|RT-LB-T" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Hedges of primroses and sunny yellow cat's-ear edge the road, adding a festive and fragrant border to the towering trees.  Occasionally, tiny brown woodmice dart out of the hedges, quickly grabbing seeds from the ground and scampering back into their flowery home.</description>
    <description>Hedges of primroses and cat's-ear edge the road, adding a fragrant border to the towering trees.  Occasionally, tiny brown woodmice dart out of the hedges, quickly grabbing seeds from the ground and scampering back into their flowery home.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-456" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The road cuts through deep, dark forest where overhanging branches form a leafy canopy that blocks out most of the light.  Here and there twiggy willow warbler nests can be seen sheltered in the limbs overhead.  Their inhabitants warble melodious greetings to travelers on the road far below them.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-476" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Heavily leafed branches arc above the roadway, reaching out to intertwine with others.  Only stray, narrow beams of daylight manage to penetrate the thick foliage.  A host of gatekeeper butterflies with iridescent orange and brown wings flutter through the beams like brilliant tropical fish swimming in the green-tinted light of the forest.</description>
    <description>Scant light from the night skies filters through the dense overhanging branches that arc above the roadway.  Dark leafy shapes loom ominously, rustling and whispering in the night's breeze.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-496" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#008000">
    <description>The hum of cicadas disrupts the stillness, echoing through the trees and filling the forest with an eerie whir.  From somewhere off to the northwest, the occasional splash of water blends in with the arboreal chorus.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-516" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#008000">
    <description>An ancient eucalyptus tree lays along the side of the road, its peeling trunk and barren branches blocking the way to a clearing off to the west.  Soft chittering noises coming from the tree's twisted roots indicate that some life still resides here.  Glimpses of sparkling water can be seen beyond the fallen trunk.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-536" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go eucalyptus tree" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb adult log" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Crystal clear water rushes around a path of smooth greyish boulders that poke out of the stream at irregular intervals across its width.  Drooping branches shed their leaves along the shoreline, filling the air with a rich peaty aroma.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-536" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go eucalyptus tree" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>A kingfisher's nest is nestled in the thick branches of a fallen tree that stretches out into the water.  Every once in a while, a brilliantly feathered bird darts out from the nest and dives toward the rushing water, quickly picking up food for its offspring.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-516" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The splashing waters of the stream spills down from one miniature pool to another, as it follows the steady incline of the sloping land.  Far overhead a glimpse of a swooping bird of prey can be seen as it pursues an unsuspecting victim.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-496" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>Mounds of watercress grow along the shoreline here, thriving in the wet soil.  The stream ripples as a speckled brown trout snatches a needlenose bug from the water's surface before the strong current whisks it away.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-476" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The water babbles melodically as it rushes between rounded boulders of granite that protrude from the stream's bed.  The rocks extending across the stream form a natural bridge but appear far too slick to be used.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-456" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The stream rushes over small granite slabs, and then almost vanishes beneath a thick screen of rhododendron and willow trees along the far bank.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-436" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The stream's current is strong here as it cuts its way through the deep wooded valley.  The air is heavy with the fragrance of eucalyptus and sweet rush.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-416" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>Abundant growths of marsh woundwort twist around the reeds and rocks on the stream's shoreline.  Occasional sounds of passing caravans can be heard rumbling and creaking along the road off to the east.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-396" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The humid air along the stream is filled with the drone and buzz of insects.  The groves of rushes and reeds here provide home to dragonflies, damselflies and needlenose bugs.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The grassy banks along the stream slope gently upward to meet the trees.  A shimmer of color and a rippling along the water's surface can be seen as a trout feasts on the many insects attracted by the moist air.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Woodlands, Forest Stream">
    <description>The heavy forest closes in here, forming an impenetrable wall to the south.  A small patch of particularly fine blackberry bushes attracts squirrels and red foxes from their sheltered home in the trees.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Dark Thicket, Tall Trees">
    <description>The close-knit trees create a dense growth of leaves and branches that catches the light and transmutes it into cool green shadows which overlap onto the forest floor.  A wind stirs the branches, causing them to rustle and whisper to one another in secretive harmony.</description>
    <description>The close-knit trees create a dense growth of foliage that heightens the deep wells of shadows which pool around the base of the trees.  A shimmering gauze of spiderwebs hangs between the trees, the moonlight catching on the droplets of water that dangle from the strands and turning the delicate constructions into shimmering silver lace.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="search go forest trail" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Dark Thicket, Shrouded Clearing" note="Dark Thicket|Huntress|pilgrim's badge|altar|shrine-2-11" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>The trees form a loose horseshoe around this dark green clearing, the heavy foliage from the various oaks and ash that grow here weaving a tangled canopy and creating a deep gloom which falls like a shroud over everything.  Pushed up against the very center of the "shoe" is a statue of a woman holding a basin in her hands.  A faint forest trail leads off from where the grove opens up, slicing neatly through a second growth of trees before vanishing.</description>
    <description>The trees form a loose horseshoe around this dark green clearing.  Pushed up against the very center of the "shoe" is a statue.  A faint forest trail leads off from where the grove opens up.</description>
    <description>The trees form a horseshoe around the dark green clearing, the heavy foliage from the various oaks and ash that grow abundantly here weaving a tangled canopy which blocks light with the completeness of death.  Pushed up against the very center of the "shoe" is a magnificent statue of a proud-faced woman holding a basin in her hands.  A faint forest trail leads off from where the grove opens up, slicing neatly through a second growth of trees before vanishing into the woods.</description>
    <description>The trees form a horseshoe around the dark green clearing.  Pushed up against the very center of the "shoe" is a magnificent statue of a proud-faced woman.  A faint forest trail leads off from where the grove opens up, slicing neatly through a second growth of trees.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go forest trail" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="North Road, Danduwen Forest" color="#008000">
    <description>The path winds its way through a small valley, sheltered between the surrounding forested hills.  Small clumps of aromatic fleabane border the roadway, attracting an array of speckled wood butterflies that hover and flit from plant to plant.</description>
    <description>The path winds its way through a small valley, sheltered between the surrounding forested hills.  Small clumps of aromatic fleabane border the roadway, attracting an array of spotted moths that swoop and flutter from plant to plant.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-556" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb young log" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="North Road, Beech Grove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The well-traveled road journeys through a grove of tall beech trees.  Their smooth grey boles converge high above creating a tunnel filled with dappled green sunlight.  Off to the north the grove opens up onto bright meadowlands.</description>
    <description>The well-traveled road journeys through a grove of tall beech trees.  Their smooth grey boles converge high above creating a tunnel of dark shadowy branches that seem to reach out to you.  Off to the north the grove opens up onto moonlit meadowlands.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb young log" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Beech Grove, Trail">
    <description>The grove continues, the beeches lining the trail and forming a tunnel of shelter.  Dry leaves from past autumns rustle with each footstep, while light dapples through the branches above.</description>
    <description>The grove continues, the beeches lining the trail and forming a tunnel of shelter.  Dry leaves from past autumns rustle with each footstep, and the night air is thick with the odors of the cycle of decay and life.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Outside the Circle, The Ironwoods" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Two closely-spaced ironwood trees stand at the end of a tunnel of beech branches and boles.  A friendly-looking young ranger stands at guard, ready to alert her mates about any unwelcome visitors, or greet those who have found their way home.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood trees" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="El'Bain's Stop, Store" note="El'Bain's Stop|ElBain's Stop">
    <description>Though positioned on the edge of the forest, El'Bain's Stop could easily be in the depth of the wilds.  Surrounded by trees and home to many small critters, the wayside is an excellent place to rest and stock up on supplies.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small path" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go store" destination="248" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="El'Bain's Stop, Quiet Walk">
    <description>As if spaced by a gardener's hand, the path is flanked by neatly rowed trees.  The silent giants offer their shade and windbreak, allowing this walk to be calm, quiet, and peaceful.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="El'Bain's Stop, Quiet Walk">
    <description>Through the silence created by the nearby trees, the sound of quick flowing water pushes through, offering to satiate thirst.</description>
    <description>Through the silence created by the nearby trees, the sound of quick flowing water pushes through, offering to satiate thirst.  Faintly, in the distance, a queer howl sings to the darkened sky.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="El'Bain's Stop, Stream">
    <description>The path ends here, meeting a fast rising hillside.  At the base of the hill runs a small stream which is shaded by a few small trees and a number of ferns.  The never ending sounds of the flowing water creates an enticing, relaxing melody which can ease both the mind and the body.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go overgrown trail" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>The road travels from the southern deep forests, swinging toward the west where the valley broadens exposing vast expanses of sky over wild and windswept moors.  A mournful call resounds, as a lone hawk soars overhead.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Fields of slender marsh bedstraw undulate in the breeze, rippling like waves on an ocean of green.  An old wooden sign stands askew next to the road, its surface worn and cracked.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Low hills and small valleys stretch out endlessly in all directions.  Ripe gooseberries, foxgloves and bracken vie for space in the hedgerows that border the road.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-616" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>The moors rise up along low hills on either side of the road.  A faint mist hangs over the air, leaching the colors of the land into shades of greyish-green.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Wild lavender stalks mixed amongst bramble bushes cover the hillsides on each side of the road, filling the air with a spicy fragrance.  Nectar-seeking butterflies and bees hover over the purple blossoms.</description>
    <description>Shadowy bushes cover the hillsides on each side of the road.  A soft breeze stirs up, rustling the bushes and sending a spicy fragrance wafting through the air.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Wild gorse blossoms splash patches of bright yellow across the countryside.  A broken wagon wheel lays discarded on the side of the road, probably abandoned there by some hurried caravan driver.</description>
    <description>Wild gorse blossoms splash patches of murky ochre across the countryside.  A broken wagon wheel lays discarded on the side of the road, probably abandoned there by some hurried caravan driver.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Thickets of heather grow across the fields, adding a strident purple to the vista.  Fat bumble bees buzz industriously as they dart from flower to flower.</description>
    <description>Silhouetted thickets grow across the fields surrounding the road, creating a vista of dark shadowy forms that dot the countryside.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>The path meanders over low headlands here.  Stretching across the hills and valleys in all directions, the sheep-studded lonely moorlands create a breathtaking vista of wild, untamed lands.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-716" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Fields of wild cotton-grass spread across the moors as far as the eye can see.  The road here is packed to a hard surface from the multitude of wagon wheels and yak hooves that have traveled it over the years.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-736" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="North Road, Dunshade Moors">
    <description>Just to the north an alder thicket stands out along the grass-covered moorlands.  Many of the trees, planted long ago to offer shelter from the elements, have been misshapen by the wind.  From a distance they look somewhat like a group of bent and gnarled old men leaning on each other for support.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-756" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="North Road, Alder Thicket">
    <description>Drifts of narcissus grow under the alder trees, their brilliant white blossoms covering the ground like snowy mounds that shift and ripple in the breeze.  The soft rustle of the alder leaves brushing against each other accompanies the graceful movement of the flowers.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-776" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>Bashful wood anemones peek out from beneath the shrubs that grow alongside the road, brightened by the bolder starry flowers of wild garlic.  A small grove of twisted alder trees stands to the south.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-796" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>A sweet, heady fragrance wafts through the air, coming from the tiny honeysuckle blossoms that ramble through the tangled hedges that border the road.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-816" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>Steep embankments climb high along the sides of the road, strewn with wild daffodils whose diminutive blossoms dance in the periodic gentle breezes of the meadowlands.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-836" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Pathway, Recent Work">
    <description>A mixture of smoothed cobblestone and vibrant moss has been carefully arranged to form a road that bends to the northwest.  The brush along each side of the road has been trimmed back, leaving only the slightest overhang from tall trees that provide intermittent shade.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-816" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Pathway, Ups and Downs">
    <description>The road appears to be new and largely unused, with very few signs of age or wear marring the stones.  After a slight incline it runs down along a few small hills,  rising and falling with the natural elevations as it meanders through the forest.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-836" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Pathway, Small Clearing">
    <description>While the area directly around the road itself is cleared, the foliage becomes much more dense further away from the path.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-836" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Pathway, Benches">
    <description>Large rectangular boulders have been placed along the roadside, providing a place for travelers to sit and rest and catch their breath.  This wide part of the road even allows enough clearance for a heavily laden caravan to pause, out of the way of bothersome traffic.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-856" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Pathway, Vine-Covered Boles">
    <description>The gentle curves of the road mimic the vines that curl through the brush and around the trees.  Each tendril forms an intricate design against the host trunk as it trails down to the ground, abruptly ending where the foliage has been cut back by fastidious caretakers.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-876" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Pathway, The Fork">
    <description>To the north, the road splits around a large tree that has been spared, one lane passing on either side of the massive trunk of this stately old forest denizen.  The area under the tree is neatly manicured, and a few tables and benches are sheltered under its branches, creating a peaceful place to stop for a picnic or merely to rest weary feet.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-896" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Pathway, Around the Trunk">
    <description>The roadway bends around the eastward side of the tree in a wide circle.  Within the arc, the tops of gnarled roots break the surface here and there, and the builders of the road have taken pains to avoid disturbing them with the paving stones.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-916" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Pathway, The Fork">
    <description>To the south, the cobbled way splits to avoid a large tree, the forks of the road diverging to circle the ground beneath its wide-spreading limbs.  The boughs of the tree almost appear to unfold and direct travelers approaching from the northwest to either side of its trunk.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-936" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Pathway, Around the Trunk">
    <description>Sturdy branches of the big tree to the east overhang the road, and under their shade the road is more moss than cobblestone, hushing each footfall.  The quiet of the scene is a peaceful change from ringing hoofbeats and rattling wagons on the rest of the road.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-916" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Pathway, Flowered Beds">
    <description>A straight stretch of the road runs through carefully tended surroundings.  Widely spaced trees line the thoroughfare, their branches forming a leafy arch overhead.  Travelers along the road pass colorful beds of flowers and decorative bushes between the trees.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-956" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Pathway, Cobbled Walk">
    <description>Cobblestones crowd close together here, leaving less room for moss to grow between the stones.  Along each side of the paving, plush beds of green sod have been laid to replace the unruly wild grasses.  Beyond the cultivated roadside stand the forest trees.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-976" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Pathway, Arboreal Gateway">
    <description>Majestic old trees appear in the distance on either side of the road, but close by, in place of what used to grow wild and free, intertwined saplings and decorative shrubs have been planted in a more formal arrangement.  Behind the entryway through this arbor, borders of stone keep the wilderness beyond from encroaching.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-996" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Pathway, Patterned Walk">
    <description>The meandering road continues, and the stones themselves begin to form a pattern.  A multitude of tiny dark and light stones have been placed to create a slightly inset maze-like design centered in the well-paved road.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-1016" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Pathway, The Clearing">
    <description>A large black marble edifice stands in the clearing, nestled snuggly at the base of the nearby mountains.  Veins of silver and gold intertwine uninterrupted along the stonework, and closer inspection reveals nary a visible seam anywhere along the outer wall.  At first glance, the building would appear to be formed from a single solid piece of rock, although that's entirely impossible.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-1036" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="El'Bain's Stop, Cabin">
    <description>The sounds of traveler	s can be heard from the main road, but the voices are faint and hard to distinguish.  Though touched by civilization's hand, the encroaching trees and chattering critters leave no doubt that nature rules here.  A small log cabin rests on the edge of the path.</description>
    <description>The sounds of travelers can be heard from the main road, but the voices are faint and hard to distinguish.  Though touched by civilization's hand, the encroaching trees and chattering critters leave no doubt that nature rules here.  A small log cabin rests on the edge of the path.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-616" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="321" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="El'Bain's Stop, Cabin">
    <description>Cutting through the forest's vegetation this packed path is used fairly often, if the numerous footprints are any indication.  The trail rises slightly to the northeast and levels out to the southwest, connecting two small log cabins.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="El'Bain's Stop, Cabin">
    <description>At the end of the path rests a small cabin, cradled gently in the arms of ancient firs.  Though the way is neatly cut-back, it appears that the wilds could take this place at any moment.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="'Neer's Hummock, Game Trail">
    <description>The smooth, cool sounds of running water from below rise up to this small trail.  Shrub trees and thick brambles cover the trail's rise, making the wetness below all the more tempting.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-616" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go running water" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="'Neer's Hummock, Game Trail">
    <description>Tiny black and green droppings lining the trail mark its frequent use.  Dense coverage of low trees and thorny bushes slow travel here, even for animals equipped with thick hide.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="347" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Kweld Andu, Narrow Ledge">
    <description>Formed by the remains of a long abandoned road, this narrow ledge appears to be unused even by the local animals.  The path drops to the northeast where a large formation of stones flank the pathway.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-616" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Kweld Andu, Pathway's End">
    <description>Abruptly ending at a great wall of soil, this path must have washed away in a slide.  Thick grass, large trees, and all types of roots have all taken hold here, displaying the stability and age of the surrounding earth.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-616" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dirt bank" destination="353" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Kweld Andu, Broken Road">
    <description>On either side of the ancient roadway, smooth, sheer rocks rise suddenly like the arms of a buried worshiper seeking the forgiveness of his god.  The high cliffs force the path to shrink but the absence of vegetation, wildlife, and the normal sounds of nature, makes the constricting feeling even stronger.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Kweld Andu, Warded Way">
    <description>The cliff walls strangle the road here.  The rocks lean inward as if to capture the insignificant travellers that walk below them.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Kweld Andu, Warded Way">
    <description>High, unscalable cliffs rise to the south, hugging the old roadway.  A huge, intricately carved gate, sculpted from the surrounding rock, blocks passage to the north.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone gate" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>The busy trade road travels a straight path through fields of wild geranium that stretch east and west to the horizon.  Growing untended, the reddened foliage and pale pink blossoms provide a colorful vista.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-856" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>The road passes over a high point in the hilly meadowlands.  Laid out below in all directions is a breathtaking panorama of lush fields of grasses decorated with vibrant patches of flowers.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-876" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>A riotous display of colors grows to either side of the north road here, giving the area a festive atmosphere.  Bold pink musk mallow reside alongside deep blue monkshood.  Occasionally, some of the travelers hurrying along the road will stop for a moment to take in the lovely view.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-896" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>A long stone bench has been placed along the roadside, offering a place for weary travelers to pause and rest before they continue on with their journeys.  Tufts of ground-hugging violets grow around the bench.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-916" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>An oddly-shaped stone stands next to the road, resembling a hunched Dwarf surveying those who pass before him.  Some voyager has hung a garland of sunflowers around his neck.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-936" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>The road narrows as it cuts through steep banks that ascend at sharp inclines to either side.  Feathery Therengian ferns peek over the ridge, shading the brightly colored primulas that adorn the banks.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-936" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>Acres of brilliant red poppies and tall sunflowers spread out from either side of the road.  The flowers nod and sway, turning their bright faces up to catch the light.</description>
    <description>Acres of dark reddish poppies and tall sunflowers spread out from either side of the road.  The silhouetted shapes of the sunflowers nod and sway in a graceful nocturnal dance.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-956" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>Towering wisteria bushes press against the road, their cascading violet blossoms graced with a gathering of swallowtail butterflies.</description>
    <description>Towering wisteria bushes press against the road, their cascading blossoms emitting a sweet, spicy perfume into the night air.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-976" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="North Road, Meadow">
    <description>A scented breeze wafts down from the surrounding hills that are clothed in wild herbs.  To the north an orchard of apple trees stands over thickly-grassed pastures.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-996" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="North Road, Orchards">
    <description>A bountiful abundance of ripe apples grows in the squat trees, shining crimson and gold amongst the glossy green leaves.  Here and there, bushel baskets have been left at the base of the trees, waiting for the next harvest.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-1016" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="North Road, Orchards">
    <description>Deep in the orchard, an ancient apple tree grows, a great-grandfather presiding over his surrounding offspring.  Crabbed, wizened and stooped, his lichened flanks are covered with a tangle of tree creeper vines.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-1036" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="North Road, Orchards">
    <description>The young apple trees that grow here provide a canopy of white apple blossoms that send petals drifting lazily to the ground like falling snow.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-1056" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="North Road, Orchards">
    <description>A flock of butterflies with orange-tipped wings flutters and swims through the rays of greenish light that shine through the dense trees.  The ground is scattered with ripe apples that have dropped from the heavy branches above.  Several piles of cores indicate that many travelers have helped themselves to the free fruit.</description>
    <description>Pale beams of moonlight shine through the dense trees.  The ground is scattered with ripe apples that have dropped from the heavy branches above.  Several piles of cores indicate that many travelers have helped themselves to the free fruit.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-1076" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="North Road, Farmlands" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Hillsides ridged with lavender surround the meandering road.  The air is heavy with a spicy perfume and the hum of contented bees.  A wooden farmer's fruitstand sits to one side of the road, offering fresh produce from the area.</description>
    <description>Darkly silhouetted hills surround the meandering road.  The air is heavy with a spicy perfume and the peaceful song of crickets.  A wooden farmer's fruitstand sits to one side of the road, its entryway closed up for the night.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-1096" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>The northern road journeys through groves of olive trees with vine-twisted trunks and glossy leaves.  The rich reddish-brown soil of the area has been well-tended with not a weed in sight.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-1116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>The surrounding, gracefully-sloping hillsides are thickly carpeted with juniper, thyme and rosemary that fill the air with a fresh herbal fragrance.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-1136" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go road" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>Produce-filled wagons belonging to local farmers join the frequent trader caravans and groups of adventurers that travel this road.  To either side, gently sloping farmlands stretch out to the horizon.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-1156" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>The road winds lazily, cutting a path through fertile straths and peat-stained creeks.  Here and there in the distance, quaint farmhouses with accompanying barns can be seen.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-1176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>The road meanders through lowland pastures covered with lush clover and grasses.  Black and white spotted cows graze placidly, eyeing passing travelers with only mild interest.</description>
    <description>The road meanders through lowland pastures covered with lush clover and grasses.  Dark forms of sleeping cows can be seen to either side, and an occasional drowsy 'moo' breaks the stillness of the night.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-1196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="North Road, Farmlands" note="RTT23|RT-T-LB" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Tawny acres of birch trees and furlongs of picturesque crofter's cottages spread out across the land, forming an enchanting panorama of Therengian farmland.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-1196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>The North Road winds through a glen of fertile farmland, with neatly cultivated fields of barley and tobacco on either side.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-1216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>Tall stalks of golden sweetcorn grow in patches alongside the road.  A whimsical scarecrow watches over the crops, discouraging the hungry crows that fly overhead eagerly eyeing the corn.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-1236" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="North Road, Farmlands">
    <description>Row after row of tidily formed haystacks fill the field to one side of the road.  A fenced-in pasture borders the other side, and the hollow clonk of cowbells resounds as grazing cows occasionally amble over to the fence to peer at the stacks with interest.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-1256" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go nearby field" destination="316" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="North Road, Barony Pass">
    <description>Acres of fertile farmland stretch out to the south.  Glimpses of tall, turreted towers can be seen to the north, slipping in and out of view beyond the treetops.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-1276" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="North Road, Barony Pass">
    <description>As the road twists and turns through sloping hills, slate roofs and buff-colored buildings surrounding a turreted castle can be glimpsed beyond the shoulders of the hills to the north.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-1296" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="North Road, Barony Pass" note="gate to Therenborough|Kraelyst start point|travel start point" color="#808000">
    <description>With one final sweep, the road straightens out from the hilly pastures in the south to stop at a walled village.  Looming above the stone boundary is the majestic Theren Keep, its battered towers still an imposing sight to behold.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-1316" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go town gate" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dusty trail" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone wall" destination="212" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A deep green lawn spotted with yellow daisies rises up from the dirt road and leads toward a colorful, eclectic neighborhood.  Juniper trees, cultivated with a concerted effort at lifesculpting, stand in little circles across the lawn, until the boundary of a home curtails the grass with a stunning wall of wild rosemary.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-1316" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dusty trail" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go graveled path" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Therenborough, Town Gate" note="Map42_Therenborough_and_Keep.xml|Therenborough">
    <description>The imposing turreted towers of Theren Keep dominate this inland town, standing proud against the sky and seen plainly from every vantage point in the area.  Walls of massive stone surround the small, but bustling community, and beyond the open gates to the south are rolling pastures and distant farmsteads.  The pedestrians milling around the gate are periodically forced to step aside as paladins in gleaming plate armor ride by on magnificent steeds, heading north toward the castle.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-1356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Theren Road">
    <description>Dust kicks up in swirls among the brambles which accent the exterior of Therenborough.  A straight, flat road runs due west from the thorny corridor created by the break between mortared stone and resident flora.  Ker'Leor, the majestic mountain range which some believe to be enchanted, rises like jagged teeth across the northwest horizon.  From the wall which rises nearby comes the cacophony of civilization.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-1316" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="rt west" destination="376" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wall" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Mistwood Forest Road" note="Map34_Mistwood_Forest.xml|Mistwood Forest|Rossman's Landing">
    <description>To the south, the rolling hills give way to orchards and neatly tended fields.  The road to Mistwood Forest stretches out to the south and east, branching off from the main North Road that connects Therenborough with the village of Langenfirth.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-1136" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go road" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="The Telgar Inn, Reception">
    <description>The reception area of this rustic inn is filled with odds, ends and historical memorabilia of Langenfirth's beginnings. The unfinished walls are all but covered with rough sketches, maps and clippings from scrolls.  The reception desk is a high, massive wood counter, hand rubbed to a glossy sheen.  Behind the desk the wall is filled from floor to ceiling with pigeonholes for holding mail and room keys.  Split log stairs lead upward to the guest rooms.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="The Telgar Inn, Tavern Room" note="Telgar Inn|Tavern Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The Telger Inn Tavern is known for its assortment of high quality local brews and fine imports.  Its kitchen offers the finest meals in the north, if your tastes run to fresh game and fish.  A large bar runs the width of the room, and a row of booths sits in the back.  The front of the tavern has several large tables to serve large groups of people.  The smell of roasting meat and fresh baking bread mingle with the sharper odor of newly brewed stout.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="The Telgar Inn, Game Room">
    <description>The walls in this room are adorned with stuffed and mounted bear heads, birds, fish and other game.  All are amazing specimens, most overly large for their species, obviously a great feat for the hunter or trapper responsible for their demise.  Several small gaming tables are scattered throughout the room.  A quiet game of cards is played unendingly by some of the towns elders.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="The Telgar Inn, Upstairs Hallway">
    <description>At the top of the stairs is the entrance to a large dormitory.  Down the hallway is a door to a more private room.  The hallway is unfurnished except for a lantern hanging from the ceiling and a ladder leading up to a loft area.  The wood floor is old and worn, warped and sagging from years of feet passing back and forth.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="go" move="wooden door" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entrance" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="The Telgar Inn, The Loft" note="Loft">
    <description>A tiny loft space is tucked up under the rafters of the peaked roof of the Inn.  A braided rug covers the rough board floor offering the only place to sit besides a trundle bed tucked to one side.  The room is usually the quarters of the tavern owner and his wife, but is occasionally used for guests when the Inn is very full so there is an absence of personal belongings.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="The Telgar Inn, Private Suite">
    <description>This is the best suite the Inn has to offer and is reserved for the town's most important guests or those with the most money.  A large window, which overlooks the great Langenfirth Tree, brightens the room with sunlight.  A large bed with a down mattress fills a good part of the room.  A small writing table with a comfortable chair has been placed near the window.</description>
    <description>This is the best suite the Inn has to offer and is reserved for the town's most important guests or those with the most money.  A large window, one of the few in the town with glass panes, is closed against the night's chill.  A large canopied bed with a down mattress fills a good part of the room.  A long white candle in a bronze candlestick flickers on a small writing table near the window.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="wooden door" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="The Telgar Inn, The Dormitory" note="Dormitory">
    <description>Most of the second floor is taken up by a huge communal dormitory for traders and trappers passing through the town.  Sunlight streams through a small window at one end of the room.  Large bunks run along the other walls of the room, comfortably spread with clean sheets and warm, although well-used, wool blankets.</description>
    <description>Most of the second floor is taken up by this huge communal dormitory for traders and trappers passing through the town.  The soft glow of a lantern lights the room enough so late arrivals do not stub a toe, but it is not bright enough to bother the sleepers.  Large bunks run along the other walls of the room, many of which are already occupied by tired travellers.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hall door" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Langenfirth, Kamze's Repairs" note="Kamze's Repair|Repair" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Several windows in the cabin's walls allow the breeze to enter and fill the room with the scent of the forest.  Kamze stands behind a tall wooden counter littered with leather armor in various stages of repair.  An ebonwood longbow hangs on the wall beside a sign made from a tanned Inkhorne pelt.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-216" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Ranger Guild, Courtyard">
    <description>A neatly kept yard covered with wispy grass surrounds a large log building with a high-peaked, green roof.  A wooden door swings back and forth on a creaky hinge in the front of the cabin.  The courtyard opens up to spacious yards on both sides.  From the distance the twanging of bow strings and the thunk of arrows hitting their mark can be heard.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple lean-to" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Ranger's Guild, Practice Yard">
    <description>Along the far side of the yard are split logs propped upright with targets drawn on them.  Many arrows are imbedded in the wood, although some have missed their mark and lay scattered about the yard.  Several bowman stand about testing the pull of their bows and examine the arrows stacked in their quivers.</description>
    <description>Utter darkness under the trees prevents identification of the source of sounds in the underbrush by sight.  The occasional whisper of a branch brushing against something could be anything from the passing of a large animal, a person or simply a stray breeze.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="The Rangers' Guild, Practice Yard">
    <description>The area here has been set aside for the practice of woodland and survival skills.  Several pits have been dug to be used for building and lighting fires and to use as cooking sites.  A half finished lean-to stands near a corner of the yard, and a pile of wood, much of which is partly carved into what eventually will be useful items, sits in another.</description>
    <description>Utter darkness under the trees prevents identification of the source of sounds in the underbrush by sight.  The occasional whisper of a branch brushing against something could be anything from the passing of a large animal, a person or simply a stray breeze.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-156" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="The Fur Exchange, Trading Office" note="Clerk|Minister|Outpost">
    <description>The Exchange is one of the busiest places in Langenfirth.  Hunters and trappers arrive constantly with new piles of hides and pelts from the northern hills.  Traders regularly arrive delivering goods from the south or looking for some select furs to buy on speculation.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-126" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Abotenik's Pawnshop, Frontroom" note="Abotenik's Pawnshop|Bynari|Pawn" color="#00FF00">
    <description>An amazing assortment of goods is strewn about the shop.  Items covered with dust as old as the glaciers, are tucked in every nook and cranny and nearly-new items from Riverhaven and Crossing shops fill one wall.  Used and outdated fishing and trapping gear are stacked in piles everywhere.  Bynari Abotenik, the eldest son, is spreading the piles to air out the more pungent odors.  He works his way back to the stone counter glancing at you occasionally to see if you have your wares ready.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Smells Like a Rat" note="Smells Like a Rat|Willurde|Rugs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Mangy pelts of all shapes, sizes and scents cover the floor, though exactly which animal is represented by what pile of fur is anyone's guess.  It's all the same to the shop owner, since his price never varies no matter what rag a foolhardy soul deigns to carry away.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Furs and Furnishings, Sales Room" note="Furs and Furnishings|Furniture" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The scrubbed pine walls and floor of D'ianrey Peral's tiny cabin are cluttered with animal skins and simple wooden furnishings, each item perfectly preserved and as rich in color as the day it was culled.  D'ianrey's tanned Elven features glow with quiet pride as she allows customers to browse amongst her inventory of rustic crafts, each bed and hammock and rug from her hand imbued with the spirit of the wilds which she embodies.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Hayseed and Hatchet" note="Hayseed and Hatchet|Xlaie" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Piles of fragrant pine sticks and sweet-smelling hay lend a pleasant, woodsy fragrance to this tiny shop.  An underlying aroma of damp earth wafts around the room, drifting off a pile of crudely-shaped mud and straw bricks stacked against the back wall.  Xlaie, a stoop-shouldered Human woman of indeterminate age, leans casually against a splintered pine counter in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Hayseed and Hatchet, Door Stack">
    <description>Stacks of doors lie haphazardly on top of each other, cluttering the narrow entrance to this ragged lean-to.  Leaning against the weathered plank walls, more doors threaten to topple like dominoes if disturbed by an inquisitive hand or a brief gust of breeze from the open back of the building.  Work benches and tools crowd the dirt floor, and a faint smell of damp wood fills the air.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Net and Bait, Fish Market" note="Net and Bait|Fish Market|Lodo" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The market reeks of fish although it sells a variety of goods.  Once nothing more than a shop for bait, it now buys the local catch and sells many sundries along with the fish to travelers and locals alike.  A large barrel marked Today's Special sits in a corner near the door.  Shelves of sundries line the wall and there is a selection of tackle along another.  The sound of fish being slapped hard on wood, and the rending sound of a knife through scales is heard from the back.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Brother Yorgi, Herbalist" note="Brother Yorgi|Yorgi|Herbs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>An ancient empath putters about the shop, tending small pots of herbs.  He seems to mutter constantly, either to himself or to his plants.  His goods are stored on shelves in various clay jars and, since none are labeled, it is hoped that the good Yorgi knows what is in them.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Calliana Leather Goods, Salesroom" note="Calliana Leather Goods|Leather" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The smell of freshly tanned leather is overwhelming.  Leather clothing, footwear and armors of many designs hang about the walls.  Calliana is young for an elf but spent many years as a Ranger until the loss of one eye forced her to retire to safer pastimes.  Her leatherworking skill is unsurpassed whether it is a new item or just the patching of an old piece.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go work room" destination="346" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Shalan's Peltry, Showroom" note="Shalan's Peltry|Bundles" color="#00FF00">
    <description>From the most casual of sportsman to the life-long hunt enthusiast, Shalan's Peltry offers a cozy, friendly place at which to conduct business after the hunt is over.  A jovial, well-respected native of Langenfirth, Mato Shalan is known for his fair appraisals and honest opinions.  Business is conducted informally around a circular table that dominates the center of the room.  A smaller table with several comfortable chairs provides a nice environment for casual discussion.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-156" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Shalan's Peltry, Tannery" note="Tannery|Kalayara" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Crates of tanning supplies are stacked in tall columns against the walls of this small back room.  A sharp, acrid smell can be detected despite the overlying sweetness of the scented candles burning about the room.  Among the crates stands a small oak table strewn with various tools and bits of leather.  A sturdy wooden plank serves as a counter for those wishing to make purchases.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-156" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Whimsical wind chimes dangle from trees and find similar perches on signposts and shrubs.  In spite of their overwhelming numbers, the chorus they produce is exceedingly soothing.  Along either side of a granite-strewn walkway are tufts of ornamental flowers, all low to the ground and caressing variegated sage.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-1336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dirt road" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A simple white-washed picket fence marks the boundary of the walkway as it traces its route along the edge of an L-shaped yard.  A dainty swing that would seat two or three small children sits forlornly on the grass, and oddly enough is surrounded by a vast assortment of pinwheels.  There are solitary pinwheels in pots, bouquets of pinwheels in great glass jars, and in between each slat of the picket fence is a double row of them -- one short, one tall.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-1336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Three shiny metal globes sit evenly spaced at the border of a yard of multi-colored grass.  Pastel ribbons criss-cross with seeming abandon over the more naturally occuring shades of green, each cut at a different height to add texture to the landscape.  Here and there in the chaotic mix is a cream-shaded ceramic pot displaying an odd arrangement of dried twigs, on which one finds an assortment of shells, beads, and arrow flights.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-1356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Sweet honeysuckle hedges border a grassy expanse punctuated by a large banyan.  The suspended roots of this ancient tree grow down to the ground at intervals to create natural nooks, where artisans have been known to gather for festivals or other neighborhood celebrations.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-1376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large banyan" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A large ditch filled with painted rocks runs along a bizarre pink lawn that leads to a handful of houses.  A layer of tin has been poured upon the sides of the ditch, so that they catch the light of the sun and reflect it back in a sparkling wash of silver.</description>
    <description>A large ditch filled with painted rocks runs along a bizarre pink lawn that leads to a handful of homes.  A layer of tin has been poured upon the sides of the ditch, so that they catch the scant light in the vicinity and reflect it back in a subtle glow of silver.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-1396" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Rainbow-hued foil hangs in an array of shapes that twist and twirl on a dead oak.  Every kiss of a breeze sets the entire collection to dancing in a surprisingly organized fashion.  There is a carving at the base of the tree, probably decades old, done in an Elothean artistic style.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-1416" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A large glass bowl filled with tiny jeweltone marbles sits upon a weathered table on an overgrown lawn.  Two candlesticks, clotted with layers of wax, lie haphazardly at its side.  The oddity of the scene becomes apparent only when you realize you are looking at a painting on the side of a stone wall -- the image is so perfect in perspective and detail, you could swear the weeds are bending in the wind.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-1416" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A snaking hedge of jasmine separates this quiet cul-de-sac from the rest of the neighborhood.  Several lifesculpted chairs surround a similarly crafted round table just beyond the hedge, right next to a wooden, hand-made set that looks rather shabby by comparison.  Two relatively young junipers stretch above the jasmine, reaching for the sky.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-1416" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Therenborough, Chanters' Retreat" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The rich soil underfoot gives up its heady aroma as one moves among the sturdy roots of this ancient banyan.  Though innumerable branches overhead are heavy with foliage, the roots themselves, which form several small alcoves, are ruddy and featureless.  Thoughtful residents have placed stone benches in a semi-circle about this side of the tree.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-1376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Northern Pride, Main Deck" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>This is the only barge of its type to ply the waters of Lake Gwenalion.  Ambitiously designed with an upper deck for passengers, its aft is completely given over to cargo.  Built recently, everything about it smacks of economy and minimalism.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="El'Bain's Stop, Picnic Area">
    <description>The quiet surroundings of this picnic area give weary travelers a short break before moving on.</description>
    <description>A singing bird, lost in the limbs of a nearby tree, pays respect to the tranquility of this rest area.  Somehow the simplistic chirping soothes tight muscles and suppresses life's worries.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go main road" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Bowyer Shop, Showroom" note="Bowyer Shop|Jarrod|Bows|Fletching" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The Bowyer, Jarrod, can supply the eager hunter with just about any finely crafted ranged weapon desired.  On display along the walls of the shop are fine bows and well-balanced arrows.  Jarrod is a wiry elf who has lived most his life in the northern hills.  His skill at his craft tends to make his items more expensive, but he is willing to dicker and loves a fair trade, as can be seen by the satisfied customers leaving happily with a purchase, and return buyers eagerly lining up to make a new selection.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go back room" destination="315" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Delkai's Store" note="Delkai's Store" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The thin, wooden slats which comprise the floor of this little store creak under the weight of customers who wander about, inspecting the goods.  Sitting near the back wall is Delkai Vendbit, who scribes endlessly in a leather-bound journal when he isn't busy helping patrons.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="The Beech Cordon, Inner Circle" note="Beech Cordon">
    <description>Two ironwood trees frame the entrance to a circle of fourteen evenly-spaced towering beech trees.  The branches arch high overhead and entangle to form a natural canopy that shelters the area from harsh weather.  A fire burns at the center of the grove, the source of the tempting aroma of roasted meats and vegetables.</description>
    <description>Two ironwood trees frame the entrance to a circle of towering silhouetted beech trees.  The branches arch high overhead and entangle to form a natural canopy.  On clear nights, the stars peek through the leafy boughs like gems woven in a goddess' tresses.  A fire burns low in the center of the grove, the source of inviting aromas of roasted meats and vegetables.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-556" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood trees" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Beech Glade, Sleeping Bower">
    <description>Sheltering branches surround a small glade and shield this area from the forest to the north.  Weary travelers may rest in one of the many hammocks strung through the trees.  A large chest stores blankets for those who prefer to sleep on the ground.  The rustle of the branches and the song of distant larks lure sweet dreams to the drowsy.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-576" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Beech Glade, Butternut Tree" note="Butternut Tree">
    <description>A huge spreading butternut tree stands just outside the circle of trees.  A large hole with earthen stairs leads to a space amongst its roots.  A nearby willow table is laden with sweet snacks.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-536" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Beech Glade, Spring Chancel">
    <description>A natural spring bubbles up over a carved stone spillway into a basin of polished rose quartz.  Light collects around the water, radiating from within the quartz.  A lattice of leaves shelters this area, making it quiet enough to commune with Kuniyo, or whichever deity speaks to the devoted's heart.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-556" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="The Beech Cordon, Inner Circle">
    <description>Nearly hidden within the massive groves of towering ironwood and beech trees, a small log cabin stands like a silent sentinel.  With its oval doorway carefully propped open by a hand-carved wooden statue, one wonders if this is a standing invitation to those who travel here.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-536" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="Beech Glade, Trail">
    <description>A narrow trail leads a short distance away from the cordon and ends at the entrance to a weathered hide tent.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-516" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="Horse's Haven">
    <description>A narrow pathway leads into an open area filled with the comings and goings of horses and their owners.  Fresh bales of hay are stacked up against the wall of a well-made stable and the whinnies of horses come from its wide-open doors.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-516" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shop" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="Beech Grove, Paddock">
    <description>Surrounded by trees, a workout area has been set up for horses and their riders.  A white-edged fence and a vine-covered wall are set up to practice jumping techniques, along with barrels to aid in mastering turns.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-536" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="Horse's Haven, Training Field">
    <description>Warning signs are painted on surrounding trees giving notice to spectators that jousters have the right of way.  A quintain is set up in the middle of the field painted in the colors of forest green and brown.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-556" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Horse's Haven, Training Field">
    <description>Freshly cleared, this area is laid out with a list for jousting.  Hard packed dirt is covered with the stamp of hoofs and dead foliage.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-556" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Standish's, Tack and Gear" note="Standish's|Tack" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This small open-air room holds all that is needed for the care of horses or ponies.  The scent of fresh oats permeates the air with a hint of apple from a nearby barrel.  From baskets and trunks to boxes of feed this shop caters to the every need of horses and their owners.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-496" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Standish's, Barding" note="Barding" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sturdy oaken racks display a variety of plate, chain, and leather barding, each set carefully polished and shined or oiled to entice you to buy.  A young girl sits in a corner embroidering a scarlet caparison, her feet tucked primly beneath her stool.  Lining the walls are colorful pictures of proud steeds outfitted in full battle regalia.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-496" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Beech Cordon, Bank Under the Roots" note="Premium Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Damp dirt held in place by a network of butternut tree roots forms the walls of a rounded underground chamber, rich with the scents of cool sweet earth.  A large rough-hewn thick plank serves as a counter, and a pale-haired Elothean teller with tiny mole-like eyes stares behind thin wired glasses in the dim light, waiting to do your bidding. The faint glow of a moongate in another chamber beyond dances within the shadows of a dimly lit earthen tunnel.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-536" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tunnel" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairs" destination="251" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Beech Cordon, Foreign Exchange" note="Premium Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A hole open to the the sky pierces the tangle of roots and earth overhead.  Although underground, a faint moonbeam pushes through the opening in the ceiling and a glimmering moon gate stands wavering in the dimness.  An ever vigilant moon mage, employed by the bank, hovers near the gate to ensure contact with other banks remains steady.  A pair of unusual wolf-like creatures, black as twilight, and fierce as wolverines, watch every move you make.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-516" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tunnel" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Langenfirth, Trail Above the Fens" note="Map40a_Langenfirth_to_Siksraja.xml|Siksraja|Rakash">
    <description>Almost buried in the fallen pine needles that cover the area between Gwenalion Fens to the east and Seord'telgi Teorn to the north, this narrow path wanders westward toward the distant hills.  Small sounds of daily life -- children squealing at play, a dinner call, the cry of a baby -- are wafted by the wind and populate the forest with echoes.</description>
    <description>Almost buried in the fallen pine needles that cover the area between Gwenalion Fens to the east and Seord'telgi Teorn to the north, this narrow path wanders westward towards the distant hills.  Small sounds of a village at sleep -- a baby's hungry cry, a dog barking, a lone door slamming -- are wafted by the wind and populate the forest with echoes.</description>
    <description />
    <position x="-80" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Kweld Andu, Warding Gate">
    <description>A huge, plain stone gate blocks entry into the canyon to the south, while a great mound of dirt fills the skyline to the north.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-716" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone gate" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>A worn dirt pathway traces along the base of a large mound to the west and northeast.  The mound's construction copies that of a mass burial pit, an obviously unnatural heap of soil placed quickly and unceremoniously to cover the dead.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-736" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>The faint smell of a blood drifts in periodically from the north.  A large gate stands to the south, barely visible around the base of the mound.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-756" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>The scent of a fresh kill rides strong in the wind.  Not entirely unwelcome, the smell proves that at least something lives in this depressing environ.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-776" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>A dwarf sized hole has been dug into the side of the mound.  An overwhelming smell of animal waste and rotten flesh emanates from the hole.  A few speckles of blood and the indention of numerous paw prints hint that the lair may just be occupied.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-856" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small hole" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>The scent of a fresh kill floats through the air, tempting the curious to explore to the south.  The trail bends to the northwest, pushing between some stone cliffs and the base of the mound.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-876" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>Smooth, high stone cliffs seem to stretch to the sky as they stand watch over the great burial mound.</description>
    <description>The light colored rock reflects the heat of the sun, making this area quite warm, even in winter.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-896" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>Smooth, high stone cliffs seem to stretch to the sky as they stand watch over the great burial mound.</description>
    <description>The light colored rock reflects the heat of the sun, making this area quite warm, even in winter.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-896" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>A queer sense of absence mingles with the soil, as if a great loss has been dealt this desolate land.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-876" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="273" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>Occasionally an old arrowhead, a rusted armguard, or a worthless sword pushes its way through the soil, giving evidence that this place was once used for something more than burial.  A sense of intermingled fear and struggle radiate off the broken pieces of warfare, almost as a warning to those who happen to pass by.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-856" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>A cloak of dread encompasses this place, pushing one to move on.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-776" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>The huge burial mound releases the silent, cool feeling of death which flows through the soil and rises into the air like the gentle hand of a temptress before pulling her victims to damnation.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-756" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Kweld Andu, Tumulus">
    <description>The worn pathway traces the base of the tumulus, but it appears to be an easy climb to the top of the great burial mound.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-736" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Kweld Andu, Atop Tumulus">
    <description>Sitting above the path which circles the tumulus below, this place is an excellent location to witness the unbelievable workmanship of the stone gate to the south.  The near perfect edges of both the gate and the gateway stand at least twenty-five feet into the air.  It is a remarkable feat to have created such a close fitting structure, let alone how it's massive weight was placed upon huge hinges.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-756" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Kweld Andu, Atop Tumulus" note="sun vultures|bone wolves|revenant zombies">
    <description>Giving a perfect view of the entire tumulus, this perch does not invite a feeling of relief or excitement.  Either the gods have forsaken this place, or this place has forsaken the gods, but whichever it is clear that the life of this land has been sucked away.  There is hardly enough left for the scavengers to eke out a hardened existence.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-816" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Kweld Andu, Atop Tumulus">
    <description>Though the mound below may be quiet and unmoving, the sense of treading upon numerous dead, all thrown together in an unceremonious mess, can give even the strongest and bravest of the lands a moment of uneasiness.  A feeling, perhaps, that the dead may rise up, or worse yet, pull the living down.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-876" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="271" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>A low, rounded ceiling gives little room for anything larger than the local carnivores to operate freely.  A small hole leads out of this stench filled lair.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-956" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small hole" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>The hardened dirt is covered in a rippled pattern of claw marks, displaying the tunneling skill of the bloodthirsty inhabitants.  A choking wall of stench pushes in from the tunnel to the northwest.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-956" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>Challenging will and fortitude, a sickening stench rushes in from the northwest.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-976" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="283" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>Half filling this enlarged room is a pile of revolting refuse.  Flesh, blood, and feces mix in a rotting mass and the stench tests the intestinal fortitude of visitors.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-996" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>An intersection of three tunnels accounts for the numerous paw prints and relative cleanliness of this room.  Although a dangerous wolf might happen along, the opportunity to breathe fresh air is tempting.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-936" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="286" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>About two feet of a large round stone peeks out from the floor, buried beneath the soil of this dark lair.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-916" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="Kweld Andu, Wolf Lair">
    <description>A shallow depression in the middle of this dead-end corridor is covered in coarse fur and cleaned bones.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-936" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Twisting Trail, Danduwen Forest">
    <description>Drooping branches cross the trail, slowing progress through the thick woods.  Though the forest rises up all around, the North Road is within sight when the wind catches the foliage at just the right angle.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-396" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go north road" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="Twisting Trail, Danduwen Forest">
    <description>Branches along each side of the trail are broken, as if something large had passed this way. The trail continues to twist and turn, well out of sight of the North Road.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-416" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="287" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Outside Gate">
    <description>The terrain breaks slightly to reveal a wooden fort tied with netting to blend in with its surroundings.  A guard tower camouflaged with branches rises above the fortress gate, providing an eagle-eye view of any who approach.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-396" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Practice Yard" note="Gorbesh Fortress">
    <description>The ground in this open square is trampled flat, aside from one young deobar tree which stands in the middle of the yard.  Ragged target dummies bearing crude parodies of the guild crests are tied in nooses from a branch.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="291" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="293" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ladder" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Stable">
    <description>Facing out onto the practice yard, these few covered stalls once provided temporary shelter for the mounts of the officers.  A few bits of straw are caught in the slats of a hayrack.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Guard Tower">
    <description>The tower walls are notched and charred, apparently damaged in a pitched battle.  Deep gouges along the outside timbers of the guard tower tell the tale of a brutal assault -- one the archers who stood here could not withstand.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-376" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ladder" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="293" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Mess Hall">
    <description>Low benches are pulled up to long wooden tables.  Some sort of greenish crust stains the tables in spots.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Firepit">
    <description>Two iron rods ending in hooks are planted in the ground next to a sooty bowl-shaped depression.  Judging from the trail of colorful splats and splotches on the ground leading west to the mess hall, this is where the Gorbesh prepared their food.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="298" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="296" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="293" />
  </node>
  <node id="295" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Storage">
    <description>Empty hooped barrels are wedged into the corners of the room, nailed to the walls with metal spikes.  The ceiling is lined with dozens of hooks.  A sign in an unknown language is carved into the wall.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-356" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Meeting Room">
    <description>High-backed chairs sit around a scarred table.  Blobs of candlewax discolor the table and floor, telling the story of long hours spent in planning, lasting deep into the night.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Officers' Quarters">
    <description>Rank may have its privileges, but you wouldn't know it to look at this room.  A half-dozen cots are lined up neatly, with one table and washbasin to serve all the inhabitants.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="296" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Gorbesh Fortress, Barracks">
    <description>The bunks filling the barracks are huge, a testament to the sheer size of the Gorbesh warriors.  There is room for little else here, and the occupants must have had to crawl over each other to reach the door.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-336" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="Forest, Shaded Path">
    <description>Tall trees clothed in resplendent foliage rise up to either side, standing like sentinels over the path.  A carpet of soft grass covers the ground the trees so jealously guard, and the hoot of owls winds in and out through the branches, calling out a quiet watch.</description>
    <description>Green trees grow to either side of the path, tall and clothed in resplendent foliage.  Shimmering leaves of a pleasant hue create a gentle music as they shiver against one another.  The path is carpeted in soft greenery, and the whistling of roosting birds fills the air and wafts on the breeze in time with the rustling leaves.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-436" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="rt north" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Forest, Shaded Path">
    <description>The sweet scent of crushed grass rises in the air, an almost palpable cloud.  Trees clothed in a myriad of greens march alongside the path, growing straight and tall as they reach for the vaulting skies above.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-456" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="rt north" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="299" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Forest, Shaded Path">
    <description>The trees grow close together, creating an arching tunnel and enforcing a sense of being closed in.  The path stretches in a line of green to the north and south, unrolling with slow, lazy ease.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-476" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="rt north" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Forest, Path's End" note="Kuniyo|pilgrim's badge|altar|shrine-2-12" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>The trees round out the path, ending it with a thick stand of tender maple, spinebrush, and aspen.  Bowing silently in homage to the small altar set up at the spot where the path terminates, the trees nod in a gentle breeze, reaffirming their faith to the entity that guards and protects them from harm.</description>
    <description>The trees round out the path, bowing silently in homage to the small altar set up at the spot where the path terminates.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-496" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="301" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Langenfirth, A Simple Lean-To" note="Simple Lean-To" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several flat pieces of wood lay precariously upon some makeshift sawhorses, creating shelves for the wares sold in this quickly constructed shop.  Sawdust thrown on the ground makes for cushioned stepping and defines the area well.  Several clerks stand about talking to each other, barely noticing any customers who enter.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-176" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go courtyard" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Ranger Guild, Hall" note="GL Ranger|Tolle|RS Ranger" color="#FF8000">
    <description>This large rustic hall is lined with many wooden benches guarded by trophy heads mounted high on the walls among an exquisite collection of bows, crossbows, arrows and bolts.  A raised platform against the far wall bears flickering torches and a large awards case that proudly displays honors achieved by guild members.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-196" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Langenfirth, The Langenfirth Tree" note="balloon|airship|Qi'Reshalia|Mer'Kresh|M'Riss|P4" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>A rickety platform in the top of this huge, tall, ancient tree provides a good look-out point with a view which is unbroken for many miles.  It has given the towns folk, as they peer in many directions, fair warning of anything coming their way from the distant hills and early sightings of the barge arriving from Riverhaven.  The town below is hidden beneath the tops of shorter firs, but the view far out into Gwenalion Lake is clear for miles.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-116" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Tinker's End, Repair Shop">
    <description>A surly, grouchy dwarf sits near a pile of broken armor and cooking utensils banging away at dents.  Down on his luck he had, years ago, opened this shop to make a few coins.  Since then he has re-edged, banged out dents, grumbled, and complained but never quite made enough money, or so he says, to get back to his mining.  In a large bin are a number of odd things for sale, apparently items brought in for repair but never picked up.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Temple, Courtyard" note="Courtyard">
    <description>A pleasant garden with several stone benches fills the area between the street and the temple.  Wildflowers and berry bushes have been cultivated in narrow plots about the courtyard.  The occasional chirp or song of a bird is all that breaks the silence.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go temple entrance" destination="308" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Temple, Main Altar" note="Temple|Depart" color="#400040">
    <description>The temple is the only stone building in Langenfirth, built so long ago that history fails to say when or by whom.  It is believed, at least by the locals, that it was here long before the town.  The strange design and construction give weight to those beliefs.  The center of the room is taken up by a huge circular altar.  Through a wide arch is a quiet courtyard garden.  The stone of the walls appears roughly cut, but the blocks are extremely uniform.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide arch" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Town Hall, Main Room">
    <description>There is not much government in Langenfirth and that is reflected in the Town Hall.  All that is ever handled here is the simple payment of taxes and debts.  The hall has a homey feel to it, furnished to resemble someone's home.  Several chairs sit near a fireplace, and there is a well worn rug on the floor.  A ledger sits on a shelf covered with a thick layer of dust.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office door" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Town Hall, Office" note="Debt" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The room is less office than personal living quarters.  A desk and a cot fill part of the room, while ledgers and stacks of trading records fill up most of the empty floor space.  Dust coats everything and motes fly about with every draft through the open door.  It does not appear that even the Mayor uses this place very often.  A clerk reads through various ledgers trying to determine who still owes debts and who has paid.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Langenfirth, Stock Pens">
    <description>Several pigs, a goat and some sheep mill about a small wooden pen.  While the towns tradesmen expect hard coin from travelers and traders, with the locals they will often barter stock for services or products.  The floor of the pen is covered with wet, mucky straw and the pen smells of both fresh and well-aged manure.  Over the years this small holding pen was built simply to keep the locals' currency from wandering about and bothering visitors.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go reed barn" destination="312" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Langenfirth, Caravan Reed Barn">
    <description>This barn was made for wealthy travelers wishing to stable their animals while in Langenfirth.  With its woven reed walls and raised slat flooring, animals are kept relatively warm and dry.  Several stable lads make sure that the animals in their charge are well-fed and watered and that the stalls are mucked out regularly.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-96" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="311" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Langenfirth, Obscure Trail">
    <description>The trail leading up to the door of a dilapidated cabin appears to have been made by small animals and not recently used.  It is hard to follow it through the underbrush, and low tree limbs block any easy movement.  The forest is almost silent except for the distant call of a bird and the wind rustling high in the tree top.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-236" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go broken-down door" destination="314" />
  </node>
  <node id="314" name="Cabin, Hideaway">
    <description>While no one has taken any time to maintain the outside of the cabin, a great deal of decorating has been done inside.  The rough log walls have been covered with embroidered hangings.  A flagstone fireplace is in pristine condition, and several large logs crackle in the fire.  A thick hide rug covers the floor and there is a pile of pillows laying near the fire. </description>
    <position x="100" y="-236" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wood door" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="315" name="Bowyer Shop, Jarrod's Quarters">
    <description>The backroom serves as both home and workshop for Jarrod.  A master tracker and hunter, he is used to living in the woods without amenities, and that shows in the sparse quarters.  On a low table is a work in progress, either a special order or a newly designed bow.</description>
    <position x="40" y="4" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="316" name="Fairegrounds Entrance" note="Guildfest.xml|Fairegrounds|festival">
    <description>A woven bracken arch festooned with ivy and flowering vines serves as the entrance to the fairegrounds.  People are milling about the entrance hawking their wares while small children run to and fro playing games and singing.  An air of frivolity and joy surrounds everyone present at the occasion.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-1256" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go north road" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bracken arch" />
  </node>
  <node id="317" name="Cabin, Front Room">
    <description>A stone fireplace with a wood mantelpiece has a warm fire which casts a warm glow throughout the room.  Shadows cast by the flickering flames dance on a nearby rocking chair and a long table along the wall.  A bearskin rug lies across the hearth making the room appear very homey and comfortable.  Log steps nailed to the wall provide a way to reach an upper loft area.  The door is closed firmly but the window is unshuttered with a nice view of the street.</description>
    <description>The main room of this cabin is furnished with a table and a rocking chair.  A stone fireplace with a wood mantelpiece has a warm fire glowing in it.  A bearskin rug lies across the hearth making the room very homey and comfortable.  Log steps nailed to the wall provide a way to reach an upper loft area.  The door is closed firmly but the window is unshuttered with a nice view of the street.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="318" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="318" name="Cabin, Loft">
    <description>Most of the loft is filled with a straw mattress covered in muslin.  The peaked roof gives plenty of headroom in the center, but descends to the floor along the walls.  This is a cozy sleeping area, separate from the living area downstairs, and warmed by the heat of the fireplace rising upward.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-236" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="317" />
  </node>
  <node id="319" name="Small Cabin, Room">
    <description>The warm glow of the lantern fills the room with a soft yellow light.  The lantern sits on a small wooden table in the center of the tidy cabin.  On one wall is a narrow bunk with a thin mattress, covered with a thin gray blanket.  A small wooden door leads out to the street.</description>
    <description>The bare logs of the walls have not even been stripped of bark.  A narrow bunk, with a thin mattress and a ragged gray wool blanket, is attached to one wall across the room from the door.  A wood table sits in the center of the small room with a lantern placed on it.  While small and sparsely furnished, the room is very tidy.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-76" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="320" name="Langenfirth, Up a Towering Deobar Tree">
    <description>Nestled amongst the newer cabins of the small town, the deobar tree is a natural escape from the urbanization of Langenfirth.  The sounds of soft rolling water drift from somewhere beyond the housing area.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="321" name="Small Cabin">
    <description>This tiny cabin offers a quick rest for the road weary in the form of a low cot which sits in a corner of the room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cabin door" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="322" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Cool water, stained dark with peat, laps around you as you swim.  About shoulder-high on a Dwarf, it seems to maintain a fairly constant depth in this area, though the darker color beyond the hummocks indicates that the bottom drops off dramatically.</description>
    <position x="260" y="264" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="323" />
  </node>
  <node id="323" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Shadows visible from the corner of the eye seem to disappear when looked at directly, hidden by the dark waters of the lake.  The water is deep, even close to shore.  Fortunately there are plenty of hummocks nearby, so it should be a simple matter to scramble out of the lake.</description>
    <position x="240" y="244" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="324" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="322" />
  </node>
  <node id="324" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Long, silvery fish dart through the water, twisting and turning with sinuous grace before disappearing into a tangle of water weeds.  Reed hummocks jostle against each other as they drift, but there is plenty of room to slip between.</description>
    <position x="260" y="224" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="336" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="323" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="325" />
  </node>
  <node id="325" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Golden petals float through the water, blown from a nearby hummock.  The color is vivid against the dark water.  For a moment, the usual miasma of rotting vegetation and dead fish is overcome by a subtle sweet fragrance to be enjoyed until the wind shifts direction.</description>
    <position x="240" y="204" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="326" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="326" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The occasional cry of a nesting gull drifts over the water, mocking you from the shore.  Visibility is low in the water, clouded by dark brown strands of peat washed off the shore each time it rains.  Still, the lake floor seems solid despite the silt.</description>
    <position x="260" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="335" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="325" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="327" />
  </node>
  <node id="327" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A chill current swirls around as thick rivulets of muddy water wash into the lake from the nearby fens.  Tufts of fur, leaves and other castoffs from the land are all carried into the depths, quickly sinking out of sight.</description>
    <position x="240" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="328" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="326" />
  </node>
  <node id="328" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Something splashes to the east, hidden from view by a nearby hummock.  The sounds of the fens carry a long way over water -- a roar, a cry of pain, a splash as something falls into the water -- making it impossible to tell with any certainty just where they originate.</description>
    <position x="260" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="327" />
  </node>
  <node id="329" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Deep brown strands of peat float in the dark water as it surges sullenly against the shoreline.  Tangled mats of dried reeds and vines dot the surface, providing homes to otters, beavers and nesting birds.  Wide enough to support several people, these hummocks drift aimlessly with the tides.</description>
    <position x="280" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="330" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="331" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="333" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="330" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Waterlogged clumps of dead reeds and branches, stripped of their bark and bleached white by the sun, toss amidst the darkling waves like dead men's bones given new life in the murky water.  Some will drift together and be caught in the weeds to form one of the floating hummocks which dot the lake.  Most will simply sink and join the uncharted obstacles beneath the surface.</description>
    <position x="280" y="104" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="331" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="329" />
  </node>
  <node id="331" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>In grannys' tales told round the fire, the words Once upon a time are a familiar beginning.  Once upon a time, legend might have it, a giant stepped into the muddy fens, his footprint forming the mighty Lake Gwenalion.  The reality is doubtless more prosaic, involving long-gone sheets of ice or curious creatures trapped in stone.  But for now, there is only dark water ruffled by a breeze that drives the floating hummocks before it.</description>
    <position x="300" y="104" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="330" />
  </node>
  <node id="332" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A strong current tugs at your legs, trying to pull you under the surface.  The steady flow makes it hard to maintain balance in the water.  Several tangled reed hummocks sway gracefully nearby, dancing in the current.  The closest is within easy reach.</description>
    <position x="320" y="124" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="343" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="333" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="333" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Twisting passages of dark water wend their way amidst the fens, defined by the floating reed islets that bob restlessly in the waves.  The shore is hidden from view -- only the desolate calls of hawks circling overhead mark its presence somewhere to the northwest.</description>
    <position x="300" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="334" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="329" />
  </node>
  <node id="334" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Rotting fish corpses emit a sickly sweet stench as they bob aimlessly in the water.  Their graceful bodies once darted quickly beneath the surface.  Now they are swept by the waves or caught in the hummocks' tangled reeds, their sightless eyes staring accusingly at the sky.</description>
    <position x="300" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="333" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="335" />
  </node>
  <node id="335" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Silvery reflections glimmer against the surface of the lake.  A soft spray of foam surges into the air as the water dashes against the reed mats that surround you, coating your face.  The crash of water drowns out the faint cries of birds, but cannot compete with the harsh, inarticulate roars from the nearby hummocks.</description>
    <position x="280" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="334" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="336" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="326" />
  </node>
  <node id="336" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>An oddly warm current eddies around you.  Warm in comparison to the rest of the lake, at least, but still cold enough to send shivers down your spine as you trudge through the murky depths of the water.  Permeating the air with a sickly sweet stench, rotting vegetation washes off the shore and hummocks, sinking to the bottom only to swirl around in dark brown clouds when disturbed.</description>
    <position x="280" y="204" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="335" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="337" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="337" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Rising from the surface, wavering tendrils of mist reach up to curl about in eldritch patterns that make it difficult to see.  Silence falls heavily upon the area, broken only by the relentless plop, plop, plop of water dripping from the nearby hummocks.</description>
    <position x="300" y="224" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="340" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="338" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="336" />
  </node>
  <node id="338" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The water darkens to a deep greenish-black to the east as the bottom slopes sharply down.  No hummocks drift past the fen's protected waters, bobbing instead in the shallows to the north and west.  To the east is merely open water as far as the eye can see.</description>
    <position x="320" y="244" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="339" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="337" />
  </node>
  <node id="339" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Swarms of gnats envelop anyone standing still along the southern end of the fens.  Visibility beneath the surface is occluded by murky clouds of silt and mud that billow up with every step.  The water is darker still near the edge of a drop-off to the east, while a dense tangle of reeds that will someday form one of the fens' floating hummocks blocks passage to the south.</description>
    <position x="300" y="264" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="338" />
  </node>
  <node id="340" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Frogs and crickets hidden on the nearby hummocks join in a joyful chorus that echoes all around the lake.  The water is cold and footing uncertain in the dim light one minute solid, the next forcing the traveler to scramble for solid ground.</description>
    <position x="320" y="204" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="341" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="337" />
  </node>
  <node id="341" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Muddy water soaks through boots and shoes to leave even the hardiest adventurer shivering as he slogs past the relative dryness of the hummocks.  While it would be easy to climb out, the traveler might thereby miss the somewhat dubious experience of the reeking stench of rotted fish and other less pleasant fragrances.</description>
    <position x="340" y="184" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="342" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="340" />
  </node>
  <node id="342" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Water and mud, mud and water...  The fens' unchanging scenery is broken only by the slight variations in the reed hummocks that bob to and fro in the icy water.  One may support a few tangled blossoms, another is home to a beaver or otter.  But from here, most are out of reach, while the frigid water is all too present.</description>
    <position x="340" y="164" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="343" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="341" />
  </node>
  <node id="343" name="Gwenalion Fens, In the Water" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Footing is uncertain at best as you skirt the edge of a drop-off to the east.  The shallow shelf at the southwestern end of the lake defines the fens region.  Winter storms sweep dried reeds into the area to tangle with water weeds and form the characteristic reed hummocks that drift aimlessly about the water for a season or two before returning to the rich soil from which they came.</description>
    <position x="340" y="144" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="342" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="332" />
  </node>
  <node id="344" name="Langenfirth, Up an Oak Tree">
    <description>Crisp clean air flows through the treetop.  From this height, one can easily spy the light stream of smoke billowing from a small cabin nestled among the trees to the north and the commercial hub of the outpost holding off the encroachment of the wilderness to the east.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="345" name="Langenfirth, Up a Tall Pine Tree">
    <description>Amongst the blue needles and pine cones of this large tree an offering of solitude for the occasional tree-sitter is provided.  Off to the west the outlines of cabins pollute the horizon of this once wild land.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-56" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="346" name="Calliana Leather Goods, Work Room">
    <description>The workroom of the shop is awash with scraps. Bits and pieces of leftover hides are strewn about the tables and floor.  On a long worktable are several leather items in various states of repair, and on a nearby rack are the beginnings of several new projects.  Well cared for tools and sharp needles are arranged on a high shelf.</description>
    <position x="0" y="4" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="347" name="'Neer's Hummock, Game Trail">
    <description>Briar bushes encroach the small path, reaching to rip at passersby.  At least one beast failed to escape the thorny grasp, as evidenced by the thick strands of wool, which hang lifelessly entrapped.  The game trail branches here, the directions most worn from travel climbing sharply to the north and cutting along a side slope to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="360" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="352" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="348" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="348" name="'Neer's Hummock, Side Hill">
    <description>The trail cuts through the brush here at the base of the hill.  Barely visible in the darkness, the trail curls around the hill, rising sharply to the east.  The ground shifts under your feet as you move, making ascent difficult.  To the northwest, the trail descends at an easier angle.</description>
    <description>The trail winds its way through the brush and rises steeply up the face of the hill to the east.  The trail does not appear to be heavily used, and the soil underfoot is loose, making ascent difficult.  To the northwest, the trail descends at an easier angle.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="349" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="347" />
  </node>
  <node id="349" name="'Neer's Hummock, Side Hill" note="thunder rams">
    <description>Grass is interspersed with small shrubs along this section of the hill.  The brush thickens downhill, while the slope opens up to the east, betraying rough terrain and a difficult climb.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="350" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="348" />
  </node>
  <node id="350" name="'Neer's Hummock, Side Hill">
    <description>The slope rises at a steep angle, the trail making the ascent only slightly less difficult as it winds its way across the uneven ground.  The trail begins to disappear to the northeast, where the grass grows taller and the terrain becomes even rougher.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-596" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="351" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="349" />
  </node>
  <node id="351" name="'Neer's Hummock, Side Hill">
    <description>The trail fades into the grass, giving way to the steep and uneven terrain.  Loose stones and tufts of grass tumble down the slope as you try to maintain your footing.  Small patches sprinkled all over the slope show signs of some recent grazing.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-616" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="350" />
  </node>
  <node id="352" name="'Neer's Hummock, Meadow">
    <description>A few ferns have sprung up here, owing their life to damp soil.  The water must percolate from below, for there is no evidence of a running spring.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="353" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="347" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="360" />
  </node>
  <node id="353" name="'Neer's Hummock, Meadow">
    <description>The vegetation thrives here, apparently unaware of the presence of a steep cliff.  Down the abrupt drop-off, loose rock and dirt promise an impossible climb and a deadly fall.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="354" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="352" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb abrupt drop-off" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="354" name="'Neer's Hummock, Wolves' Refuge">
    <description>Alone, in the ground covering grass, stands a tall, proud, yet oddly colored oak tree.  Spreading wide its thick limbs, the tree offers shade and protection from the elements.  Beneath the tree, the grass is broken, trampled, and torn.  Bone, hide, and the distinct odor of blood mark this place as home to the wolves of 'Neer's Hummock.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="353" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak tree" destination="371" />
  </node>
  <node id="355" name="'Neer's Hummock, Meadow">
    <description>A few rogue wildflowers dance among the grass, daring to claim their place.  Leading through a break in the trees, an exposed path veers off towards a small glade.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="356" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="354" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="353" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb birch tree" destination="363" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ash tree" destination="364" />
  </node>
  <node id="356" name="'Neer's Hummock, Meadow">
    <description>Rising to the calf of a human, the grass of this plain, quiet meadow spreads forth in a sea of yellow-green.  The temptation to lie and take rest is strong, but not advised when the local carnivorous beast happens along.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb birch tree" destination="365" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ash tree" destination="366" />
  </node>
  <node id="357" name="'Neer's Hummock, Meadow">
    <description>The view from atop this hill is quite limited due to the trees, which surround this lush meadow.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="356" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="358" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb elm tree" destination="367" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak tree" destination="368" />
  </node>
  <node id="358" name="'Neer's Hummock, Game Trail">
    <description>The game trail is wide, level, and holds a few shrubs atop this hummock.  Intermittent, frightening howls can be heard, swirling among the trees.</description>
    <description>The game trail is wide, level, and holds few trees atop this hummock.  Sounds of the wild are unnervingly absent here, save the occasional rambling beast.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="360" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="359" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak tree" destination="369" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb elm tree" destination="370" />
  </node>
  <node id="359" name="'Neer's Hummock, Game Trail">
    <description>Pressed into the soft dirt alongside this steep trail are an animal's tracks.  It doesn't take a ranger to discern that these large, deep paw prints are the work of a predator.  Although the trail descends steeply to the south, a change in grade can be seen towards the east, over the next rise.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="358" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="360" />
  </node>
  <node id="360" name="'Neer's Hummock, Game Trail">
    <description>The steep grade of the trail doesn't seem to bother the wildlife that use it daily, but for adventurers used to flatter lands, it is a sweaty climb.  The path continues its relentless rise to the north.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="359" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="358" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="352" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="347" />
  </node>
  <node id="361" name="'Neer's Hummock, Meadow" note="blood wolves">
    <description>Faint, barely surviving upon the wind, is the scent of blood.  The smell seems to arrive from the east, hinting at a fresh kill.  Grass covered ground continues to descend slightly to the south.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="358" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="362" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="353" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="352" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="347" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="360" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="359" />
  </node>
  <node id="362" name="'Neer's Hummock, Clearing">
    <description>Sparse trees and shrubs mingle with short, fragile grass beneath the open sky.  Small, criss-crossing paths cut through the grass, revealing the heavy use creatures give this place.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="357" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="356" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="355" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="354" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="353" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="352" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="361" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="358" />
  </node>
  <node id="363" name="'Neer's Hummock, White Birch Tree Limb">
    <description>The narrow branch trembles with the weight of visitors seeking a peaceful spot to rest in the tree.  White bark covering the trunk peels easily and is marked by narrow horizontal stripes, which camouflage the marks left by travelers on their climb.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="355" />
  </node>
  <node id="364" name="'Neer's Hummock, Green Ash Tree Limb">
    <description>Long green leaves surrounding the branch each have several pairs of leaflets, which are darker at the base and grow paler near the tips.  The bark on the tree's trunk is brown to dark grey and covered in interlacing furrows that add traction for visitors needing to climb down from here.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="355" />
  </node>
  <node id="365" name="'Neer's Hummock, Red Birch Tree Limb">
    <description>The narrow branch trembles with the weight of visitors seeking a peaceful spot to rest in the tree.  Salmon-colored bark covering the trunk peels and turns to dark red-brown plates as it ages, making the climb back down a challenge.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="356" />
  </node>
  <node id="366" name="'Neer's Hummock, Blue Ash Tree Limb">
    <description>Fern-like fronds covered in long, pointed leaves drape down from the surrounding branches, resembling graceful fans awaiting the next passing breeze.  Tiny ridges cover the bluish tinged bark, adding a little traction for visitors needing to climb down from here.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="356" />
  </node>
  <node id="367" name="'Neer's Hummock, Elm Tree Limb">
    <description>Leaves drooping off branches overhead blanket each side of the limb in foliage, muffling any sounds from the meadow.  The smooth bark of the tree's trunk is marred with scars and slashes left from visitors clumsily climbing down to resume their travels.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="357" />
  </node>
  <node id="368" name="'Neer's Hummock, Oak Tree Limb">
    <description>Chunks of bark missing along the branch look as if something or someone has pulled it off to expose the raw wood.  Scarring the tree's trunk, stumps left from broken limbs form makeshift footholds for anyone needing to climb down from here.</description>
    <position x="210" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="357" />
  </node>
  <node id="369" name="'Neer's Hummock, Oak Tree Limb">
    <description>From this branch, one can easily see across the meadow while safely observing the beasts prowling below.  Scarring the tree's trunk, stumps left from broken limbs form makeshift footholds for anyone needing to climb down from here.</description>
    <position x="190" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="358" />
  </node>
  <node id="370" name="'Neer's Hummock, Elm Tree Limb">
    <description>From this height, visitors can easily see across the meadow to a path that leads through a break in the surrounding wall of trees.  Scratches on the smooth bark of the trunk show that more than travelers have used it to climb on.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-696" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="358" />
  </node>
  <node id="371" name="Wolf Oak, Lower Branches">
    <description>The multi-layered, thickly leafed branches of the oak allow very little light to penetrate to this section of the tree. It is dark, yet not quite pitch black as an occasional vagrant beam sneaks past a branch swayed by a passing breeze.  A large twisted limb branches out from the tree to the northeast while two smaller limbs extend to the north and to the southeast.</description>
    <description>Sunlight filters past the thickly leafed, multi-layered branches of the oak in dancing motes that play upon the dark trunk of the tree like fireflies flitting through a midnight sky.  A large twisted limb branches out from the tree to the northeast while two smaller limbs extend to the north and to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-656" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="354" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb northern limb" destination="372" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb southeastern limb" destination="373" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb twisted limb" destination="374" />
  </node>
  <node id="372" name="Wolf Oak, Smooth Limb">
    <description>Much of the outer bark of this limb has been stripped away, leaving exposed the smooth inner wood of the tree.  Though the limb extends far out to the north it would be dangerous to proceed further in that direction.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-676" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="371" />
  </node>
  <node id="373" name="Wolf Oak, Scarred Limb">
    <description>Lightning from a long forgotten storm has left a legacy of scars along the length of this tree limb.  The limb thins quickly as it extends to the southeast, making it impossible to proceed any further in that direction.  It is, however, possible to go back down to the main trunk of the tree.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="371" />
  </node>
  <node id="374" name="Wolf Oak, Twisted Limb">
    <description>The growth of this limb has been twisted by the weight of several branches pressing against it.  It manages, however, to provide a stable perch for climbers despite its oddly configured dips and curves.  Moving further along the limb to the southwest would be practical only for birds and squirrels, but one might travel down the limb to the main trunk of the tree with ease.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-636" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="371" />
  </node>
  <node id="375" name="Fang Cove, Fate's Fortune Lane" note="Map150_Fang_Cove.xml">
    <description>A towering marble archway opens a gap in the wall to the north and separates the ongoing construction and somewhat more refined completed structures of Fate's Fortune Lane from the crude structures and makeshift walkway along the beach.  The entrance to a squat, wide bungalow sits in opposition to the arch, and the sheltering cliffs of Fang's Peak rise up from behind it.  To either side of the arch, cobblestones of different shapes and sizes have been laid out to form the wide Fate's Fortune Lane.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit portal" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="376" name="Ker'Leor, Deep Forest Path" note="Map41_Marauders.xml|Vines|Creepers|Marauders">
    <description>An endless assortment of towering trees and vividly-colored underbrush crowd the base of Ker'Leor.  So dense is the forest that steam rises from its floor, hanging as a still mist which threatens to obscure the faint path.  Eerie wails, moans and hisses echo forth from the deep shadows, bending the imagination toward the hideous and threatening.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-1316" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="north" />
  </node>
  <node id="377" name="Theren's Star, Deck" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>The first of the massive barges to traverse Lake Gwenalion, Theren's Star still maintains a quiet elegance despite its apparent age.  The utilitarian deck upon which casual travelers walk is spartan, but the decking is made of expensive tabor wood felled from far southern forests.  An oval doorway leads down to the barge's cargo bay, while an elaborately-carved wooden door provides ingress to the comfortably appointed lounge.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-36" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="378" name="Langenfirth Woods, Across the Brook">
    <description>Gurgling sounds come from the water flowing past the embankment as it wends its way through the trees towards the distant lake.  The constant humidity fosters the growth of luxuriant moss on the trunks, giving them a fuzzy appearance much like that of an animal's pelt.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="383" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="379" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brook" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="379" name="Langenfirth Woods, Brookside">
    <description>Trees thin as the forest approaches a stream flowing within steep embankments.  The sounds of rushing water fill the area, a deep musical splash and bubble sound underlaid with a deep occasional rumble.  The noise of the brook covers all other sounds of the woods, obscuring the passage of both humanoids and beasts.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="378" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="380" />
  </node>
  <node id="380" name="Langenfirth Woods, Dense Woods">
    <description>Clusters of trees clump together, as if each parent tree is surrounded by a horde of offspring that are seeking to protect their elder from harm.  Between the clusters of trunks, the ground is covered with low shrubs and other underbrush.  The rustle of leaves and twigs testify to the passage of numerous small animals as they scurry in search of food.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="4" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="379" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="381" />
  </node>
  <node id="381" name="Langenfirth Woods, Forest Floor">
    <description>Colossal trunks rise from the leaf-covered ground, rising seemingly effortlessly to the distant sky with outstretched limbs and branches.  Little of the sky is visible, most of it blocked by the thick foliage above.  Dangling from the distant branches are wispy strands of moss that help obscure the vault of the heavens.</description>
    <position x="-200" y="4" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="382" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="380" />
  </node>
  <node id="382" name="Langenfirth Woods, Glade">
    <description>Something long ago brought down one of the forest giants, allowing a break in the canopy.  The rotting remains of the fallen titan lie on the forest floor, half-covered in rotting leaves and burgeoning vegetation.  The distant sounds of nightbirds ring through the open space, welcome in the silence of the forest.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-16" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="383" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="381" />
  </node>
  <node id="383" name="Langenfirth Woods, Thicket">
    <description>Trunks of towering trees close in near the game trail, blocking most light and making the route twist and bend in order to make any progress.  The air hangs heavy and humid, helping the growth of the underbrush pack what little space remains beneath the canopy.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-36" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="382" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="378" />
  </node>
  <label text="Therenborough">
    <position x="155" y="-1380" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Homesite">
    <position x="250" y="-1396" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Droughtmans Maze (Closed)">
    <position x="-230" y="-1066" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Sun Vultures">
    <position x="140" y="-850" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="El'Bain's Stop">
    <position x="50" y="-566" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Thunder Rams">
    <position x="180" y="-586" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blood Wolves">
    <position x="150" y="-716" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Swamp Trolls, Small Peccaries">
    <position x="30" y="74" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Barge to Riverhaven">
    <position x="210" y="-46" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Mistwood Forest (to Rossman's)">
    <position x="150" y="-1146" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wood Trolls, Kelpies">
    <position x="140" y="-476" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cougars, Boars">
    <position x="150" y="-466" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Fendryads">
    <position x="120" y="234" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Marauders">
    <position x="80" y="-1336" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Langenfirth">
    <position x="140" y="-176" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Premium Clubhouse">
    <position x="-140" y="-506" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Rakash Village">
    <position x="-160" y="-30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bone Wolves">
    <position x="140" y="-838" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blood Wolves">
    <position x="140" y="-827" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bone Wolves">
    <position x="310" y="-986" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blood Wolves">
    <position x="310" y="-976" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Kuniyo">
    <position x="40" y="-516" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Revenant Zombies">
    <position x="120" y="-816" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Elsralael">
    <position x="270" y="84" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Fairegrounds">
    <position x="222" y="-1251" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bundles">
    <position x="-10" y="-175" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Debt">
    <position x="-17" y="-83" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="&lt;--Leather Repair">
    <position x="80" y="-224" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Marina">
    <position x="145" y="-83" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Daelfa Seord'telgi">
    <position x="-250" y="-116" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Huntress">
    <position x="120" y="-331" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Ker'Leor and">
    <position x="70" y="-1346" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gwenalion Fens">
    <position x="140" y="114" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Terminus from Haven Ferry">
    <position x="-187" y="56" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Trail to Haven Ferry">
    <position x="-148" y="116" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bronze Leucro">
    <position x="-240" y="14" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Fruitstand">
    <position x="20" y="-1106" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>
