<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Leth Deriel" id="61">
  <node id="1" name="Deobar Bower Gate, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>A tall gate rises over a well-kept road.  Ironwood trees gather in patches around the steep city walls, their dark forms casting shadows over the thin brush.  The slender bows and branches that make the thick panels of the gateway into Leth curve and twist, their still-tender bark formed into a living arch by a lifesculptor's hand.</description>
    <description>Shadows of the night sky descend, their inky tendrils tugging at the stalwart wooden gate.  The path winds south away from Leth, into the most remote of the Deriels.  Behind the deobar barrier the city sleeps soundly.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bower gate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Leth Deriel, Deobar Bower Gate" note="Deobar Bower Gate|SW Gate">
    <description>A tremulous throbbing fills the air, replete with murmurings from an unseen host, like pulsations from the heart of the impenetrable forest beyond the barrier of deobars that grow here.  Sympathetic vibrations, higher pitched, seem to emanate from the Sana'ati Dyaus at the town's center due northeast.  The living wall of trees has been recently fitted with a rattan and wicker gate that remains open night and day, leading out to a road winding south through the forest.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bower gate" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>A break in the living barricade forms a clearing that leads to the southwestern city gate.  Through it, all you see is forest beyond, lofty, silent and forbidding.  An old ranger, bowed and wizened, hobbles past, spewing a wad of some masticated greenish ooze directly across your path.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>A sudden snap in the deobars overhead is followed by soft, urgent footfalls along the arboreal platforms that circle the Elven stronghold.  You can barely hear the creak of a willow bow being drawn taut, ready to loose a well-aimed shaft at the heart of an enemy.  Not wishing to stay for target practice, you redouble your pace.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Fiddlehead ferns and low growing shrubs line both sides of the path between the tree trunks.  Many tender young fern stalks poke out of the soil, as though someone had harvested their tips.  Along the inner curve are thirsty green willows among whose roots play delicate, crystal trickles of clear water.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden building" destination="224" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The deobars here sport large patches of brownish-green moss on the north sides of their trunks.  The humus on the ground is exceedingly damp as well and home to lichens, toadstools, and clumps of feathery fronds.  Your footsteps leave depressions that fill up with small puddles of water.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Elder Bark Circle intersects with Black Willow Lane to the east here.  The junction is broad and the hard packed, rich loam that paves the byways of Leth Deriel looks well trampled.  The earth feels solid and comforting beneath your feet, but a damp, musty scent wafts in from the south.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Peering into the foliage to the southeast, you notice a great black willow tree.  Its hoary, drooping branches cascade down and the leaves tumble earthward like innumerable, brilliant green sparks from an Elothean fireworks display.  In an upper fork of the willow's massive trunk is a tall, thin structure.  With no apparent access from here, there must be some other way to approach the willow.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The inner arc of the road is bordered by neatly trimmed primrose bushes, a little beyond which are tall stands of poplar, plane and birch in an unlikely mix.  Remarkably they are all thriving, magnificent specimens of their kind.  Small paths, hardly noticeable at all, leave the main road and meander off into the growth but are too faint to follow.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>A thinning of the wall here lets you catch a glimpse of Oracle Hollow, beyond to the northwest.  You feel drawn back to the early ages of Elanthia, to the days of those ancient oracles in primitive times when the forest had a life unto itself.  Vows, oaths and prophecies were often uttered in the sheltered glades, canopied groves, the stone cromlechs and sacred precincts of the primeval woods.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large hut" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Dense stands of deobars form the town palisades that curve to the northeast and southwest.  The impenetrable defense is made even more daunting by clumps of raevelthorn bushes that grow close to the ground in the gaps between the trees.  Their branches, with razor sharp thorns facing outward, appear to have been woven craftily among the trees.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The path here circles northeast and southwest, with the deobar walls crowding along the north side of the road.  A rustling makes you glance up instinctively, the tall stands forcing you to crane your neck almost to its limits.  It is only then that you notice what appears to be a network of platforms in the treetops concealed by the foliage.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Leth Deriel, Black Willow Lane">
    <description>The straight road heads east-west here and is demarcated by the same neatly tended hedges as elsewhere in town.  On the north side of the road is a narrow gap in the living fence, barely large enough for a single Gor'Tog to squeeze past.  Through the underbrush you can see that the path leads to the base of a huge black willow tree.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow gap" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Leth Deriel, Black Willow Lane">
    <description>Black Willow Lane connects the westernmost point in Leth Deriel to the heart of town, the clearing in which stands the venerable Sana'ati Dyaus.  That eternal tree, whose beginnings are shrouded in mist, was the original Elven fortress around which the town grew.  In all the lore, among all the sacred Sana'ati trees that form the core of Elven settlements, Sana'ati Dyaus is perhaps the most fabled.</description>
    <position x="-59" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle" note="Forge">
    <description>A remarkably fine oak tree adorned with iron strips, brass wind chimes and other glittering trinkets, around which on poles are the desiccated heads of oxen, hourens and deer, hangs over the southwest half of the path here.  Clustered around a glowing brazier beside the tree are a rune engraved anvil, assorted tongs, bellows and other tools, all resting on a bed of white sand.  An iron fitted door seals a high opening in the tree's trunk.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Leth Deriel, Acanth Court">
    <description>Birch trees and wicker fences entwine like giant winnowing baskets to shield this part of Leth Deriel from fickle weather.  A stand of delicate acanth trees is nurtured here, and they scent the air with their pungent leaves.  Plump squirrels and rotund chipmunks happily munch away among their branches, looking very healthy.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>The astringent scent of Sufil trees suffuses the air, and you breathe the soothing vapors deeply.  Directly under the shade of a huge, overhanging Sana'ati branch that reaches out over its central clearing to this corner, is a small tent of painted bark cloth.  Stretched out upon cots and hammocks, with typical reserve, are the ill and wounded, waiting to be tended by the legendary Elven empath within.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Leth Deriel, Sana'ati Dyaus Drui'tas" note="Sana'ati Dyaus Drui'tas|Portal|Kraelyst start point|travel start point" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>In the midst of this clearing is the mighty tree known throughout Elanthia as Sana'ati Dyaus.  Its limbs glow with a phosphorescent light and you can trace the very course of its roots by their faint glimmer.  Every vein on every leaf is a streak of pale fire, and the diverse crowd here in the main gathering place is subtly illuminated.  The tree houses all the town's official services, and people come and go through a large, open burl in the trunk.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open burl" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meeting portal" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>The view to the west consists of the clearing surrounding the ancient tree that forms the hub of Leth Deriel, and the tree itself, the fabled Sana'ati Dyaus.  Its trunk blocks out anything else you might have been able to see in that direction.  Merchants, traders, and other outsiders bent on commerce pass by, some headed to the bank just east, others headed to the trading post, shops and offices clustered in the area.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Leth Deriel, Dragon Tree Road">
    <description>A tall, smooth barked ebonwood tree dominates the southwest side of the road here.  Its strong, black walls form a perfect circular trunk of huge diameter.  All the low hanging branches have been trimmed to prevent climbing.  An ebony door, fashioned with exquisite metal fittings and inlaid with semi-precious gems, marks this tree as the seat of Leth Deriel's financial life, the Imperial Depository.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebony door" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>This is a busy junction, leading to and from the main clearing of town, as well as a good many vital shops and institutions, such as the Imperial Depository due west, the provisions store due east, and the main temple to the northwest.  The well trodden path extends a bit beneath shady plane trees on either side, fading off into a dense cover of large bracken, their tough stalks and lacy fronds sprouting up at all angles.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Leth Deriel, Dragon Tree Road">
    <description>Haunches of venison, braces of wild fowl, and slabs of boar meat hang from tree limbs over smoldering fires of sage and fragrant woods.  Baskets of berries, mushrooms and fruits lie drying in the sun.  Sacks and kegs are piled alongside a tree trunk here, more of a very high stump actually.  Above a chiseled-out opening in the stump is a crudely carved sign.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Leth Deriel, Dragon Tree Road">
    <description>Two old trees, one ash, the other elm, lash against each other, their limbs whipping and thrashing, yet no wind seems to be stirring them.  They rail as though they would beat one another to the ground.  You can detect no creature in their foliage that would cause these violent movements.  Perhaps the timeless rage of clan feuds across the millennia has suffused the very soil of Leth Deriel.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Elder Bark Circle intersects to the west with Dragon Tree Road, creating a small clearing through which light filters.  A goshawk swoops down and snatches up a squirming field mouse.  To one side of the path, an Elven cleric decked in a homespun cassock places a sprig of alkanet leaves at the base of an ancient, twisted shade tree.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>Bergamot and citrus trees, lovingly cultivated in several small copses, ring the intersection here.  Their limbs are laden with fruit and bedecked with strips of ethereal gauze, serving as votive offerings to the woodland deities. Oakenheart Circle merges to the northeast into Aldiyaus Square, site of Leth Deriel's main shrine.  Looming large and stentorian to the southwest is Sana'ati Dyaus, most sacred of trees.  A broad clearing encircles the mammoth trunk.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>You arrive at a busy intersection where Oakenheart Circle merges with Merewala Court to the southeast, and flows into the central clearing to the northwest.  At this pivotal junction sits a mean-looking shanty, in and out of which trudge seedy adventurers who appear down on their luck, as well as richly dressed traders.  For a single establishment to cater to such an odd mix of clientele strikes you as odd.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shanty" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>The mighty tree that is the heart and soul of Leth Deriel towers above, a few paces to the north.  Its massive trunk and thick limbs house the town hall, where citizens can store their valuables in safety, and various official functions are performed there.  To the northeast in a triangular clearing between the paths, a dovecote made of lashed branches holds messenger pigeons that serve as the town's link to far flung Elven settlements.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go square" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Leth Deriel, Basswood Terrace">
    <description>A mature oak tree with impeccably pruned foliage seems to flourish in the shadows of Sana'ati Dyaus to the north.  Cleverly trimmed hedges in the shapes of fanciful animals are admired by a casual, well dressed crowd of Elvenfolk.  One flowering vine, growing over a large hole in the oak's trunk, is cunningly trained around some branches to form the image of a dashing figure in a long, green cloak.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>Oaks line the inner arcs of this junction in an astonishing array of varieties.  Red oaks, white oaks, and holm oaks are all in the process of shedding acorns, much to the joy of the spotted piglet rooting among them.  Basswood Terrace intersects with the Circle here, straight north to the main clearing, and south to connect with the outer road that girds the city.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>Thorny shrubs clog the ground to the northwest.  On the opposite side, there towers a stately white oak with a trunk over five feet in diameter.  More striking still is the fact that the branches and surface are covered in intricate knotwork and figures carved in high relief.  You notice what appears to be some kind of door in the side of the trunk, cleverly fitted to almost conceal it.</description>
    <position x="140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>The circle here intersects with Merewala Court to the northwest.  Ankis Dir Boulevard, which lies southeast, leads out one of the gates to the mysterious stone observatory on the outskirts of town.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Leth Deriel, Merewala Court">
    <description>The path is wide, bowing out into the encroaching trees to form a court here.  It appears the leaves and branches of the surrounding wood have been carefully pruned to reveal a clear, welcome patch of sky.  A slender Elven lass, holding an exquisite brass telescope, smiles at you shyly before redirecting her gaze heavenward for a brief moment, and then disappears into the undergrowth.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>A high pitched shriek pierces the calm of the canopied road, and you instinctively tense up in a defensive posture.  Looking around, you perceive no threat, no foe, no foul creature that might be the source of such a bloodcurdling cry.  Like a knife, the shrill call shatters the peace again, and you notice a magnificent male peacock, his fan open, strutting along one of the arboreal platforms.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>One great tree, looking almost as old as Sana'ati Dyaus itself, nearly blocks the path here.  Its roots are a jumbled network of tendrils reaching above the surface and out across the road.  Sheets of bark are sloughing off the trunk in spots, and the tree throws its branches out wildly in all directions, as though casting jealously about to snare those beings fortunate enough not be rooted where they stand.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>An ancient banyan tree, the town's main temple, looms to the southwest, as pilgrims come and go in a steady, quiet stream.  Not only are there clerics, empaths, mages and other devotees of the spiritual in the mix, but more secular types also seem to cluster around the temple.  Its dark, leathery leaves rustle on high, maintaining rhythm with the intoned prayers, chants and hymns of worshippers gathered in its precincts.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>Twisted trees with scaly bark and glossy, dark green leaves surround you here.  Underfoot the path feels a bit dry and sandy.  To the north, on a swath of land that has been painstakingly cleared, stands an arbor of entwining vines.  Heady, musky bunches of deep purple grapes hang from the trellises.  A few willow baskets are scattered before a modest wattle structure to one side.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wattle structure" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>A perpetual, low lying mist obscures the ground in this part of Leth Deriel.  It curls around your feet and makes it difficult to see where you are stepping.  Something slimy reaches around your ankle and tugs at it, then lets go.  Nothing seems to be moving beneath the haze, all you can see are some half buried roots and a few vines whose ends are lost in fog.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>Stands of birches with gleaming white bark brighten the way.  Set back from the path slightly are the usual bothersome brambles.  A flash of tawny brown and a soft sighing from shadows close by reveal a sloe-eyed doe, dining contentedly on a feast of blackberries served up on thorny offshoots.  Behind the deer, several cloaked figures with aquiline features gather the ripe fruit.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>The surreal sense of being caught in a web, being toyed with by the unseen inhabitants all about you is heightened by the soft, elusive perfumes of leaf and wood floating by on the warm, moist zephyrs.  A whiff of a lady's cologne, or a curl of pipe smoke, a scent of leather all taunt your nostrils.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>The northwest side of the path is lined with fresh, green willow trees, eternally thirsty for the nourishment and moisture in the dark, rich soil here.  A sudden breeze playfully toys with their branches, like a kitten batting at a length of yarn.  Just as abruptly, the air currents subside and all is still, save for the sound of your own heavy footsteps.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Leth Deriel, Liyos Approach">
    <description>Tall proud conifers line the approach here.  The faint scent of pine resin gives you cause to stop and recall the last time that you enjoyed that refreshingly clear smell.  Squirrels leap cheerfully from limb to limb in search of more bounty and to escape each other.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Leth Deriel, Liyos Approach">
    <description>Chains of liberated prisoners are hanging from trees and serve as a remembrance of times more harsh.  In former times, the condemned prisoner was dragged to the gallows, hanged by the neck until either a prolonged gurgling sound issued forth or a quick clean snap was heard.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gallows tree" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Leth Deriel, Peri'el Way">
    <description>Light and shadow weave a tangled web of enchantment, with dappled forms falling along the well-tended path here.  Shapes that sometimes look man-like, sometimes bird-like, quickly dissolve into undifferentiated shadows.  The hedge here is no longer purely ornamental, but composed of various species of medicinal shrubs.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle" note="street vendor's cart|Chestnuts" color="#FF0000">
    <description>On the northeast verge of the central clearing, in the shadow of Sana'ati Dyaus, stands a figure shod in rags and cloaked in a tattered green blanket.  She huddles over an iron brazier, stirring chestnuts in a pan.  The crowd around the tree, which also serves as the town hall, barely notices her cries as she hawks her wares.  Nor do they heed those of the infant swaddled in dirty skins that she bends down to comfort every now and again.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Leth Deriel, Ankis Dir Boulevard">
    <description>A riotous melange of colorful berry bushes flourish beneath the fragrant durmast trees here.  Some look ripe, plump and pleasingly edible, others, of more vivid hue, look violently poisonous.  A brilliantly painted willow shack off the path is surrounded by low hanging limbs.  From these boughs hang freshly dyed votive strips of fabric and wet garments in every shade of the rainbow.</description>
    <position x="200" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go willow shack" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Leth Deriel, Ankis Dir Boulevard">
    <description>Southeast lies the Durmast Bower Gate that leads to the stone observatory of Ankis Dir, built by an ancient Elven dynasty that once called Leth Deriel its capital.  The boulevard continues straight to the center of town northwest, where you can see the leafy spires of Sana'ati Dyaus.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vine-covered cottage" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The air is heavy with the oily scent of the durmast trees that grow thickly along the inner arc of the circle here.  To the southeast, they thin out into a single file, meeting the deobars of the town walls at right angles.  The durmasts continue, forming the overarching gate that leads to the stone observatory of Ankis Dir.</description>
    <position x="260" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Leth Deriel, Durmast Bower Gate" note="Durmast Bower Gate|SE Gate">
    <description>A few thickets form tangled blankets over sharp, irregular outcrops of native stone, while dense, regular stands of thick-trunked durmast trees form a narrow defile leading southeast.  Their grey, fissured bark marks them as ghostly guardians and their stiff, leathery leaves rustle of their own accord, voices on a wind yet unborn that beckon and admonish you to pass beyond.</description>
    <position x="280" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go durmast gate" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Some great force, beyond any a mortal spellcaster or axe wielder could muster, has split the trunk of a stout deobar here in two, leaving a V-shaped gash from crown to roots.  The splintered edges of the inner wood are green and alive, with no signs of charring from fire or lightning.  Through the fissure to the east, you can see the outline of Ankas Dir, the Observatory of the Cosmic Eye.</description>
    <position x="240" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Looking down to avoid the roots and creepers that lay in your way, you barely keep your footing.  Suddenly, a soft chittering commands your attention.  A ruddy faced Elven lad stands just off the path, conversing with a ferret lurking in the underbrush.  Absorbed in watching, you trip over a stray taproot.  Instantly, the boy leaps to your aid, lifts you up effortlessly and smiles.  You amble off sheepishly.</description>
    <position x="220" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The path here is rutted and unkempt.  Ground ivy and fallen vines line the walkway.  Between two spear-like young poplars is stretched an enormous spider web, its silken strands glinting with drops of a sticky substance.  Something brushes against your cheek and you jump back, only to find it is just an overhanging, leafy branch.</description>
    <position x="200" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>You have reached the southernmost point along the outer rim of the Elven stronghold.  One broad spoke, Basswood Terrace, leads north directly to the central hub that is the town's gathering place.  Even from here, you can see the weathered, hoary crown of Sana'ati Dyaus towering above all the other trees.</description>
    <position x="120" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The sharp, cedar-like scent of the deobar wood along the south mingles with the resinous aroma of the slender, pyramidal pines that line the inner area.  The pines are sparse, and thickets of berry bushes grow in their shade.  Soft beds of fallen needles entice you to leave the path, as does a curious wooden shed set back under one of the taller conifers.</description>
    <position x="40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden shed" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>A shallow pond north of the path is surrounded by reeds and rushes.  Overhanging the water are young willows, their tender limbs trailing across its surface.  Pointy leaves float towards shore, launched by a breeze in a miniature re-enactment of the mighty Elven fleets of yore.  Tied bundles of cut twigs and stalks are piled along the far bank, next to a wattle-and-daub hut.</description>
    <position x="20" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hut" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Gradually, imperceptibly, the defensive stands of deobars merge with the darker, higher trees beyond.  These wild woodland interlopers form the fringe of the inaccessible weald surrounding Leth Deriel to the south and southwest.  In a gloomy hollow beneath the roots of a half-dead deobar, you see a crudely carved wooden figure.</description>
    <position x="0" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The deobar fence here rises high, but there is a narrow gap left where one of the trees has fallen.  A peek through it reveals a grassy clearing to the southeast, with a grey granite dome rising at its center.  Atop the outcrop, immense angular stone blocks are silhouetted against the heavens.</description>
    <position x="280" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The roots of the deobars, deep and strong, quest downward for nourishment.  In their inexorable search, the trees are mightier than the very stones, as their roots crack and pulverize the rock.  Along with their fallen leaves, the deobars thus transform the terrain into dark, fertile soil, which provides the residents with nature's bounty.</description>
    <position x="300" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The path curves north and southwest, with the deobar walls directly to your east.  So tall and lush is their growth here that it is difficult to see much in the shadows.  Warblings, calls and responses, echo from the branches of the red maples to the west.  A watch of nightingales has honored you with their chorus, but are roused from their roosts by several green garbed figures hurrying by.</description>
    <position x="320" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>A rustic Elven youth weaves among the mature red maples that crowd along the path to the west, gathering small buckets filled with thick, sweet sap.  Following behind him, an Elothean trader calmly and rationally negotiates for his sticky goods, having little apparent success.  A few plump, slow moving honey bees buzz by your ears, heading northwest.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The deobar stands and the sturdy platforms high among their branches bound the east side of the circle here.  They protect the residents of Leth Deriel from unwanted visitors and serve as a windbreak in this fairly open spot.  A clearing along the inner area holds several wooden frames around which swarm black clouds of loudly buzzing bees.  A colorful one room house sits behind the crude apiaries.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go house" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The earthy aroma of the packed dirt road invigorates you.  Just off the path, the soil is less compact, and leaf mold and fallen logs play host to colonies of brightly colored mushrooms.  Their spotted, angry red caps attract the local insects, who occasionally buzz past your nose.  Depressions in the soft beds indicate some of the fungus has been recently gathered.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The deobars thin out, leaving the path northeast to E'erdream Bower Gate lined only with straight, wispy E'erdream trees.  Their lacy foliage sways lazily overhead and the fragrance of their flowers fills your nostrils.  The soft beds of fallen leaves at their bases look like the perfect spot for a short nap.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Bracket fungus clings to the bark and roots of the deobar barricades here.  Dignified elder Eloths, Elves, Humans and even a Halfling or two, all dressed in loose, dark robes that swish about their ankles, stride by.  Groups of lanky Elven boys and girls dash past, all clad in some kind of green sylvan uniform.  Their haste seems at once purposeful and graceful.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Sullen Elven lads wield pine-bough brooms and sweep the path perfunctorily.  The platform in the trees along the north bristles with vigilant archers.  Such protection is merited by the presence of eminent scholars from all over Elanthia, who lecture at Izma Ru'ef, Leth Deriel's university.  Truly a seat of higher learning, it is headquartered in the tall sequoia set off from the south side of the road.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>Venerable mages, veteran fighters, intense empaths, and otherworldly clerics of all races pass by, headed west to the main gate of town or east to the Elven university of Izma Ru'ef.  There appears to be a conspicuous lack of traders, bards, thieves and other frivolous sorts among the mix.  You straighten up and try to look intellectual while a blue-black raven perched in a redwood regards you with disdain.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Leth Deriel, Rowntree Shade">
    <description>A small arbor marks a quiet spot by the side of the road for rest and contemplation.  A wooden bench, hewn of ash and lovingly shaped, looks surprisingly comfortable.  Beneath a cool bush, a wide oaken bucket with a ladle fashioned from a gourd offers liquid refreshment for the weary pedestrian.  Perched on its rim, a bright red cardinal daintily sips and then flits off.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shop" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>The road seems oddly empty, in fact the entire town seems more like a silent forest than an urban center.  The few folks that you encounter appear to be outsiders, travelers, hunters, pilgrims, foragers, and traders.  Nevertheless a constant soft whispering, and movement of leaves just beyond the road hint at hidden life and the secret bustle of a city.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Leth Deriel, Elder Bark Circle">
    <description>To the southeast beyond the solid wall of hedges you spy a great hickory tree rising above its surroundings.  Its branches are heavy with nuts and all the woodland creatures that those attract.  Impossibly straddling the stouter branches in the midst of the tree is a two story wooden structure that you can just barely make out from this vantage point.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Leth Deriel, Rowntree Walk">
    <description>This part of town seems relatively well frequented, its haughty citizens mingling somewhat condescendingly with outsiders who have business in Leth Deriel.  Reserved laughter and banter with a distinctive Elvish lilt, mixed with harsh cries and shouts from less refined tongues, reverberate overhead.  Mesmerizing music in the wide branches of the hickory tree a few paces west off the walkway tugs at you from above.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Leth Deriel, Rowntree Walk">
    <description>An old trunk, shattered by age or a storm, mossy and hoary with lichen, assumes a supernatural aspect in the shifting light that filters into the heart of the sylvan fastness of the city.  Around its rotting form swirl mists that seem to take on shapes of woodland spirits.  Faint laughter echoes from the treetops.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Leth Deriel, Rowntree Walk">
    <description>Acacia gum and sandalwood trees line the path.  Their fragrance mingles with an indescribable melange of scents that drift up from the south, complex, heady and entirely enchanting.  A brilliant yellow brimstone butterfly zigzags past, as though it too were intoxicated by the very air here.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>A meandering path off the main road leads to a tiny shack, so covered in vines and dried leaves that it is almost invisible in the half-murk of the woodland interior that is the essence of Leth Deriel.  A sweet, elusive scent drifts over from it that tantalizes, inflames and soothes the senses all at once.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meandering path" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Leth Deriel, Before Rest of Ages Inn">
    <description>This is the base of the hickory tree in which is housed the Rest of Ages Inn.  Irresistible scents of cooked meat, sausages and stews drift out of the door and windows all the while exciting the taste buds.  The constant coming and going of patrons suggests that the Inn has a lively trade.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stable door" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hickory tree" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Leth Deriel, Stable Yard">
    <description>Set into the back side of the hickory tree that houses the Rest of Ages Inn, this small stable has little to offer beyond fresh straw, a clean stall, and a dry roof for its equine residents.  Two pots of white geraniums rest near the tree's massive trunk, and a path of trampled straw leads back to the inn.  A metal sign with a cut-out of a prancing horse swings above the stable door.  Stablehands wander through the area, taking horses into the barn for customers looking to stable their animals.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stable door" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Leth Deriel, Lorethew Lerili Road">
    <description>The leafy tunnel overhead provides a highway for fuzzy tailed squirrels, fat-cheeked chipmunks, and darting greenish-brown lizards.  A few stray acorns fall to the ground with a dull thud, missing you by a narrow margin.  A break in the hedgerow to the south leads to a hut with a smoking chimney, from which wafts the unmistakable aroma of baking bread.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hut" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Leth Deriel, Lorethew Lerili Road">
    <description>The trees converge here, and their crowns spread out to meet in a canopy of leafy boughs.  Passing through this soothing and shady tunnel of foliage, the songs of the feathered sylvan orchestra overhead are amplified as they warble their myriad hymns to the ageless deities who watch over Leth Deriel.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Leth Deriel, E'erdream Bower Gate" note="E'erdream Bower Gate|Northeast Gate|NE Gate">
    <description>You could listen to the melody of the calling birds here in the greenwood for what would seem to be mere minutes but when roused from your reverie, actual years, so enchanting and vibrant are their songs at this gate.  Brilliant E'erdream trees form colonnades on either side of the way, leading southwest back into the heart of town, and northeast to a grassy hillock.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go e'erdream gate" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Leth Deriel, Aldiyaus Square">
    <description>Kilth Aldiyaus, Leth Deriel's main temple dedicated to all the gods and goddesses of Elanthia, is housed in the intersecting aerial roots and branches of an old banyan tree off the south side of the path here.  The branches arcing to the ground form new saplings, and those too will do the same when they mature.  The chambers of the temple are contained within the labyrinthian thickets of rooted limbs and limb-like roots, allowing communion with the elements and open air.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Leth Deriel, Oakenheart Circle">
    <description>A circle of interlocking wooden logs, about waist high, stands off to one side.  Over it, broad leafed Zulnatha trees form a sheltering roof.  Beads of dew roll off the leaves and into the center of the log circle with a muffled plop.  You realize that the structure is some kind of well or reservoir.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>An unusual flurry in the undergrowth beyond bursts out onto the road in the form of a full fledged gaggle of geese that waddle furiously past.  In their haste to reach the other side, they scatter feathers everywhere, as if some unseen keeper were guiding them.  Just when their honking subsides, a downy yellow gosling toddles by with a plaintive *PEEP PEEP*.</description>
    <position x="80" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tool shed" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>Here is yet another intersection, where Cambium Circle joins Myristica Wynd to the southwest and Atila Lane to the northeast.  You sense at this and at every corner or turn along the streets of Leth Deriel, that clearings, tended paths and compacted dirt roads are grudging concessions to the outsiders who provide essential trade goods, foodstuffs and raw materials to the disdainful locals.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Leth Deriel, Cambium Circle">
    <description>This area is slightly marshy, with broad banyan trees sending off shoots into the spongy, black ground.  Bunches of thin stalked, green fringed papyrus plants grow along the margins of a deep artificial pool here.  Dry clumps of stubble indicate these plants have been cultivated and harvested from time to time.  A shed, constructed of oiled paper stretched over branches lashed crosswise, stands to one side.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk tent" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Leth Deriel, Atila Lane">
    <description>A log cabin, one of the more prosperous-looking freestanding structures in Leth Deriel, perches jauntily just off the path to the north.  Elegantly planned and planted beds of fern and fir alternating with colorful flame-leaf shrubs landscape the cabin grounds, cleverly melding into the surrounding forested environment.  A gilded sign hangs over the door.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go side door" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Leth Deriel, Myristica Wynd">
    <description>Scattered along the wayside are exquisitely carved miniatures of horses, unicorns, gazelles, and carts.  A rush doll, dressed in an immaculate replica of an Elven lady's finery, lies in the middle of the path.  From the hedgerows on both sides, you hear high-pitched childish giggles, though you see nothing in the shadows.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Leth Deriel, Myristica Wynd">
    <description>The path is carpeted with a soft, springy cover of mosses and wildflowers.  On either side, immense tree trunks limit your view. Each is clad in its own coloring of leaves, texture of bark and mantle of woodland life, as unique as any sentient being.  Seated cozily in the crooks of the trees are humble structures from which emanate sounds of domestic harmony.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden staircase" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Leth Deriel, Basswood Terrace">
    <description>The gladdening sight of crowds greets you along this busy section of Basswood Terrace.  Here are races both local and far flung gathered in animated conversation.  Snatches of heraldic verse and snippets of recitations both sacred and profane fill the air.  Ensconced in vine-sheltered nooks between the basswood trunks, groups of bards engaged in impromptu competitions hold forth.</description>
    <position x="120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Leth Deriel, Basswood Terrace">
    <description>Wandering in your own bemused solitude, you ignore the tall, graceful figures treading almost noiselessly past, who leave the road and melt mysteriously into the verdant depths of the woods that are the soul of Leth Deriel's inner life.  Captivating music and convivial clamor drift in from the north.  A carved, lyre-shaped sign hangs from a basswood tree, over a man high knothole.</description>
    <position x="120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go knothole" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Leth Deriel, Izma Ru'ef Entrance">
    <description>Exuding a sense of serenity, the tall sequoia which houses Leth Deriel's university towers over you.  A handful of students make their way past, heading out to the main road.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go great knot" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove Lawn" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Due east, a clearing atop a small grassy hill rises to a point.  At its summit you can barely make out a circular growth of plants at regularly-spaced intervals.  To the southwest is E'erdream Bower gate, through which lies the Elven stronghold of Leth Deriel.  Thick stands of deobar trees form an impenetrable wall around the city on either side of the arching canopy of E'erdream trees.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Bosque Deriel, Trelda's Faery Ring">
    <description>You come upon a circular clearing, wreathed in mist and ringed by the largest toadstools you have ever seen.  The haze curls around the base and beneath the caps of the gigantic mushrooms, creeping noiselessly along and from time to time assuming fanciful Elven shapes.  Inside the ring, the dirt is trodden down, and the grass does not grow, as if a circle dance of intense frenzy had been performed here night after night, since before time was.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Bosque Deriel, Dense Woods">
    <description>Something brownish-green darts through the branches overhead, and suddenly falls at your feet with a *THWAP*!  The chameleon skitters away, and hot on its tail, out of nowhere, bursts an Elven child, clad in brownish green like its quarry.  Amid shrieks of delight, the child pursues the lizard as they both melt into the forest.  To the north, the land becomes more open and grassy, rising slightly, while to the south are clumps of trees.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Bosque Deriel, Dense Woods">
    <description>The darkness of the woods is almost absolute here, making you lose all sense of time and place.  Low locust trees line the path, their long, thin pods hanging down like serpents ready to drop and squeeze your last life's breath out of you.  Looking at the ground, you notice a diamond-backed snake slowly coiling its way into a hollow root cave.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Bosque Deriel, Hermit's Shacks">
    <description>Here on the route between the sacred sites of the Observatory and the Faery Ring is a semi-circular clearing.  At its center stands a hut made of lashed branches, roofed with broad leaves.  A certain sect of Elven clerics, who are renowned for their devotion to contemplation, are wont to retire into the solitudes of the woods and groves hereabouts.  They are not, however, renowned for their hospitality.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Bosque Deriel, Burial Ground">
    <description>You come upon an Elven burial ground in the shade of sacred groves.  The graves are almost impossible to distinguish from the surrounding forest growth, save for a slight elevation, greener cover, and saplings planted at their heads to commemorate the departed soul.  The forest nomads also come here, and leave their dead in the trees, to be stripped by scavenger birds.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Bosque Deriel, Greengrove">
    <description>The trees here are uniform and have all the appearance of being trimmed by art or artifice.  They almost take on the shapes of the very woodland creatures that cavort among them.  One especially fine beech tree has clay watering pots filled with wine resting among its roots.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Bosque Deriel, Greengrove">
    <description>A grove of evergreen oaks and laurels flourishs in the dry, gritty soil here.  Several fresh holes, dark and moist, are apparent, as though someone were planting trees.  Trunks, charred by forest fire or split by lightning, lie on the ground, torn up by their roots.  A few deer carcasses are draped over them, newly killed.  A path leads up to the south, rising to the top of Ankis Dir.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Bosque Deriel, Ankis Dir Observatory">
    <description>A monument to the ancient Elven craftsmen of stone, the main observatory at Ankis Dir consists of four enormous rocks placed two by two so as to form an alley ten feet long and six feet wide between them.  A fifth rock, higher and thicker than the others, closes the space to the east.  The whole platform on which these stones stand is carved from a huge, thick mass of bedrock.  A path leads down to the north.</description>
    <position x="360" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Bosque Deriel, Ankis Dir Observatory">
    <description>A ruined dolmen in the shape of a royal tomb squats solidly in the middle of the stone rubble atop the granite dome.  Close by it is a fountain, carved from a massive block of native black rock.  Beside the fountain is a marvelous step-like structure of stone, and an oak from which hangs a golden basin.  The basin is filled with fresh rain water.</description>
    <position x="360" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Bosque Deriel, Ankis Dir Observatory" note="Ankis Dir Observatory|Observatory">
    <description>The Durmast Bower Gate leading into Leth Deriel lies to the northwest.  The level forest floor transitions to a sloping hill here.  It becomes less grassy and steeper to the east, and the path in that direction is composed mostly of granite with a few weeds in the cracks.  Atop this outcrop stand the grey stone menhirs of Ankis Dir, the ancient Elven Observatory of the Cosmic Eye.  To the southwest, a small trail meanders off into dense forest.</description>
    <position x="320" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Bosque Deriel, Dense Woods">
    <description>Dense woodlands, undergrowth and lack of any visible path apart from the way back all prove daunting enough to prevent you from exploring any farther.  A shriek in the trees overhead and a barely audible rustle reveal the unseen presence of a Neldian forest cat.  To the northeast looms the grey granite hill crowned with the jagged stone monoliths of Ankis Dir.</description>
    <position x="300" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grass-covered hill" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Bosque Deriel, Trelda's Faery Ring">
    <description>These gloomy groves surround the Faery Ring and are said to be tenanted by supernatural beings and phantom wayfarers, all too charmed to leave this place, even in death.  When passing through the somber shade, the breeze rustles the heavy foliage and causes branches to sway and creak.  To the northwest, to your relief, is a golden glow along the tree line.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Bosque Deriel, Golden Grove">
    <description>The trees here all bear foliage in a glorious yellow hue.  On a tree of deep gold-yellow shade is a branch with supple leaves and limber twigs of real gold, the mark of a sacred site.  This whole grove covers and shades a carpet of yellow-tipped mosses.  It is said if a traveler plucks the golden bough, a wood sprite will appear to lead the adventurer to a sacred secret place.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go faint path" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches">
    <description>Trees to the north, where Bosque Deriel merges with the Endrus Forest, seem different, more homogenous, while those to the south in the heart of the Bosque grow in a riotous profusion of color, height, flower, fruit and foliage, appearing to be in all stages of development and season.  The view to the south truly would gladden the heart of all but the most jaded of travelers.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches">
    <description>A falcon stoops from on high, swooping down to snatch up some smaller, tastier game bird.  A quick whistle, a whirring and flapping send the feathered hunter on its way.  Although there is no sign of two-legged hunters about, you wonder whether that choice catch will grace some Elven lord's dinner table shortly.  This path through the trees continues around Leth Deriel's northern border.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches">
    <description>A covey of pheasants races across the road, some running, some flying, flushed out of the undergrowth by some unseen hunting party.  Shouts in Elvish ring out from the forest, and an arrow whizzes by your ear, lodging in the breast of a particularly plump bird.  Not wanting to get caught in another crossfire, you hurry along.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches">
    <description>At the bases of the trees here are thick beds of matted, decaying leaves and twigs.  Flourishing in the rich mixture are curiously beautiful bird's nest orchids.  The tangled roots of the woodland plants grow up from out of the ground, surrounding the stalks with what appear to be untidy nests.  Overhead, their arboreal cousins, epiphytes of other sorts, grow in the crooks of branches.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Stout pines and deobars predominate here, and at the base of one of the taller trees, dug deep into the loamy ground, is a burrow hole.  A heap of dirt forms a mound marking the entrance.  All the surrounding standing timber shows deep, ragged claw marks, where the resident badger is wont to sharpen its claws.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches">
    <description>A dun-colored woodcock, the plain female of the species, scratches with her feet and pokes for worms in the soft earth here.  A rustling in the scrubby bush startles her and she takes flight.  Out of the corner of your eye, you spy an Elven hunter making her way through the foliage, a brace of game birds over her shoulder.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brush-choked pathway" destination="260" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Bosque Deriel, Northern Reaches" note="RTZ23|RT-LNW-LF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The trees thin out a bit to the southeast, where the path leads to some kind of junction.  The sounds of crowds and carts along the way echo from that direction, an uneasy interruption of the deep silent reverie that pervades Bosque Deriel.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel">
    <description>Sounds unlike any you know whirl about you in a choir of whisperings, rustlings, murmurings, and guttural hisses.  Strange calls, unlike those of any bird, reverberate in the treetops.  You feel as though this is all for your benefit or rather to your detriment, as though someone or something were watching all the traffic along this route, and signaling your approach.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel">
    <description>A purposeful rustling overhead makes you look up.  Atop platforms of lashed branches and planks stand Elven archers, watchfully guarding the approach to Leth Deriel.  The treetops bristle with their numbers.  In various spots of the road, you notice broken arrow shafts sticking out of the dirt.  These appear to be recent additions to the roadbed.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel">
    <description>The Elven woodland fortress of Leth Deriel looms before you to the south, its walls of defensive deobar trees forming huge arcs to the southwest and east.  The high tops and entwined branches of the Alder Bower Gate overshadow the south section of the road.  Even from this distance, you see the tallest, most ancient and most venerated tree in the Elven lands, the Sana'ati Dyaus, which stands at the center of the city.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Southern Trade Route, Outside Leth Deriel" note="NW Gate">
    <description>Directly before you to the south stands the main entrance that connects Leth Deriel with the outside world.  Huge stands of alder trees form the gate, their branches raising and falling to allow caravans, expeditions and large groups to pass through.  On either side, a living palisade of deobar trees serves as a protective, impenetrable fortification around the entire stronghold.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bower gate" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Leth Deriel, Alder Bower Gate" note="Alder Bower Gate|Northwest Gate|NW Gate">
    <description>Huge, broad leafed alder trees shoot up tall and straight, sentinels in constant watch over the main gate that leads into and out of Leth Deriel, ancient Elven stronghold.  Their spreading crowns meet high overhead, forming a dense, impenetrable roof, as stalwart as any fortress made by nature or artifice.  The way leading into the town is quite wide here.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bower gate" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel" note="Map60_STR1.xml|STR1|Crossing">
    <description>While pondering the fantastic variety of flora here, you listen to the wildlife encircling you.  Familiar bird songs, insect chirpings, and the rooting of forest-floor foragers all comfort you.  And yet, there is an undercurrent, a foreign and disquieting subtext of sounds and voices that lie just outside your conscious range of hearing.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Bosque Deriel, Whispering Woods">
    <description>Oracle Hollow dips to the northwest, a slight depression with rushes, reeds, bamboos and willows growing in abundance, fed by a stream from the south.  The whispering of these tall, swaying plants together with the murmurings of the spring form an unearthly chorus.  To the southwest you see the gleaming surface of Mirror Lake, while to the northeast traffic to and from the town passes through.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Bosque Deriel, Whispering Woods" note="RTZ22|RT-LNW-GPN" color="#C2B280">
    <description>A grove of old trees has shot up above the common height of the surrounding forest.  They shut out the sight of the sky by the gloom of their matted boughs.  You feel there is a spirit in this place, so lofty is the wood, so lone the spot, so wondrous the thick, unbroken shade.  Their entwined leaves rustle amid the gurgling of the stream that flows north into the hollow, from its source, the lake to the south.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Bosque Deriel, Ilkas Veridun">
    <description>Frogs croak and call to each other, from limb to limb, shore to shore.  The west side of the lake is swathed in lily pads and floating lotuses, their black seeds gleaming like myriad dark moons.  A small stream flows north from the lake, its murmurings seeming to carry portents in their effervescent currents.  The mirror-smooth surface of the water remains impossibly undisturbed.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Bosque Deriel, Oracle Hollow">
    <description>The ground is grassy in this slight depression.  A gentle upward slope to the southeast leads to the forest encircling Leth Deriel.  Here, in Oracle Hollow, have the Elvenfolk and other seekers of knowledge gathered since time immemorial, beseeching the woodland spirits to foretell the fates of men and empires.  At the bottom of the hollow a sacred grove of bamboo marks the spot where ceremonies are conducted.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Bosque Deriel, Ilkas Veridun">
    <description>The path verges on the eastern shore of Ilkas Veridun, the Mirror Lake, sacred to the Elven peoples of Elanthia.  Its waters are said to raise the dead, if used with a pure spirit and a right mind.  The surface is like glass, reflecting the sky and trees, with no ripples or bubbles breaking it.  Two streams lead out of the lake, one flowing north, the other east.  You cannot detect the source of all this water though.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Bosque Deriel, Hag's Rill">
    <description>A small stream flows out of Ilkas Veridun eastwards, and disappears into the ground beneath a large tree.  A korrigan is said to haunt the sylvan spring here by night.  She lures unwary travelers to an enchanted castle far beneath the floor of Ilkas Veridun, or so the superstition goes, for a night of faery revelry.  At dawn, she turns into her true form, a hideous hag, and leaves her victims beside the path, most quite mad for life.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Bosque Deriel, Clearing">
    <description>The clearing here is eerily desolate, blanketed in brambles and other thorny plants.  Local legend has it this clearing is the haunt of hags and witches, and should be shunned by all but the bravest travelers.  The air hums with hordes of almost-invisible gnats.  Perhaps the strangest feature of the terrain is a large, out-of-place boulder that appears to cover a hole leading underground.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Bosque Deriel, Clearing">
    <description>A solitary rowan tree, apparently never growing any larger, sits by itself in this corner of the clearing, seeming forlorn and abandoned.  There is a gravel path circling it, along which are glistening trails of slime that appear to be left by some species of gastropod, although the oozing tracks are ten times wider than any snail could possibly leave.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Stalks of spiny bladebrush growing along the roadside have been neatly pruned back to keep from attacking any passerby who stays to the trail, but the sharp fronds and thorn bushes discourage most from venturing into the woods.  A few scraps of tattered cloth and strands of beast-like hair prove that not everybody is so timid of the vicious plants.  The path is a misshapen fork, one tine pulling northwest, the other tine bending southwest.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Old Crank's Road, Field">
    <description>Invisible through the dense forest, the only indication of the nearby city wall and catwalk overhead is the occasional call from tree to tree where Leth Deriel's Elven guards watch for danger.  A large boulder forces the path to bend around it.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" note="Map112_Ilaya_Taipa.xml|Ilaya Taipa">
    <description>Tufts of dragon lilies edge the rutted path, adding a vibrant wash of red and orange to the muted greens of the forest's trees, moss and weeds.  A nearby gurgle of water soaks the ear with sound, and the cool tang of damp earth tingles the nose.  Relatively straight through this section of the forest, the path becomes slightly wider as it flows southwesterly.</description>
    <position x="-220" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>Roots from a massive oak growing beside the road erupt from below, threatening to lame beasts and break wheels.  Sharp cuts in the bark are evidence of attempts to remove the hazard, but thus far, the tree is winning the battle.  The road takes a sharp bend as it continues to follow the diamond-shaped outline of the city wall.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="slow south" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="slow northwest" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest" note="RTZ30|RT-LWN-IT" color="#C2B280">
    <description>Veering away from the Southern Trade Route to travel northwesterly into the Bosque Deriel, this narrow roadway is little more than a rutted caravan track meandering beneath the great canopy of trees.  Grey with age and leaning precariously, a weathered sign is wedged into a mound of stones near the edge of the track.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>Smooth flagstones line the dusky-red soil of the road.  Bright yellow flowers peek from around dark patches of green moss, their tones falling gently over the sparse earth like abandoned drops of sunlight.</description>
    <description>Patches of night shadow the flagstones of the road.  Their darkness blots over and dims the bright yellow of the delicate flowers nearby.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel" note="Map62_STR2.xml|STR2|Gondola|Shard">
    <description>The road twists and winds southward, the density of trees becoming sparse and thin as the frequency of travel picks up.  The Deobar Bower Gate to the north peeks quietly over the dark ironwood trees clustering around Leth Deriel.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Bosque Deriel, Forest">
    <description>Only the loudest shouts filter this deep into the forest, where a bird's whistle is more common than a teamster's.  Thick stands of deobar trees laced together by half-hidden catwalks overlook the narrow dirt pathway meandering through the woods.  These swinging perches are part of the high road encircling the city, where the Leth Deriel guards patrol and keep a watchful eye upon those approaching and leaving the gates.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Bosque Deriel, Forest">
    <description>This far from the gate, the brool of the forest's voice has replaced all town noises.  The roadway, no more than a wide earthen trail hewn from the forest floor, bends sharply to accommodate the exposed root of a sequoia.  The tree is short by reckoning of its kind and seems out of place among the crowding deobar and leaf-patched rutted road.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Bosque Deriel, Forest">
    <description>Beyond the weeds marking this winding, well-traveled road's edge, is a busted wagon wheel leaning against a moss-dappled boulder.  Strands of honeysuckle twisting up the wheel's cracked wooden spokes look as though they are trying to mend the wheel so that it can continue upon its way.  High overhead, the forest's canopy twitches with life as the branches and leaves shake with unseen activity.</description>
    <description>Beyond the weeds marking this winding, well-traveled road's edge, is the dim shape of a wagon wheel leaning against a dark boulder.  Bound in place by honeysuckle vines twisting up the wheel's wooden spokes, it has come to its journey's end.  High overhead, the branches of the forest's canopy are visible only as swaying shades of dark that call and howl with nocturnal life.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Bosque Deriel, Forest">
    <description>Shrubs and weeds vie with lacy ferns for space along the twisting, deeply rutted road's edge.  Someone has tried to patch the worst of the holes with loose stones and leaves, but the repairs are impermanent and already failing.  Slabs of white stones are piled into a cairn at the edge of the road.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Fala Inisulen, Road">
    <description>Mountain laurel grow in clumps among the sequoia, like small flowers clustered against the base of a towering oak.  The road twists among the giant trees, then merges with a wide, dry stream bed before heaving itself over the bank and continuing into the forest.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Fala Inisulen, Road">
    <description>Veering neither left nor right, the road continues straight into an arched tunnel cut through a massive sequoia straddling the road.  From a distance the tunnel looks dangerously narrow, but the opening proves wide enough to allow for two lane caravan travel.  A sign planted at the base of the tree cautions, Yell first!</description>
    <position x="440" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sequoia tunnel" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Eik Wood, Granite Outcroppings">
    <description>A smooth, sloping granite outcropping, like a monolith fallen and half buried, stands as a gate between familiar ground and the forest beyond.  With the momentum of a trot it is an easy climb up and over to the forest trail.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb monolith" destination="182" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Imperial Depository, Lobby" note="Imperial Depository|Bank">
    <description>The inside of the lobby here is breathtaking, unlike anything else you have seen so far in Leth Deriel in terms of its display of wealth and worldliness.  The interior of the ebonwood tree has been polished and grooved to resemble rich paneling.  A brass sign along the far wall points up.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Imperial Depository, Domestic Branch" note="Teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Here at the inside of a large fork is a chamber that houses the tellers for local currency transactions.  Despite their rather conservative nature, the local merchants, traders and citizens seem to be conducting a fair amount of business.  A sign points up for the Foreign Branch.</description>
    <position x="190" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Imperial Depository, Foreign Branch" note="Exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Here is the foreign exchange window at which one province's currency may be exchanged for that of another.  Exchange rates in Leth Deriel have always been governed primarily by the forces of supply and demand - if you want supplies here, the town's merchants demand local currency.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Alberdeen's Meats and Provisions, Front Room" note="Alberdeen's Meats and Provisions|General" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Alberdeen the Provisioner is a rather rustic-looking Elf, more used to hunting and foraging than dealing with customers, but helpful nonetheless.  Salted and cured game, jerked meats, pickled eggs, and hard Elven waybread sit on simple shelves behind the counter, along with necessities like rope, sacks and simple tools.  The prices are reasonable, and one could equip a good-sized caravan or hunting party for a relatively modest outlay.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Alberdeen's Meats and Provisions, Storage Cellar">
    <description>Bags of produce and carcasses wrapped in burlap hang from cool recesses between tangled roots and rafters shored up with earth.  Kegs of salt, hogsheads of flour, crocks of honey and cheese, are all piled high in niches dug into the cool floor of the cellar.  Crates of ropes, candles, sacks, and other general merchandise lie open, ready to be restocked upstairs as needed.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="De'ali's Elven Delights, Salesroom" note="De'ali's Elven Delights|Candy" color="#FF0000">
    <description>De'ali, a grandmotherly elf and the proprietor of this popular sweet shop, is somewhat plump for her kind, but pleasingly so.  In her starched white apron, she meticulously arranges bonbons on trays atop a spotless display counter.  A sweet, heady almost cloying aroma wafts up from the back.  You can hear laughter and conversation from below and from outside the door.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="De'ali's Elven Delights, Cooking Room">
    <description>In a hollow just below ground, behind the shop's salesroom, is De'ali's Cooking Room, where wooden vats of simmering syrups and succulent fruits, herbs, nuts and other delights of the woods are transformed into scrumptious, sumptuous treats, almost magically.  Her young apprentices carefully monitor the process, gathered around the vats with long spoons and mixing paddles.  Despite their obvious dedication, they manage to laugh and gossip in the midst of their hot toil.</description>
    <position x="290" y="-170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Mithin's Bakery, Sales Counter" note="Mithin's Bakery|Bakery" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A profusion of loaves, rolls, biscuits and pastries greets you in this cheery hut, filled with the aroma of baking bread and rising sweetdough.  Mithin the baker stands smiling and ready to serve you.  A cool marble counter holds assorted fresh merchandise.</description>
    <position x="210" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Reena's Rainbow, Salesroom" note="Reena's Rainbow|Dyer" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Reena the Dyer dashes around the showroom, as flamboyant as the colors she produces.  Despite appearances, she is a painstaking and methodical perfectionist, since her calling requires her to be part artist, part alchemist.  All her dyes are prepared from the leaves, twigs, roots, berries, and flowers of indigenous plants or from local animal substances.  Swatches of dyed sample cloths are strewn across a faux marble counter next to a menu board listing all available color choices.</description>
    <position x="190" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Reena's Rainbow, Dyeing Vats">
    <description>Skeins of wool, spools of thread and bolts of fabric rest on wooden decks surrounding bubbling dye vats.  Reena's secret mixtures of natural substances and mordents produce noxious fumes but long-lasting, intense colors.  Apprentice dyers of various races and regions, hoping to learn the trade and start their own shops back home, tend to the actual operations.</description>
    <position x="190" y="10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Dove's Delightful Dwellings" note="Dove's Delightful Dwellings" color="#FF0000">
    <description>At first glance, one might easily mistake this charming shop for a private home, so discreet and well-placed are the displays of quality building materials.  Thin slabs of stone form colorful tiled patterns up the walls, and thick logs of expensive woods form an attractive border around the floor.  Dove, a slender Elven woman, busies herself about her wares with a jar of lemon oil and a soft cotton cloth.</description>
    <position x="240" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vine curtain" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Dove's Doors" note="Doors" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The pleasing fragrance of fresh-cut elm and wild flowers fills the back room of Dove's charming shop, drifting in on a light breeze from the woods beyond the wide-open windows.  A young Elf closely resembling the proprietor leans against a low counter at the back of the room, her face alight with an impish smile as customers peruse the selection of hand-turned doors on display.</description>
    <position x="250" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vine curtain" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Yerui's Woodcraft, Workshop" note="Yerui's Woodcraft|Woodcraft" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Wood shavings cover the floor, causing a slightly musty odor to permeate throughout the workshop.  Scattered all around are examples of Yerui's knowledge of woods and his skill with tools, displaying a fine talent in design in the various statues, toys and sundry items set out for sale.</description>
    <position x="140" y="10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Sinjian's Bardic Requisites, Sales Room" note="Sinjian's Bardic Requisites|Music" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Inside the basswood tree grows a green patch of grass, lending it the ambience of a courtyard.  Full of goldfish, a stone fount is an unexpected centerpiece to the eccentric atelier of Sinjian the bard, the charismatic but mercurial musical instrument maker and teacher.  Examples of his work, from harps, lyres, psalteries, and lutes to recorders, flutes and pennywhistles, line the shop walls.</description>
    <position x="130" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Sinjian's Bardic Requisites, Workshop">
    <description>Soundboards, strings, reeds, frets and various unidentifiable pieces cover a broad work table here, forgotten remnants of projects from earlier in the day.  Casting odd-shaped shadows that dance in the flickering lamplight, they seem more like a macabre jigsaw puzzle come to life rather than the exquisite instruments they will be turned into by the skillful hands of Sinjian and his apprentices.</description>
    <description>Soundboards, strings, reeds, frets and various unidentifiable pieces cover a broad work table here, looking more like a giant, unsolved jigsaw puzzle than the exquisite instruments they will be turned into by the skilled hands of Sinjian and his apprentices.  One such apprentice is planing some wood in the corner, her gaze intent upon her task.</description>
    <position x="130" y="70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut arch" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Sinjian's Bardic Requisites, Practice Room">
    <description>This modest sized chamber has curved walls and an arched ceiling to enhance the acoustics of any practice or performance.  Bardic verses, with their strict metrical patterns and themes of battle, glory and heroism, may be recited at the top of one's lungs, or that shaky fiddle tune practiced until it is impossible to resist its call to the dance.  It is in this room that Sinjian's select students receive their lessons as well.</description>
    <position x="130" y="90" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Blanca's Basketry and Wickerworks, Showroom" note="Blanca's Basketry and Wickerworks|Baskets|Wicker" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Twisted and woven works of basketry art hang from hooks and line shelves in the cramped interior of this wattle-and-daub hut.  Blanca, renowned throughout Elanthia, is a master at basketweaving and the art of turning wicker and willow into marvelous and useful creations.  Whimsical containers shaped like animals, trees and flowers, as well as more practical baskets for carrying and storage, can all be had here.</description>
    <position x="30" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Leth Deriel, Treetop Platform">
    <description>A heavy plank platform provides a solid base for a tiny wooden shack perched high in the branches of this ancient tree.</description>
    <position x="32" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden shack" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden staircase" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Leth Deriel, Wooden Shack" note="Wooden Shack|Weapons|Yithye" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Oil lanterns hung from the roof of the shack light the surrounding area with fitful flames.  The head of a large predatory cat snarls above two crossed wooden spears hanging from the wall.  Spread over the floor of the hut are a variety of animal pelts, providing a soft cushion of silky fur underfoot.</description>
    <description>Sunlight filtering through the high openings near the roof of the shack lights the surrounding area with a dim glow.  The head of a large predatory cat snarls above two crossed wooden spears hanging from the wall.  Spread over the floor of the hut are a variety of animal pelts, providing a soft cushion of silky fur underfoot.</description>
    <position x="45" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Khushi's, Back Room" note="Khushi's|Gems" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Several glass cases display exotic gems and rare corals gathered from throughout Elanthia.  Polishing equipment which, when used by skilled hands, will transform dull, common-looking stones into twinkling jewels rests on a workbench behind a counter.  Towards the rear of the room, Ghendil handles the business of acquiring precious materials for his partner's artistry.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Origami Boutique" note="Origami Boutique" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A tasteful, pale blue carpet and matching silk walls give this tent an open, airy feel.  Lighting is provided by a set of silver filigree lamps set most securely on the tent poles.  Fire is, understandably, a serious concern here.</description>
    <position x="32" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Leth Deriel, Willow Tree">
    <description>Arriving at the base of the willow tree, you hear the faint clanging noise of metal upon metal.  Though you can't see the source of this sound, you do notice you've come upon some sort of shop or abode, for in the side of the willow is a door of intricately woven branches.  A few broken arrow shafts lie on the ground around the entrance, and an arrow-shaped sign hangs above the door.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-90" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Huyelm's Trueflight Bow and Arrow Shop, Salesroom" note="Huyelm's Trueflight Bow and Arrow Shop|Bows|Fletching" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Huyelm is an expert archer, bowmaker and fletcher, who likes to expound on his craft and goods at great length to anyone who will listen.  Constructed inside this huge black willow tree, his shop sells archery equipment of all kinds, made from wood and hide, as well as more exotic material like bone, horn, and ivory.  Here bows and arrows can be purchased for sport, hunt or battle.  In one corner stands his own formidable weapon, an ash long bow as tall as a Human.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Huyelm's Trueflight Bow and Arrow Shop, Practice Branch">
    <description>A thick willow branch has been hollowed out but still appears much bigger inside than you could possibly imagine from outside.  At the wide entrance, where it intersects the trunk, are racks of quivers and bows of various sizes.  In the far tapering end of this branch is a very small target, the bull's eye looking no bigger than the eye of a sparrow from this vantage point.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Morikai's, Salesroom" note="Morikai's|Tannery" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Exceedingly large in size, this hut provides room for storage shelves filled with almost every kind of skin and hide known.  A fresh, almost comforting, scent of leather permeates everything.  A large catalog sits on one end of the counter while an assistant waits to serve your every need.  Fresh sawdust mingles with old, providing a dry and cushioned floor to walk on.  Morikai's Assistant stands beside a hide covered doorway.</description>
    <position x="-50" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doorway" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Morikai's, The Back Office" note="Bundles" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Nothing more than a small portion of the main hut blocked off with hide walls, this is where Morikai does his business of buying the skins and hides he sells on the main salesroom floor.  Plunked down behind a make-shift desk crowded with papers and dirty dishes, Morikai smiles up at you with a snaggle-toothed grin as he waits to see what you have to offer.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Leth Deriel, Meandering Path">
    <description>The tiny shack here is tidy and almost elegant in a simple way.  Spice bushes, flowering herbs and shrubs with scented bark grow all around it, and vines with bright yellow flowers trail up its sides.  A mixture of enchanting scents from the vegetation and from the activity in the shack itself greet you.  A meandering path leads back to the main road.</description>
    <position x="110" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny shack" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meandering path" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Madame Orris' Perfumerie, Salon" note="Madame Orris' Perfumerie|Perfume|Orris" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Madame Orris, an ancient mage of regal bearing, concocts brash and subtle perfumes with almost mystical effects.  Inside her tiny shack, she works olfactory magic with secret mixtures of aromatic substances derived from flowers, herbs and spices, all of which abound in the surrounding woods.  The walls and floor are plain, yet there is a richness here that hangs in the very air.</description>
    <position x="110" y="-130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Madame Orris' Perfumerie, Root Cellar">
    <description>Beneath the trunk that houses Madame's Salon is a cellar whose walls are the great roots of several trees.  Musky fungus grows liberally among the roots and decaying matter in the soil.  Airtight clay jars, large oaken casks, and ewers of essential oils and resins are half sunk into the dirt floor to keep them from the harmful effects of heat and light.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Carousel Square">
    <description>A massive conic building rises at the square's center, ringed by a series of lanterns supported atop high wrought-iron posts.  The structure glitters, the low glow of the lanterns flashing brilliantly off millions of colored crystals set into its surface.  Above an oval door, a mosaic of green and white marble reads THE CAROUSEL.</description>
    <position x="143" y="-30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="east" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Carousel" note="Carousel|Vault" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tiled in flawless green and white marble, a curved wall encircles the building's core.  A circular roof supports a vast framework of silversteel and timbers rising to the building's distant pinnacle.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights within the structure form the strikingly complex and beautiful mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="133" y="-30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go desk" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken arch" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandalwood arch" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Carousel Desk" note="Lost and Found" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A long wooden desk spans the width of the western wall.  Brass lanterns hang from the ceiling, and the floor behind the desk is covered in spotless red tile.</description>
    <position x="143" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go registrar's office" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go office" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Ongadine's Garb and Gear, Showroom" note="Ongadine's Garb and Gear|Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several lean mannequins, obviously based on Elven aesthetics, are set up inside the showroom, sporting the latest outfits for the well dressed urban ranger.  The polished oak walls glow softly, with full-sized mirrors inset at intervals.  Perched on a chair standing like a crane is the famous Elven clothier Ongadine.  Barely attempting to mask a sigh, he pauses long enough to peer down his nose at you.</description>
    <position x="108" y="-10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Ongadine's Garb and Gear, Fitting Room">
    <description>This rather claustrophobic room has a low ceiling and sharply curving walls.  It is barely large enough for someone to shed an old outfit and try on some smart new creation.  Straight pins and needles, wisps of thread and snippets of fabric are scattered all over the oak floor.</description>
    <position x="108" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Public Hall" note="Public Hall">
    <description>A large, bulging lower branch of the mighty Sana'ati Dyaus has been hollowed out to form the public auditorium here.  The arching ceiling and concave walls make the acoustics perfect for speeches, bardic recitals, music and plays.  Thick, sturdy grass mats form the spacious seating area, and spectators can spread out and enjoy the programs.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doorway" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open burl" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Grand Hollow" note="Grand Hollow">
    <description>You stand within the Grand Hollow of Sana'ati Dyaus.  Great vertical ribs of wood have been lovingly shaped over generations into upward-sweeping vaults and buttresses that support the vast interior space.  Light filters in from an unseen source on high.  As in all multistoried structures in Leth Deriel, inconspicuous wooden stairs sculpted into the sides of the chamber lead to the higher levels and upper branches of the trunk.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral ramp" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Mayoral Branch" note="Mayoral Branch">
    <description>It is difficult to tell from this office who it actually belongs to, save for some faceless, nameless town official.  Since the mundane day-to-day tasks of running a municipality have never appealed to the most talented and bright of Leth Deriel's citizens, having a politician in one's family line is more often a source of embarrassment than not.  There are not even portraits of former town officials on the walls here.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Fees Branch" note="Fees Branch|Debt" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A rather bored Elven lass presides over the office here, where debts, taxes, fees and other fines incurred within the jurisdiction of Leth Deriel are paid.  The spare furnishings consist of a table with a few cast-off chairs.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Registry Branch" note="Registry Branch">
    <description>Here is where legal and official things are recorded, including births, deaths, marriages and such, wills, inheritance, property deeds, and items.  The dusty folders on a decrepit desk in the center of the room attest to the regard that most Elvenfolk have for bureaucracy.  Behind the desk sits an even more decrepit looking Head Registrar, appearing emaciated even for one of his race.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Top Platform">
    <description>You stand at the highest point of the famed sylvan stronghold of Leth Deriel.  This platform is nestled in a fork of the topmost branches of the venerable Sana'ati tree which forms the focus of the town.  Groves and footpaths radiate out from this massive arbor in a series of concentric rings, much as the growth of a tree trunk is marked.  As you gaze down to observe the scurrying of townsfolk far below, you instinctively clutch for a secure branch.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Fala Inisulen, Sequoia Tunnel" note="Map58_Acenamacra_Village.xml|Acenamacra|Fang Cove|FC|Mammoth">
    <description>Carved initials and blown handprints cover the sides of the tunnel, souvenirs left by centuries of travelers.  The floor is littered with leaves and small bits of rubble have been pushed against the walls by passing caravans.  The ceiling, what can be seen in the dim light, looks covered in soot.  Some helpful traveler has painted a westerly-facing arrow on one wall that proclaims, Leth and on the opposite wall, an eastward arrow labeled, Ocean.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go east opening" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go west opening" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Old Crank's Road, Forest">
    <description>The carter's track winds northward, keeping a respectful distance from the city walls of Leth Deriel.  Overhead, and barely visible among the leaves, a catwalk is slung among the branches.  The arboreal bridge sways occasionally, perhaps from the wind or the weight of a high-road passerby.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Gallows Tree, Town Warden's Office" note="Guard House|Jail">
    <description>This room is chiseled out of the base of the old Gallows Tree, where hangings and drawing and quartering used to be regular features in the more tyrannical days of the Elven empires.  The Warden's Office nowadays shows that more peaceable tis a straight-backed rush chair before a long table.  Atop the Warden's desk sit a pot of hot herb tea and a tray of Mithin's donuts. </description>
    <description>This room is chiseled out of the base of the old Gallows Tree, where hangings and drawing and quartering used to be regular features in the more tyrannical days of the Elven empires.  The Warden's Office nowadays shows that more peaceable tis a straight-backed rush chair before a long table.  Atop the Warden's desk sit a pot of hot herb tea and a tray of Mithin's donuts.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-170" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Gallows Tree, Dungeon">
    <description>Though now in disuse, in more turbulent times criminals and prisoners of war were brought here to confess to crimes, treason and heretical views, whether they were guilty or not.  Notorious Elven inquisitors made use of such painful procedures as stretching limbs on the rack, burning flesh with live coals, squeezing fingers and toes or for those particularly stubborn cases the strappado, a vertical rack.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Eik Wood, Granite Outcroppings" note="Map59_Boggy_Wood.xml|Boggy Wood|Moss Meys">
    <description>Granite outcroppings scattered among the trees and brush sit like the abandoned toys of giants.  The trail leads deeper into the forest and back up over a larger sloping granite monolith partially buried in the soil.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb monolith" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Kilth Aldiyaus, Atrium">
    <description>You are within the main temple of Leth Deriel, devoted to all the gods and goddesses of Elanthia, for each to worship in his or her own way.  This atrium is in the heart of an old banyan tree that constantly sends out new shoots.  It is hollow all the way to the top, allowing the air and light to filter down through green leaves, more radiant than any stained-glass cathedral window could ever be.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Kilth Aldiyaus, Meditation Branch" note="Meditation Branch">
    <description>Low benches, slanted to be knelt upon, are arranged in rows along the floor of the room.  Devotees and layfolk of all races and professions sit side by side, silently immersed in meditative exercises.  Along the walls are mats, and racks bearing wooden staves and swords, as well as ceremonial longbows.</description>
    <position x="150" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Kilth Aldiyaus, Prayer Branch" note="Shrine1-14|Kilth Aldiyaus|Temple|Prayer Branch" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Vaulted beams are carved into the grain of the wooden walls. Echoes of mumbled prayers and heartfelt supplications are amplified by the room's curvature.  In the reverberating din, the names of all the deities mingle, then merge as one.  A polished Sana'ati wood altar is surrounded by hooded figures kneeling on the bare floor.</description>
    <position x="170" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Arthianna's Clinic, Healing Tent" note="Arthianna's Clinic|Healer" color="#00BF80">
    <description>Arthianna, the famed Elven empath, appears young but carries herself around the treatment tent with a grace and self-assurance that could only come from many years of experience, wisdom and practice in the healing arts.  Under the barkcloth canopy, she methodically and compassionately moves from cot to cot, tending to the most seriously injured first, revitalizing patients with her touch.</description>
    <position x="90" y="-90" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Eshar's Trading Post, Backroom">
    <description>There is very little room to move about in the backroom, except for a narrow aisle cleared from the door to a long counter in the rear.  The rest of the floor is strewn with boxes, crates and cartons piled and stacked to make use of all available space.  Locked cabinets and shelves cover every inch of wall space.  At the counter stands Eshar's appraiser busily examining numerous items heaped in front of him.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Eshar's Trading Post, Main Room" note="Eshar's Trading Post|Trader Outpost|trade minister|shipment clerk" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Eshar the pawnbroker casts you a surly glance as you enter the dusty, disheveled trading post.  His attitude strikes you as odd, especially for someone dealing with those who come here to part regretfully with their valuables.  It is even more puzzling because he is also a contact for many of the traders doing business in Leth Deriel.  But recalling some of the traders you have met, perhaps his attitude is understandable.  He is the younger brother of Ershem the papermaker.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Eshar's Trading Post, The Pit" note="Pit|Commodities Board">
    <description>A small, rounded room at the back of the trading post serves as its brokerage area.  Now and again, a clerk or two consult with the pricing board located near the entrance, making updates or verifying the information they find.  The clerk in charge of commodities nods at you in greeting as you enter, but otherwise seems disinterested in your company.</description>
    <position x="150" y="-70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Bosque Deriel, Sloping Path">
    <description>This narrow dirt path appears to be in a constant twilight regardless of the actual time, forever shadowed by the dense forest to the west and Ankis Dir to the east.  To the north lies Durmast Gate, adding both darkness and light on the way into Leth Deriel, while to the southwest, the trail skirts the foothills and descends around the edge of the forest.</description>
    <position x="280" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grass-covered hill" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Bosque Deriel, Forest Edge">
    <description>This path follows the forest down a tall grassy hill crowned by stone menhirs.  A tiny stream trickles across the lower end of the trail, breaching the dense forest to the south and creating a possible route inwards.  Ever vigilant, an Elven scout stands guard near the stream.</description>
    <position x="260" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny stream" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Bosque Deriel, Dense Woods">
    <description>A muddy streambed provides the only standing room inside this dense forest, crowded with spindly trees, brush and massive roots that push under, past, and in places even above the plant life which seems to inhabit every available inch.  Fortunately, the path seems to open up towards the north.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark hole" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go muddy streambed" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Bosque Deriel, Tunnel Below the Roots">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Massive silvery roots weave in and out, forming the walls of this cavern-like area under the foot of a huge tree.  Slightly above and to the west, there is a fissure in the wall of the root cave.</description>
    <position x="160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole;stand" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go root fissure;stand" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove of the White Laurel" color="#008000">
    <description>The dense forest has been pushed back here by the massive roots of a huge camphor laurel with a canopy that reaches almost forty yards high.  Although not nearly as wide as the great Sana'ati Dyaus, the tree could very likely be just as old.  Long branches stretch out in every direction over the root-ridden ground.  One limb is low enough that it may be possible to climb it.  It is far from serene here, for loud croaking sounds seem to be coming from all directions, including from above.</description>
    <position x="160" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go root fissure" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb low limb" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove of the White Laurel" color="#008000">
    <description>A low thick branch stretches its dense canopy of leaves across the area, attempting to push back the advance of the wild forest surrounding the tree.</description>
    <position x="200" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb thick branch" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove of the White Laurel" color="#008000">
    <description>A gnarled and twisted limb swoops down towards the ground as if reaching for the tiny spring that bubbles up from the brush to the west and trickles south.  The branch has such deep lines that it almost looks as if it were made of small vines braided together over time.</description>
    <position x="120" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb gnarled limb" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove of the White Laurel" color="#008000">
    <description>Vines wind up the southeast side of the tree, covering the bark in tiny white blossoms with very little fragrance.  The flowers cover a high bough and drape down as if hanging from a trellis in a well-tended garden.</description>
    <position x="200" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb vines" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove of the White Laurel" color="#008000">
    <description>The branches of the laurel are very high on the south side, but even here, ominous croaking threatens from above.  Invasive vines and brush creep up from the dense forest around the tree, attempting to take the area the great laurel has long guarded.  Only the presence of thick roots breaking the surface of the ground keeps the brush at bay enough for a traversable path to exist.</description>
    <position x="160" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Bosque Deriel, Grove of the White Laurel" color="#008000">
    <description>A V-shape in the branches has allowed daylight to reach the ground here, feeding a crop of bushes crowded around a tiny stream.  Large red trumpet flowers blanket the sunny side of the intermingled bushes, filling the air with their sweet scent.  The branches of the camphor laurel are out of reach, although it is plain to see an easier ascent to the north.</description>
    <description>Long dark stalks invade a patch of ground under the tree.  The bulbous flowers have pulled in their petals, reminding one of tiny gem pouches drawn closed for protection from the shadows of the night.</description>
    <position x="120" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="In the White Laurel, A Sturdy Limb">
    <description>The laurel's thick canopy provides a lush home for treehopper toads.  Despite the constant croaking noise coming from all directions, this area seems subdued compared to the ground below.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low limb" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb gnarled limb" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb higher branch" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="In the White Laurel, A Gnarled Limb">
    <description>Deep hills and valleys permeate the wood, making it easy to imagine shapes within the textured bark.  A pair of knots in the main trunk looks out at the scenery like unblinking eyes.  The gnarled limb slopes downward to the northwest, making it easy to get down from here.</description>
    <position x="140" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy bough" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb twisted branch" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb gnarled limb" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="In the White Laurel, A Thick Branch">
    <description>This long branch stretches east, pushing back the brush and trees and demanding its full share of sunlight.  It is fairly low to the ground, making it easy to jump down from here.</description>
    <position x="180" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sturdy limb" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb knotted bough" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb branch" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="In the White Laurel, A Twisted Branch">
    <description>Jutting out of the main trunk at a curious angle, this twisted branch seems to right itself as it ascends out of the mesh of other limbs and boughs until it pushes out southwest over thick brush.  Daylight streams down on a small patch of ground, unhindered because of the curious change in direction.  The drop from here would be precarious at best, but with a little work one might still be able to get down by scaling the trunk of the laurel.</description>
    <position x="140" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb gnarled limb" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb thin bough" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb white laurel" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="In the White Laurel, A Thin Bough">
    <description>This precarious perch offers a good view of the top of the White Laurel and the impressive forest which it inhabits.  To the north is Leth Deriel, and the great Sana'ati reminds one of a great umbrella stretching out over the crowns of the other trees.</description>
    <position x="160" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb twisted branch" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb knotted bough" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="In the White Laurel, A Knotted Bough">
    <description>Vines filled with tiny flowers drape across the tertiary branches of the knotted bough, forming a cradle of snowy white petals that drape down towards the ground below.</description>
    <position x="180" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb thick branch" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb thin bough" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb vines" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Caravan Stables" note="Caravan Stables" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Once an outbuilding for storing casks of wine, yaks and mules now quietly nuzzle hay ricks seeking their dinner.  Slim Elven youths work amongst the stalls, raking out old bedding and laying down fresh straw, preparing for the next caravan seeking shelter for the night.  Perched upon a sack of grain, a grizzled stable master trades jokes with passing traders as he efficiently repairs a worn out leather bridle.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Horse Barn, Inside" note="Stable" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Delightfully fragrant to a horse, the barn's humid air is redolent with the aroma of manure mingled with sweat.  Several wooden stalls heaped with fresh, dry straw line this oblong room.  Each stall has a feedbag hanging from the back wall, and a stone trough filled with water.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Gulthorn's Hearth Room" note="Rest of Ages Inn" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The dining room is one large open hearth.  A curved fireback along the far wall leads to a hollow chimney branch.  Tall, iron firedogs cradle logs that burn over a bed of embers, in which stand mullers of beer and spiced wine.  Gridirons hold sizzling hunks of game while rich stews and savory soups bubble in great, blackened cauldrons.  Despite the smoke and heat, the food and the atmosphere here are irresistible, as are the charms of the reserved yet solicitous proprietor, Gulthorn.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Hall Trunk" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The trunk is wide here, showing the intersection of many large limbs.  From below you hear the sounds and smell the aromas of good company and good food.  Above, you hear only the sighing of leaf laden branches in the wind.  Closing off the north branch is a sand colored door, to the south is a marble colored door, and to the west is a grass colored door.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sand-colored door" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble-colored door" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grass-colored door" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go penthouse door" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Desert Suite" note="Desert Suite">
    <description>In the center of this large circular chamber stands an open-sided tent of fine white gauze.  Luxurious, hand woven Neldian rugs are spread beneath it, with bolster pillows scattered about.  On a round brass tray beside the tent rest plates of sweetmeats and decanters of rose water.  A door painted to resemble fine grained sand leads out.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sand-colored door" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Mountain Suite" note="Mountain Suite">
    <description>The tinkling laughter of a mountain stream rushing over rocks to become a waterfall fills the room.  This indoor fountain of cleverly painted wood resembles famous Lumerian marble, with cool water cascading down to a pool below.  A soft down mattress rests upon a niche in the faux marble, surrounded by heaping baskets full of berries and nuts, and flasks of wild grape wine.  A door painted to resemble crystal specked marble leads out.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble-colored door" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Savannah Suite" note="Savannah Suite">
    <description>The walls of this chamber are covered in cool green grasscloth.  A magnificent ebonwood carving of a gazelle serves as a frame for a canopied featherbed.  Beside it, a table in the shape of an hourglass skin drum holds hollow gourds and wooden trays filled with exotic liqueurs and fruits.  A door painted to resemble flowing tall grass leads out.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grass-colored door" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Treetop Penthouse" note="Penthouse">
    <description>You look out over all of Leth Deriel from this lofty perch.  Somehow, you are outside, in the very highest branch of the Rest of Ages Inn, but still, oddly, no outside winds penetrate nor sounds of the forest disturb you.  The light takes on a subtle shimmer, as though mediated by some sheltering barrier.  In a mighty fork is a great wicker bed, a nest-like affair, but there is little else here that matches your idea of luxury.</description>
    <position x="70" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go penthouse door" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Rest of Ages Inn, Taproot Tavern" note="Taproot Tavern" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Hollowed out of massive roots, this tavern is homey yet somehow elegant.  Intimate tables of rich woods in the shape of large slices of tree trunks are surrounded by plush banquettes.  The semi-circular bar is hewn from the tree itself, carefully sculpted into a single piece and covered with glorious depictions of forest life in the golden Elven age.  It is low to the ground, and patrons sit on velvet pillows around it conversing with Ulipher, the silver-haired tapster.</description>
    <position x="90" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Izma Ru'ef University, Grand Hall">
    <description>Inside the hollow trunk of a huge sequoia, nearly as old as Sana'ati Dyaus, is the Grand Hall of Izma Ru'ef University.  Along the curved, arching walls are carved bas reliefs in the native wood, scenes of the glory of the Elven Empires of Elanthia.  Busts sculpted of precious hardwoods stand on pedestals in a semi-circle along the hall, likenesses of eminent lorethews, Elven and non-Elven, who have taught at the University.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Izma Ru'ef University, Lecture Hall">
    <description>Above the arched roof of the entry is a vast, domed lecture hall.  The wood is carved in step-like terraces, to seat large crowds of knowledge-thirsty students.  The dome and walls are shaped in such a way as to naturally amplify the sound from the speaker's platform.  This hall is also the site of concerts, bardic recitals, dramas and pageants that make up the cycles of life in Leth Deriel.</description>
    <position x="170" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Izma Ru'ef University, Library Branch" note="Izma Ru'ef University|University|Library" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The curved walls of the old redwood are carved with deep, high shelves crammed with books, scrolls, all irreplaceable and priceless.  One fortunate characteristic of the aromatic wood is that it serves as a natural repellent to bugs, mildew and all the other enemies of paper and parchment.  Rough hewn benches and tables topped with flickering oil lamps are occupied by students and professors absorbed in the wonders of the words before their eyes.</description>
    <position x="170" y="-230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Izma Ru'ef University, Study Branch" note="Telescope">
    <description>A circular skylight carved into the wooden wall here affords a clear view of the sky above the forest stronghold of Leth Deriel.  A small brass telescope on a raised platform points towards the opening.  Devices of brass and iron, mechanical models of some sort, sit on some worktables.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-230" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Izma Ru'ef University, Dormitory Branch" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Small wooden doors line the walls, evenly spaced around the circumference of the trunk.  These are the student quarters and here live mostly non-Elven exchange students of outstanding ability who have passed the rigorous entrance examinations and interviews required to gain admission into Izma Ru'ef.  All Elves, by birthright, are automatically entitled to attend University classes.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Kazimel's Woodland Spirits, Tasting Room" note="Kazimel's Woodland Spirits|Vintner" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Kazimel the Vintner is red-cheeked and looks like he samples his stock more often than mere quality control would dictate.  But he is always willing to offer a wee dram to his customers as free samples.  Most likely, he enjoys the drinking company.  Inside a modest wattle structure are baskets of flavoring agents, herbs like strongly-scented feverfew and vanilla-like dried woodruff, used in making seasonal wines that the Elven palette favors so.</description>
    <position x="150" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Kazimel's Woodland Spirits, Wine Cellar">
    <description>Amid the oak aging barrels is a formidable contraption, the winepress, with its slatted wooden vats and corkscrew device covers.  Traditional Elven wine takes up to two years to mellow in these oak casks.  Kazimel's assistants circulate among the containers, racking the wine by drawing off its lees and rotating the stock.  Flasks of matured wines sit in racks for additional aging.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Sinjian's Bardic Requisites, Workshop" note="Sinysa|Instrument Repair" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Book-lined shelves and cabinets stand to either side of a large, arched window.  Dappled sunlight showers in through its many panes to wash over the cluttered surfaces of polished hardwood sewing tables scattered throughout the room, glinting off of pins and needles scattered amongst the cloth.  Finished suits and gowns presented upon mannequins sit at the end of each table, each garment a product of a student's hard work awaiting an admiring Bard.</description>
    <description>Silver moonlight spilling in from a large bay window to the north casts deep shadows in the lee of the shelves and cabinets to either side.  Only the illumination of a single glass lantern sitting on a long table lightens the enveloping darkness.  Sitting there in the pool of golden radiance are several piles of unsewn cloth, awaiting a tailor's touch in the morning.</description>
    <position x="140" y="70" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut arch" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Curious Wooden Shed, Abandoned Room" note="Shed">
    <description>This shed is deserted, a few oddly shaped glass flasks, vials, and beakers lying shattered on the dirt floor.  It appears that the occupant left in a hurry.</description>
    <position x="50" y="110" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Gymnasium, Entrance">
    <description>A statue of Everild stands in the center of the room, with its arms raised to the sky like wings ready for flight.  From behind it rolls loud chiming punctuated by staccato drumming.  The musky scent of sweat mixed with incense hangs in the air.  An archway beyond the sculpture leads deeper into the building.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="1" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Gymnasium, Dance Pit" note="Gymnasium|Dance Pit|Nightlark">
    <description>Countless bare feet have stomped a hard-packed circle into the dark earthen floor.  The air is hazy from burning incense and damp from perspiring bodies.  Swan-emblazoned shields hang from one wall, on another rough charcoal drawings depict stick figures in various positions.  A pair of ancient Elven barbarians sit in a corner of the sultry room, one thumping a huge kettle drum, the other striking a row of metal chimes with a mallet.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="227" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Gymnasium, Poolside">
    <description>Murky water masks the depth of the swimming pool, but a diving board at one end and a Gor'Tog with water to her chin hint that it's safe to jump.  A dirty skylight centered over the pool casts a dim glow throughout the room.  Some damp towels are thrown haphazardly on the wooden benches lining the walls and a pair of moldy shower shoes lay abandoned in a corner.</description>
    <position x="-50" y="-9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go diving board" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Gymnasium, Meditation Room">
    <description>Woven straw mats are scattered around the dimly lit room for those who wish to nourish their inner self.  What little light there is filters in through chinks in the walls, illuminating floating motes of dust settling to the floor.  A cluttered pile of armor and weapons abruptly snores, proclaiming a person somewhere within.</description>
    <position x="-70" y="-9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="225" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Gymnasium, Pool" note="Pool" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Bits of -- something -- floats just below the surface of the turbid water.  The jagged walls of the pool gives the impression that this was once a small quarry and a chilly spot in the otherwise tepid water marks where an underground stream feeds into the pool.</description>
    <position x="-50" y="1" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Bosque Deriel, A Path">
    <description>A path is barely discernable over the golden-tipped mosses that cover the ground off to the east.  The golden-leafed trees thin here and intermix with small, newly-planted fruit trees.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Bosque Deriel, A Path">
    <description>The path is lined with small Halfling-high fruit trees that are covered with both fruit and flowers.  Bees lurk within most of the blossoms, quietly gathering their sweet nectar until they zip with a buzz to the next blossom.  The slightly sour smell of overly ripe fruit fills the air.</description>
    <description>The path is lined with small Halfling-high fruit trees that are covered with both fruit and flowers.  The slightly sour smell of overly ripe fruit fills the night air.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Bosque Deriel, A Path">
    <description>The path leads to a clearing and gardens off to the northeast.  The forest of trees protects the site, a wild tangle of growth just ever-so-slightly tamed.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Shrine, A Clearing" note="Shrine|Glythtide" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Low-mown sweet grass, chamomile and yarrow carpet this small clearing, centered around a stump of a once-great tree.  A nearby plank holds a smoothly polished ram's horn as well as fresh offerings of tarts and ale.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vine-covered gazebo" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Shrine, A Vine-Covered Gazebo">
    <description>A twisting vine twines about the roof and ceiling joists of this open-air shelter.  Heavy blossoms dangle from the vine, swaying gently in the perfume-scented breeze.  The wooden planks of the gazebo floor have worn smooth by footsteps, weather and years of polishing with beeswax and care.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="232" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go garden path" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Shrine, A Rose Garden" note="Rose Garden">
    <description>The garden is a tumult of tangled blooms, all sweetly scented with rare colors and petal formations.  The thorns are very long and sharp, however, protecting the precious blossoms from ravage.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gazebo" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Shrine, Herb Garden">
    <description>A cobblestone walkway surrounds a circular garden, a mass of useful plants divided down the middle with a winding pathway.  One section of the garden contains herbs used for medicinal and decorative purposes, the other side full of specimens for poison and known for their bitter properties.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Fang Cove, Fate's Fortune Lane" note="Map150_Fang_Cove.xml">
    <description>A towering marble archway opens a gap in the wall to the north and separates the ongoing construction and somewhat more refined completed structures of Fate's Fortune Lane from the crude structures and makeshift walkway along the beach.  The entrance to a squat, wide bungalow sits in opposition to the arch, and the sheltering cliffs of Fang's Peak rise up from behind it.  To either side of the arch, cobblestones of different shapes and sizes have been laid out to form the wide Fate's Fortune Lane.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit portal" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Entryway">
    <description>The scent of ash and soot floats in the air, drifting from the large, rounded structure to the south.  Flowered terraces rise on either side of the building's entrance, built in an attempt to cover the air's odor, but the acrid smell of fire and metal easily overpowers the sweetness of the delicate plants.  Though no glimpses of flame can be had, an occasional wave of a warm breeze manages to work its way past the dyed leather curtain that hangs across the entryway.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-63" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Tool Store" note="Forging Society|Forging Tools|Forging prestige board" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Surrounding the forge is a rock wall, meticulously arranged from a variety of colored stone in an obvious attempt to compensate for the normally sooty condition of the foundries.  Despite the overall state of the well-maintained corral, indelible stains mark its surface, left by uncaring or uncautious workers as they dragged, pushed or pulled their metal projects across the earthen ground and out into the world.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-45" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Book Store" note="Forging Books" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Radically designed for a forge, Iltesh Neg Degti resembles more a stable than a place for serious metal working.  Circular in shape, the outer building is predominantly wooden, with a low wall of unburnable stone as a foundation and wide windows to release the heat.  Nestled at its heart, however, is a squat granite structure in which all the hottest work takes place.</description>
    <position x="-5" y="-45" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Maker's Mark Ordering" note="Maker's Marks" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The low stone wall that surrounds the entire complex curves toward the south, reminiscent of the serpentine tail of some lazy dragon.  Stray grasses and weeds grow up here and there, close enough along the wall to be spared from being trodden by passing boots.  Though the roof is high enough to allow the swirling of an occasional breeze, the constant use of the forges keeps the whole area heated to an extreme.</description>
    <position x="10" y="-45" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Foundry">
    <description>Large indentations in the inner structure of the forge are each home to one or more huge iron crucibles, safely tucked away from heat-stealing drafts.  Shovels have been rammed deep into the massive piles of coal along the opposite wall, as though some worker fancied himself a warrior and the coal a foul beast in need of slaying.  Colored in similar fashion to the heaps is the bellows, making suitable imaginary wings for the savage, slain monstrosity.</description>
    <position x="25" y="-30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Foundry">
    <description>The wind swirls tauntingly a mere stone's throw away, just on the other side of the open frames of the outer wall.  Presumably, the gaps were designed to offer some relief from the broiling heat suffered by forge workers, but the necessary safe distance from the blazing fires, the blistering iron crucibles, and the fatigue-draining bellows means that there can be little release from the painful temperatures.</description>
    <position x="25" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Foundry">
    <description>As fitting for a place built by Elven hands, the ironwood timbers bear intricate inscriptions and artistic representations of workers in various stages of effort and relaxation.  Since its construction, at least a few of the users of this facility have grown uncaring, as the lower designs vanish beneath piles of coal or are obscured by black dust.  Nonetheless, the essence of craftsmanship is evident in everything from the crucible to the bellows, regardless of the forge's rugged functionality.</description>
    <position x="25" y="-10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge Yard">
    <description>Unlike the other portions of the forge, the southern-most forge yard is home to regular cool breezes and free from the worst of the heat.  Unfortunately, that same cooling wind whips the dust and debris from the grinding rooms against anyone or anything that dares to rest too long.  A fine layer of grey and black covers the wall surrounding the complex, a grim testimony that the molten metals and furnace-temperature air are not always the worst hazards in a forge.</description>
    <position x="10" y="5" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge Yard">
    <description>Judging by the marks in the dirt, many have made use of the ample space available in the forge yard to work on large projects, leaving behind only hoof prints and the deep scars of the horses' dragged burdens.  In emergency situations, this area likely has served as additional room to house troops or repair arms and armor, but for now, it sits unused.  Only the dust from the grinding rooms sweeps through the area on any regular basis.</description>
    <position x="-5" y="5" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge Yard">
    <description>Left to rust in the one section of the forge open to the sky, several scrap metal bits of incomprehensible design lean against the wooden slats of the outer wall.  Some are combinations of basic geometric shapes, while others seem to be nothing more than large hunks of slag.  Here they lie, exposed to the ravages of wind and rain, ignoring the blatant sign proclaiming that all workers should dispose of unwanted materials appropriately.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="5" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Grinding Area">
    <description>Unmistakably in a favorite location, the grindstone here has been kept routinely cleaned, revealing its white stone surface.  The reason for the preference is obvious with every breath.  Though the stifling heat that plagues the other areas of the forge is not absent here, a gentle draft manages to pull most of the aberrant dust out into the forge yard and away from panting workers slaving over the grindstone.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-5" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge Supply Shop" note="Forging Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>All along the eaves, reed wind chimes and ornamental decorations jangle and dance, bouncing gently off one another.  With every breeze, the soft clinks and jingles of the noisemakers rise in subtle crescendo, playing counterpoint with the steady pounding of hammer on steel in other sections of the forge.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-25" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="east" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge">
    <description>Resembling little more than extravagant walk-in chimneys, the smithies of Leth Deriel's renowned forge works are smartly crafted with fluted stones to direct smoke and ash upward.  Though free of smoky obstruction, the air is still hot enough to induce instant beads of sweat on exposed flesh.  Presumably, the vents near the roof that release the gaseous by-products of heated metal and burning wood are too far above to make for an equal respite from temperature.</description>
    <position x="10" y="-35" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge">
    <description>A constant sibilant sound of hissing stirs the chamber, augmented in orchestral fashion by the odd low pops of heat and the high-pitched whistle of outside breezes.  Grey streamers of smoke flutter upward from a reinforced forge, ascending like a pack of drab butterflies to freedom through the vents in the roof.</description>
    <position x="-5" y="-35" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Forge">
    <description>Arranged neatly in this cramped area is a good assortment of the tools of the trade.  A steel anvil awaits every new blow of the hammer, its horn polished by either a tidy hand or regular use.  Standing half the height of the chimney-like room, a stone forge melds flawlessly with the back wall.  Lines of soot and dust trail upward in little spirals along the wall, the only remains of the smoke and ash from the forge's previous use.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-35" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Grinding Area">
    <description>Beneath the cover of the high, sloped roof, the grindstones have been used for years, spouting layer upon layer of dust in a triangular spray against the walls and ground.  Often, a miscreant burst of wind will suck away some of residue, sending it into the forge yard as short swirls of choking filth.  Luckily, the area is not left just for the wind to clean, and the ground is scraped by the marks of shovel and broom.</description>
    <position x="10" y="-5" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Grinding Area">
    <description>The sounds of work in the other sections of the forge echo through the walls of this area, reverberating even over the noisy spinning of grindstones.  Since this space is bordered on two sides by stone walls -- one being the back of the forge area -- the ringing tones of metal on metal bounce noisily, clashing with the rasping grindstones, and creating a distorted cacophony of sound.</description>
    <position x="-5" y="-5" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Carousel Booth">
    <description>A carved ivory lever protrudes from the eastern wall of the small, brightly-tapestried room, flanking a silversteel door to the north.</description>
    <position x="133" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oaken arch" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sandalwood arch" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany arch" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Item Regstration Office">
    <description>Green and white marble tiles cover the floor in a crisscrossing pattern.   Two brass lanterns hang on the wall behind a low counter.  Stacks of papers cover the tops of a row of cabinets, waiting to be filed away.</description>
    <position x="153" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple curtain" destination="256" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Registrar's Office" note="Registrar's Office|item registration" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Elegant dark oak cabinets with polished brass hardware line the wall behind a stately maple desk.  A tall brass lantern sits in each corner of the room, providing ample light to do business.</description>
    <position x="153" y="-10" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple curtain" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curtain" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Carousel Family Services">
    <description>A series of guarded arches line the southern wall.  The complicated framework of iron and timbers spans across the ceiling.  Countless gears, pulleys and weights form the strikingly complex mechanism which drives the Carousel.</description>
    <position x="133" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Dira'ela Lloriena's Beauty Salon" note="Dira'ela Lloriena's Beauty Salon|Salon" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Ornate statuary, brilliant emerald and maroon satin curtains, and several golden-gilded floor-to-ceiling mirrors testify to Lady Lloriena's motto too much is never enough.  Half a dozen elaborately carved chairs, plush with thick, embroidered pillows stand before each of the enormous oval mirrors, ready to seat customers.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Sana'ati Dyaus, Rundmolen Post Office" note="259|Post Office|mail" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tucked up against the conic building is a low stone counter made from green and white marble.  Potted plants ring the area, their lush foliage sectioning off the area from the bustling square beyond.  Vast, countless rows of differently sized shelves are behind the counter, and complex Dwarven mechanisms can be heard as they rearrange the package-covered storage.  Clerks shuffle endlessly back and forth between the counters and shelving as they assist patrons with their packaging and mailing needs.</description>
    <position x="153" y="-30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Forest Clearing, Pathway">
    <description>The sounds of Bosque Deriel and Leth Deriel further on are muted by the suddenly dense woods.  The brush-choked pathway makes its way further east, eventually opening up into a wide clearing.  Wooden bridges link some of the trees here, likely for the town's scouting guardsmen and hunters alike.  Crates of tools and supplies are nestled amongst the creeping vines and other undergrowth of the forest.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brush-choked pathway" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Forest Clearing, Gathering Pit" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>From time to time, the sounds of a team of woodsmen can be heard as they carefully choose and fell another of the forest's elder trees.  The pruning serves dual purposes -- to supply the needs of nearby Leth Deriel as well as to renew the woods with younger, stouter growth.  The small clearing here allows travelers and workers alike a brief respite from the day's duties while the stone-encircled firepit provides food, light, and warmth during the colder months.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Forest Clearing, Old Growth" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Elder trees, some native and others clearly transported, dot the clearing at irregular intervals.  A mix of trees including spruce, pines, oaks and more are evident, as well as stumps of other, now unidentifiable ones.  An abundance of wildlife including raccoons, rabbits, birds, wolves and more are frequently seen or heard moving through without care for the woodsmen nearby.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Forest Clearing, Old Growth" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A handful of cabins, each constructed from wood found nearby, provide shelter for those of the small encampment.  The trees encircling the broader clearing draw up against the backs of these dwellings, their intertwined canopies draping protectively over the roofs.  As the breeze shifts, both smells and smoke periodically fill the air from the nearby firepit.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Forest Clearing, Old Growth" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Melodies that would make even members of the Bards' Guild jealous rise and fall in intensity, pacing, and volume as birds of all shapes, sizes and colors fill the clearing with their songs.  The cabins nearby blend into the trees along the edges of the small outpost.  Covered with creeping vines and flowering plants that weave throughout them, the foliage provides ample nesting space for the varied species bringing life to the space.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Forest Clearing, Old Growth" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Aimlessly in trios and pairs, dragonflies of shimmering opalescent rainbow colors hover and dart from one lichen-covered trunk to the next in an endless dance.  Up above, a series of simple rope and wood bridges weave amongst the nearby trees and disappear into the denser woods beyond the clearing.  From time to time, the smells of charring meat accompany the sizzling sounds of a meal being prepared via the firepit at the heart of the clearing.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Forest Clearing, Rocky Mound" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>In this small corner of the clearing, a giant mound of boulders and rocks dominates the setting.  A majestic weave of different vines has been coaxed into covering most to soften their surfaces.  The weaving doesn't appear entirely natural, even for delicate Elven hands, but rather as if enhanced by a Nature Binder's skilled magical training.  One of the flat, rocky surfaces was left exposed, and small tools and trinkets are frequently left for others in need.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="265" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Leth Deriel Crafting Society Outpost, Main Room" note="Crafting Society" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Hooks shaped like small leaves hold decorative tools more ornamental than useful, their polished handles gleaming softly.  A faint scent of cedar drifts from the smooth plank floor, grounding the room in simple craftsmanship.</description>
    <position x="80" y="30" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vine-framed doorway" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Leth Deriel Crafting Society Outpost, Enchanting Emporium" note="Enchanting Emporium" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Exposed rafters span the ceiling, supporting an assortment of hanging lanterns.  Wide boards cover the floor in even rows, their surfaces worn smooth from use.  Along one wall, sheets of worked metal display etched symbols arranged in precise, deliberate patterns.</description>
    <position x="70" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Leth Deriel Crafting Society Outpost, Engineering Enclave" note="Engineering Enclave" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Panels of brushed steel form a decorative border along the walls, their matte finish accented by precise rivetwork.  The walls are covered in detailed diagrams, and anchored with sprocket-headed brass pins.</description>
    <position x="90" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Leth Deriel Crafting Society Outpost, Outfitting Outlet" note="Outfitting Outlet" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Soft plum and ivory stripes accent the plank walls, bordered with intricate filigree trim painted in stitch-like strokes.  Delicate silhouettes of spools, needles, and looping thread are woven into the decorative motif.</description>
    <position x="90" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Leth Deriel Crafting Society Outpost, Alchemy Annex" note="Alchemy Annex" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Wood plank walls bear faint scorch marks that form curling patterns across their surface, as if left by careful experimentation.  Large wooden plaques hang in neat alignment, each carved to resemble a piece of parchment inscribed with simple geometric symbols.</description>
    <position x="70" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Iltesh Neg Degti, Bulk Materials" note="bulk Forging supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tucked into a corner of the shop is a small alcove circumscribed by stone walls.  While the thickly mortared masonry is discolored from the ever-present soot of the surrounding forges, everything is well-maintained and swept clean.</description>
    <position x="-30" y="-25" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="248" />
  </node>
  <label text="to Shard">
    <position x="-90" y="160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Illaya Taipa">
    <position x="-230" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Acenamacra">
    <position x="390" y="-385" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="and M'Riss">
    <position x="390" y="-370" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Southern Trade Route">
    <position x="-160" y="-380" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Crossing">
    <position x="-130" y="-370" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moss Meys">
    <position x="30" y="-430" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="">
    <position x="1" y="1" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ilaya Taipa">
    <position x="-180" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Southern Trade Route">
    <position x="-120" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="and Ain Ghazal">
    <position x="-230" y="40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Treehopper Toads">
    <position x="190" y="260" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cleric-only area">
    <position x="312" y="-440" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Stable">
    <position x="72" y="-270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bundles">
    <position x="-80" y="-220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bows">
    <position x="-75" y="-114" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Origami">
    <position x="10" y="-80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="University">
    <position x="140" y="-215" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Candy">
    <position x="270" y="-190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="General">
    <position x="263" y="-77" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bakery">
    <position x="205" y="-157" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Weapons">
    <position x="8" y="25" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Baskets">
    <position x="23" y="82" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Music">
    <position x="133" y="75" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dyer">
    <position x="182" y="15" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gymnasium">
    <position x="8" y="4769" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bank">
    <position x="176" y="-65" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Vault">
    <position x="118" y="-20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Clothes">
    <position x="70" y="-30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Housing">
    <position x="223" y="11" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Rest of Ages">
    <position x="30" y="-195" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wood">
    <position x="127" y="25" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Healer">
    <position x="50" y="-100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Observatory">
    <position x="252" y="111" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Grove of the White Laurel">
    <position x="98" y="284" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gym">
    <position x="-92" y="-28" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Premie">
    <position x="-67" y="-62" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Forge">
    <position x="-63" y="-51" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crafting">
    <position x="60" y="50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text=" Society">
    <position x="60" y="60" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>