<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Southern Trade Road Part 1 (Ferry to Leth Deriel)" id="60">
  <node id="1" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A more enchanting mix of foliage, exotic herbs, fragrant plants and glorious undergrowth exists perhaps nowhere else on Elanthia.  Surrounded by what can only be called a forager's paradise, you marvel at the bounty of nature.  Each individual species here has something of value to offer the body, soul, or spirit.  Taking a deep breath and casting a long, wistful gaze, you continue on.</description>
    <position x="0" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel">
    <description>While pondering the fantastic variety of flora here, you listen to the wildlife encircling you.  Familiar bird songs, insect chirpings, and the rooting of forest-floor foragers all comfort you.  And yet, there is an undercurrent, a foreign and disquieting subtext of sounds and voices that lie just outside your conscious range of hearing.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meandering path" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel">
    <description>Handcarts, porters, and caravans laden with trade goods and commodities bound for Leth Deriel pass through here heading south, while heading north are soldiers, mages, and savants of one kind or another, fighters and other less prosperous figures.  A ranger is bent over the side of the path, inspecting some curious flowering plant.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Southern Trade Route, Customs Post">
    <description>Several thin trees are propped up across the path in a kind of makeshift gate.  Half a dozen Elven archers are stationed around their commander, a tall and stern figure in the flowing green cloak of his regiment.  A large balance scale, some wooden pallets, and a tent form the inspection station where those entering and leaving the domain of Leth Deriel pay tolls and taxes, and attend to the inevitable ensuing paperwork.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>There is a clearing to the southeast, and the sounds of several languages not indigenous to the precincts of Leth Deriel can be heard from that direction.  A few carts and wagons, an overburdened camel, and a very annoyed-looking Elothean trader loiter here, as though waiting to pass southeast but unable to proceed for some reason.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Mysterious voices echo in the shadowy glades along the sides of the road here.  Filmy forms seem to glide among the towering trees, hinting at a magical and miraculous world beckoning you to stray from the safe, mundane limits of the trade route.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Southern Trade Route, Zurinda's Bale">
    <description>The air is stuffy, humid and oppressive here, as though the leaves have conspired to make a verdant canopy to contain the heat spawned by the forest's decay and regeneration.  The low humming in your ears grows louder, a chorus of katydids beating their wings in an unrelenting, blood-quickening rhythm.  You feel oddly drowsy, or perhaps you are about to swoon from the unnatural warmth.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The broad, stiff-veined leaves of the remeka trees here shut out the sky and the stirring of the forest breezes.  The remekas absorb great quantities of water through their roots and release it in the form of droplets that collect on the underside of the leaves, dripping to the forest floor like a localized rain shower.  This shower is too tepid to be refreshing, but a good source of drinking water so far from rivers or wells.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Diminutive hoof prints from some cloven-footed animal pepper the road here.  The underbrush on both sides has been trampled down repeatedly, and there is a noticeable track worn into the hard-packed roadbed at a right angle.  You hear faint grunts and rustlings to the east and west, but the low thorn bushes rule out leaving the path to investigate.  A dripping sound emanates from the southwest.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Thick trees line the route here, with rope-like roots swelling the surface and bursting through in places.  Most of them have been hacked back by the passing caravans and travelers.  At the base of one of the greater trees, the jumble of roots encloses a murky hole, leading into a hollow.  In such places are said to dwell Elven hermits and anchorites.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The track through the choking forest is difficult to follow here.  The path is extremely muddy and treacherous underfoot.  At times the snaking detours into which the main route has jumbled become impossible to discern.  A spider's web partially blocks the road, waiting to ensnare some unwary traveler.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Along the north, the trees and shrubs are fairly homogeneous, much the same as other wild growth at the same latitude and altitude anywhere in this hemisphere of Elanthia.  To the south, abruptly and preternaturally, all sorts of trees appear that ought not to be growing side by side or in each other's shade.  A profusion of evergreens, hardwoods, fruit trees, flowering trees and shrubs, spread themselves out as far south as you can see.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The ground here is hard and unyielding, packed to rock-like consistency by ceaseless caravans and the boots of stalwart adventurers.  Faint cracks trace the surface like webs from a demented spider, prompting a slight detour for an orderly column of black ants.  Southwest, an overgrown footpath leads off the main road towards a grove of sana'ati trees.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go overgrown footpath" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Endrus Forest, Secluded Glade" note="Secluded Glade">
    <description>A score of ancient sana'ati trees stand like primeval guardians around this circular clearing, stretching their weathered boughs overhead in a protective canopy of scintillating green.  Lush grass and blooming flowers surround a pool of clear water, bubbling upwards from an unknown source beneath the surface.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go overgrown footpath" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Resplendent pine trees tower over a low-lying thicket laden with oralana.  Nearby, a bushy-tailed squirrel scampers under the brush with a pine cone in its mouth, either not caring or in too much of a hurry to critique nature's contrast of lustrous yellow and dark green.</description>
    <description>Resplendent pine trees tower over a low-lying thicket laden with oralana.  The branches rustle with movement, and a small woodland creature scampers to the ground, darting into the thicket with something in its mouth.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Southern Trade Route, Hillock">
    <description>The gradual slope provides a limited view of the surrounding treetops, but not much else.  Pointed conifers and other evergreens form the skyline in all directions save the east-northeast, where black-twisted trees plague the forlorn landscape.  These must be the warped creations of a maddened mage, for such monstrosities could never grow naturally in Endrus Forest.</description>
    <description>The gradual slope provides a limited view of the surrounding treetops, but not much else.  Pointed conifers and other evergreens form the skyline in all directions save the east-northeast, where black-twisted trees consume the landscape with a darkness far deeper than mere night.  These must be the warped creations of a maddened mage, for such monstrosities could never grow naturally in Endrus Forest.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>A deobar sapling, no taller than a Human child, stretches its slender limbs outward and embraces the daytime sky as if glimpsing it for the first time.  Turning southwards, the road assumes a gentle incline that reaches its peak atop a barren hillock, which is spared the ravaging weeds that pervade the northeast passage.</description>
    <description>A deobar sapling, no taller than a Human child, stretches its slender limbs outward and embraces the nighttime sky as if glimpsing it for the first time.  Turning southwards, the road assumes a gentle incline that reaches its peak atop a barren hillock, which is spared the tangled briars and ravaging weeds that pervade the northeast passage.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Dead and dying wildflowers litter the roadside, overrun with voracious weeds that rob the soil of its precious nutrients.  The less hardy flora withers away midst the dust of bright yellow blossoms, but the earth harbors their seeds, ensuring that life shall one day come full circle.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>A wall of twisted raevelthorn thrives alongside the eastern edge of the road, providing a welcome barrier between you and the foreboding trees beyond.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Endrus Forest, Crossroads">
    <description>A stand of lofty ironwood trees chokes the winding road which narrows to barely a wagon's width.  Thick, bulbous roots snake over the earth, and gnarled branches twist overhead nearly blotting out the sky.  Odd noises and beastly grunts drift from the malevolent shadows, lending truth to the bardic myths of a haunted forest along the trade route.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go malevolent shadows" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Shadows envelop the foliage to the southeast as if hiding an ancient and shameful secret.  The deobars weep silent tears from mossy tendrils, and even a majestic sana'ati tree shies away from the heart of Endrus Forest.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The road weaves around a scorched deobar tree rooted in ash.  Its blackened limbs reach skywards, defying the very forces that seared its fate, or perhaps they seek deliverance from the remnants of life once possessed.  A skeletal branch points southwards, whether in welcome or warning you do not know, but the murky woods in that direction strongly suggest the latter.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Closely-knit vegetation shuts out most of the natural light.  Between two gloomy trees arise overlapping shadows that seem to form human-like figures.  Only a few paces off the road, the blackness is impenetrable, and home to all the dark horrors the mind can conjure.  But, you repeat to yourself, mere shades cannot harm you.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The road passes through a defile of vedda trees here, their white inner pith exposed, stripped of all bark.  In times of famine or scarcity, the nomads of this forest have been known to eat the bark in order to survive.  Unfortunately, in addition to meager nutrition, it contains a powerful hallucinogen which tends to drive tribesmen into a frenzy directed primarily at interlopers into their forest domain.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The oldest tree along the route here is a curious specimen.  A very young rowan tree is growing in a fork of its hoary branches.  Such small trees are deposited as seeds by passing birds, and are called flying trees.  Their leaves, bark and wood are said to possess magical protective qualities.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Fallen logs line both sides of the route here, snapped or hacked into pieces.  Some huge trunks are only charred husks, hollow inside.  Jagged tree stumps, the source of the fallen logs, are scattered to the east and west.  The underbrush has grown up quickly and closed in around them, so you cannot see into the forest beyond.  A single, bird-like whistle pierces the air.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The forest is very dense here, restricting the flow of traffic to the center of the road as the foliage closes in.  In this tunnel of the twisting wood, prodigious oaks extend their groping boughs and shine dimly with a phosphorescence of strange fungi.  Empty sacks, stray scraps of leather, and bits of grain are trampled down into the mud, indicating some mishap occurred here.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go serpentine path" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Traffic is forced to come and go in turns as the road narrows.  The stench of habitation, almost sacrilege in this hallowed greenwood, assaults you from the northwest.  The congestion and contagion of civilization grows more pronounced as you squeeze past greedy merchants, bloodthirsty mercenaries, power-obsessed mages and ragtag wanderers who ply this route.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Southern Trade Route, Trenilar's Slavers' Haven">
    <description>This route was once a notorious artery for slave trade in Elanthia, bringing captives, conscripts and labor to and from the imperial Elven kingdoms.  The filthy wayside eatery here was a rest stop for slave caravans, and has been run by ten generations of S'Kra proprietors.  String cots under the trees provide minimal sleeping accommodations and split tree trunks form the outdoor dining room.  Trenches dug along the opposite side of the road offer primitive sanitary facilities.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>Overhead in the foliage, you spot what appear to be gigantic birds' nests in the forks of the trees.  Twigs, leafy limbs, dried sedges and grasses, are all piled up into massive arboreal beds.  Some primal inhabitants of the deep forest, nomadic hunters and gatherers, must have slept here in the trees for safety.  Recalling tales of their poison-tipped arrows, you hope they have long since moved on.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest" note="RTZ31|RT-LF-IT" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The road continues to the southwest and northeast, wide enough here to allow pack animals, carts, and small bands of travelers to pass in both directions at once.  A view southwest reveals a narrowing of the way, while to the northeast, you see a small clearing and hear strange sounds and cries.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Southern Trade Route, Soothsayer's Hut" note="Soothsayer's Hut">
    <description>In the midst of the dense wood, off to the southwest, stands a grey hut supported by the bones of four great birds' feet.  Here dwells the mad S'Kra soothsayer, Berdachun.  The corners of the hut are carved in the shapes of a lion, a dragon, a cockatrice, and a viper.  In front of the hut is a carved oaken basin filled with carcasses of birds and small mammals in various states of decay and disembowelment.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey hut" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Southern Trade Route, Tripp's Cairn">
    <description>A knot of travelers, pilgrims, traders and adventurers clusters around a pile of stones beneath an old oak on the east side of the path.  The trunk of the oak has been riven in twain, perhaps by an ancient lightning strike.  The stone cairn is surrounded by offerings of rare herbs, flowers, and clay cups filled with home-brewed ale and sap wine.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The growth here is deciduous forest, with branches mingling high overhead.  A leafy canopy traps the natural moisture given off by the soil and foliage, encouraging mosses, ferns, lichen and fungi to flourish.  Deep ruts in the damp roadbed, caused by carts, hooves and boots, show that heavily-laden traffic passes through regularly.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go faint path" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest">
    <description>The grassy, weed-choked flood plain of the Segoltha River to the north transitions into the forest of Endrus.  The fringe of the woods here, growing ever denser as you gaze southward, consists mainly of oak and beech, interlaced with whitethorn, tangled briars and low-growing shrubs.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go boulder" hidden="True" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Southern Trade Route, Segoltha Plain" note="RTZ20|RT-LF-LNW" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The shouts of traders, caravan drivers, soldiers of fortune, scoundrels, thieves, bards, and less unsavory travelers echo across the flood plain along the road here as it narrows.  Everyone must jostle each other to pass.  Occasionally, a full-blown caravan or war party thunders by, which causes all the foot traffic to leap to the side of the road and turns the shouting to swearing.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Southern Trade Route, Segoltha Plain">
    <description>Sparse grass, weeds and a few hardy shrubs grow along this flat stretch of land that lies between the river bluffs and the nearby woodland.  The angry floods sweep away most of the vegetation, and each time the waters subside, life must begin here anew.  To the northeast lie the outskirts of Chelsea Overlook, a small community overlooking the south bank of the Segoltha.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-680" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go footpath" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Endrus Forest">
    <description>The soft turf is blanketed by multiple layers of leaves deposited by the trees each year in observance of the great cycle of seasons.  A single beam of sunlight dances through the thick canopy overhead before warming the thin underbrush with its gentle caress.  Ahead of you, a large clearing is consumed by the mammoth trunk of a massive grandfather tree.</description>
    <description>The soft turf is blanketed by multiple layers of leaves deposited by the trees each year in observance of the great cycle of seasons.  A single beam of starlight dances through the thick canopy overhead before tickling the thin underbrush with its cool, silvery glow.  Ahead, a large clearing is consumed by the mammoth trunk of a massive grandfather tree.</description>
    <description>The soft turf is blanketed by multiple layers of leaves deposited by the trees each year in observance of the great cycle of seasons.  A single beam of daylight dances through the thick canopy overhead before warming the thin underbrush with its gentle caress.  Ahead, a large clearing is consumed by the mammoth trunk of a massive grandfather tree.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large clearing" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go road" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Endrus Forest, Clearing" note="RTZ21|RT-LF-GPN" color="#C2B280">
    <description>A thick, tangled wall of trees, underbrush and twining vines stands a respectful distance from the thick trunk of an ancient, and most peculiar, tree.  Below your feet the moss-laden ground is even and free of debris and weeds.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go living archway" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go break" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="An Ancient Tree" note="Shrine1-13|Hodierna|Ancient Tree|Book of Hodierna" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Brilliant beams of multicolored light stream through irregular stained-glass windows, illuminating the intricate carvings which adorn the walls and dome of this cylindrical living chapel.  A single, ornately engraved column grows from the center of the room and rises to meet the delicate arched ceiling.  The subtle scent of rich wood and fertile soil heightens your perception of your place in the warm embrace of life.</description>
    <description>Silvery beams of moonlight stream through irregular stained-glass windows, illuminating the intricate carvings which adorn the walls and dome of this cylindrical living chapel.  A single, ornately engraved column grows from the center of the room and rises to meet the delicate arched ceiling.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-640" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="rt climb circular staircase" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="An Ancient Tree, Hodierna's Solace" note="Hodierna's Solace">
    <description>More a platform than a room, the leafy crown of the tree spreads overhead, creating a natural canopy of green that insulates the chamber from the wind and elements.  All around you are tiny niches in the side of the tree that look as if they were sculpted out of the living wood.  Candles, flowers, and tiny trinkets fill them, token memories for those who will not be forgotten.  A circular staircase -- also sculpted out of the tree -- leads back down, winding so far that you cannot see the bottom.</description>
    <description>More a platform than a room, the chamber is lit softly by the glow of hundreds of candles that have been carefully set into niches along the walls.  The leaves of the tree's crown block out the night sky, creating a naturally woven canopy that protects the tiny room from the wind and elements.  A circular staircase that appears to be sculpted out of the sides of the tree leads back down, winding so far that you cannot see the bottom.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-660" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="rt climb circular staircase" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Southern Trade Route, Segoltha South Bank" note="Ferry" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>The southern bank of the Segoltha River presents a wide, flat flood plain far to the east and west.  The alluvial soil here is deep brown and fertile, nourished by the unpredictable rains that cause the river to rise rapidly and without warning.  Off in the distance to the south, you can spy the crests of trees.  This marks the boundary of the Endrus Forest, which surrounds the fabled Elven stronghold of Leth Deriel.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ferry" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ferry" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Chelsea Overlook, Hearthstone Lane" note="Hearthstone Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Pale stone cobbles line a narrow lane that meanders through a small community set along the bluffs that rise from the banks of the Segoltha.  Flowering hedges follow a stone wall that surrounds the cluster of buildings.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Chelsea Overlook, Hearthstone Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Wrought iron balconies peer out over the cobbled streets, like larger copies of the filigree baskets that hang from them.  Colorful blossoms and long tendrils of cicely vine cascade down like a gently rustling waterfall to the slate walkways lining the street.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Chelsea Overlook, Driftwood Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A low stone wall follows the edge of the steep drop behind the modest homes overlooking the wide river.  Blue-blossomed sjarta bushes form a neat hedge along the cobbled road, releasing their sweet fragrance with each breath of wind blowing inland from the water.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Chelsea Overlook" note="Chelsea Overlook" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The cobbled lanes converge and open into a large plaza that juts out over the dark silt banks of the azure river.  Filigree iron benches welcome those passing the overlook to take in the magnificent vista.  In the center of the plaza, a tall marble statue rises on a pedestal from an ivy-draped fountain.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plank steps" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Chelsea Overlook, Driftwood Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Patches of bright green moss creep over the low stone wall running along the edge of the bluffs that fall down to the Segoltha's dark silt banks.  The rush of the river sings softly below the sounds of horses clopping through the streets and life milling among the thatched cottages and half-timbered buildings.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Chelsea Overlook, Lane's End" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The stony bluffs fall off just behind a scattering of homes looking out over the river.  To the side of the path, the pitted contours of a rusted ship anchor rise from the golden waves of grass that bend in supplication to the wide sky.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-760" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Chelsea Overlook, Lane's End" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The lodestone cobbles fade into a dirt road at the edge of the community.  Stone cottages rise like small islands from a shallow sea of grass speckled with wildflowers.  From beyond the bluffs, the sound of the river wells up and fills the air.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Chelsea Overlook, Hearthstone Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Half-barrels planted with catmint and pansies mark each corner of the small neighborhood.  An occasional cart rumbles through the cobbled streets, sounding like thunder over the nearby water.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-740" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Chelsea Overlook, Stony Bluff" note="Stony Bluff" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A wide dirt pathway leads to the level places on the steep bluffs and winds among small wood plank homes that perch on the stony cliff-side like river birds.  Weathered rocks jut from the dark soil like teeth, fighting for footholds with clumps of tall grass.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plank steps" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Chelsea Overlook, Stony Bluff" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The dirt path ends as the level ground gives way to a steeper, stonier ground to the west.  Large wind-worn rocks rest where they slid down the bluffs to the silt beach of the river's shore.  Gulls cry out overhead, punctuating the steady rush of the water.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wind-worn rocks" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Chelsea Overlook, Stony Bluff" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Swift breezes whip across the bluffs, rippling the tall grasses and spinning the weather vanes adorning the quaint homes set among the rocks.  A painted milk can planted with violets stands at the edge of the path, a bright splash of purple amid the cold grey stones.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-780" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Chelsea Overlook, Blacksilt Beach" note="Blacksilt Beach" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The swift waters of the Segoltha rush past small houses that rise on stilts from the powdery black silt of the riverbank.  The air carries the briny smell of the river and a fine mist that makes everything glisten with moisture.  Pale white and pink shells stand out against the dark soil.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wind-worn rocks" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Chelsea Overlook, Blacksilt Beach" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The breeze blows the dark silt across plank walkways weaving among the shorefront homes and plays the wind chimes hanging from pylons in the water that keep boats from the stony shallows.  Insects chirp and hum from the clumps of cattails and reeds growing along the river.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Chelsea Overlook, Blacksilt Beach" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The swift waters of the Segoltha rush past small houses that rise on stilts from the powdery black silt of the riverbank.  The air carries the briny smell of the river and a fine mist that makes everything glisten with moisture.  Pale white and pink shells stand out against the dark soil.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-800" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Southern Trade Route, Bosque Deriel" note="Map61_Leth_Deriel.xml|Leth Deriel">
    <description>Sounds unlike any you know whirl about you in a choir of whisperings, rustlings, murmurings, and guttural hisses.  Strange calls, unlike those of any bird, reverberate in the treetops.  You feel as though this is all for your benefit or rather to your detriment, as though someone or something were watching all the traffic along this route, and signaling your approach.</description>
    <position x="40" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Forest of Night, Path" note="Forest of Night" color="#008000">
    <description>Trees tower about you, their trunks and foliage creating a living wall of black-veined greenery.  A brown dirt path winds its way cautiously through the woods, as if afraid of intruding upon the stillness of the forest.</description>
    <description>Black trees stand silent guard over the path as it winds its way through the forest.  From an unseen perch, a night owl cries out, its shrieks of "Kie!  Kie!  Kie!" echoing through the still wood.</description>
    <description>The trunks and foliage of towering trees create a living wall of black-veined greenery.  A brown dirt path winds its way cautiously through the woods as if afraid of intruding upon the stillness of the forest.</description>
    <description>Black trees stand silent guard over the path as it winds its way through the forest.  From an unseen perch, a night owl cries out, its shrieks of Kie!  Kie!  Kie! echoing through the still wood.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark opening" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go weed-choked trail" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The ironwood trees whisper to themselves in a language forgotten long ago, their glossy leaves glistening like fresh blood as they shiver in a gentle breeze.  A thick pall of uneasiness no mortal wind can disperse hangs in the air.  A thin, nearly invisible deer trail leaps away from the main road and vanishes into a thick stand of trees.</description>
    <description>The ironwood trees shiver in a ghostly breeze you do not feel, giving them the illusion of free-willed movement.  The dark, glossy leaves shimmer like black steel, and a sickly white fog floats inches off the ground, its tendrils reaching out and wrapping the base of the trees.  A thin, nearly invisible deer trail leaps away from the main road and vanishes into a thick stand of trees.</description>
    <description>The ironwood trees shiver in a ghostly breeze, giving them the illusion of free-willed movement.  The dark, glossy leaves shimmer like black steel and a sickly white fog floats inches off the ground, its tendrils reaching out and wrapping the base of the trees.  A thin, nearly invisible deer trail leaps away from the main road and vanishes into a thick stand of trees.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow trail" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>Gnarled oak and twisted pines grow in abundance here, but neither outnumber nor out-tower the black ironwood that gave this forest its name.  Dark jade grass carpets the forest floor, growing fat on the rich loam created by fallen leaves and needles.</description>
    <description>Gnarled oak and twisted pines grow in abundance here, but not one out-towers or outnumbers the black ironwood that gave this forest its name.  Dark jade grass carpets the forest floor, growing fat on the rich loam created by fallen leaves and needles.</description>
    <description>The oaks and pines of the forest seem to fall under the shadow of the black ironwood that earned the forest its name.  Twisted beyond belief, the knotted trunks and boughs of the trees look agonized in their deformed states.</description>
    <description>Gnarled oak and twisted pines grow in abundance here, but neither outnumber nor out-tower the black ironwood that gave this forest its name.  Dark jade grass carpets the forest floor, growing fat on the rich loam created by fallen leaves and needles.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>Somewhere in the distance, you hear the rushing sound of a river pounding over the sinister whispering of the trees.  Overhead, the branches lift and stretch, blocking all sight of the sky save for a few patches where the leaves fail to weave themselves together.</description>
    <description>Light fails almost utterly here, and the dark foliage about you only serves to foster old, primal fears of the dark.  Over the soft roar of a nearby river, you hear the movement of something as it makes its way through the trees, but the light is too dim to discover the source of the sound.  </description>
    <position x="180" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The spreading boughs of the black ironwood trees cast deep shadows over the winding path.  A slope off to one side of the path descends down toward a grassy river bank, the black waters of the river barely visible from the road, but clearly audible.</description>
    <description>The spreading boughs of the black ironwood trees shield what little light is available, trapping you inside the cold, shivering night.  Eerily, the one thing that keeps you from being plunged in total darkness is a layer of white fog that covers the ground and reflects a pale light of its own, just barely illuminating a river bank that rises up off to the side.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go river bank" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>It is nearly as dark as night here, and certainly as gloomy.  The coloring of the bark on the ironwoods is so flat and depthless, it causes them at first glance to appear to be shadowy doorways into an unknown abyss.  Black-feathered birds perch on the trees, each and every one a carrion species.  Beady yellow eyes gaze down at you, watching, waiting.</description>
    <description>The trees and foliage are so black they seem to blend into each other, making it hard to distinguish separate shapes.  The only thing you can pick out is the glaring reflection of the eyes of the birds that perch in the trees, their steady, hateful gaze watching you, as if waiting expectantly for something.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The forest's silent sentinels, the black ironwood trees, rise up to either side, blocking off any attempt to advance through the wood other than by the path that it seems they have deigned to allow pass through here.  The bright, restless eyes of the nesting ravens that reside within the boughs of the trees watch you as you pass, and you feel an unnatural intelligence within their cold, yellowed gaze.</description>
    <description>The bright shine of raven eyes watch you as you pass along the sylvan path.  A cold, restless white mist covers the forest floor, and from time to time a clinging tendril reaches out and seems to almost seek you out, wrapping about feet, ankles, and legs.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The path winds unsteadily through the wood like a drunken snake with half-protruding stones for scales.  Sadly, most of these scales have long vanished, pried out as time and disuse wear down the road to a ghost of what it used to be.  Patches of deep green grass stick through the cracks in the remaining stones, the serrated edges catching at flesh and clothing.  An overgrown path, in worse state than the road you now walk, splits off from the main trail, eventually vanishing into the trees.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go overgrown path" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Forest of Night, Path" color="#008000">
    <description>Tangled trees of the famed black ironwood rise about you, their foliage twining and intertwining with each other.  Light struggles in vain to creep through the canopy, and the scent of loam is heavy and pungent.  The trail finally fades here, a living wall of gnarled trunk and leaf cutting off any further advancement through the wood.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees grow close together, as if trying to halt your progress through the woods.  To the west, the path leads up to what would appear to be a well-traveled road, or, at least, a road better traveled than this one, while to the southeast the trail continues to skirt the outer wood of the forest.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Here, at the edge of the forest, the light yet penetrates the curtain of leaves above you, throwing cool green-black shade over you.  The barely worn trail is little aid in helping you navigate your way through the thick grasses and weeds, but enough of it yet remains to keep you from becoming totally lost.  </description>
    <description>The light is almost totally gone, blocked out by the close-growing canopy.  Only the glitter of exposed earth where the trail is worn down and bits of reflective minerals shine through keeps you from becoming irrevocably lost.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The haunting cry of a bird of prey ripples through the forest, sounding from somewhere far away.  The foliage above you stirs at the passage of some tree-dwelling creature, disturbing the leaves and causing a few to shower down on your head.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Forest of Night, Silent Glade" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees quietly shuffle aside here, moving a graceful step back to allow the glade plenty of room.  Grass carpets the forest floor, and yellow and white wildflowers dot the ground in colorful abundance.  A ring of mushrooms circles a mossy hollow, releasing spore to float on a gentle forest breeze.</description>
    <description>The trees quietly shuffle aside here, moving a graceful step back to allow the glade plenty of room.  Grass carpets the forest floor, shimmering darkly in the dim light of the evening.  A ring of mushrooms circles a mossy hollow nearby, releasing spore to float on a gentle night breeze.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Forest of Night, Silent Glade" color="#008000">
    <description>Darkness hovers at the edge of your vision as you behold a cavern dripping with luminous nitre.  A faint glow of color pulses near its center, throwing tentative fingers of light into the gloom.</description>
    <description>Light reflects faintly off the remains of a column of polished white marble.  A clinging white mist swirls thickly in the center of the glade, all but obscuring the ground.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees form a living wall about you, making deviation from the path impossible.  A few of the drooping branches give the illusion that they are reaching out for you, perhaps to snag on skin or clothing.</description>
    <description>The trees form a living wall about you, making deviation from the path impossible.  In a way, this is a good thing as the forest is now so dark that you can only find your way through by feeling along the trees.  Pale white mist swirls on the ground, giving the trees an eerie glow but not lending enough light to see by.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The leaves of the tall ironwood trees brush the sky, the black metallic color of the foliage stark against the heavens.  The watchful eyes of ravens alight on you as you pass beneath their perches, and from time to time one ruffles its feathers, finding your passage so far below it intruding.</description>
    <description>The leaves of the tall ironwood trees all but melt into the inky sky.  A thick mist rises nearly two feet off the forest floor, carpeting everything in a blanket of white and emitting an odd, pale nimbus.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees of the forest stand about you, their trunks glistening black and their leaves shimmering as a forest breeze passes through them.  Oddly, rather than the normal whisper that usually accompanies leaf against leaf, the sound this foliage makes is metallic in nature.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Two of the trees bend toward each other here, creating a living doorway that opens up on more forest.  The path winds onward, tripping a thin line between the deeper, thicker clusters of the inner wood and the looser, more open growth of the outer grove.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Somewhere to the south you hear the soft roar of a river.  The only thing that muffles this sound is the occasional squawk from one of the ravens that roosts in the trees above you, or the crunch of the leaves coming from your own feet.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Forest of Night, Broken Shrine" color="#008000">
    <description>The forest pulls aside to give plenty of room to the tiny building that occupies this clearing.  Made of granite and black-veined gray marble, it seems a wonder that anything could have shattered it.  Grass and moss grows out of the cracked stones, and the darkened doorway of its entrance gapes open in slack-jawed awe.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go broken shrine" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The black leaves of the trees shimmer with a metallic sheen, and the trunks stand straight and upright, like the poles of spears.  The path seems to fork toward the southeast here, but the hope of another road is a false one, as the deviating trail eventually fades off into forest too thick to walk through.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deviating trail" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The secretive whispering of the wind that shakes the trees is unnerving and a little sinister.  Tendrils of raevelthorn reach out from the low brush, creating barely visible caltrops that all but vanish in the dark grass.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go main path" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The rustle of leaves cuts like a knife through the uneasy silence, followed swiftly by the flurry of wings as small forest birds take flight through the gloom.  The bare bones of the earth lay revealed where someone has painstakingly scraped a path through the wood, disregarding the presence of the trees and brush with the neglience of nobility.</description>
    <description>The rustle of leaves cuts like a knife through the uneasy silence, followed swiftly by the flurry of wings as ravens take flight through the shadows, melting seamlessly into the gloom.  A thick mist flows around the tree trunks, stopping with curious precaution by the side of the path that winds through the wood, as if it feared to tread there.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Dark boughs and trunks hunch miserably over the path or against each other, some so warped that they have grown together in convoluted twists that make it hard to trace with the eye where one begins and the other ends.  The ground that marks the trail has been pulled up and scraped away with surgical purity, leaving nothing but stark, packed black earth where the eldritch life of the forest once harbored its plants and took root.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowed trail" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Ironwood trees grow thickly to the left and right, cloaked in robes of powdery grey moss that drape from their boughs and branches with all the elegance of a rain-dampened cat.  Thick black-green grass grows at the base of the trees, and raevelthorn creepers -- stripped of their treacherous thorns -- create a criss-cross pattern over the bare earth that marks the path through the forest.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Thick layers of leaves and sweeping boughs choke back the light, murdering it with a wild, terrible beauty.  A dense wall of trunks block any further passage south, while to the northeast a painstakingly cleared path leads into the gloom of the forest.</description>
    <description>Thick layers of leaves and sweeping boughs compound the darkness, transmuting night to nightmare.  The path through the wood grinds southward, moving inexorably toward a wall of churning mist, where it is swallowed whole.  A grouping of trees eat up the northeast bend in the path, obfuscating what may lay beyond.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go churning mist" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The burning yellow eyes of ravens glower down at you from the crown of a particularly large ironwood.  Grass and weeds all but choke this old trail, but its worn path remains visible, if difficult to follow.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Shadows drip from the boughs of the ironwood, gathering at the roots and forming pools as dark and as cold as a mad mage's soul.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shallow ford" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Forest of Night, Shallow Ford" color="#008000">
    <description>The waters swirl about you, high enough to reach a Human's ankles and a Halfling's kneecaps.  A fine layer of black silt covers the river's bed, beneath which lies thick, gooey mud.  Delicate growths of reeds raise their heads out of the watery swirl, while up on the muddy banks to the west and east graceful willows bend in silent mourning.  A sheltered cove off to the side provides protection from the onslaught of the currents.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sheltered cove" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Forest of Night, Sheltered Cove" note="Sheltered Cove">
    <description>The murky waters of the river eddy here, making it a pleasant place to simply sit and relax.  A large piece of driftwood found its way here in some distant time, and is now covered nearly halfway with silt and mud, leaving it stuck firmly in place.  Along with a few tangled roots that jut out of the river bank, they provide relatively dry resting spots.  The long branches of willows bend toward the water, giving you the distinct impression of widows weeping for a lost love.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Forest of Night, The River Bank" color="#008000">
    <description>Hollow plops, the crash of stream on stone, and the swirl of obsidian waters compose the deafening roar of the river.  The multitude of sounds fill your ears and dull all ability to hear past it.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shallow ford" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Forest of Night, The River Bank" note="Sanrisi Tree" color="#008000">
    <description>The river bank thins to nothing here, becoming too treacherous to continue along.  The river eventually vanishes around a bend, its waters becoming more turbulent as it winds southward.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Forest of Night, The River Bank" color="#008000">
    <description>Patches of mud dot the river bank, making it even more treacherous than it already was.  A set of footprints lead away from one part of the bank and vanish into the river.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Forest of Night, The River Bank" color="#008000">
    <description>The river bank narrows to a nearly perilous path, the brambles to one side pushing you toward the drop off that leads to only one thing: swift, deadly waters.  Oddly, the river does not throw back your reflection, and, indeed, the water seems to swallow not only images, but light...what little there is.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Forest of Night, The River Bank" color="#008000">
    <description>Fine droplets of water dash up against you from time to time as the river gushes along its way.  Overhead, the trees yet rise, casting long shadows and dropping the occasional stray leaf into the rapid waters.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Forest of Night, The River Bank" color="#008000">
    <description>The black waters of the river surge forward, heedlessly crashing over stones and watery reeds.  The river bank is relatively dry, and a dirt path leads up from it, heading back to the main road.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Forest of Night, Outer Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>A barely visible path winds through the forest, dodging between the trees and leaping around bushes and low-lying shrubbery.  A narrow deer trail jumps from the path and up a steep embankment, eventually vanishing between two slender ironwood trunks.</description>
    <description>The heavy darkness of night obscures the path which winds through the forest.  Barely visible, a narrow deer trail jumps from the path and up a steep embankment.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deer trail" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Forest of Night, Outer Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees grow thick here, shouldering up against one another as if they had something to fear.  Metallic-sheened leaves glitter, reflecting light that never seems to reach you.</description>
    <description>The trees grow thick here, shoulder up against each other and blending so perfectly that it is hard to discern them from the cloak of the night sky.  A thick white mist coils at the base of the trees, its light, silvery tendrils caressing the tree trunks with a pale, watered light.</description>
    <description>The trees grow thick here, shouldering up against each other and blending so perfectly that it is hard to discern them from the cloak of the night sky.  A thick white mist coils at the base of the trees, its light, silvery tendrils caressing the tree trunks with a pale, watered light.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Forest of Night, Dying Oak" color="#008000">
    <description>A single, sickly oak grows here, enduring a pitiful existence as it is slowly suffocated by the taller, greedier ironwoods.  Their black boughs reach for the light they so crave, as if, were they to grow high enough, they could drain all the sunlight from the land and leave it as dark as the forest within which they dwell.</description>
    <description>Pitiful amongst the living foliage of night, a small, sickly oak grows beside the ironwoods, enduring a pitiful existence as it is slowly suffocated by the taller, greedier trees of the forest.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Forest of Night, Outer Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>Black steel-sheened leaves brush the sky and black roots ocasionally poke up from the forest floor.  Thick, massive trunks create a living fence that bars you from leaving the trail the ironwoods have deigned you shall take.</description>
    <description>Black steel-sheened leaves brush the sky and equally black roots occasionally poke up from the forest floor.  Thick, massive trunks create a living fence that bars deviating from the narrow trail that the ironwoods have deigned to allow.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb black roots" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Forest of Night, Outer Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>Somewhere to the south you can hear the distant trill of a songbird, echoing through the wood and cutting the squawks of the roosting ravens like a knife.  A sense of heaviness weighs you down, as if the trees wished to set the burden of air and darkness upon your shoulders.</description>
    <description>A clinging white mist on the forest floor seems to tug at your feet, and the heaviness of the night air seeks to aid the strange miasma in its task.</description>
    <description>A clinging white mist on the forest floor seems to tug at the feet, and the heaviness of the night air seeks to aid the strange miasma in its task.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb black roots" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Forest of Night, Outer Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>The delicate trill of a songbird fills the wood about you, its song at once beautiful and sad.</description>
    <description>Silent silvery-white mist wraps its coils about ankles and knees, moving up from where it wraps around the trees, like a snake waiting to strike.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Forest of Night, Outer Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees thin out to the south, but grow all the more thicker to the north.  The grass looks freshly trodden with tracks made by something other than deer or rabbit.</description>
    <description>Southward, the wood appears to thin and grows ever more thickly to the north.  The path seems a bit wider here as if this is a well-traveled stretch of grass, but between the darkness of night and the foliage cover above it is difficult to make out any clear tracks.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Forest of Night, Raevelthorn Patch" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees move aside here to allow the raevelthorn to grow.  The bushes, with their wicked thorns, seem to almost willingly seek out flesh or scale, reaching for the fluid that pumps within the veins that the flesh sheathes.</description>
    <description>The trees are sparser here as if to make more room for the abundant raevelthorn that sprawls through the area.  The bushes, with their wicked thorns, seem to intentionally seek out flesh or scale, using the cover of night to better ambush those that dare tread here and draw out the fluid that pumps through the victims' veins.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Forest of Night, Blackfruit Tree" note="Blackfruit Tree|Asketi|Shrine" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>A wide clearing of bare, black earth lies before you, in the center of which grows a tall blackfruit tree.  A small altar rests in front of the tree, and a smoking censer releases a heavy perfume into the air.  The silence here is unnatural, and the back of your neck prickles with the heavy foreboding that permeates the air.</description>
    <description>The grass of the path ends abruptly as a large swatch of circular bare dirt interrupts the path.  At the center of the clearing, a large blackfruit tree grows and before it rests a small altar.  A smoking censer releases a heavy perfume into the thick and heavy night air, attracting insects who announce their presence with dischordant buzzing and pricking bites.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Forest of Night, Raevelthorn Patch" color="#008000">
    <description>The low-lying raevelthorn outgrows the ironwood tree in this part of the forest.  Small, questing trailers covered in black thorns crawl over the path you tread, perhaps seeking out a quick snack from an unprotected foot.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Forest of Night, Outer Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>Overgrown and underused, the path winds heedlessly through the wood, one way leading to the heart of a grove of black-leaved trees, the other up a steep embankment.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Forest of Night, Inner Shrine" note="Inner Shrine|Hav'roth|Ushnish">
    <description>Light creeps through the cracks of this broken shrine and pours in through the roof.  An altar rests against the northmost wall, and the tiles that covered the floor have been mostly pulled up to let grass poke through.</description>
    <description>Here, more than anywhere else in the forest, the sky is visible.  Through the gloom you can make out an altar resting against the northmost wall, and the places where the tiles that once covered the floor have been pulled up to let grass poke through.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Hodierna's Grace" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>A few weary travelers lean against a railing at the bow of this ferry, anxiously waiting to reach the opposite bank.  An elderly S'Kra Mur stands alone at the stern, thoughtfully watching the shallow wake of the ferry shiver and become still.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dock" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Southern Trade Route, Endrus Forest" note="Map1a_Crossing_Thief.xml|5th Passage">
    <description>Coppery leaves casting dappled shadows against their pale bark, a few ragged shrubs grow among a tumbled collection of boulders left behind by floodwaters.  Between a dense growth of briars, a narrow gap leads back toward the trade route.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-640" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Fisherman's Trail, Footpath" note="Map50_Segoltha_River.xml|Segoltha River">
    <description>The well-worn path winds its way erratically between and around the few hardy bushes and shrubs that cling to the perpetually muddy riverbank.  Sparse vegetation interspersed with forgotten whiskey bottles and broken fishing poles lines the edges of the beaten track between the river to the west and the trail running southeast to the trade route.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-700" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small trail" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Berdachun's Hut" note="Berdachun's Hut" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Faded paint chips lie in a heap amidst the clutter of dust and other fallen objects in the corner of the musty hut.  The floor lists precariously where one of the giant bird legs supporting the hut has settled into the ground outside, making the shelf which hangs upon the wall look distinctly lop-sided.  A shallow rack holds various cleaning supplies and other tools, while a door in the back of the room leads to a small pantry.</description>
    <position x="90" y="-580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pantry" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Berdachun's Hut, Pantry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A cobweb quivers in the breeze of your passing, pale grey lace strung along the inner corner of the doorway.  The pantry is small and stuffy with a dust-covered floor displaying tiny clawed footprints of chickens or some other bird.  A shelf has been nailed to the exposed studs of the wall -- the wood cracked and broken from many years use.  Jumbled together upon the shelf is an assortment of supplies used by the seer in his divinations.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="none" move="jump moldy leaves" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="300" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="280" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="300" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="360" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark valley" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="340" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="340" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="320" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Forest of Night, Murky Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black matte trunks grow aimlessly about you, their branches creating a curtain of thick leaves and shadows.  The light is just enough to make you wish for more, and dim enough to make every tree look like the next.</description>
    <position x="320" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Kertigen's Honor" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>The length of this ferry is filled to capacity with travelers making their way to the opposite bank of the Segoltha.  Several children kneel at the ferry's edge, watching the water lap gently against its side, while a group of Dwarven merchants glance longingly towards land.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-720" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dock" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Forest of Night, Willow Valley" note="Willow Valley" color="#008000">
    <description>Permeated by a dense miasma and greenish fog, the forest here is left dim and much of the area is obscured by large weeping bloodwood and willow trees.  Rising to a small hill, the path parts beneath a split tree.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go murky woods" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Forest of Night, Willow Valley" color="#008000">
    <description>Breaking through the murky air, the occasional branch of a nearby willow tree crosses the path.  Echoes of dripping water and something scuttling in the brush nearby only seems to highlight the lack of any indigenous creatures.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go footpath" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Forest of Night, Willow Valley" color="#008000">
    <description>Appearing suddenly out of the gloom, a boggy, marsh-like stream cuts across the path, flooding over a partially submerged bridge.  Deep ruts appear along the trail, as if something heavy had been brought this way.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tangled break" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Forest of Night, Willow Valley" color="#008000">
    <description>Opening up slightly into a haze-filled meadow, the area here is largely arranged around a broken altar.  Large chunks of moss crawl across the surface of the altar, obscuring lumps on its surface.  Small, recently planted khor'vela trees encircle the altar.</description>
    <position x="440" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Forest of Night, Darkened Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Off from the main path, the forest darkens substantially as the trees crowd ever closer into a dense grove.  The occasional echo of odd-sounding giggles can be heard from the shadows.</description>
    <position x="480" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tangled break" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Forest of Night, Darkened Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Gloomy and somber, the trees here are strung with small painted flags and lines of prayer beads.  The heavy scent of rich earth and mud impregnates the air, leaving it feeling somehow both stifling and refreshing.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Forest of Night, Darkened Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Widening out, the path here is littered with deep furrows and ditches filled with swampy waters.  Bits of cattail shoot up around the particularly deep spots, their long fronds swaying as something disturbs them.</description>
    <position x="500" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Forest of Night, Tangled Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Warped and twisted bloodwood trees rise out of the darkness of the forest, sprawling their draping limbs overhead and blotting out the sky.  A tangled snarl of bushes cut off several directions, leaving only a few paths available.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go footpath" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Forest of Night, Tangled Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Irregular and unsettling sounds verberate through the bosk, a clear sign to travelers that they are not alone.  Thick redwood trees intermingle with bloodwoods, their expansive canopies blanketing the forest in darkness.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Forest of Night, Tangled Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Rising up to the north, a dense grove of ancient redwood trees appears.  Along the treeline, a dark platform hangs just out of immediate view.  Thick shrubbery brings a halt to the trail here.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Forest of Night, Tangled Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Winding through the shade of the forest, the trail disappears into the gloom betwixt the spindly and abnormal willow and bloodwood trees here.  Intermittent shadows dart through the forest, just out of immediate view. </description>
    <position x="420" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowed trail" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Forest of Night, Tangled Bosk" color="#008000">
    <description>Allowed to grow beyond measure, redwood trees of enormous proportions sprawl through the forest, draping the woods in deep shadows filled with chaotic underbrush that threatens to trip the feet of unwary travelers.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowed gap" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Forest of Night, Marsh" color="#008000">
    <description>Muck and mud squishes underfoot and the thick, rotten smell of wet wood left too long in water fills the air.  Thick grasses and cattails sprout out of the water lining the path while spindly, twisted trees appear sporadically across the landscape.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowed gap" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Forest of Night, Marsh" color="#008000">
    <description>The path branches into two directions away from the main trail, leading further into the dim marsh.  Large trees growing near the water coat the trail in darkness.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Forest of Night, Marsh" color="#008000">
    <description>Blanketing the trail here in shadows are expansive bloodwood and willow trees, surrounded by a large marsh filled with thick grasses and the occasional bare tree.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Silverclaw Hub, Entry Platform" note="Silverclaw Hub">
    <description>Situated high in the grove, brief flickers of light and movement reveal that this particular platform is only a small part of the hidden Hub.  Opening expansively around a central hut, the platform is populated by wandering Prydaen.  A nearby Prydaen woman helps others to ascend or descend from the platform.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go central hut" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Silverclaw Hub, Warriors Treehouse" note="Warriors Treehouse">
    <description>Half walls surround the treehouse itself, providing a safe walkway and a route for patrolling warriors.  Set up in several nearby branches are cunning snares, some wriggling with unlucky squirrels.  Prydaen warriors chat with each other, work on their weapons, and idly lounge across the area.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go creaking bridge" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Silverclaw Hub, Sleeping Hut" note="Sleeping Hut">
    <description>Thick wooden walls are lined with pelts, keeping the hut warm while deadening the interior from sounds outside.  A small wash basin and pitcher sit atop a low table that rests near a stack of pallets.  Several other pallets filled with slumbering occupants appear throughout the quiet area.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Silverclaw Hub, Crafting Hut" note="Crafting Hut|project bin" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The rich smell of redwood permeates the area, bringing a sense of calm to the busy hut that is built around an expansive tree.  Baskets of supplies are stacked near the walls and tanning hides are stretched taunt on racks.  Several stations are set up in the area, where gathered Prydaen work on projects.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Silverclaw Hub, Lookout">
    <description>Covered by a truncated roof, the platform here is open to the elements.  A wooden-seated swing suspends from an overhanging branch.  </description>
    <position x="440" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Silverclaw Hub, Central Treehouse" note="Central Treehouse">
    <description>Built into the sprawling canopy of a shorter tree, the central platform features a large firepit.  Several young Prydaen run through the area, squealing and making various babyish mewling sounds at each other while a handful of Elders watch over them with a tolerant expression.  Nearby warriors feign negligence, but fiercely approach any that get too close to the playing kits.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go creaking bridge" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Silverclaw Hub, Hut of the Three" note="Hut of the Three">
    <description>Surprisingly large inside, the hut itself consist only partially of platform.  A wide hallway is cut into the massive tree, allowing for much more space.  Thick, woven rugs and dense pelts line the floors, providing seating for the inhabitants and visitors alike.  You also see Teacher of the Kin Seryal, Eidola Bailon and Ra Vaelorn.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>The trees here are subtly twisted, their gnarled trunks hung with ivy and lichen.  High above, their branches seem to twine together like grasping, skeletal hands, bearing only a scattering of blackened leaves.  Snarls of tangled and matted vegetation are an obstacle for any who pass this way, creating hummocks and lumps resembling scattered corpses in varying states of decay.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go serpentine path" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>A massive boulder dominates this spot, its stony bulk reaching nearly as high as a tall Gor'Tog.  Its grey flanks are crusted with lichen and snarled with vines, though thus far it has not been completed subsumed by the ravening plant life.  A small deobar tree appears to be growing from the boulder's summit, the added height provided by the hulking rock providing the tiny sapling a meager edge in the war for survival.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>The metronomic sound of dripping water pervades the area here, though the noise's source is not apparent.  A fungal reek lingers in the air, mixing noxiously with the smell of mouldering leaves and an unmistakable whiff of rotting flesh.  The vines here are so profuse that a few small trees have succumbed, their skeletons now serving only as support for the parasitic plants that killed them.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>A humanoid skeleton reclines into the grasping embrace of the pervasive vines, its bony limbs sprawling in a morbid parody of decadent relaxation.  A few tatters of silk cling to the remains, bleached by wind and weather to a gaudy red-orange.  Below the corpse, the hilt of a rusted sword rises from the sea of foliage.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>The vegetation here is thickly studded with thorns, burrs, spines and prickles of every description.  Despite the plants' warlike defenses, the area here is somewhat clear and open, as though daring those who pass this way to move with careless inattention.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>Skeins of vines tangle with the branches of trees and the area's dense undergrowth to form a living web that seems to suffocate this place.  The air here is still and torpid, redolent of rotting vegetation and the cloying odor of decay.  Even the trees seem choked and smothered, the clinging vines and mosses overwhelming smaller individuals in the arboreal battle for light and life.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>The skeletal remains of some fox-sized creature are suspended in a snarl of coiling vines, its body wrenched and splayed in a way no living animal could hope to survive.  The trees are slightly blackened along one side, but the undergrowth is thriving ferociously, forming an impenetrable wall blocking passage to the east and south.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat">
    <description>The undergrowth is thinner here, burnt by some calamity to a spiky, blackened stubble.  The boles of the surviving trees are scaled and charred along one side, though enough are unscathed to ensure little light penetrates the dense tangle of branches above.  A few blackened stumps are a lingering testament of those who did not survive, their ashy remains lending the whole area a suffocating odor of scorched pine.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Endrus Forest, Sushu Rahat" note="Sushu Rahat|Endrus serpents">
    <description>The area around a massive, lightning-struck deobar tree is burned down to the ground, creating a clearing that is nearly perfectly round.  A large hole in the tree's bole seems to peer at all that passes here like a gigantic, lidless eye.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deobar tree" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Silverclaw Hub, Private Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Built solidly around a tree, a large wooden building with a thatched bloodwood roof has been neatly partitioned into psuedo-apartments that share a communal porch that circles around the broad trunk.  Along the covered porch, several chimes constructed of bones, shells, and feathers flutter in the wind, bringing the occasional sound to the otherwise quiet area.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Silverclaw Hub, Private Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Leading around a large tree, more doorways to living quarters appear along the covered platform here.  A sturdy bloodwood bench dominates the end of the walkway, providing seating for any that wish to pause to enjoy the weather or the sounds of the forest beyond the Hub.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Endrus Forest, Deobar Sentinel">
    <description>A fork in the burned tree's trunk provides precarious footing for those who venture here.  Slender, nearly-straight branches reach upward from the blackened wrack of the tree, like a multitude of fingers yearning toward the sky.  The higher canopy of the forest all around looms in every direction like walls of a living castle.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tree trunk" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="The Grove, Arched Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Majestic trees line a wide gravel path, their thick branches arching high to mingle with one another and create a tunnel that leads deeper into the wooded copse.  Soft moss covers the ground, interspersed with clusters of delicate ferns and vibrant wildflowers.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go meandering path" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="The Grove, Shaded Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The gravel path meanders over the moss-covered ground and giant oaks grow along its borders, their thick branches stretching to form a dense canopy overhead.  Vibrant wildflowers peek out here and there, adding color to the verdant space.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="The Grove, Shaded Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Tall trees reach up towards the sky, their thick branches covered in clumps of spongy moss.  Tiny pink and purple fairy slipper orchids sprout from the forest floor along a gravel path, their blooms adding a subtle, sweet aroma to the area.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="The Grove, Shaded Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The wide path winds through densely populated trees, its route mimicking the twisted limbs reaching toward the sky and forming a lush canopy overhead.  Slender vines drape down from the branches to brush the ground.  A cozy bench swing hangs between two large birch trees, tiny flowers sprouting to each side of it.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="The Grove, Shaded Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The dense canopy above blocks the sky, making it difficult to tell if it's night or day amongst the trees crowding the forest floor.  Snaking through the thick underbrush, the gravel path narrows considerably as its route is disrupted by rotting logs and protruding roots.  An unsettling silence hangs in the air, broken only by the occasional creak of the branches or the rustle of unseen creatures.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="The Grove, Shaded Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Lofty trees stand proudly along the gravel path, thick moss hanging from their branches and forming long, wispy curtains that brush the spongy ground.  Fiddlehead ferns sprout beneath the sturdy trunks, along with patches of grass and small shrubs.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="The Grove, Shaded Pathway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Clusters of tiny mushrooms grow around the trunks of the enormous trees comprising this portion of the grove, their red caps standing out against the lush greenery.  The gentle rustle of leaves in the breeze mixes with the soft chirping of birds and the chattering of chipmunks, creating a subtle symphony.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <label text="Leth Deriel">
    <position x="50" y="40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blood Nyads, Dryads">
    <position x="330" y="-330" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ferry to Crossing">
    <position x="80" y="-740" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Only open at night">
    <position x="294" y="-40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pale Grey Death Spirits">
    <position x="250" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Forest of Night">
    <position x="150" y="-370" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Murky Woods">
    <position x="200" y="-20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Sanrisi Tree">
    <position x="230" y="-155" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Inner Shrine">
    <position x="290" y="-220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Soothsayer's Hut">
    <position x="10" y="-600" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ancient Tree">
    <position x="60" y="-680" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Chelsea Overlook">
    <position x="190" y="-730" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dryad Priestesses">
    <position x="402" y="5" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Twisted Dryads">
    <position x="420" y="-140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Silverclaw Hub">
    <position x="380" y="-220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Endrus serpents">
    <position x="120" y="-475" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Grove">
    <position x="50" y="-70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Cougars">
    <position x="280" y="-180" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>