<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Southern Trade Route Part 2 (Leth to Gondola)" id="62">
  <node id="1" name="Gondola, Cab North" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>Worn down to a dusky grey color, the proud wood once cut and fitted to compose this gondola creaks with age and disrepair, but appears to be steady.  Seats have been lifesculpted up from the floor and melded into the sides.  Weak light streams in through the yellow-tinted windows, eating away patiently at what little color remains in the tiny, musty chamber.</description>
    <position x="420" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Obsidian Pass, Platform" note="Platform|Gondola" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Like an aerie forgotten in the wilderness, the platform remains despite being abandoned by its creators.  While rickety and creaking uneasily, it appears to have held up well.  Two side-by-side granite beams rise up from the edge of the ridge, around which have been wound the lengths of rope used by the gondola that provides transport over the great chasm.</description>
    <position x="420" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ridge" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gondola" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Obsidian Pass, Chasm's Ridge">
    <description>The mountain trail comes to an abrupt end at the edge of a massive chasm with sheer walls that fall down into darkness.  Twin thick cables of some indiscernable substance hang over the chasm, tied off on this end to a rickety platform that looks about as stable as a faenrae reaver on samatak.</description>
    <position x="420" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety platform" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Obsidian Pass, Mountain Trail">
    <description>Cracks in the sides of the pass ooze a darkness flatter than the glassy black of the smoothed walls.  The silence here is disturbing.</description>
    <position x="420" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb branch" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Obsidian Pass, Mountain Trail">
    <description>The creak of ropes and the screech of stone clashing with stone bounces through the pass from somewhere to the south.  A trickle of dust followed by a shower of pebbles falls down the sheer mountainside, serving as an irregular waterfall of stone and earth as well a reminder that this place is not so stable as it may seem.</description>
    <description>The cry of an owl and the creak of ropes bounces through the pass from somewhere to the south.  A trickle of dust followed by a shower of pebbles falls down the glass-sheer mountainside, serving as an irregular waterfall of stone and earth as well as a reminder that this place is not so deserted as it may seem.</description>
    <position x="440" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Obsidian Pass, Garrison Trail">
    <description>Curving tightly through a narrow crevice in the mountain face, the trail looks like an unremarkable natural feature.  Yet a fresh scuff on the rock wall and crushed rock underfoot hint that more than wildlife may travel this path.</description>
    <position x="460" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Obsidian Pass, Culvert">
    <description>Twisting away from the main trail, the narrow path mazes through natural breaks in the stone before finally widening into this secluded culvert.  Building supplies and provisions are neatly organized in military precision around a dusty tent.  A series of ledges jut from the sheer mountain face high above, connected by rope bridges.</description>
    <position x="480" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dusty tent" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Obsidian Pass, Mountain Trail" note="RTZ28|RT-GPN-LNW" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The walls of the pass press in on both sides, as if the trail were some sort of uninvited wound the rocks were trying to mend.</description>
    <position x="420" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow track" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Obsidian Pass, Mountain Trail" note="RTZ29|RT-GPN-LF" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The lonely cry of an eagle echoes between the sides of the narrow pass, a haunting sound.  Dark trees creep slowly up the mountainside in either direction, and further to the west the eternally white peak of Icespear Reach rises up majestically.  Rubble and scree lie scattered across the trail.</description>
    <description>Harsh sounds echo uneasily between the sides of the narrow pass, clawing icy tracks along your spine.  Dark foliage climbs up the mountainside, feathering the skyline in bold brushes of dark color.  Rubble and scree lie scattered across the trail, making footing treacherous.</description>
    <position x="420" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Obsidian Pass, Guard House">
    <description>The jagged black mountains for which this pass is named jut to the east and west, just barely allowing passage for the north-south road.  A guard house is situated beside the path, looking as if it were melting out of the mountainside.  Elven runes are cut into the walls, and a sigil of warding has been carved over the doorway.</description>
    <description>The night sky is rent by mountainscape darkness even more jagged and deep than the domain of Damaris.  A guard house can just barely be detected, rising up out of the rubble that has been piled up here somewhat recently.</description>
    <position x="420" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go guard house" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blockade" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow track" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Obsidian Pass, Narrow Track" note="snowbeasts|Gash">
    <description>Shards of obsidian littering the ground make it even more difficult to traverse the tight confines of this track.  A chilling breeze, blowing steadily from the west, wraps itself around you in its cold embrace.</description>
    <position x="360" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Narrow Track, A Tight Spot">
    <description>Obsidian flecked walls of gray granite draw close to each other and threaten to block your progress.  A stiff wind whistles its displeasure at being confined and bites at your clothing with its cold teeth.</description>
    <position x="300" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Narrow Track, Gravel Path">
    <description>Pea-sized gravel trickles down from the cliff overhead.  This rain of stone covers the path and hides the passage of both man and beast.  In places where the icy hand of the prevailing wind does not reach, lacy webs of frost sparkle like crystal necklaces.</description>
    <position x="280" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="The Gash, Northern Rim">
    <description>A narrow track widens to meet a barren and craggy ledge.  Named 'The Gash' because it looks as though the World Dragon itself had dragged a claw through the ground leaving a deep wound, the canyon towards the south is both deep and sheer.  An icy wind upwells from The Gash and whispers in your ear before it races off into the distance. </description>
    <position x="260" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#008000">
    <description>Stunted trees, not venturing too far from the ground, fear that the winds would rend their limbs from them.  Shimmering ice crystals, blowing up from below, angrily sting your face and then quickly melt away.</description>
    <position x="240" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go snow-choked passage" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#008000">
    <description>The sun brings Berengaria's light to return what warmth the winds stole from the land during the night.  Small mounds of snow cling to the shadows of trees and rocks as a reminder of the recent night.</description>
    <description>Frigid winds, in the service of Asketi, steal the warmth from the land.  Snow rides on the wind to reclaim the land taken by the light of day.</description>
    <position x="260" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The sun's relief brings its own price as the frozen ground thaws into slick mud which sticks to everything it touches.  Small rivulets of melted snow race downward to a small gully towards the south.  Small creatures, basking on sun-warmed rocks, quickly dart away instinctively as you walk by.</description>
    <description>In the darkness of night, the muddy ground freezes to the hardness of stone.  Other than the movement of leaves in the wind, the area is void of the all signs of movement.</description>
    <position x="280" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#008000">
    <description>Low growing plants, clinging to the steep incline, quickly respond to the light of day with a burst of colorful flowers.  Around you, insects buzz around in a blur and visit each blossom for a drink of sweet nectar.</description>
    <description>Low growing plants, covered in layers of frost and snow, prepare their buds for the next day of light.  A somber silence blankets the area.</description>
    <position x="300" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go passage" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#008000">
    <description>Warmth from the day brings some relief from the bitter cold of night.  Flocks of small swallows soar overhead demonstrating their mastery of the sky in intricate patterns.</description>
    <description>Frigid winds quickly steal what warmth the sun freely gave during its time in the sky.  A covering of wind-borne snow encases everything for the night.</description>
    <position x="280" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="The Gash, Central Gully">
    <description>Caught between the frozen order of the south face and the cyclic chaos of the north face, you find little comfort for either man or beast.  Flurries of snow dance around the stones which cover the ground.</description>
    <position x="300" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="The Gash, Lonely Grotto">
    <description>While this sheltered spot keeps the wild winds at bay, little comfort can be found from the cold of the shadows as the light is also kept out.</description>
    <position x="320" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="The Gash, South Face">
    <description>Up towards the south, icy winds race over a great sheet of ice in their pursuit of the light and the warmth it brings.  Sensing a warm body, they rush down to feast upon body heat.</description>
    <position x="280" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="The Gash, Glacier">
    <description>In the shadow of the south face, the ice field paints a dull, life-less landscape.  The wild wind replies with a bitter blast as you intrude in its domain.</description>
    <position x="260" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="The Gash, Glacier">
    <description>The mounds of ice and snow offers little to look at, both are equally gray and featureless in the dimness of the shadows.  The only difference notable is that while the snow readily follows the command of the wind, the ice pointedly ignores it.</description>
    <position x="240" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ice wall" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="The Gash, Glacier">
    <description>Thin scratches in the ice prove that you are not alone in this icy wasteland.  The frigid wind, enraged at the intrusion into its domain, howls a challenge.</description>
    <position x="280" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="The Gash, Glacier">
    <description>The steep trail ends abruptly at the base of a vertical wall of ice.  The ever present wind races down the wall and brings a stinging haze of ice and snow with it.</description>
    <position x="300" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="The Gash, Glacier">
    <description>The sheer wall of ice rising towards the south prevents any further progress in that direction nor does it seem scalable.  Through the wind blown snow, a darkened spot draws attention itself. </description>
    <position x="260" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark opening" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="The Gash, South Face">
    <description>Thick banks of snow move around at the whims of the ever-present wind covering almost everything.  Only a few of the larger rocks stand high enough to poke through the waves of white. </description>
    <position x="220" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="The Gash, South Face">
    <description>In contrast with the north face, this area remains cloaked in shadow and is always locked in the wind's freezing grasp.  Except for the faint cries of hunting beasts in the distance, all you hear is the wind.</description>
    <position x="200" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="The Gash, Central Gully" color="#008000">
    <description>In the deepest part of The Gash, this gully harbors the accumulation of rock and frozen mud from years of melting flows in from the north face.  The south face, ever frozen, offers only ice and snow to the gully's hoard.</description>
    <position x="220" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#008000">
    <description>With the thaw that day brings, mud slowly oozes down from the north and continues its trek southward towards the gully below.  The cold wind, blowing against this flow in an attempt to halt its progress, leaves ripples in the wet mud.</description>
    <description>The cold wind, supreme ruler in the hours of darkness, enforces its will on the flow of mud and freezes its trek towards the gully.</description>
    <position x="240" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="The Gash, Central Gully" color="#008000">
    <description>Here on the boundary of the north face with its cycles of day and night and the south face with its ever present sun-less shadow, Asketi's winds cry loudly for the death of light and warmth.</description>
    <position x="260" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="The Gash, South Face">
    <description>The wind, like a hungry wolf, rushes down from the south and clamps its icy teeth around your body.  An urge to keep moving cries out a warning against staying here and becoming a part of the frozen landscape.</description>
    <position x="240" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="The Gash, North Face" color="#008000">
    <description>The path rises sharply towards the northwest to a small copse of trees.</description>
    <position x="220" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="The Gash, Small Copse" note="Shrine3-1|Berengaria" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Strangely, the ravages of day and night, which affect the other parts of The Gash, do not invade this secluded sanctuary.  A sense of calm pervades this peaceful thicket.</description>
    <position x="200" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="The Gash, Ice Cave">
    <description>This large chamber could house a clan or two if it were not so bitter cold.  Just outside, the whistling wind reverberates deeper in the cave with a deadly moaning.  Deeply sunk into the floor along the wall, a shadowy figure is barely visible and warrants further examination. </description>
    <position x="260" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="The Gash, Ice Cave">
    <description>Only a dim glow from the southeast barely illuminates this passage and only a thorough search along the icy walls reveals the exits.</description>
    <position x="240" y="580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="The Gash, Ice Cave">
    <description>Darkness obscures most of the details of this area.  A strong odor of animal musk permeates the air and stifles the breath.</description>
    <position x="220" y="560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="The Gash, Ice Cave">
    <description>Darker than midnight on a moonless evening, one can barely see their hands before their face.  The crunching under foot reveals itself to be a pile of gnawed bones from beastly feasts.</description>
    <position x="220" y="600" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Foothills, Steep Path" note="RTZ27|RT-GPN-IT" color="#C2B280">
    <description>The mountains begin reclaiming road here, their rocky mouths and jagged teeth piercing the passage with fang and claw.  Even the very sky seems to betray the land, for water and wind erode the dirt of the route away, leaving patches of bare rock facing the lone sky, naked to plain sight.</description>
    <position x="440" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Foothills, Artesian Well">
    <description>An old artesian well, still used by traveler and trader alike, stands alone in the dark shadow of the great mountains before it.  Oblivious to the road, to the northern city of Leth, to the dark peaks in the south - it remains a symbol of the enduring adventurer's spirit.</description>
    <position x="460" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Southern Trade Route, Foothills">
    <description>Numerous rocks and boulders lie to each side of the road.  Despite the evidence of frequent travel, the steepness and insurmountable height of the mountains to the south make travel in either direction seem fraught with the promise of hardship.</description>
    <position x="460" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Southern Trade Route, Fallen Statue">
    <description>A large marble statue has been shattered and broken by the roadside.  The image of a Human woman's face, mouth wide with terror and fear, stares out at you from shattered stone eyes.  The dress, the body - all else has been smashed into thousands of marble slivers, some stained with a dark brown hue.</description>
    <position x="480" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Southern Trade Route, Gold Fence">
    <description>An ornate gate stands to the north, the tall pinnacles of gold shimmering before the path leading into the cemetery.  The edge of the road begins to overlap with the curve of the foothills to the south, the face of the Dragon Spine leering from its haughty throne of rock.</description>
    <position x="480" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Southern Trade Route, Gate of Heroes">
    <description>A large golden gate, carved with ornate patterns of Fae and Immortals, towers far above.  The golden spires of its points stretch upwards as if daring to pierce the belly of the sky.</description>
    <description>Darkness casts a sinister hand over an ornate gilded gate.  Shadows mingle with the silken flags hanging from each post, the silver roses stitched so beautifully on them twisted and distorted by the same darkling scent of night which makes the evening itself so lovely.</description>
    <position x="500" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Southern Trade Route, Gold Fence">
    <description>A large gold fence stands to one side of the road, its ornate metal form guarding an expansive cemetery behind a lanky frame.  A tall gate stands further to the south.  Black silk flags stitched with thorn-wrapped silver roses billow softly in the wind.</description>
    <position x="500" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Southern Trade Route, Road to the Pass">
    <description>Weathered rocks lie by the roadside, their forms twisted and gnarled by time and by weather.  Their figures seemed turned towards the sky in eternal supplication, hands and faces of rough unworked stone forever gazing at the endless sky.</description>
    <description>Twilight dances across the horizon.  Shadow and starlight mingle in their ever-eternal dance, forever young, forever lovely from their places in the sky.  The twisted figures of rocks sit sullenly on the earth, an unwilling and immortal audience to the night's performance.</description>
    <position x="520" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Southern Trade Route, Road to the Pass">
    <description>Few trees stand alongside the path.  The road inclines to the south, seeming to grow in steepness at the onset of the foothills.  The spires of Leth linger far to the north, their sky-kissed pinnacles barely within sight.</description>
    <description>Ribbons of indigo and cobalt silk hang from the sky, tatters of the night's silken cloak that drape over the world.  The evening's dark hair flows with the wind, shadows of her countenance unveiling over all.</description>
    <position x="520" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Southern Trade Route, Road to the Pass">
    <description>As if some angry artist had taken his knife and cut black swatches into his canvas, so like that image of passionate anger stand the Dragon Spine Mountains.  It is as if the very earth had thrown them against the sky, their forms tearing into the silken threads that weave the very atmosphere around Elanthia. </description>
    <description>Starlight casts shadows using the jagged rocks and stones, making eerie unnatural puppets of shadow that the depth of night manipulates as it wanes on.  The mountains to the south bear an even blacker shade compared to the dark cobalt of the skies.</description>
    <position x="540" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Southern Trade Route, Road to the Pass">
    <description>The well-traveled road becomes rocky.  The larger obstacles have been cleared from the way, boulders and jagged outcroppings lying to the side of the passage.  To the north, Leth seems scarce - especially when compared to the gargantuan shadow of the southern mountains.</description>
    <description>Starlight casts shadows using the jagged rocks and stones, making eerie unnatural puppets of shadow that the depth of night manipulates as it wanes on.  The mountains to the south bear an even blacker shade compared to the dark cobalt of the skies.</description>
    <position x="60" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Southern Trade Route, Edge of the Valley">
    <description>The edge of the meadow connects to the harsher land leading up to the foothills.  The green ocean of grass that softly moves with the breeze contrasts sharply with the spartan surroundings that lie ahead.</description>
    <position x="80" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Southern Trade Route, Edge of the Valley">
    <description>The wide expanse of the trade route increases its breadth to accommodate the busy trade and travel that increases near to the mountains.  The signs of frequent commerce litter the roadside, broken transports and abandoned garbage dwindle in the dry winds.</description>
    <position x="100" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Quiet Meadow, Edge of the Valley">
    <description>The valley here diverges two ways.  Large rocks jut out from the ground to the south, while to the north a gentle slope gives way to the bright green meadows beyond.</description>
    <description>Darkness reflects off of the southern mountain range, the tall angular forms of rock glimmering with an almost unholy sheen.  To the north, a gentle meadow lines the route beneath the twilight sky.</description>
    <position x="100" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>A mass of wild grapes is encroaching upon the space of a tall aspen.  Sinewy vines climb the wide body of the trunk, clinging with all their might.  Ripe fruit, full and dark, hangs precariously from the slight branches.</description>
    <position x="100" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>Tulips and honeysuckle sway in the breeze, their perfumed scents drifting over the large expanse of the meadow.  The warbling song of birds moves softly with the winds.</description>
    <description>Starlight brushes over the smooth silken waves of dark grass below.  The perfection of night drifts over the world, blanketing the meadow in a veil of silence.</description>
    <position x="120" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>The rolling hills of the meadow begin to grow slightly steeper towards the south.  The silken grass surrounding the road ripples in the wind, a living ocean of green vegetation.</description>
    <position x="120" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>A young sapling struggles along the roadside, its leaves trembling in the racking breezes that tremulously pass by.  The roots wrestle with the ground below, a struggle for survival.</description>
    <position x="140" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>An old apple tree rests surrounded by a circle of soft pink flowers.  A lone squirrel titters precariously from a branch before leaping high into the air.  Blushing red apples dangle from the branches, far out of reach above.</description>
    <position x="140" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>The soft coo of a lone sparrow flitting through the air accompanies the melody of a gentle breeze rustling leaf against leaf.  Serenity of the rarest kind lurks here in the shadow of the ominous mountains to the south.</description>
    <position x="160" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>Gentle grasses sway and bend, their only burden the unending sky that looms above.  Soft twittering sounds linger in the air, gentle melodies that soothe the soul and the body.</description>
    <description>Darkness of the evening brings a soft wind that brushes against the silken grass of the meadow.  Its soothing gentle cadence stirs nightingales from their hidden nests to sing.</description>
    <position x="180" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Southern Trade Route, Quiet Meadow">
    <description>Grass stretches as far as the eye can see, its lush green interspersed with fiery flashes of color.  Wood-violets and irises peek from among mottled patches of shadow that dot the fields.</description>
    <description>Shadows catch the pale petals of small flowers hiding amidst the tall grass.  They shine and reflect snippets of color, flickering beneath the dusky evening skies.</description>
    <position x="200" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Southern Trade Route, Edge of the Valley">
    <description>A well-kept road leads into the valley, softly moved by gentle breezes that hail from over the foothills of the mountains.</description>
    <position x="200" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Alongside the Forest, Dwindling Way">
    <description>The road slopes downward towards the south into a small valley that stands before the mountains and the precarious Obsidian Pass, while to the north it leans into the forest slightly, winding around it like a coiled serpent.</description>
    <position x="200" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Alongside the Forest, Dwindling Way">
    <description>A wild rose bush twines around an old wooden fence, its thorns and blossoms radiant with savage beauty.  Its fierceness is complemented by the pale lavender crocuses peeking softly from beneath their bed in the earth.</description>
    <description>Darkness immerses the petals of the roses on a wild bush nearby, as if each flower was a shroud to be placed over the hearts of the dead.  Small lavender petals from some indistinguishable flowers peek through the dense earth.</description>
    <position x="220" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Alongside the Forest, Dwindling Way">
    <description>Dust of the road gingerly settles, haggard brush beside the way loose in the dehydrated earth.  Rocks and twisted branches skuttle about, the wind raking brakish claws of air over the dried dirt, eroding it away.</description>
    <position x="240" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Alongside the Forest, Winding Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A large willow tree solemnly bows its stately head over the road.  A clearing beneath provides a quaint spot for a picnic, or respite from the day's long travels.  Daisies and clementine open their sweet faces to the skies.</description>
    <description>Beneath a tall willow tree, the heady scent of jes-roses mingling with pure-white daisies courts the thick dampness in the night air.  The soft flowers open their bright faces to the sky, opening themselves as the evening draws gently overhead.</description>
    <position x="260" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Southern Trade Route">
    <description>The stump of an old tree rests with an axe wedged firmly into its center.  Piles of wood overgrown with weeds and wildflowers lie by the roadside, a forgotten woodsman's dream.</description>
    <description>Starlight glints off the rusted metal of an axe-head lodged into the thick wood of the tree.  Beneath the night sky, dozens of fragile violets peek through the rotting wood, their petals glistening with moisture from their daytime hiding places.</description>
    <position x="280" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Alongside the Woods, Break in the Forest">
    <description>A ring of mushrooms solemnly crests a small opening in the forest.  Small motes of light drift aimlessly around, settling on the moist grass below.</description>
    <description>Starlight trickles through breaks in the leaves.  A circle of fey mushrooms rests within the clearing, small offerings left by wandering travelers and nearby village-inhabitants placed on the edge.</description>
    <position x="300" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Alongside the Woods, Winding Path">
    <description>A broken picket fence stands forlornly before the ruins of a small hut.  Perhaps once the home of a forester or hermit, the place now stands in shambles, its memories sealed by time's unrelenting hand.</description>
    <position x="300" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Alongside the Woods, Winding Path">
    <description>Further south, twisted trees line the way.  Their arching branches form a lifeless arbor overhead.  A fallen log, rotting inside and out, rests to one side.  The small flowers and grass nearby are in the process of consuming its crumbling body.</description>
    <position x="320" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Alongside the Forest, Winding Path">
    <description>Trees stand, sickly figures thrown against the spartan sky above.  Their gnarled and twisting limbs seem to contort as if out of pain, their bodies those of hunchbacks mournfully bent over the roadside.</description>
    <description>Branches shake and sway, eerie emaciated fingers edging closer inch by inch.  Night makes the forest seem more sinister, a pall of darkness drawn over its weary face.</description>
    <position x="340" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Alongside the Forest, Winding Path">
    <description>The curves and dips in the road make for somewhat difficult travel, rocks and branches reaching out to deter the way.  Most travelers seem to have cleared a passage through the debris.</description>
    <position x="340" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest">
    <description>A soft cooing echoes unbounded through the forest.  The road cuts a thick swatch through the brush, a pale shadow compared to the almost malignant ones surrounding it.</description>
    <position x="340" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tangled path" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest">
    <description>Speckled rocks mottle the dusky color of the road.  The bleak way winds around the edge of the forest like a snake coiling around a polished apple.</description>
    <description>The bleak way, interspersed by small, round stones, rests sullenly beneath the heavy mantle of evening.  The road coils and winds in a serpentine way, meandering both to the north and to the south.</description>
    <position x="360" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest">
    <description>The hollows and dips in the path are filled with rocks and muddy water.  Wagon-ruts leave indelible tracks in the dirt, insects and various unidentifiable things make their dark homes in the shallow pools that form.</description>
    <position x="400" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest">
    <description>Tall, lanky trees rise up over a small hill that the road travels over.  Their sinewy figures are barely recognizable as trees, leaves and branches slender and emaciated.</description>
    <position x="400" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest">
    <description>Southwards, the brush becomes thicker, the trees still far more skeleton than forest.  Rocks intersperse the growth, their solid forms marring the complexion of verdant green carpeting the area.</description>
    <description>Evening draws her cloak around the edges of the forest, this small stronghold of nature left before the face of the great road south.  Even the night seems to shy away from the earth, the glittering light of stars edging from the perimeter of trees.</description>
    <position x="40" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Southern Trade Route, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>Trees begin to become wilder here, losing the gait and gaze of sentience that the lifesculpted artworks possessed.  The sounds of the forest primeval begin to echo around you, the stray call of a bird trembling against the air.</description>
    <description>Shadows of darkness waver as night descends on the world.  Stars peek from behind the dusky canopy of leaves above, their diamond-like tears radiant overhead.</description>
    <position x="60" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Southern Trade Route, Ez'keari's Orchards">
    <description>The orchard begins to thin, rows of mineral trees becoming less dense.  Lifesculptures surround the perimeter, their hand-like boughs twined with snowflowers.  A sparse forest before a large mountain range lingers over your view to the south.</description>
    <position x="80" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Southern Trade Route, Ez'keari's Orchards">
    <description>A graceful fountain emerges from amidst a small grove of lifesculpted trees molded and shaped into abstract images from dreams.  They twirl and spiral in almost unrecognizable shapes, unidentifiable to all save their creator.</description>
    <description>A white marble fountain glistens in the light of the stars.  It glows from among a secluded grove of lifesculpted trees bathing in the shadows of the night.</description>
    <position x="100" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Southern Trade Route, Ez'keari's Orchards">
    <description>Lifesculptures reach out, branches molded to be unnatural hand-like shapes, each finger grasping at travelers passing by.  Eerie wooden faces leer at you, their features contorted and twisted to the point that they only vaguely resemble a Human countenance.</description>
    <description>Blue-black darkness ripples over the hauntingly lucid figures of all-too Human lifesculpted trees.  Branches reaching out towards you waver as the breeze of the evening gifts them with preternatural life.</description>
    <position x="120" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Southern Trade Route, Ez'keari's Orchards">
    <description>Sleek stones line the road as it winds its way southwest.  Rosewood trees peek over the edges of tall fences, their sorrel hues almost a blood-red beneath the sun.</description>
    <description>Stars wink over the wrought bronze fence guarding the more precious of mineral trees behind it.  The stray sound of metal leaves rustling echoes through the sacred silence of the night.</description>
    <position x="140" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Southern Trade Route, Ez'keari's Orchards">
    <description>Silverwood trees line the dusky roadway, their metal-wrought trunks sparkling with the beauty of nature's abundance.  To the south, the tips of a tall fence peek into view.</description>
    <position x="140" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Southern Trade Route, Ez'keari's Orchards">
    <description>Tall bronze gates tower far overhead, standing to one side of the road.  Beyond them, expanses of mineral trees and gracefully lifesculpted figures rest.  The road transverses through, the exotic flora nearby chiming softly as the wind strikes their precious leaves.</description>
    <description>The night casts strange mottled patterns on the metallic woods of the orchard.  Amorphous shadows cling and clutch at gold and silver leaves, a wind from behind them brushing against their delicate surfaces.</description>
    <position x="160" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Southern Trade Route, Near the Woods">
    <description>The soft cadence of the breeze echoes like a siren's lone song as it whips and whistles through the mass of ironwood trees.  The voice of the sky sings softly, a voice filled with the pain of unending sorrow, and the darkling soul of the forest.</description>
    <position x="160" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Southern Trade Route, Near the Woods">
    <description>Small wildflowers dot the dark green grass that lines the road.  Streaks of dull, black rock peek from beneath rents torn into the dirt by a wagon that left deep ruts in the earth after her passing.</description>
    <description>Night trickles through breaks in the dense blanket of leaves above.  Stars sparkle over the well-used road beneath.</description>
    <position x="160" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Southern Trade Route, Near the Woods">
    <description>The sky lucidly stretches far above, moving with the all the grace and sleekness of a cat as it stalks over the ground below.  The road is clear, the path well-maintained and managed for travel and commerce.</description>
    <description>The edge of the wood trembles with the fruit of the night.  The soft solo of a wanton nightingale echoes mournfully through the wood.  Stars hang suspended on transluscent threads, their light piercing through the dark canopy of leaves.</description>
    <position x="160" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Southern Trade Route, Lonely Outpost">
    <description>An old shed stands lopsided, one wall resting uneasily against the strong trunk of a modwir tree.  Wind batters against the rotting walls, the wood disintegrating as it is clawed at by the elements.</description>
    <position x="160" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Southern Trade Route, Lonely Outpost">
    <description>An old military outpost lies in a heap, slowly falling apart.  The encroaching green is wrapping its sinewy tendrils around it.  Once it stood as a tall and proud waystation, but now the shadows of the past are all that remain.</description>
    <description>Moonlight wanders over broken rotting walls belonging to an old waystation.  The sound of chirring insects echoes from within the black mass of debris.  Breaks in the leaves above let moonlight fall in scattered patches along the ground.</description>
    <position x="180" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Southern Trade Route, Traveler's Rest">
    <description>Caravans come and go, but a large and seemingly unremarkable stone remains unchanging here.  Perhaps a shrine to some unnamed God, or merely a token of good fortune, Traders, Bards, Mages and countless others leave small tributes of luck and hope nearby.</description>
    <description>A tall and somewhat ungainly rough stone sits in the center of a quiet clearing.  Darkness washes over offerings left by unseen travelers that rest strewn in a circle around the odd piece of rock.</description>
    <position x="200" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Southern Trade Route, Traveler's Rest">
    <description>A small glade here bears rough-cut wooden benches and a stone well.  Passersby rest there, languidly stretching beneath the sun, telling tales of lands near and far away.  Stories from divergent lands such as Ilithi to the south and as far as Therenborough to the north mingle in a flurry of culture and song.</description>
    <description>A slender Mountain Elf patrols the grounds, warily scanning the nearby shadows of the forest outside the clearing.  A panoply of tents and bedrolls rest beneath the evening sky, the people slumbering within them reposing peacefully in the depths of Damaris' realm.</description>
    <position x="220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Southern Trade Route, Small Cottage">
    <description>Nearby, a house is dug into one of the small hills.  A small garden encircles the odd structure, extending to the very edge of the roadside.  Delicate cherry trees are planted in precise, neat rows alongside of the dwelling.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trees" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>The ironwood trees tremble with the passing of caravans and people.  The signs of heavy use lie strewn about, from broken wagon wheels to long-abandoned cargo.  These interruptions on the surrounding nature of the forest seem to intrude and mar the gentle calm that prevails.</description>
    <position x="220" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>Sparse vegetation lines the roadside.  Signs of countless caravans and people passing by mar the pale grey stones that smooth the rough briskness of travel. </description>
    <description>Rocks and stones strewn over the road are concealed by the veil of night.  The way winds its direction south and north, the shadowed skies looming far overhead.</description>
    <position x="240" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>The stream dwindles to a fine thread of silver, almost too slight to be seen, damp soil beside the road all that remains of the crystalline water.  Small flowers spring up around the area, heads bowed softly.</description>
    <description>Darkness blankets all, save for a few small flowers peeking through the veil of night.  The trickling of a nearby stream echoes softly, the movement of water pattering against stones weaving a quiet song that drifts through the air.</description>
    <position x="260" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>A stream's silver hue breaks through the monotonous dark of the landscape.  The cadence of rushing water dancing around rocks and branches echoes quietly through the trees, a deft, delicate movement of song.</description>
    <description>A stream rushes by, a thin ribbon of silver in the impermeable night.  Trees sway and bend, their leaves softly vaulting from their perch to spiral gracefully downward.</description>
    <position x="260" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go forest trail" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>A haunting shadow, perhaps the spirit of some child lost long ago to the forest, lingers in the area.  Leaves rustle, their bleak hues perhaps a shade lighter than they should be.  The dark skins of the ironwoods glimmer sullenly with the sheen of a thousand dew drops.</description>
    <position x="260" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel">
    <description>A cracked rock lies near the roadside, large and wide enough for a weary traveler to rest their heated pace.  Its edges are smooth, the roughness of the stone worn away by countless passersby who have all made their small, if indelible, impression upon it.</description>
    <description>The night's blackness washes over a cracked, broken rock to the side of the road.  Beneath the twinkling stars, the path stretches to the north and south, moving on despite the shadowed skies above.</description>
    <position x="280" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The road twists and winds southward, the density of trees becoming sparse and thin as the frequency of travel picks up.  The Deobar Bower Gate to the north peeks quietly over the dark ironwood trees clustering around Leth Deriel.</description>
    <position x="300" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Southern Trade Route, Esouvar Deriel" note="Map61_Leth_Deriel.xml|Leth Deriel">
    <description>Smooth flagstones line the dusky-red soil of the road.  Bright yellow flowers peek from around dark patches of green moss, their tones falling gently over the sparse earth like abandoned drops of sunlight.</description>
    <description>Patches of night shadow the flagstones of the road.  Their darkness blots over and dims the bright yellow of the delicate flowers nearby.</description>
    <position x="300" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Silhouette Forest, Near the Southern Trade Route" note="Map63_Oshu'ehhrsk_Manor.xml|Oshu'ehhrsk_Manor">
    <description>The distant sounds of travelers and caravans moving along the trade routes is muffled further by the dense vegetation that closes in upon the trail.  Not only is the aural sense dulled by the heavy cloak of plant life, but visibility is hindered beyond a stone's throw by layers of interposing leaves and branches.  Even looking above, the canopy of mingling limbs and outstretched trees blocks a fully clear view of the sky.</description>
    <position x="240" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Tamsine's Rest, Outside Gate">
    <description>Carved jasper cats stand sentinal atop the massive stone pillars on either side of a wrought iron gate.  A bronze plaque on the wall identifies this as the home of the abbey of Tamsine's Rest, a well-known school near Leth Deriel.  Just beyond the gate, a two-story stone gate house stands guard over the path leading up to the school, while a trail leads east, following a stream that runs through the forest toward the trade route.</description>
    <position x="80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go forest trail" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wrought-iron gate" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Tamsine's Rest, Gate House" note="Gate House">
    <description>A small stone house guards the wrought-iron gates of the abbey.  At one time, this was the home of the gatekeeper, in the long ago days before al'Tresnith Manor became the abbey of Tamsine's Rest.  Now, according to the wooden sign next to the house, it is the home of Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el.  A white gravelled path leads north toward the abbey gardens.</description>
    <position x="60" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate house" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravelled path" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wrought-iron gate" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Entry" note="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el">
    <description>White walls and mirrors reflect the light from the candles upon the tables on either side of the entryway, making the small foyer appear larger.  A dark oak stairway leads to the second floor, while an archway on the eastern wall leads to the gentlemen's and travelers clothing rooms, and a sliding oak door leads west into the women's apparel section.  Upon the wall, a sign directs visitors to the various areas of the shop.</description>
    <position x="20" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak doors" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak staircase" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Clerical Supplies" note="Clerical Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Tucked away in a corner under the stairs is a small counter displaying robes, vestments, altar cloths and other embroidered clerical accessories.  From its perch atop an ornate newel post, a tabby cat carved of lunat wood surveys the hall, just one of the many symbols of the gentle domestic goddess which fill the abbey buildings.  Though crafted of lifeless wood, some minor trick of the artist causes the cat's inquiring eyes to appear to follow all who enter the house.</description>
    <position x="20" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Women's Clothing" note="Women's Clothing" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Vases of roses have been placed upon marble pedestals about the edges of the room, the sweet scent perfuming the air and the clothing on display.  Trevellyn's offers an ever-changing supply of fine garments, crafted by the students of the Abbey of Tamsine's Rest.</description>
    <position x="0" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak doors" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Bridal Fashions" note="Bridal Fashions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Elven seamstresses bustle about, carrying bolts of fabric, fragile lace and fragrant flower petals.  In one corner, a dressmaker's dummy is swathed in yard after yard of creamy silk, held in place by pins.  A padded bench has been placed beneath a lattice arch, forming a small and cozy alcove where customers may sit and chat while they examine the merchandise.</description>
    <position x="0" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white curtain" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Travel Fashions" note="Travel Fashions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A row of diamond-paned windows lines the outer wall, offering a view of the abbey in the distance.  Nearby, a group of mannequins have been arranged to display a selection of cloaks, coats and jackets suitable for both men and women.  Boots and other footwear are neatly stacked on the dark oak shelves which line the inner wall of the room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Gentlemen's Attire" note="Gentlemen's Attire" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Wicker mannequins are grouped about a polished rosewood table on the far end of the room.  Despite the lack of features, the arrangement has an air of genial conviviality, reinforced by the formal clothing dressing the mannequins and the red-stemmed champagne glasses upon the small rosewood occasional table.  A workbasket and half-finished jacket lie upon a chair in the corner, waiting for the tailor to return and finish his work.</description>
    <position x="40" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Upstairs Hallway">
    <description>Deep blue velvet hangs in graceful folds along the wall at the top of the stairs, forming a backdrop for an arrangement of flowers from the abbey gardens.  The pale yellow roses nestle amidst deep green ferns in a sparkling crystal vase.  To the east, a brass plaque has been mounted on a heavy oak door, while the upstairs hallway continues to the south.</description>
    <position x="20" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak staircase" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Upstairs Hallway">
    <description>Stained glass shimmers in the sunlight, the colorful glass window refracting the light to send it dancing about the hallway.  A gleaming brass plaque has been mounted upon the wall next to a heavy oak door, while the hallway continues to the north.</description>
    <description>A crystal vase filled with pale blue sirese blossoms sits atop a polished satinwood table at the southern end of the hallway.  Above it, the gentle glow of the moon illuminates a stained glass window, and reflects off the gleaming brass plaque mounted on the wall beside the oak door.</description>
    <position x="20" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Fine Jewelry" note="Fine Jewelry" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sparkling crystal boxes line the walls of the room, displaying an array of jewelry to delight the eye and adorn the wearer.  A velvet-lined tray and ebonwood case sit atop one of the displays, holding several lovely rings.  On the back wall, a parchment sign hangs beside an arch leading to another room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow arch" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Jeweler's Workroom" note="Jeweler's Workroom|Workroom">
    <description>There is no sparkling crystal, nor glittering gems on display in this tiny back room.  Only a heat-scarred wooden workbench and a stool line the walls, along with a locked safe to store gems and precious metals until needed.</description>
    <position x="60" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow arch" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, Party Planning" note="Party Planning" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Festive garlands of ivy and pale blue silk sirese blossoms hang in shallow scallops along the top of the walls and counter.  Garlands strung from the corners of the room meet in the center where they are tied with a colorful bow above a sparkling crystal wind chime.  Beneath the garlands, paintings on the walls show some of the different sites available for a party, while a sign on the back wall offers a list of services.</description>
    <position x="40" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Tamsine's Rest, Gravel Path">
    <description>The gravel path wends its way north from the gates of the grounds, passing through a thickly wooded area.  From the splashing sounds to the east, there must be a stream somewhere nearby -- but the dense underbrush forces the traveler to remain on the shady path.</description>
    <position x="60" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Tamsine's Rest, Lawn" note="Tamsine's Rest">
    <description>The Abbey of Tamsine's Rest stands atop a small rise to the north, the stark lines of the red brick manor house softened by time and the thick tangle of ivy.  Once, the manor was home to the al'Tresnith family, but for many years now it has been a school, instructing first the daughters of landed nobility and now those of humble birth in the domestic skills so beloved by the gentle goddess, Tamsine.</description>
    <position x="60" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Tamsine's Rest, Topiary Garden" note="Topiary Garden">
    <description>A flowering willow sways in the wind, scattering delicate small white petals along the smooth green lawn.  Living statues, sculpted of yew, are posed at various points in this section of the garden.  Beneath the flowering fronds of the willow tree, a topiary pegasus stretches its wings, pawing the earth with one dainty green hoof.  A topiary unicorn stands with head lowered, as if cropping at the crimson roses which grow near a gap in the boxwood hedge.</description>
    <position x="40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Tamsine's Rest, West Lawn">
    <description>Along the western lawn, a topiary gryphon has been sculpted to lie sleepily curled up in the shade of an ancient flame maple tree.  The artist who created her imparted a sense of wonder, from the horn beak, to her wings, outstretched protectively to shelter a tiny yew gryphonette.  Each gentle breeze which flows across the lawn ruffles the yew feathers of her wing, giving life to the graceful sculpture.</description>
    <position x="20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Tamsine's Rest, Knot Garden" note="Knot Garden">
    <description>Low boxwood hedges have been carefully trimmed into precise geometric patterns in this tiny knot garden behind the abbey.  White gravel crunches underfoot as you move along the paths which wend their way through the hedges.  The paths wind about in all directions, yet all finally lead toward a central medallion, an intricate knot of roses surrounding a white marble statue of the goddess Albreda, holding a dove on her outstretched hand.</description>
    <position x="20" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Tamsine's Rest, North Lawn">
    <description>Sunlight casts a warm glow across the dark green lawn.  Near the house, primroses and sirese blossoms grow in cheerful profusion.  A tall hedge borders the northern end of the lawn, towering higher than any Wind Elf.  Dim shadows fill the hedge, flickering amidst the tangled mass of boxwood, as though some unseen being stalked within the shadowy maze.</description>
    <description>Shadows fall at odd angles across the dark green lawn.  Near the abbey walls, sirese blossoms seem to glow softly in the moonlight.  A tall hedge borders the northern end of the lawn, towering higher than any Wind Elf.  Dim shadows fill the hedge, flickering within the tangled mass of boxwood as though some unseen being stalked within the shadowy maze.</description>
    <position x="40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hedge" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Tamsine's Rest, Herb Gardens" note="Herb Gardens">
    <description>Brick walkways, laid out in a herringbone pattern, criss-cross the walled kitchen garden at the back of the Abbey.  The garden, originally planned by Meralla al'Tresnith, the founder of the abbey, maintains a balance between fresh vegetables and neatly tended beds of herbs.  At the center of the garden is a sprawling patch of catnip surrounding a statue of the gentle goddess Tamsine seated at her spinning wheel.</description>
    <position x="80" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Tamsine's Rest, Formal Garden" note="Formal Garden">
    <description>Pale pink and yellow roses cling to the weathered brick wall which shelters the tiny rose garden at the rear of the abbey, their soft colors contrasting with the rust-colored bricks and the deep green moss which grows along the mortar lines.  At the center of the garden, vivid crimson climbing roses twine about the white latticework of a charming gazebo.</description>
    <position x="100" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lattice gazebo" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Tamsine's Rest, East Lawn">
    <description>A soft carpet of green grass rolls down the incline from the manor house along the eastern lawn.  Goats browse along the narrow stream, cropping the grass and providing milk for the school's cooking classes.  A weathered bridge spans the stream, leading away from the spacious lawn to a path into the woods on the other side.  Beside the stream, yellow-bearded irises gently sway in the breeze.</description>
    <position x="100" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden bridge" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Tamsine's Rest, Beside a Stream">
    <description>A stream babbles along the border of the east lawn, the water sparkling in the pale sunlight as it tumbles over the rocky bed.  Beside the stream, a wrought iron bench stands beneath a large willow tree, whose pale green fronds reach protectively down to the ground and drift along in the water's current.</description>
    <description>A stream babbles along the border of the east lawn, the water sparkling in the pale light of Elanthia's moons as it tumbles over the rocky bed.  Beside the stream, a wrought iron bench stands beneath a large willow tree, whose pale green fronds reach protectively down to the ground and drift along in the water's current.</description>
    <position x="80" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Tamsine's Rest, Wooden Bridge" note="Wooden Bridge">
    <description>Water tumbles with a lyrical rhythm over the rocky streambed beneath the whitewashed wooden bridge.  Droplets of water glitter like diamonds from spiderwebs spun amidst the deep green ferns which line the banks of the stream.  In the distance, a stately manor sprawls atop a grassy hillside with a contented aura.</description>
    <position x="120" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Tamsine's Rest, Wooded Path">
    <description>Pale yellow beards decorate the throats of the purple and white irises growing along the edge of the stream.  The flowers nod and bob with each passing breeze as if participating in a stately dance along the border of the white gravel path.  Downstream, a gnarled willow tree can be glimpsed just around a bend, its pale green fronds gently floating in the current.</description>
    <position x="140" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden bridge" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Tamsine's Rest, Wooded Path">
    <description>A nightingale sings from a perch on the branch of a moss-covered oak, its music echoing throughout the forest.  Ropy strands of maiden's tresses fall in tangled masses from the tree limbs to form a natural curtain screening a small clearing to the south.  The thick green strands reflect the light, lending a misty greenish tinge to the white gravel path.</description>
    <position x="160" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small clearing" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Tamsine's Rest, Lake Shore" note="Lake Shore">
    <description>The path leads to the southern shore of the sacred lake of Ilkas Veridun, the Mirror Lake.  Near the shore, the island of Ailaeteorn floats on the lake's surface like an emerald set in a gleaming silver crown.  Legend holds that the waters of the lake, when used by one of pure heart and spirit, can raise the dead.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Tamsine's Rest, Wooded Clearing">
    <description>A tangled curtain of maiden's tresses fall from the branches of the trees which surround this tiny clearing, while velvety soft moss carpets the floor.  The sweet song of a nightingale blends with the distant murmur of a stream to the west, forming a simple symphony to delight listeners.</description>
    <position x="140" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooded path" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Rose-covered Gazebo" note="Gazebo">
    <description>The tiny octagonal gazebo is surrounded by fragrant crimson climbing roses which twine their way along the lattice sides.  A wide bench swing hangs from the ceiling, swaying back and forth in a gentle breeze.  Nearby, you can hear goats bleating somewhere on the abbey grounds.</description>
    <position x="80" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Boxwood Maze, Entrance">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="120" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="60" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Boxwood Maze, Center">
    <description>Hidden deep within the maze is a rocky grotto, cool and moist.  Spiders spin their webs undisturbed at the base of a bronze statue of a grotesque crone, poised with two gleaming swords against a silver lightning bolt.  A tiny garden flourishes in the dim green light, filled with lacy white hemlock, bobbing purple monkshood and scarlet nightshade blossoms.  The beauty of the delicate flowers belies their poisonous nature.</description>
    <position x="40" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="20" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="0" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Boxwood Maze">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  That, combined with the twisting turns of the passages, make it difficult to keep your bearings as you wander through the maze.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Boxwood Maze, Dead End">
    <description>Tunnels have been carved within a tall hedge of boxwood.  The green branches cover the roof of the tunnel, allowing little light to filter through.  A shallow niche has been carved in the boxwood here at the end of one of the many false passages of the maze.  You've no choice but to retrace your steps and try again.</description>
    <position x="0" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Guard House" note="Clerk" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Sparse and comfortless, this guard house appears to have been either abandoned or forgotten.  A very fine layer of dust covers the stone benches and table that flow up out of the floor, and the bedding in the stone boxbed has rotted away to tatters that seem ready to decay if they are so much as stared at too hard.</description>
    <position x="440" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Chasm, Vertical Pothole" note="Map65_Under_the_Gondola.xml|Undergondola">
    <description>A stand of tall trees comes into view overhead, further dimming the light and making it increasingly difficult to find a foothold up through the pothole.  Caution is absolutely necessary to prevent a case of vertigo from settling in and overwhelming the senses.</description>
    <position x="440" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb branch" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Garrison Tent, Entrance">
    <description>Roughly circular, the garrison tent has a tall central post and eight shorter perimeter posts supporting its structure.  Guards, alert for trouble and weapons ready, are stationed at regular intervals along the canvas walls.  Two soldiers guard the aisle leading to several rows of benches.  A single tent flap at one end leads out.  There is a small table offering basic refreshment: black coffee and hard-crusted bread.</description>
    <position x="500" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Ice Cave, Hidden Passage">
    <description>The slick, icy surface of the dark passage makes it difficult to gain purchase.  The walls close in tightly and the ceiling presses down, an unspoken reminder of the scarcity of fresh air.</description>
    <position x="220" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Ice Cave, Frozen Falls">
    <description>An icefall flows in frozen beauty, ending in a large patch at the rear of this cave.  Low ledges littered with small bones and ancient firepits abound along the perimeter.  The faint outline of an opening is barely visible above the icefall.</description>
    <position x="240" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb small opening" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Ice Cave, Forgotten Chambers">
    <description>Visible in the dim light, a pile of refuse consisting of broken bones, charred branches and shattered icicles covers most of the floor of the cave.  The wall behind the refuse pile has crudely carved handholds rimmed in frost leading upward to a deep icy ledge near the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="260" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb small opening" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Ice Cave, Forgotten Chambers">
    <description>A rockslide has strewn small pieces of frozen rubble across the slippery ice surface of the ledge.  Just beyond the rockslide, a huge frost-encrusted slab leans precariously against the pile of debris, held in place by the rather dubious structural support of a series of icicles which anchor it to the wall.  If you could get up there, the narrow gap between the wall and the top of the slab looks like it's just wide enough to slip through. </description>
    <position x="280" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb slab" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb frost handholds" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Ice Cave, Forgotten Chambers">
    <description>A bitter cold that chills the bones grips all who enter this smaller cavern.  The walls are slick with ice which covers and obscures ancient markings to the point of making them non-decipherable, and the floor is smooth and free of debris.  A path of scrape marks mar the floor, leading to a large block of stone at the far end of the chamber.</description>
    <position x="300" y="620" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb jagged crack" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="The Frozen Heavens, Silent Ascent">
    <description>Deep banks of snow choke the steep, narrow passage.  The surroundings are unnaturally still and perfectly soundless the ceaseless howling of the wind below conspicuously absent.  A tiny assortment of stunted trees and shrubs struggle to survive against all odds.</description>
    <position x="220" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="rt east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="rt west" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="The Frozen Heavens, Silent Ascent">
    <description>Deep banks of snow choke the steep, narrow passage.  The surroundings are unnaturally still and perfectly soundless the ceaseless howling of the wind below conspicuously absent.  Shimmering ice crystals float effortlessly above the hoar frost.</description>
    <position x="200" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="rt east" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="rt southwest" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="The Frozen Heavens, Silent Ascent">
    <description>Deep banks of snow choke the steep, narrow passage.  The surroundings are unnaturally still and perfectly soundless the ceaseless howling of the wind below conspicuously absent.  Shimmering ice crystals float effortlessly above the hoar frost, and an aberrant chill seeps through air.</description>
    <position x="170" y="430" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="rt southwest" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="The Frozen Heavens, Silent Ascent" note="Nimbuses">
    <description>Deep banks of snow choke the steep, narrow passage.  The surroundings are unnaturally still and perfectly soundless the ceaseless howling of the wind below conspicuously absent.  Shimmering ice crystals hang effortlessly in the air, shimmering like a field of stars.</description>
    <description>Deep banks of snow choke the steep, narrow passage.  The surroundings are unnaturally still and perfectly soundless the ceaseless howling of the wind below conspicuously absent.  Shimmering ice crystals hang effortlessly in the air, sparkling in the daylight.</description>
    <position x="140" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="east" move="rt east" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="160" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go snow-choked passage" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="160" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb icy cliff" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="180" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="160" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="140" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="140" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.  Irregular flickers of light dance from the darkened entrance of a cave to the east.</description>
    <position x="140" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="The Frozen Heavens, Unfathomable Grotto" note="Obelisk|mine" color="#993300">
    <description>Chunks of obsidian hang in the air, some as large as a Gor'Tog's fist.  Exactly centered in the chamber is a translucent obelisk of roughly Human height that leans at an impossible angle.</description>
    <position x="180" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="The Frozen Heavens, Unfathomable Grotto" color="#993300">
    <description>The obsidian walls of the cave are absolutely smooth, and form a mathematically perfect arc above.  Tiny flecks of ice float in from the mouth of the cave, gracefully swirling about in an otherworldly dance.</description>
    <position x="160" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="The Frozen Heavens, Tranquil Tundra">
    <description>Flakes of snow and ice crystals casually float by in abject defiance of both gravity and the still air as any trace of warmth is quickly extinguished.</description>
    <position x="120" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="The Frozen Heavens, Lifeless Ascent">
    <description>Scarce handholds are offered by tiny juts of obsidian for those who wish to brave the upward climb, while occasional fissures in the sheer ice wall offer scant footing for a careful retreat from the icy ascent.</description>
    <position x="192" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb obsidian" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fissures" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="The Frozen Heavens, Lifeless Ascent">
    <description>The occasional fissure in the sheer ice wall offers a precarious purchase for those who wish to brave the upward climb, while scant juts of obsidian offer just enough footing for a careful retreat from the icy ascent.</description>
    <position x="192" y="540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb obsidian" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fissures" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, The Bridal Blush" note="Bridal Blush" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaily decorated with silk flowers and yard upon yard of lace and tulle, the brilliant white walls exhibit a wide variety of wedding attire and accessories.  Brides-to-be cluster around the wares, commenting on the trendiest fashions for their own fairytale weddings.</description>
    <position x="20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white curtain" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, The Bridal Blush" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Small mirrors are mounted on mahogany counters to showcase the glittering jewelry under the watchful eyes of well-groomed guards.  Stationed around the room are broad displays of wedding rings, and a parchment sign is mounted against the far wall.</description>
    <position x="20" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, The Bridal Blush">
    <description>Plush couches dyed a pale gold hue are scattered about the room, plump pillows atop them.  Vases of roses in many hues grace tall mahogany pillars, filling the air with their sweet fragrance.</description>
    <position x="10" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tulle curtain" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el, The Bridal Blush">
    <description>Bolts of fabric are piled high on a sturdy table, many in differing shades of white and ivory.  A small workbench is piled high with a seamstress's tools -- spools of thread, differently sized needles, a hedgehog-shaped pincushion, and the like.  An elaborately carved mahogany screen sits to one side of the room, allowing for a client's modesty during fittings.</description>
    <position x="0" y="250" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tulle curtain" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Woodland Path, Brambles">
    <description>Thick brambles almost completely obscure the pathway, the runners twisting across the ground in a mesh of thorny vines.  Trunks loom above the massed heaps of foliage.  The air feels oppressive, almost as if it has physical weight.</description>
    <position x="500" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowy opening" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Woodland Path, Brambles">
    <description>Rustling sounds echo from the brambles although nothing can be seen except a few shaking leaves.  The thorny bushes have almost completely covered what was once a wide pathway through the woods.  Now all that is left is a twisting trail that soon will be engulfed by the forest.</description>
    <position x="520" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Woodland Path, Thorny Track">
    <description>The forest clears out a bit, allowing a gap in the tree cover that provides a glimpse of sky overhead.  Attached to one tree is a weathered plank with one lone nail still keeping it affixed.  Occasional sounds of running water can be heard in the distance, but the echoes within the trees prevent any idea of where they are coming from.</description>
    <position x="520" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Woodland Path, Thorny Track">
    <description>Gurgling sounds come from the west, perhaps from a stream or spring hidden within the dense forest.  The thorn bushes crowd close to the narrow track, grabbing at passersby almost as if they were alive and wanted to keep intruders out.</description>
    <position x="500" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Woodland Path, Rutted Crossing">
    <description>What once was a bridge now lies collapsed across the stream, the beams and planks providing a slippery but passable crossing of the running stream.  The rotting stumps of the supports stand upright in the water, their lower reaches covered with moss that grows in the spray of the brook.</description>
    <position x="480" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Woodland Path, Before the Gateway">
    <description>Crumbling stone walls end at a gateway inset into the dilapidated enclosure.  Formed from wrought iron bars set upright within a frame, the two panels of the gate have fallen off their hinges and lean drunkenly against the arched gateway.  The gaping space thus formed allows access into the courtyard beyond, while further progress on the pathway is blocked by a wall of thorn bushes.</description>
    <position x="480" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Tref Dinta, Courtyard">
    <description>Weeds push through the cobbles of the courtyard which lies within the enclosing stone walls.  An arched gateway pierces the enclosure, allowing egress through the ramparts.  Two gate panels lie off their hinges in the gateway, leaning against the walls like drunken soldiers sleeping off a late night drinking bout.  The grass-choked yard stretches to the west and north, while a tower rises to the northwest.</description>
    <position x="480" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Tref Dinta, Courtyard">
    <description>A wooden stable stands in the northern section of the courtyard, its still sturdy doors barred and locked against intrusion.  The closed window shutters likewise prevent all entry.  An occasional rustle or other sound comes forth from within, but no way of access can be discerned.</description>
    <position x="480" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Tref Dinta, Courtyard">
    <description>Looming over the courtyard, a tall stone tower stands majestic and forlorn.  A few stones have begun to crumble, but the structure is still mainly intact and in good shape.  The wooden doorway into the keep is covered with thick iron bands and is mostly closed, although a small gap could allow entry for adventurers eager to see what lies within.</description>
    <position x="460" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gap" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Main Floor, Entry">
    <description>Tumbled stones litter the entryway floor, fallen from the circular staircase that once led into the upper reaches of the structure.  Now the stairs end abruptly halfway up the wall although a gaping hole in the ceiling allows glimpses of the darkened spaces above.  Piles of dirt and debris brought in from the cracked doorway lie heaped in the corners.  Arches to the north and west offer further access to the building.</description>
    <position x="440" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doorway" destination="188" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Main Floor, Library">
    <description>Shelves once lined the walls, but now only a few supports and boards still cling to the walls.  Miraculously, a couple of volumes still stand upright on some of the upper reaches, their spines dusty and covered with cobwebs.  Slime-covered trails snake across the floor, circling around a large pile that perhaps was once a desk, but is now just a heap of wooden scraps.</description>
    <position x="440" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Main Floor, Pantry">
    <description>Odors of rot and decay overwhelm the senses, causing the eyes to water and the stomach to churn.  The noxious smells emanate from the corners where remains of various barrels and boxes spill their decomposing contents onto the wooden floor.</description>
    <position x="440" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Main Floor, Kitchen">
    <description>Standing against one wall is a long table that ends at a metal sink.  Amazingly, both are still intact, although covered with dust and grime.  A pump with a water spout perches on the edge of the sink, its handle halfway raised as if some kitchen maid was interrupted in mid-use and never returned to their task.  Opposite the sink is a circular opening leading to a staircase descending into the cellar.</description>
    <position x="420" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Main Floor, Parlor">
    <description>Bits of wallpaper still cling to a few spots, but most of the walls are now bare stone with a some crumbling masonry between the blocks.  Piles of splintered wood and decaying fabric mark where once splendid furniture stood gleaming.  Belying the general air of decay, there are long trails through the dust on the floors, giving evidence that something still stirs within the tower.</description>
    <position x="420" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Main Floor, Dining Room">
    <description>Half of an enormous dining table lies canted on the floor, the rest of it lying in pieces and splinters around it on the scarred floorboards.  A few pieces of broken pottery are heaped in the corner, perhaps the last remnants of a long-decayed sideboard.</description>
    <position x="420" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Cellar">
    <description>Vaulted ceilings of cut stone blocks loom overhead in the gloomy depths of the basement.  A long trail of slime twists through the dust and dirt on the floor, moving through the area and deeper into the cellar.  The broad steps of the circular staircase lead upwards towards the upper floors and escape from the dismal dank of the basement.</description>
    <position x="440" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Cellar">
    <description>Heaps of coal lie abandoned here, spilling out from the rotting remains of large wooden bins.  Unlike most of the rest of the cellar contents, the coal lumps have not begun to disintegrate.  Dark dust from the coal mingles with dirt to hide the nature of the flooring underfoot.</description>
    <position x="440" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Cellar">
    <description>Mysterious slime trails trace through the dust-covered floor, criss-crossing in wild abandon.  Little else remains in this corner of the cellar, just a few splinters of wood and piles of dirt to mark where stored items once stood.</description>
    <position x="420" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Cellar">
    <description>A shelf holding casks has collapsed and spilled its contents across the floor.  Many of the containers broke up and the sticky residue from them mixes with the dust to create a gummy gunk on the floor that clings to footwear.  The very faint odor of vinegar permeates the area, further identifying the cask's contents as wine.  A single mage light high above provides fitful illumination for the area, beating back the dark gloom of the cellar.</description>
    <position x="420" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Kruar Li Dael, Clearing">
    <description>Short juniper and cedar hunker in snowdrifts, wind whipped but reaching for the available light.  Several pathways through the snow suggest heavy traffic, though the tracks are unclear.</description>
    <position x="300" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="209" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go passage" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Kruar Li Dael, Clearing">
    <description>Sparse trees provide a poor windbreak, resulting in frequent icy gusts tearing across the area.  The ground is swept clean of snow, and the bare dirt is smooth and even.</description>
    <position x="320" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Kruar Li Dael, Clearing">
    <description>A pair of trees stands to the southwest, their surface roots cleanly pruned back.  Oval pebbles are scattered in radiating lines emanating from the east and southeast.</description>
    <position x="340" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Kruar Li Dael, Clearing">
    <description>All flora has been stripped from the area, and the ground is covered in oval pebbles, tightly packed in an intricate mosaic.  To the east, several large boulders block further passage.</description>
    <position x="360" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Kruar Li Dael, Clearing">
    <description>A line of birch and pine marks the southern boundary of the clearing providing a partial windbreak.  The ground is littered with oval pebbles, but is otherwise clean of debris.</description>
    <position x="340" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Kruar Li Dael, Clearing">
    <description>A lone aspen rises from the south and the ground is covered in oval pebbles, tightly packed in an intricate mosaic.  To the east, several large boulders block further passage, fine columnar red crystals growing between the gaps in the rocky wall.</description>
    <description>A lone aspen rises from the south and the ground is covered in oval pebbles, tightly packed in an intricate mosaic.  To the east, several large boulders form a rocky wall, interspersed with fine columnar red crystals.</description>
    <position x="360" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow gap" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="A Small Cottage, Cherry Trees">
    <description>Rows upon rows of cherry trees surround a small alcove within their midst.  Some wood-slatted chairs and a polished white ironwood table, low to the ground, provides a place to have a nice picnic, or to lie back and relax.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Kruar Li Dael, Circular Valley">
    <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing.  Despite the proximity to the forest, there is no sound of wildlife, and no birds seem to fly nearby or overhead.</description>
  <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, glowing with a soft, periodic pulsation, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing, gently illuminating the area.  Despite the proximity to the forest, there is no sound of wildlife, and no bats seem to fly nearby or overhead.</description>
    <position x="360" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gap" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Kruar Li Dael, Circular Valley">
    <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing.  To the north rises a squat rocky hill, a smooth semi-circle demarking the clearing carved cleanly into the rock face.</description>
  <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, glowing with a soft, periodic pulsation, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing, gently illuminating the area.  To the north rises a squat rocky hill, a smooth, glowing, semi-circle demarking the clearing carved cleanly into the rock face.</description>
    <position x="380" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Kruar Li Dael, Circular Valley">
    <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing.  The view east is blocked by a wall of neatly stacked boulders, fit together with stunning precision.</description>
  <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, glowing with a soft, periodic pulsation, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing, gently illuminating the area.  The view east is blocked by a wall of neatly stacked boulders, fit together with stunning precision.</description>
    <position x="400" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Kruar Li Dael, Circular Valley">
    <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing.  A particularly convoluted and concentrated portion of the mosiac extends from the north, appearing to point south.</description>
    <description>Picked clean of all flora and fauna, a smooth trabe crystal mosiac lines the ground, glowing with a soft, periodic pulsation, delineating a series of whorls and forms in a clean arc.  The pattern continues in a broad arc around the clearing, gently illuminating the area.  A particularly convoluted and concentrated portion of the glowing mosiac extends from the north, appearing to point south.</description>
    <position x="380" y="520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Kruar Li Dael, Center of the Mosaic">
    <description>Centered over the crystal mosaic, the full pattern is easier to view.  Nested and overlapping geometric forms radiate outward, strung along a fractal spiral.  Lacking any identifiable symmetry, the mosiac blends smooth organic whorls with exacting circles and triangles, and bears several large features that point south.  A chill wafts upward, and the air feels thin.</description>
    <description>Centered over the glowing crystal mosaic, the full pattern is easier to view.  Nested and overlapping geometric forms radiate outward, strung along a fractal spiral.  Lacking any identifiable symmetry, the mosiac blends smooth organic whorls with exacting circles and triangles, and bears several large features that point south.  Light pulses from the center of the mosaic and radiates outward along the diagrams in a mesmerizing sequence.  A chill wafts upward, and the air feels thin.</description>
    <position x="380" y="500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <label text="to Shard">
    <position x="430" y="480" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Oshu'ehhrsk Manor">
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Leth Deriel">
    <position x="310" y="0" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Snowbeasts">
    <position x="270" y="510" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Trevellyn's of Leth Deri'el">
    <position x="0" y="345" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tasmine's Rest">
    <position x="18" y="150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Boxwood Maze">
    <position x="70" y="10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="A">
    <position x="20" y="460" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="A">
    <position x="360" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="B">
    <position x="530" y="160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="B">
    <position x="40" y="490" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="To Undergondola">
    <position x="450" y="430" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Gash">
    <position x="290" y="390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ice Cave">
    <position x="240" y="600" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gondola">
    <position x="430" y="470" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Nimbuses">
    <position x="130" y="550" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zoluren">
    <position x="370" y="330" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ilithi">
    <position x="370" y="350" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="-------------------">
    <position x="370" y="340" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gigantic Lachmates">
    <position x="390" y="80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crauyarin">
    <position x="310" y="430" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Scuttlers">
    <position x="310" y="440" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Avtalia">
    <position x="360" y="520" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Scuttlers">
    <position x="360" y="530" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>