<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Crossing North Gate" id="6">
  <node id="1" name="North Turnpike, Forest" color="#008000">
    <description>Dirt gradually replaces the remaining pavement stones to form a rutted earthen track.  The sweet smell of rotting leaves and pine needles wafts from the surrounding woods.  The road breaks through the forest, bending to the northeast towards open meadow and farmland.</description>
    <position x="180" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="North Turnpike, Meadow" color="#008000">
    <description>Clumps of tiny wild flowers hug the dirt road as it winds through the meadow.  Towards the northwest, rippling hills cloaked with greenish-brown fields and a large monastery are visible in the distance.</description>
    <position x="200" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="North Turnpike, Grassland">
    <description>The scent of rotting vegetation rises from a cut by the road where loose rocks and stones mix with the weeds to mark the start of a small gully.  To the right of the road, a small herd of cows rests beneath a large oak tree as they chew their cuds and watch a spirited calf chase a butterfly fluttering across the pasture.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rain-cut gully" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="North Turnpike, Grassland">
    <description>A passing wind raises little swirls of dust from the deep ruts gouged in the road by heavily laden carts.  Off to one side among the weeds lie some fewmets, too withered to be identified, but a sure sign of game in the area.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>Despite the quiet, travellers have left their mark.  A sparrow pecks at a discarded canteen cover, pulls a thread from it, and flies off -- no doubt to add it to the lining of a nest.  To the northeast, the edge of the monastery's stone wall juts against the road, looming like a bold stroke drawn against the horizon.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="North Turnpike, Farmland" note="Necro Guild Entrance" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Spidery vines stretch from the road bank to climb the face of the fence, pausing only at a break in the stones.  Looking through the gap in the wall, row after row of blueberry bushes are visible.  Tatters of white netting sway from the shrubbery's slender branches like wispy shrouds snatched from the wraiths of long dead monks.  The road curves snugly eastward around the stonework.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go broken fence" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="none" move="rt ask monk about monastery;ask monk about monastery" hidden="True" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>As the road bends sharply to the north, an ancient campsite is just visible through the trees.  The wind has scattered the long-cold ashes from the confines of the stone fire ring, and gnarled tree roots embrace the handle of a rusty pick.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>The road continues northward, embracing the edge of the monastery's fence.  Fields of green and gold stretch from the opposite side of the road, their rich stands of grain rippling beneath the soft touch of the breeze.  Barely visible lines betray the presence of paths between the fields.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go village gate" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>The monastery wall, blank as a blind giant, continues along the road, its unbroken expanse at once teasing and forbidding, concealing who knows what mysteries behind it.  Birds settle on the wall with avian unconcern and arise from it to feed in the fields across the road.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>The monastery's stone wall edges away from the road to follow its own meandering course.  A farmer, hardly more than a dot in the distance, leads a dray horse pulling a cart through the fields.  Northward, the skeleton of an old farmstead lies partially buried in weeds and grass.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>As the road winds by the farmhouse, piles of grey stones, nearly swallowed by grass, trace the foundation of the farmhouse.  Some abandoned farming equipment sits rusting near the edge of an overgrown field.  A dull red stack of splintered planking set between the ruins and field marks the site of what was once a barn.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>Fields stretch away from the road, some fallow, others filled with sun-colored wheat and strong green stalks of corn.  Beyond the fields to the west, the monastery's buildings and stone-enclosed walls parallel the road.  To the southwest lie the scattered ruins of an old farmstead.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>Stone gives way to ruddy brick where the field-fencing wall adjoins the high walls enclosing the monastery complex.  A reddish patch on the monastery wall resolves into a bricked-up doorway.  At just about human eye-level, one of the bricks protrudes noticeably from the rest.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>The road wends close to the monastery, where ivy leaves soften the gray walls, dappling the stone with their color and shadow.  To the other side of the turnpike, fields ascend and descend gently rolling hills, their furrows lending an odd texture to the contours of the land.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>To the southwest the stone wall curves around the building complex, stretching in an unbroken expanse westward.  A tower at the corner of the monastery looms high into the air, overlooking the turning road, its travelers, and the fields beyond with a stony impartiality.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="North Turnpike, Meadow">
    <description>The grey bulk of a monastery rises to the south, an obvious landmark on the route. Cultivated fields surround it to both sides of the road, the checkered browns, yellows, and soft greens of the fields arranged in this landscape with a natural grace that any artist would envy.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="North Turnpike, Washed Out Bridge">
    <description>A rotted wooden bridge partially spans a drying stream bed. The bridge footings descend into a mix of lush cattails and creekbroom -- a hint that some water remains.  Towards the center of the bridge, the planking has broken, leaving the bridge nearly impassable.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden bridge" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Gravel Path">
    <description>A wall of tall boxwoods lines the gravel path leading toward a squat, square brick building.  The roof of a gatekeeper's cottage pokes above the line of shrubbery, and a few stray weeds huddle below the neatly clipped hedges.  The grey chipped stones are precise in their course, like a river of rock, flowing toward two wrought iron gates set into an imposing brick archway straddling the gravel path.</description>
    <position x="220" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wrought gates" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Northwall Trail, Grassland">
    <description>A narrow trail, either cut or worn through grasses waist-high on a stout elf, winds northeast from the turnpike that rumbles with traffic.  The calls of caravan drivers hurrying their animals along can be heard from the road, while the quietude of the flatlands offers no such command but the whispering of the wind through the grass.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Northwall Trail, Grassland">
    <description>As you move through the green-gold waves of tall grass, barley and dogbane, small burrs catch on your clothing like the hands of a child vying for attention.  The gilded spires and slate roofs of the town rise over the grey stone wall to the south.</description>
    <description>As you move through the fragrant waves of grasses, small burrs catch on your clothing like the small hands of a child vying for attention.  The warm glow of the town rises in the night sky just above the horizon to the south.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Northwall Trail, Grassland">
    <description>The relentless winds bend the tall grasses in submission to the wide sky.  Birds of prey soar effortlessly far above and cry out as they pass, some landing in a copse of birch trees to the northeast.</description>
    <description>The winds skim through the tall grasses, whispering secrets to the constellations floating in the night sky.  A copse of birch trees rises to the northeast like a pale specter in the darkness.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch copse" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="North Turnpike, Forest" color="#008000">
    <description>Plunging into the woods, the road deteriorates still further into a track of loose stones and cobbles.  Brambles, spike bushes, and poison fern line the edges of the turnpike, forming an impassable barrier to anyone who wished to explore the depths of the forest.</description>
    <position x="180" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crumbling archway" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="North Gate, Gate" note="Map1_Crossing.xml|Crossing|N Gate">
    <description>Nearly forgotten and in disrepair, the North Gate sits untended among a cluster of weeds.  Thorny vines grow unheeded against its crumbling archway, and the decorative carvings along the sides of the arch have long since eroded to impressionistic ridges and gashes.  Deep ruts slicing through the road's surface waylay unwary travelers even in the daylight.</description>
    <description>Nearly forgotten and in disrepair, the North Gate sits untended among a cluster of weeds.  Night's dim light casts shadows among the impressionistic ridges and gashes covering the sides of the arches:  all that erosion has left of once magnificent decorative carvings.  Loose stones scattered across the broken pavement threaten to send unwary travelers sprawling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Brambles">
    <description>The narrow track winds in and out among the brambles.  Its narrowness, along with its meandering path, suggest that it's a game trail, rather than anything built by or meant for people.  There certainly seem to be animals in here somewhere, if the hissing and honking noises coming from beyond the thicket walls are any clue.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="296" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Brambles">
    <description>The ground has been churned up by something.  It's dug and scored and turned over as though some one or some thing were searching for buried treasure.  The dug-up dirt is still dark and moist, so whatever was digging here left not too long ago.  Nearly hidden beneath a bush, the trampled remnant of something whitish is barely visible.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Brambles">
    <description>Something that hasn't bathed in far too long was here just a short time ago.  The pungent odor covers even the spicy scent of the bramble bushes, instilling in one a strong desire to be elsewhere.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Brambles">
    <description>The land rises to the north and east, and the brambles grow thicker.  Some kind of vine with striped green and white leaves spiraling up its length winds its way among the bushes, weaving them into a dense wall.  A squirrel would have a hard time finding a path in that direction, but the tangle of thorns is somewhat less dense in a couple of other places.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Brambles">
    <description>The ground pitches upward to the northeast, and dense, brambly foliage covers the hillside.  The rise is neither steep nor high, but the thickly spined vegetation makes it impossible to climb.  Mounds of thorny bushes grow in lush and painful profusion along the base of the hill as well, except for a narrow game trail which winds along its base.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Brambles">
    <description>A brisk breeze blowing up from the center of the bramble thicket to the southwest brings with it a number of strange sounds -- low hisses are occasionally pierced by outraged honks.  Something is in there, and it's probably not a group of picnickers.  The bushes shiver and rustle, marking the movements of whatever's back there.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Brambles">
    <description>A half-rotted corpse lies on -- and partially in -- the muddy, uneven ground.  One withered arm is stretched out in the direction of the low hill, its bony fingers clutching for a handhold that wasn't there.  Whatever killed it apparently gored it into immobility and then began to feast, beginning with the legs and working its way up.  The spicy scent of the brambles is overpowered by the foul stink of the decaying body, and even the cool breeze blowing up the hill isn't enough to disperse the stench.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Brambles">
    <description>A flowering vine winds its way among the thorny brambles, uncaring of the sharp spines.  Using the bushes as a living trellis, the vine sends its spiraling tendrils twining through the branches and twigs, decorating them with big trumpet-shaped flowers.  Arrowhead-shaped leaves provide a fresh green background for the pink and white striped blossoms.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Brambles">
    <description>The thorns press in close on every side, tall enough to meet overhead where they block out the twinkle of the stars, barring even their dim light from the gloom of the thicket.  Only a couple of dark gaps in the bushes suggest a way out.</description>
    <description>In the bend of the trail there are signs that an animal has passed by here recently, but the bushes are thick and make it difficult to distinguish.  The thorns press in close on every side, even meeting overhead where they block out the blue of the sky and cast a gloomy shade over the thicket.  Only a couple of gaps in the bushes suggest a way out.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Brambles">
    <description>Something has passed this way recently, leaving tracks in the dark, loamy dirt.  Other spoor lie scattered about in the leaf litter covering the ground, and broken branches and shredded leaves indicate that whatever it was wasn't feeling terribly peaceful.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Brambles">
    <description>A stand of berry bushes holds its own on the western side of the track against the press of brambles.  The berries are greenish yellow with light brown veins, about the size of a large grape.  They don't look terribly appetizing, but judging by the stripped branches at the lower levels, something that lives in this thicket finds them yummy.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Brambles">
    <description>Mounds of thorny bushes press in on the narrow trail, leaving barely enough room to pass without getting stuck or scratched.  Rustling sounds occasionally drift by with the breeze, but it's hard to tell where the noises are coming from.  There's something moving around in here, though, just out of sight, behind the greenery.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Brambles">
    <description>The narrow trail winds through the bramble patch, and around a number of trees.  Thorn bushes press hard up against the tree trunks, but the trees are taller and rise up above the underbrush with uncaring dignity.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Brambles">
    <description>A huge boulder rests in a crease between two gentle rises.  The slopes are covered with thick thornbushes, but nothing grows on the boulder except the occasional lichen.  Tall and steep, it looks like a giant's egg resting in a thorny basket.  Deep shadows obscure the niche beneath the lower curve of the boulder, which in any case is too low to put more than a hand into.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Brambles">
    <description>The soft whistle of the cool night breeze blends with the call of nocturnal birds to soften the otherwise stark mood.  The game trail curves from the east to the southwest, paralleling the base of the slope, through a dense thicket of brambles.  Sprays of tall grasses grow in spiky black silhouettes, poking their narrow spears out the tops of the mounded branches.</description>
    <description>The soft sighing of the breeze blends with the chirrup of birds and the humm-buzz of insects to create some rather pleasant background noise.  The game trail curves from the east to the southwest, paralleling the base of the slope, through a dense thicket of brambles.  Tall purple grass grows in sprays here and there in the bushes, poking its narrow spears through the open lattice of the woody branches.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Brambles">
    <description>Mounds of spiny bushes press in from the darkness on all sides, thorn-laden branches reaching in like skeletal fingers, poking and brushing and stinging.  Tiny sounds echo from out of the shadows, rustlings and chirpings and poppings, and now and again a louder honk or crunch.</description>
    <description>Mounds of spiny bushes press in from all sides, thorn-laden branches reaching in like skeletal fingers.  Dusty sunbeams pierce through the branches overhead, illuminating drifting motes and falling leaves, throwing twisted shadows upon the ground.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Brambles, Clearing">
    <description>Gaps of bare dirt in the grass around the oak tree have been smoothed over and patted down.  In one of the larger ones, someone drew a smiling face with a beard and a little round hat, using a stick or perhaps a small finger.  Buttercups grow here and there in the grass, along with a few other flowers.  The brambles form a nearly solid wall about the clearing, but haven't penetrated into it.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="286" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Brambles, Clearing">
    <description>A huge, spreading oak tree dominates the center of the clearing, lifting its great branches up into the sky.  The thorn bushes stop just outside the rounded perimeter, allowing grass and some flowers to grow beneath the great tree.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Brambles">
    <description>The bushes on either side of the track loom high, dense enough to obscure whatever lies beyond.  Every now and again they rustle, sometimes on one side, sometimes on the other.  Something is moving about within the depths of the bramble patch.  And considering the long, wicked thorns sticking out from the brambles in every direction, anything that would casually rustle its way through them must have an incredibly tough hide.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="298" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Brambles">
    <description>Nocturnal birds hoot and screech to each other up in the leafy canopy.  Little scavengers rustle about in the bushes, unseen but always present.  Deep shadows draw a curtain of obscurity over the scene, leaving only the larger outlines to be avoided and hiding the smaller details to be tripped over.</description>
    <description>Birds chirp and call back and forth to each other, up in the leafy canopy spreading between several trees on either side of the narrow track.  There's an edge of urgency to the bird calls, as though there were a predator about, or some other lurking danger.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Brambles">
    <description>The brambles converge on a small stand of trees to form a dead-end in the trail.  The greenery grows dense here, with the swagged branches of the trees competing for light and air with the tough little thorn bushes.  The leaf litter on the ground is thick and spongy, covering the dirt and all but a few of the larger rocks.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="pull branch;-.5 push rock;-.5 go hole" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Brambles">
    <description>The brambles grow particularly dense here, leaving only a tiny pocket barely large enough to stand in.  In the leaves covering the ground are signs that some animal has made its nest here recently, leaving only scuffed ground and litter.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Brambles">
    <description>Curling tendrils carry a twisted vine through the thorny brambles and up into the swaying trees, cloaking the harsh thorns and tiny leaves in greenery.  Leaves shaped like arrowheads nod in the breeze, casting oddly shaped shadows across the spines lurking just behind them.</description>
    <description>Fresh green tendrils carry a twisting vine through the thorny brambles and up into the swaying trees, cloaking the harsh thorns and tiny leaves in bright greenery.  Leaves shaped like arrowheads nod in the breeze, flanking trumpet-shaped flowers striped in pink and white.  Bees buzz and hum as they go about their work, collecting pollen from the gaudy blossoms.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="go" move="push rock;-.5 pull branch;-.5 go hole" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Brambles">
    <description>A crooked trail winds its way around a huge boulder.  Half buried in the soil, the great rock is rounded and smoothed, nearly polished in places.  Plush, green moss grows up the lower surfaces, and the top is carpeted in dead leaves and wind-blown dirt.  Enough of the rock itself shows that you can see it's made of a black and white flecked granite.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Brambles">
    <description>A low spot in the ground has collected water, creating a breeding ground for wriggling water bugs and spreading green growths.  Tracks in the mud indicate that a number of animals come here regularly to drink, although the slimy, bug-infested mud puddle looks anything but inviting to someone with fewer than four legs.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Brambles">
    <description>The game trail dead-ends here, surrounded by dense thorn bushes an all sides, with only a narrow gap in the foliage to the west.  Rustlings coming from the leafy shadows and the brambles sway back and forth, now here, now there.  Something is lurking in amongst the undergrowth.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Brambles">
    <description>Filtered moonlight wafts its way through the leafy tree cover, separate beams gently illuminating a branch here, a leaf there.  The shadows are gentler, softened by the dim lighting, and seem somehow not as threatening as they otherwise might.</description>
    <description>A few puffy yellow flowers have managed to force their way through the dense brambles in search of sunlight.  In among the tiny grey-green leaves of the bushes are a number of larger curled leaves, poking out here and there.  Only filtered light makes it through the leafy tree cover, but it's enough to support the scattering of flowers.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Brambles">
    <description>The trail makes a sharp corner to avoid a particularly dense stand of brambles.  There's hardly enough space for a gnat to crawl through, or so it seems.  Something in the soil must be encouraging the unusually luxuriant growth.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Brambles">
    <description>The trail widens into a small clearing, surrounded by mature thorn bushes and carpeted with grass and a number of wildflowers.  Half a dozen thick stumps are spotted about the area, indicating that this used to be as thickly overgrown as any other part of the area, and indeed there are several hundred baby brambles, from tiny sprouts to couple of fat little bushes a foot or more tall.  Within a few years, this area will be impassable once more.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Brambles">
    <description>Several narrow tracks intersect here, in a spot that seems to get a lot of trampling.  A sickly-looking thorn bush grows in the middle of the intersection, trying to spread out and block passage, but bruises and scars and broken branches have prevented it from making much headway.  Some deep tracks in the dirt show that a large, heavy animal frequents this place, likely the cause of the bramble's misfortunes.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Brambles">
    <description>A rutted animal track runs between and around a number of thorny brambles.  Little round leaves, dried to resemble nothing so much as oversized rolled oats, cover the ground, while their living green counterparts spiral their way up the branches of the bushes. </description>
    <position x="80" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Brambles">
    <description>A large oak tree grows a short way south of the track, forcing its way up from among the thorny bushes pressing in all around it.  One of the thorn branches grew so close that the oak's bark has grown over it, trapping it forever against the gnarled trunk.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Brambles">
    <description>The brambles are a bit thinner to the south, neither very high nor very dense.  Other types of plants grow intermixed with the thorn bushes, softening the appearance of the area into something approaching a gentle woodland.  A couple of tree ferns spread their feathery fronds overhead, blocking out the twinkle of the stars, while a stand of callas pushes its way amongst the thorns, the waxy white flowers glowing in the moonlight.</description>
    <description>The brambles are a bit thinner to the south, neither very high nor very dense.  Other types of plants grow intermixed with the thorn bushes, softening the appearance of the area into something approaching a gentle woodland.  A couple of tree ferns spread their feathery fronds over the thorns, while a stand of callas pushes its way in amongst them.  Here and there, tiny violets peek out from under larger leaves, hiding from the sun.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Brambles">
    <description>Most of the surrounding foliage is thornless, with only a few brambles mixed in.  The conglomerate of greenery is just as dense as the bramble thicket, but less painful when one brushes against it.  Tall, green bushes with leaves shaped like spearheads dominate, intermixed with leggy cane-like plants, huge grasses taller than a Tog's head, and a fibrous vine with straggly orange flowers.  A short clover covers the ground in fragrant patches, making this a pleasant little spot.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Brambles">
    <description>Young oak trees fill what little space there is in between the thorn bushes, rising above the spiny undergrowth like giants striding through a cornfield.  Many years' accumulation of curled brown leaves blend on the ground with the crackly little grey leaves from the brambles, forming a thick, spongy loam.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Brambles">
    <description>Some small animal got itself caught on the long thorns of the bramble bushes.  Attempts to free itself only caught it more firmly, and it died pinned into that spiny prison.  Small scavengers have made of its body a hollow shell.  The skeleton is clean and white, doubtless picked over and polished by ants and beetles.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Brambles">
    <description>The thorn bushes in this area are half-naked and sick-looking.  Branches bare of leaves wave in the breeze, showing their thorns without the usual cover of little round leaves.  A number of leaves look half eaten, and here and there are tiny black worms, chewing and chewing, gorging themselves on the greenery, tough and leathery though it may be.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Brambles">
    <description>Tall brambles loom high on either side of the narrow track, their thorny limbs fluttering with little green leaves that spiral up the branches.  The breeze stirs the bushes, sending a soft rustle through the thicket, but every now and again a louder, harsher crackle and honk is heard, sounds made by no wind.  Something moves back in the thicket, in the densest parts where none, not even a Dwarf or Halfling, may venture.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Brambles">
    <description>A stone the size of two fists together has been disturbed, kicked out of its home in the loamy soil, leaving behind a shallow hole filled with half rotten acorns.  Some squirrel must have chosen this stone to guard his winter cache, but someone else -- or something else -- came along and kicked the rock aside.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Brambles">
    <description>A huge fallen tree trunk lies cradled in the embrace of a pair of relatively smaller trees, wedged tightly between them.  Soil has packed close about the lower curve of the trunk, burying it firmly -- it must have been resting here for a long time.  The game trail stops at the enormous trunk, which prevents movement to the east as the dense brambles block all other ways save the northwest.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Northwall Trail, Grassland">
    <description>To the northwest, a copse of birch trees stands thin and stark against the sky, the swift breezes animating their skeletal forms in a gentle dance.</description>
    <description>To the northwest, a copse of birch trees stand thin and stark against the sky, the swift breezes animating their skeletal forms in a gentle dance.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vast crater" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch copse" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Northwall Trail, Grassland">
    <description>The rhythmic chirping of crickets hums from the tall wind-swept grasses pressing inward on the narrow trail.  Moths hover close, flying in looping patterns toward any glint of light.</description>
    <description>Swift breezes ruffle the tall grasses beneath the wind-scoured sky that stretches far above like a pale awning.  Sprays of orange and purple wildflowers attract the attention of a few butterflies, who flutter across the trail.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Northwall Trail, Edge of the Forest">
    <description>Thin pine saplings, field laurel and shrub grass form a narrow border on the edge of the forest, a blending of life easily yielded to either side.  The darkness of the close-set trees to the northwest bustles with unseen movement, while the open grasslands stretching out to the west breathe quietly the open air.</description>
    <description>Thin pine saplings, field laurel and shrub grass form a narrow border on the edge of the forest.  The darkness of the close-set trees to the northwest rustles with unseen movement, while the open grasslands stretching out to the west breathe quietly the open air.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Northwall Trail, Open Forest" note="boxes">
    <description>The air is heavy with the scent of pine and the sounds of scree littering the trail crunching underfoot.  A large web spanning the branches of a stunted sourwood tree glistens in the moonlight.</description>
    <description>Longleaf pine and spruce outnumbering the hardwoods in the area drip a sticky sap that sugars the underbrush, and litter the trail with needles that crunch underfoot.  Spanning the branches of a stunted sourwood tree, an orbweaver's web twitches slightly with the struggles of a small fly.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Northwall Trail, Open Forest" note="east">
    <description>The darkness of night grips the forest tightly, like a black-gloved fist holding back the light of dawn.  The staccato questions of owls echo from the boughs far above, while lower to the ground the cries of unseen creatures ring through the trees.</description>
    <description>Growing in the shade of towering oak and fir trees, azalea bushes add bright splashes of color to the brown-green gloom of the forest.  Tangles of ivy creep alongside the trail and cloak the trees in jade filigree.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Northern Trade Road, Open Forest" note="Map7_NTR.xml|NTR">
    <description>Trees rise dimly along the roadway and you can faintly hear a quiet chittering, perhaps from sleepy squirrels annoyed at your disturbing their rest.</description>
    <description>Trees to both sides of the road thin out southward where the land changes to open grassland.  Large grey squirrels leap across the road overhead from branch to branch and chitter down at you as they regard you with curious eyes.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Seord'moda Crater, Ridge" note="Seord'moda Crater">
    <description>Burnt shards of wood and bone are strewn outward from the ridge of a vast crater torn into the landscape.  The ragged pit gapes widely at the sky like a giant maw screaming in rage and sorrow.  An uneven trail littered with gravel and blasted rock weaves down the steep walls through thick layers of soil, sand and stone to the bottom of the great hole.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Seord'moda Crater, Wall">
    <description>Stones charred and cracked from a great explosion jut from the jagged walls of the crater and alter the trail's course.  The sharp edges of silver-flecked stone glisten in the pale moonlight like the dagger blades of assassins in the shadows.</description>
    <description>Stones charred and cracked from a great explosion jut from the jagged walls of the crater and alter the trail's course.  The sharp edges of silver-flecked stone glisten from the dark soil like the sword blades of a legion raised in battle.</description>
    <position x="300" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Seord'moda Crater, Wall">
    <description>Devoid of vegetation, the dark topsoil yields to a coarse grey loam.  Sand fused by fire crackles under foot, and the slippery grit sends shards of stone and unwary travelers alike hurtling down the slope.  A broken broadsword protrudes from a large sandstone, its blackened blade twisted like a coiled adder.</description>
    <position x="300" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Seord'moda Crater, Wall">
    <description>A stony black carpet glimmers slightly in the darkness, at once illuminating the trail and absorbing what light touches it.  Large shards of stone rise from the steep ground and bend the narrow pass in directions unpredictable in the sightless night.</description>
    <description>Fist-sized black stones carpet the narrow pass between two large shards of rock that rise from the base of the crater.  The stones glimmer with the dull iridescence of onyx and swallow the surrounding light.  As the carpet thickens nearer the bottom, the wall seems to fall off into darkness.</description>
    <position x="300" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Seord'moda Crater">
    <description>Darkness consumes the base of the crater, the towering walls swallowing the moonlight.  Only silver sparkles of stars peek in from above.  The stars themselves seem to rain down into the crater, as their light glints from small avalanches of stone that bounce down the walls.</description>
    <description>Tall slopes tower overhead in every direction, casting long shadows across the stony floor and chasing sunlight from the great crater.  Small avalanches of stone and gravel rain down from above, startling small flocks of birds that flap off into the pale sky.</description>
    <position x="320" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Seord'moda Crater">
    <description>The jagged base of the crater is run through with cracks in the black stone like open wounds in ebon flesh.  A buzzard perched atop mineral-flecked stone pecks at the stringy remains of a small meal.  It glances up occasionally to survey the vast pit littered with debris, and glare at the interlopers in its domain.</description>
    <position x="320" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="103" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Seord'moda Crater">
    <description>The wind howls against the stony walls like braying hounds in the winter and whips up small whirlwinds of sand and skree.  Gossamer veils of shadow hover far above, casting a barren vista of monochrome greys and blacks.</description>
    <position x="340" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Northwall Trail, Birch Copse">
    <description>The small copse of birch trees provides a welcome oasis of shade in the open grassland.  The trees stand thin and tall, their pale trunks catching the sunlight and glowing softly in the shade of their rustling canopy.  Oddly set amidst the birches is a curiously bent black willow tree.</description>
    <description>Glowing a ghostly pale in the moonlight softly filtered through their rustling canopy, the birch trees lend credence to the old traveler's tale of the spirit of the birch.  The White Handed Ones could stop any heart or riddle with wicked visions any head their bony limbs touched.  Oddly set amidst the birch is a curiously bent black willow tree.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb willow tree" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Northwall Trail, Near the Road">
    <description>Rumbling carts from the North Turnpike lend a low bass to the sweet aria of field wrens, whose small choirs spot the meadow on either side of the trail.  Far to the north, a thick plume of grey smoke billows from the tall chimneys of a monastery.</description>
    <description>The clatter of caravans on the turnpike rumbles low like thunder in the stillness of the night.  To the north, the lights of the monastery are visible, floating dimly in the darkness.</description>
    <position x="180" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Northwall Trail, Phaedic's Field" note="Phaedic's Field">
    <description>An uneven expanse of grass stretches to the south and west.  Fresh mounds of dirt stand not far from the trail, while closer to the town wall the mounds are sunken to mere ripples in the meadow.  Paupers, street urchins, soldiers fallen short of glory, and anonymous travelers all meet their final destination here.  Beside the trail, a broken shovel leans against a boulder.</description>
    <description>The sound of digging echoes from somewhere across the field, broken occasionally by the ring of metal as it strikes stone.  Fresh mounds of dirt stand not far from the trail, while closer to the town wall the mounds have sunk to mere ripples in the meadow.  Paupers, street urchins, soldiers fallen short of glory, and anonymous travelers all meet their final destination here.  A large boulder stands beside the trail.</description>
    <position x="120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Northwall Trail, Meadow">
    <description>Cornflowers, violets and poppies color the green velvet meadow in twilight shades and fill the air with a cloying fragrance.  The sound of the river burbling to the west blends with the mournful song of the wind's gust across the flatlands.</description>
    <description>The mournful wind gusts unheeded across the meadow, melding with the song of the river to the west.  The thick scent of grass and wildflowers lingers in the darkness.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Northwall Trail, River's Edge" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Cattails and rushes border the river, softening the steep angle of the riverbank.  The lush grasses of a nearby meadow yield here to a thick mud that clutches at your feet, making each step difficult.  The deep croaking of bullfrogs punctuates the steady rush of the river, and the distant twitter of meadowlarks completes the arboreal symphony.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="rt east" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Northwall Trail, Riverbank">
    <description>A tall poplar forms a natural bridge across the swiftly moving river, its roots still entangled in a great mass of deadwood on the western riverbank. A kingfisher perched on one of the silvered branches of the felled tree calmly watches the rushing waters for the glimmer of its next meal.</description>
    <description>Faint light reflected from the river outlines the natural bridge made by a tall poplar, the tree's roots still entangled in a great mass of deadwood on the western riverbank.  The splash and roll of the river's flow thunders loudly in the quiet of night.</description>
    <position x="80" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="go" move="rt go fallen poplar" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Northwall Trail, Deadfall">
    <description>A tall poplar forms a natural bridge across the swiftly moving river, its roots still entangled in a great mass of deadwood on the western riverbank.  A kingfisher perched on one of the silvered branches of the felled tree calmly watches the rushing waters for the glimmer of its next meal.</description>
    <description>Faint light reflecting off of the river outlines the natural bridge made by a tall poplar, the tree's roots still entangled in a great mass of deadwood on the western riverbank.  The splash and roll of the river's flow thunders loudly in the quiet of night.</description>
    <position x="80" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="go" move="rt go fallen poplar" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Northwall Trail, Wooded Grove" note="Pfanston's grove">
    <description>The sounds of the river splash through the trees from the southeast, where the woods end abruptly in a tangle of felled trees.  The massive deadfall looks like the remains of some giant creature, its weather-bleached bones laying in a great heap beside the river.</description>
    <description>The sounds of the river splash through the trees to the southeast, where the tangled trunks of a massive deadfall laying along the riverbank glow a ghostly pale in the moonlight.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deadfall" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb contorted tree" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Northwall Trail, Wooded Grove" note="Map4_Crossing_West_Gate.xml|W Gate">
    <description>The sweet smell of wildflowers carried on the breeze mingles with the spicy smell of cedar and juniper.  Sunlight dapples the mossy ground in golden hues and glistens on the dew-laden petals of tiny snowflowers.  A gnarled oak tree, cracked in two by a great tempest's fury, lays beside the trail.</description>
    <description>The sweet smell of wildflowers carried on the breeze mingles with the spicy scent of cedar and juniper.  At the sound of an owl, a startled woodmouse scurries across the trail toward a gnarled and broken oak tree.</description>
    <position x="60" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Northwall Trail, Tree Top">
    <description>Faint light streams down through the tree's upper limbs, painting the branches in an eerie, pale hue.  Now and then the surrounding foliage rustles with movement, though whatever is causing it cannot be seen.  Occasionally something glints in the depth of the shadows -- could it be watchful eyes?  But they appear and are gone again so quickly that perhaps they were only a trick of the imagination.</description>
    <description>Natural light filters down through the tree's mighty limbs.  The bark of the trunk is well worn with use, as if something or someone has been using this as a way of getting around.  Often, the leaves overhead flicker with movement as squirrels leap playfully through the canopy.  The tree has several crude carvings on it, apparently done by someone who had nothing better to do.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb branch" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Ranger's Guild, The Tree House" note="Map1_Crossing.xml|Tree house|Ranger">
    <description>This platform perched high in the treetop offers a breathtaking view of the surroundings, and a small spyglass secured to the banister provides an opportunity to get a closer look.  A slight breeze caresses the leaves of the trees with a sound like the voice of nature whispering secrets to those who will listen.  A few leaves occasionally blow down the carved steps leading to the room below.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Rows and rows of blueberry bushes grow within the stone fence enclosure.  The narrow path following the stone wall bends from the north to the southwest, other less well marked paths disappear into the stands of shrubs.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go broken fence" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  A crow struts among the dried leaves and berries littering the ground.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  A smoky tang rises from a charred pile of twigs pruned from the berry shrubs at the end of the season.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  The path plunges deeper into the blueberry bushes from several directions.  Curving southeast, the rock fence separates the edge of the thicket from the road.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  The path plunges deeper into the blueberry bushes from several directions.  Curving northeast, the rock fence separates the edge of the thicket from the road.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  Tiny black ants have built several mounds near the base of one bush.  One struggles with a plump blueberry, straining to haul it back to the nest.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  Tiny black ants have built several mounds near the base of one bush.  An ant struggles with a plump blueberry, straining to haul it back to the nest.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  A group of tiny black ants contest possession of plump blueberry with an army of red ants.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  A group of tiny black ants contest possession of a plump blueberry with an army of red ants.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  Tiny red ants have built several mounds near the base of one bush.  One struggles with a plump blueberry, straining to haul it back to the nest.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Brambly bushes create a close thicket criss-crossed by paths littered with fallen blueberries.  The smell of over-ripe fruit lingers in the air like drying honey.  Scraps of loosely woven netting -- an attempt to foil birds -- cling to the shrubs.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Dark green moss dapples the high stone wall skirting one side of the path, and fronds from the bushes overhang the narrow trail in places.  Tiny red ants have built several mounds near the base of one bush.  One struggles with a plump blueberry, straining to haul it back to the nest.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>Gnarled and blackened from a lightning strike, this stunted little shrub at the far northwest corner of the thicket yields no fruit, yet some green shoots thrusting from new growth promise renewal.  The path curves to the southwest towards the cornfield and eastwards deeper into the blueberry grove.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blueberry grove" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Monastery, Field Path">
    <description>Turning abruptly to the northeast from the main path, the stone wall plunges into a dense patch of blueberry bushes.  The soil is packed hard from the passage of people, equipment and creatures between the field, blueberry patch and path to the monastery.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow track" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>The field path wends into a grove of blueberry bushes.  Unharvested by the monks, fat berries hang in luscious profusion from the slender branches, providing a feast for the creatures living here.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Monastery, Blueberry Bushes">
    <description>The thicket of blueberries thins to the southwest, exposing a view of a cornfield.  The leaves of a nearby shrub shake violently as something hidden by the greenery scurries among the limbs.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dirt path" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Brown and dried out, stunted stalks of corn lie trampled in the dirt.  Even the grubs disdain the hard ears of corn abandoned in furrows.  Once straight rows of corn continue to the west, and a drainage ditch skirts one side of the field.  Some blueberry bushes are visible to the northeast, just beyond a dirt path.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dirt path" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Monastery, Field Path">
    <description>Hardly noticeable as a break in the wall, vine covered rubble and debris blocks an ancient entrance gate to the monastery.  Peering over the crumbling stone, the outer buildings of the monastery can be seen to the northeast.  Southeast, the path continues, cutting between the drained fields and blueberry bushes.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Monastery, Field Path">
    <description>Impressions left by the hooves of dray beasts and footprints left by the monks mix with those of ...something else... in the rich black soil.  Clumps of tough grass grow against the weathered stone wall which lines one side of the path, preventing entry onto the monastery grounds.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow track" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>A raccoon's beady black eyes peer from behind a clump of stalks still standing, as it gnaws hopefully at a dried out ear of corn.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the west and a dirt path leads off to the northeast.  A chirring sound comes from the drainage ditch lining the field.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow track" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  Thick wooden planks bridge the drainage ditch separating the north from the middle field.  Eastward, the ravaged furrows continue, only a few tracks of small animals giving evidence that there is still life in the field.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  Thick wooden planks bridge the drainage ditches separating the fields.  Eastward, the ravaged furrows continue, only a few tracks of small animals giving evidence that there is still life in the field.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  Thick wooden planks bridge the drainage ditches separating the fields.  Eastward, the ravaged furrows continue, only a few tracks of small animals giving evidence that there is still life in the field.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Several forlorn stalks of corn still stand, seemingly huddled together for protection against whatever creatures roam the fields.  A fetid smell of stale water rises from the drainage ditch that skirts one side of the field.  Some blueberry bushes are visible to the northeast, just beyond a dirt path.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow track" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Monastery, Drained Field">
    <description>Ruined stalks of corn lie crushed in the dirt, the ears torn from the stem and cast haphazardly about.  The furrow of stricken plants continues to the east and west.  From within the drainage ditch edging the field can be heard the sounds of insects buzzing and something rustling in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Monastery, Drainage Ditch">
    <description>Water pools at the bottom of the ditch, just deep enough to soak feet and breed mosquitos.  Weeds sprout from the mud, and tufts of grass cling to the ditch walls.  An unseen frog croaks in the vegetation.  Small, nearly invisible insects buzz near your ears and nose.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" hidden="True" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Monastery, Drainage Ditch">
    <description>Water pools at the bottom of the ditch, just deep enough to soak feet and breed mosquitos.  Weeds sprout from the mud, and tufts of grass cling to the ditch walls.  An unseen frog croaks in the vegetation.  Small, almost invisible insects buzz near your ears and nose.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" hidden="True" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Monastery, Drainage Ditch">
    <description>Water pools at the bottom of the ditch, just deep enough to soak feet and breed mosquitos.  Weeds sprout from the mud, and tufts of grass cling to the ditch walls.  An unseen frog croaks in the vegetation.  Small, nearly invisible bugs buzz near your ears and nose.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" hidden="True" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Monastery, Drainage Ditch">
    <description>Water pools at the bottom of the ditch, just deep enough to soak feet and breed mosquitos.  Weeds sprout from the mud, and tufts of grass cling to the ditch walls.  An unseen frog croaks in the vegetation.  Small, nearly invisible insects buzz near your ears.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" hidden="True" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Monastery, Drainage Ditch">
    <description>Water pools at the bottom of the ditch, just deep enough to soak feet and breed mosquitos.  Weeds sprout from the mud, and tufts of grass cling to the ditch walls.  An unseen frog croaks in the vegetation.  Small, almost invisible insects buzz near your ears.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" hidden="True" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Monastery, Gully">
    <description>High as a most men's heads, the soft soil of one wall is pocked with gouges, as if someone had tried to climb it.  Insects buzz around weeds sprouting from the shallow water covering the gully floor.  An unseen cricket chirps in the vegetation.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Monastery, Gully">
    <description>Although dry now, loose rocks moved by flowing water and careless feet litter the bottom of the gully slope.  The trench is close to waist deep on a Gor'tog and mounds of dirt mixed among the brambles on the wall rim indicate nature has had help digging.  From somewhere within the brambles, a wren warbles.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Monastery, Gully">
    <description>Seasonal rains have cut a channel leading away from the road in the soft soil.  Only about knee-deep, it might be possible to climb over the sides were it not for the thorny spikeplants that grow along the flanks of the gully.  A few hardy weeds hold tenaciously to the sides of the channel as it cuts deeper into the earth.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rutted road" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Deep Forest, Winding Path">
    <description>Apple trees grow tall in this part of the forest, spread out between the maple and occasionally a willow tree.  Large knotholes in several of them appear to house nests for forest creatures, although many seem to have gone unused for quite some time.  Barely visible through the thick trees to the east is a small pond.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Deep Forest, Winding Path" note="Path">
    <description>Large huckleberry shrubs somewhat obscure the beginning of this small trail, which winds its way between several tall maple and poplar trees.  Their branches tangle together overhead, forming a dense canopy.  In contrast, the forest floor is sparsely covered, with only a few small wildflowers poking through the cover of decaying leaves.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Deep Forest, Winding Path">
    <description>A crumbled piece of white marble is set in a wide spot between two half-dead trees, the chunk of stone looking to be the broken remnants of a monument or statue.  No longer recognizable at all, the marble's surface is covered in the forest's climbing vines, making it their home.  Overhead, the branches are quite thick, the apple trees flourishing in this area.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Deep Forest, Winding Path" note="Firewood">
    <description>The path here splits in two different directions, each one branching off sharply.  Set at the center of the junction is a large sana'ati tree, much taller than any of the others in the forest.  Small white mushrooms dot the dirt around the tree's roots, although the area is otherwise quite clear of debris or undergrowth.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Deep Forest, Winding Path" note="Tynick">
    <description>The forest path sharply ends here at a fallen tree trunk, although the trail looks like it once continued further.  Shining clubmoss covers the ground and some of the trees, and the area feels somewhat damp.  Tangles of vine, shrubs and other undergrowth cover the felled trunk and the space around it, making passage completely impossible.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Deep Forest, Monastery Wall" note="Adano">
    <description>Stopping the trees abruptly, a tall stone wall rises above the forest canopy.  Set into the wall's outward face is a small iron gate, and the courtyard of a monastery can be seen through it.  Far too small to be a main entrance, it appears to be a back way into the grounds and is a little rusted from years of weathering.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Monastery Grounds, Gate">
    <description>A well-kept cobblestone path runs through the center of a large green lawn, which appears to be very freshly cut.  Although a tall iron fence runs parallel to the pathway and cuts off passage, it's still easy to see several buildings through it, each of them made of mortared stone.  Standing next to the walkway is a single lamppost, also made of cast iron.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="176" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Monastery Grounds, Courtyard Path">
    <description>The expansive lawn is meticulously kept free of any weeds, creating a completely uniform sea of green on either side of the cobblestone path.  The view through a wrought iron fence shows several buildings, and each one appears to be set aside for a specific purpose.  Directly to the north is a modestly sized chapel, its stained glass windows and wooden doors a bit marred by the accumulation of dust and dirt.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Monastery Grounds, Side Entrance" note="Side Entrance">
    <description>The cobblestone pathway passes between two buildings, turning the space briefly into an alleyway.  Each structure is several stories tall, although it's hard to judge exactly because of the flat roofing.  Though the southern building has a small window facing the alley, the interior is fully obscured by heavy grey curtains.  A small wooden door leads into the northern building, apparently a side entrance.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Monastery Grounds, Iron Gate" note="Iron Gate">
    <description>The cobblestone pathway stops at a tall stone fence, which seems to be more for appearance than to keep out intruders.  A sign hangs above the entrance, marking it as the monastery's private cemetery.  Growing near the entrance is a small poplar tree, looking like it's not much older than a sapling.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron gate" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Monastery Grounds, Greenhouse Entrance">
    <description>The narrow cobblestone path continues east and west, looking as if its surface was washed recently.  Visible through a wrought iron fence is a large covered greenhouse, rows of ripening grapes and other plants visible within.  A small wooden gate leads into the carefully crafted structure, and next to it sits a large washtub full of monk's clothes.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open wooden gate" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Monastery Grounds, Abandoned Tower">
    <description>A tall tower stands at the end of the cobblestone path, made from the same stone as the other buildings dotting the grounds of the complex.  With a sturdy iron door that looks solidly locked, the structure's function seems to be a mystery, though the occasional window is visible a few stories up.  Lush vineyards can be seen through the wrought iron fence to the north, growing in neat rows on white trellises.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="go" move="knock tower" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Monastery Grounds, Graveyard" note="Graveyard">
    <description>Neat rows of headstones fill three quarters of this small cemetery, which looks to be kept clean and regularly maintained.  Set into the stone at the front of each grave marker is a simple medallion bearing the names of the monks entombed in the area.  Small poplar trees planted in each corner of the cemetery give a bit of shade.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="none" move="open iron gate" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Monastery Grounds, Greenhouse" note="Greenhouse">
    <description>Rows upon rows of flourishing plants grow inside this greenhouse, protected no matter the weather or season.  Clusters of fat grapes hang on carefully spaced vines, clearly labeled to show when they will ripen.  Other fresh fruits and vegetables are planted in rows near the back, providing fresh food for the winter months.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open wooden gate" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Monastery, Narrow Passage">
    <description>The stone walls contrast somewhat with the polished white marble floor, which has a narrow strip of dark red carpeting running down the center.  Although careful work has gone into detailing and carving the architecture, the walls are completely bare and seem almost sterile.  Set into the eastern wall is a steepled window featuring plain glass in an iron frame, which looks out into a small graveyard.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Monastery, Narrow Passage">
    <description>Large portions of the hallway's walls are very smooth, divided by columns that break up the pattern of the flagstone.  Though these sections are almost completely bare, flecks of paint at the very edges imply that images once decorated the walls but have long since been scrubbed away.  Gaethzen orbs hang from the ceiling high above, illuminating the narrow hall in a somewhat dim light.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="go" move="knock iron doors" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Monastery, Winding Passage">
    <description>The hallway here bends slightly, a single raised step in the center of the floor.  Though the walls are made of bare mortar stone, elaborate borderwork near the ceiling and floor give it just a touch of elegance.  Placed upon a white stone pedestal at the slight corner is a small sword of polished silver, resting atop a dark red pillow.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open narrow door" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Monastery, Winding Passage" note="Markat|Spell Preps" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A single raised step in the center of the hallway marks a slight bend in the passage.  Gold leaf adorns the top and bottom borders of the rough stone walls, which are spaced every so often with carved marble columns.  Securely bolted to the northern wall is a large lead sheet, which looks somewhat scuffed in various places.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Monastery, Winding Passage">
    <description>Torches are set at periodic intervals on each wall of this wide passageway, flickering and sending tongues of orange light to play over the grey stone.  Crafted from polished steel, a small medallion hangs around the base of one of dark iron sconces.  The hallway ends to the east at an elegantly arched door, its surface covered with ornate carvings.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="go" move="knock on arched door;knock on arched door" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Monastery Commons Room, Southwest Corner">
    <description>The ceiling rises upward and toward the northeast to form a dramatic arched dome, a large marble obelisk centered exactly underneath it.  Puffy white clouds are painted onto the dome, giving it a very open feeling.  Several granite benches line the southern wall, providing a convenient place for a brief respite.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open arched door" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Monastery Commons Room, Northwest Corner">
    <description>Overshadowing everything else in the room is a massive set of double doors in the northern wall, marking the main entrance to the building.  Although it appears to have been carved with many deities, all of the work is very abstract, making it impossible to recognize any individual one.  The rest of this corner of the commons room is quite bare, with no furnishings at all except a tall marble obelisk standing in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow archway" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Monastery Commons Room, Southeast Corner" note="bucket">
    <description>A curious arrangement graces the southern wall of the common room.  Three arched windows rise high in the stonework, two of them filled with clear, textured glass.  The third is crafted from elaborate stained glass, seeming a little out of place next to the others.  To the east is a small entryway, and a large marble obelisk stands in the center of the common room.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Monastery, Narrow Entryway">
    <description>Apparently a side entrance leading into the building, the door is rather plain, although it apparently sees frequent use.  Twin torches frame the entryway, set into metallic sconces bolted to rising columns in the corners of this short hallway.  A large common area opens up to the west, with a white obelisk standing in the center of it.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plain door" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Monastery Commons Room, Northeast Corner">
    <description>A dramatic arched dome rises in the center of the common room, a large marble obelisk positioned underneath it and standing quite tall.  Muted wisps of cloud are painted onto the dome, mimicking the noontime sky.  Several prayer mats are lined against the north and eastern walls, providing a convenient place for worship.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Monastery, Cloister" note="Tea" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Two shade-filled arcades flanked by an array of plaster columns meet at the corner of this plain cloister, which ends to the south and west at grey stone walls.  The curving tops of the columns give way to stylized ogee arches that look out into a secret garden.  A small window is set in the northern wall, offering a glimpse into the monastery grounds.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Monastery, Cloister">
    <description>The bright colors of the gardens beyond the massive arched opening are a vibrant contrast to the dull grey of the stone walls surrounding the meditation area.  A trio of thick reed mats lines the floor, each arranged in a circle surrounding a small fountain.  From outside, the peaceful cloister garden contributes its own natural perfume to the combination of fragrances wafting from the stalks of burning incense.</description>
    <position x="620" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Monastery, Cloister" note="Cloister|Belt Knives" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A light breeze drifts in from the open ogee arches to the south, bringing with it the scent of fresh flowers.  In sharp contrast to the color in the garden, the greyish stone walls are rather plain and completely unadorned.  Set in the eastern wall is a solid door made from cast iron, its top slightly arched.</description>
    <position x="640" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go solid door" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Monastery, Side Passage">
    <description>Very narrow and rather claustrophobic, the interior of this hallway is quite plain and unadorned, the walls crafted from mortared stones.  Thick red carpeting covers the entire floor, perhaps placed to mute the sound of footsteps.  The only light in the area is somewhat dim torchlight, filtering in from the passage to the north.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Monastery, Stairwell">
    <description>The cramped, curving hallway is difficult to see down, its southern end washed out by torchlight.  A narrow strip of red carpeting runs down the center of the stone floor, both kept very clean.  Twin torches burn on the walls, their red and orange light flickering and playing off the mortared stone.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding stairwell" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Monastery, Shaded Balcony">
    <description>Though the rest of the hallway is almost sterile in appearance, the northern wall opens completely out into a balcony, providing a view just over the treetops.  The resulting view extends for miles, offering a distant glimpse of the Greater Fist on the horizon.  Somehow the area is kept completely clean, even while exposed to the elements and inclement weather.</description>
    <description>Though the rest of the hallway is almost sterile in appearance, the northern wall opens completely out into a balcony, providing a view just over the treetops.  The nighttime sky is clearly visible, extending over the forest like a dark blanket.  Dim torches line the railing, burning with an orange glow.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-300" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding stairwell" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Monastery, Shaded Balcony">
    <description>The northern wall of this narrow hallway fans out into a covered balcony, providing a sharp view of the forest below.  Endless trees form a rough canopy that hides anything below them, extending to the mountains to the distant north.  Occasionally a small bird passes in front of the stone railing, fluttering its wings and keeping a fair distance away.</description>
    <description>Brightly burning torches set on the southern wall nearly obscure the view from a balcony to the north.  The sky appears pitch black, and the trees below look like little more than the vague outline of shadows.  A waist-high stone railing blocks off the balcony, preventing any serious falls.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-300" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Monastery, Narrow Passage">
    <description>Both walls are very smooth and completely bare, contrasting sharply with the arching ceiling overhead and its elaborate design.  A deep red carpet runs down the center of the marble floor, muting footsteps and adding just a hint of warmth to the room.  Blazing torches frame both sides of an ornately carved wooden door set in the northern wall.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open wooden door" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Monastery, Alcove">
    <description>Standing in the circular end of the hallway is an elegant statue crafted from white marble which depicts a woman in a long robe.  Coated in elegant gold leaf, the alcove's interior is designed to reflect a shower of light onto the figure, giving it a surreal feeling.  A small window on the southern wall looks out onto the monastery grounds.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Book's Private Study" note="Guildleader|GL Necromancer" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Row upon row of volumes and tomes line several darkly stained cedar shelves, taking up the entire eastern wall of the room.  A dark mahogany desk stands in the center of the room, a large and comfortable-looking chair behind it.  Two narrow strips of deep red carpeting run along each side of the desk, simply accenting the black marble floor.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-300" z="1" />
    <arc exit="none" move="open wooden door" destination="202" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Courtyard">
    <description>Swaths of grass cover the interior courtyard, broken only by a rectangular reflecting pool that doubles as a trough and bath for the horses.  The field is hemmed by brick buildings on three sides, with the facade wall and gated archway forming the fourth enclosing structure.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wrought gates" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brick building" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Courtyard">
    <description>Hungry -- or bored -- horses have ignored the stacks of baled hay nearby in favor of cropping several bare patches into the grass.  A low set of fieldstone steps leads up to a red door.  A plaque next to the door reads, Stablemaster.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red door" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Courtyard" note="Zoluren Royal Mews">
    <description>A large brick stable stands here with its dark wooden doors thrown wide open.  A nearby well is festooned with buckets and rope, with young children often seen sprinting from the stable to the well, enhancing their daily chores with a race.  Some slightly trampled climbing rose bushes grow up against one side of the stable.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow pathway" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden doors" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Courtyard">
    <description>Just off the courtyard stands a red brick building with a profusion of roses guarding its entrance.  Stone steps that lead to its dark doors bear the print of horses' hoofs, giving them a faintly whimsical look.  A wooden sign peeks out from behind one of the thorny rose bushes.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark doors" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Brokerage Offices" note="Brokerage Offices">
    <description>Crisp, clean smells emanate from the freshly polished chestnut floor.  An archway to one side of the entryway leads to a cozy sitting room while on the other is a mahogany door.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="317" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="318" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Stablemaster" note="Stablemaster Kenefick" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Shelves filled with tastefully arranged trophies and ribbons line one wall of the Stablemaster's office, and the wall opposite is taken up with books describing all aspects of horse care and instruction in equestrian skills.  An ornate desk, set upon wood carved horse-hoof feet is pushed against a window overlooking the stableyard.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red door" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Training Field" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The air is filled with the scent of fresh grass and the smell of horses.  A narrow pathway opens into a practice field for trainers and their spirited horses.  High fences covered in ivy and moss offer jumpers a challenging course.  The field also features a row of barrels and a low brick wall that gives the horses variety of tasks as their handlers put them through their paces.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Training Field" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Another practice area opens up, with the scent of fresh grass and the smell of horses in sharp contrast to the fragrant roses planted against a nearby brick wall.  Wooden barrels and fences provide the perfect opportunity for practicing jumps and turns.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="213" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="211" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Jousting Field" note="Jousting Field" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sectioned off for more strenuous training, this jousting field offers benches for watchers to be comfortably seated.  A ring of tall oak trees forms a natural stadium for horses and their riders to showcase their jousting abilities.  Not a day goes by that some poor soul isn't led off the field by helpful spectators.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="212" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Stables" note="Stables" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The pungent smell of horses is kept at bay by a wreath of dried herbs and flowers hung on the stall doors of this huge stable.  Made of the finest of maple and oak, each uniform stall is pristinely kept, with nary a straw out of place.  Various instruments of the trade are hung upon one wall, all in neat order.  A trough of fresh water is kept full by young boys, often seen carrying buckets from a nearby well.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="A Bit For Horses, Entrance" note="Bit For Horses" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Dark oak-paneled walls adorned with oval mirrors and lace-covered shelves enclose this room.  Wide arches on each side of the room lead to more merchandise.  Burgundy velvet settees and chairs are comfortably situated to offer customers a place to rest while contemplating their purchases.</description>
    <position x="520" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="A Bit For Horses, Feed" note="Feed" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Eager young clerks stand behind a dark oak counter ready to take orders and handle the horse's feed that is being sold.  From stacks of hay to bags of oats, they lift and haul them from the nearby loading dock and neatly place them along the wooden paneled walls.</description>
    <position x="540" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="A Bit For Horses, Barding" note="Barding" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The fresh smell of leather permeates the air adrift from the newly made saddles and gear that reside in this room.  Sturdy racks and shelves hold various items, from simple horse's brushes to elaborate flanchards polished to perfection.</description>
    <position x="500" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small archway" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="A Bit For Horses, Backroom">
    <description>A cheerful fire blazes from a brick fireplace along the far wall, a cast-iron teakettle warming inside it.  Brown leather armchairs standing before the fireplace offer a perfect spot for a break.  A narrow stairway at one end leads up into the second story.</description>
    <position x="500" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small archway" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow stairway" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="A Bit For Horses, Top Of Stairs" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A narrow stairwell leading back down to the main floor is covered with a well-worn carpet.  Set between a green door and a blue door is a painting of a stunning black stallion.</description>
    <position x="520" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow stairwell" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green door" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="A Bit For Horses, Clerk's Room">
    <description>Neat and tidy describes this room with its small quilt-covered bed and oak wardrobe.  Green throw rugs cover the floor and carvings of horses line a couple of narrow shelves.  A bouquet of dried daisies tied with leather cord hang upside down from the top of an arched window.</description>
    <position x="520" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green door" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="A Bit For Horses, Workroom">
    <description>Tables line one wall of this workroom, covered with neatly folded cloth and rough carvings.  A dark green couch sits opposite with a maple table placed beside it.  Candlelight flickers making shadows against the walls of this quiet area.</description>
    <description>Tables line one wall of this workroom, covered with cloth and rough carvings.  A dark green couch sits opposite with a maple table placed beside it.  Arched windows offer light to those working on various projects, from mending caparisons to making handcrafted brushes.</description>
    <position x="540" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="North Turnpike, Farmland">
    <description>Northwest of the road, a burnt-out farmhouse stands, or perhaps lies is a better word, since all that time or war has left is a stone chimney, cold among the meadow grasses.  Bright splashes of color -- wild red roses, orange butterfly weed, yellow day-lilies -- surround the ruins, like nature's funeral wreath.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble tower" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Rugglestone Close, Glennview Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Whitewash and dark oak beams mix on the tiny half-timbered cottages which line the cobblestoned lane.  Granite-topped brick walls surround the houses, their hard outlines softened by deep green moss which clings to the mortar.  Kitchen gardens grow within the shelter of the walls -- herbs, fruit trees and vegetables all within easy reach of the door.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="224" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Rugglestone Close, Glennview Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The tile roofs of the cottages along the lane are carefully laid out to channel rainwater away from the plaster walls and into barrels, where it may be collected for use in cooking and laundry.  A tangled mass of ivy sends winding tendrils out to wrap around the brick chimneys and walls of one cottage, leaving little to see but the diamond-shaped panes of glass in its windows.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Rugglestone Close, Glennview Lane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A rishyarla bush grows close to the wall surrounding a nearby home, its pale yellow blossoms filling the air with an intense, sweet fragrance.  Like the other cottages which line the street, the half-timbered structure shows signs of careful upkeep.  The shrubs surrounding the house are carefully pruned, and cheesecloth netting protects the fruit trees from the ravages of the local birds.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Rugglestone Close, The Common" note="Rugglestone Close" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>At the center of the close, a grassy square provides an open area where cattle graze during the day.  The hoarse bray of a mule mingles with the sharp noise of a chisel as a stonemason works on the other side of the square, shaping the stones for a new fence.  A gravel-lined path leads to a small rose-covered gazebo.</description>
    <description>At night, young people gather beneath a rose-covered gazebo in the center of the square.  Lively strains of music float through the air to set toes tapping and tempt even the most conservative matron to remember the carefree days of her youth.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gazebo" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Rugglestone Close, Poltrefanli Road" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Painted wooden planters filled with herbs or colorful flowers grow outside the windows of cottages lining the street.  Within the brick walls surrounding each house, tiny gardens grow in the limited space.  At one home, a row of pies cools on the window ledge sending a tantalizing aroma wafting across the cobblestone street.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Rugglestone Close, Shar'hen Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Diamond-shaped panes of thick, wavy glass attest to the age of the homes which line the cobblestoned streets.  Impurities in the glass have resulted in a faint violet tint to the glazing, an attractive contrast to the blackened solder which holds the windows together.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="224" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Rugglestone Close, Poltrefanli Road" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The dark oak beams of the cottages have been carved with fanciful figures of gargoyles and fae, or with intricate knotwork patterns which run along the front of the homes.  Other homes have stark white plaster walls broken by a decorative arrangement of the exposed oak beams.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Rugglestone Close, Poltrefanli Road" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Nestled amidst the homes of the close, a tiny shop displays an assortment of carpets and other floor coverings hanging from its wall.  Imported from distant lands like Aesry Surlaenis'a and Mer'Kresh, the rugs feature wool dyed in vibrant shades of scarlet, blue and golden, and woven into intricate floral or geometric designs.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tiny shop" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Rugglestone Close, Du'hen Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Housewives gather to gossip over the brick walls which divide the half-timbered cottages around the square.  Their sharp glances measure the probable worth of passersby, or take in the poorly mended sleeve of a neighbor's gown, all of which is discussed in low tones as they fold laundry or work in their tiny garden plots.</description>
    <description>The streets are quiet in the evening, the shadows partially dispelled by the warm glow of candle light which streams through the windows of nearby cottages.  The stillness is broken only by the faint clatter of footsteps against the cobblestones, or the occasional barking of a neighbor's dog.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Rugglestone Close, Gazebo on the Common" note="Gazebo on the Common">
    <description>The soft pine floorboards of the gazebo have been polished to a warm, golden glow by the footsteps of dancers who gather here during the evening.  In one corner, a semicircle of music stands holds sheet music for a lively medley of songs to be played by musicians while laughing couples perform the steps of a traditional country dance.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Monastery, Side Yard">
    <description>This small yard is rather enclosed but is maintained very well.  Covering the entire lawn is a bed of healthy-looking green grass, and a narrow fence connects to a small wooden building nearby, surrounding the peaceful area.  The walls of the structure look very freshly painted in a plain grey color.</description>
    <position x="660" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cloister" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Monastery, Monks' Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Plain white walls interspersed with pillars rise to meet a low ceiling.  Each plaster wall is lined with burning oil lamps set on small shelves in even intervals.  Light streams in through a single stained glass window set high above the entrance, creating a perfect circle of blue-tinged light on the cold marble floor.</description>
    <description>Plain white walls interspersed with pillars rise to meet a low ceiling.  Each plaster wall is lined with burning oil lamps set on small shelves in even intervals, casting flickers of shadow across the cold stone marble.  Noise from crickets outside echoes quietly through the wide hallway, punctuated occasionally by the distant hoot of an owl.</description>
    <position x="680" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Monastery, Monks' Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>White marble columns flecked with veins of silver and jade stand at regular intervals of this wide hallway, with doors to individual sleeping areas spaced between them.  The cool marble floor is bare, although polished and very clean.  Standing in one corner is a small vase that holds a delicate fern, the small plant thriving in the cool indoors.</description>
    <position x="700" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Monastery, Monks' Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Light streams unhindered through an arched window on the eastern wall, illuminating small motes drifting through the hall.  Doors on either side of the hall lead to the monks' living quarters.  A lone wooden bench pushed against the wall gives a place for brief respite for the weary.</description>
    <description>Burning hot in the corner of the room, an iron brazier illuminates the wide hallway, staining the ceiling above it with circles of dark smoke.  Doors on either side of the hall lead to the monks' living quarters.  A lone wooden bench pushed against the wall gives a place for brief respite for the weary.</description>
    <position x="700" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron stairs" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Monastery, Monks' Quarters" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A single small painting hangs on the northern wall of this wide hallway, placed on one of the columns between the doors to the individual monks' quarters.  A bright spot of color in an otherwise monotone area, the artwork depicts an elaborate forest scene that contrasts sharply with the sterile hall.</description>
    <position x="680" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Monastery, Narrow Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Barely wide enough for two people to walk side by side, this cramped hallway has been left undecorated, designed more for function than show.  The ceiling slopes sharply and shows the underside of the roof overhead, while the plain wooden floor is softened somewhat by a runner of deep red carpet.</description>
    <position x="740" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron stairs" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Monastery, Narrow Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Bare ends of nails are still visible in the wooden walls, making this hallway seem almost like an afterthought.  Although the beginnings of paint and plaster are visible, the project appears to have been abandoned halfway through.  Only the deep red carpeting is fully in place.  The cramped hall is very poorly lit, with deep shadows lurking in every corner.</description>
    <position x="740" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Monastery, Narrow Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The wooden walls in this portion of the monks' quarters are left unpainted, the area seeming unfinished.  Deep red carpeting softens the floor, although the fabric is marred with a little dust.  A lone oil lamp burns on a table in the corner of the windowless hall, carefully isolated from the walls.</description>
    <position x="720" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Monastery, Narrow Hallway" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The ceiling rises sharply to disappear into darkness in a point, marking this location as just underneath the building's watchtower.  Suspended by support beams high overhead is a platform made of wood, the walls rising past it in all directions.</description>
    <position x="720" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Monastery, Watch Tower">
    <description>Built on support beams in the center of the tower and ringed by a waist-high railing, the platform is surrounded on all sides by open-air windows, offering a panoramic view of the monastery below.  Grapevines to the northwest spread out next to the common area, while several still-ruined portions litter the southeastern grounds.</description>
    <position x="700" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb iron ladder" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Monastery, Dining Hall">
    <description>A large, ornate table covered with a white cloth shows that this expansive room may have once served as a dining hall.  However, the furniture stands disused and has been pushed far to one side to make way for a large obelisk in the center of the room.  Several arches thinly edged in silver cross high overhead in a sunburst pattern, displaying masterfully carved architecture.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron doors" destination="186" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Monastery, Dining Hall">
    <description>Hanging on the eastern wall is a tapestry painting with a nearly blank canvas, the few splashes of paint vaguely resembling the dawn sun rising over a calm blue ocean.  It gives a bit of color to the otherwise large, spartan dining hall, which is dominated by a tall obelisk in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Monastery, Dining Hall">
    <description>A series of towering glass windows rises to the west, letting light filter in from outside.  Standing in the center of the expansive room is a tall marble obelisk, made of chiseled marble but quite plain.  Pushed up against the northern wall is a plain-looking bench, lightly padded across the top with a light red cushion.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Monastery, Dining Hall">
    <description>Light streams in through towering glass windows on the western wall rising in elaborate arches, hints of colored glass marring their edges slightly.  The rays illuminate a tall obelisk standing in the center of the expansive room.  An ornate cloth-covered dining table fills the area just under the windows, shoved aside to leave most of the room bare.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="North Tower, Air Floor" note="N Tower|Tower North|Air Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A dark grey carpet decorated with a pattern of crossing black lightning bolts covers the floor, matching the decoration on the grey-painted walls.  A constant, low thrum hangs just inside the range of hearing, its source nearby but not readily apparent.  Doors spaced in an even circle around the perimeter lead to initiates' private cells.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble staircase" destination="248" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="North Tower, Earth Floor" note="Earth Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Bare, dark soil forms the floor underfoot.  The stony walls surrounding this circular room are similarly devoid of decoration, keeping instead the plain, natural look preferred by those mages who favor the element of Earth.  Doors leading to the initiates' private cells line the walls.</description>
    <position x="270" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb marble staircase" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="North Tower, Water Floor" note="Water Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Deep blue carpeting covers the floor, its surface cut in a manner that suggests the rippling of waves upon the surface of a lake.  Bright blue spirals, representing the element of water, fill the walls between a series of doors leading to initiates' private cells.  The air here is moist and cool upon the skin.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-270" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="247" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="North Tower, Fire Floor" note="Fire Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Lush, red carpeting covers the floor, muffling any ambient noise into oblivion.  Images of bloated red suns, representing the element of fire, fill the walls between a series of doors leading to initiates' private cells.  The air here is significantly warmer than on the tower's other floors, although the reason is not readily apparent.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="North Tower, Aether Floor" note="Aether Floor" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Carpeting the color of a death shroud covers the floor, devouring the light as hungrily as Aldauth consumes souls.  The walls are devoid of decoration, instead painted a uniform black to match the floor.  Only the doors leading to initiates' cells betray any hint of color in this otherwise cold, bleak room.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-290" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Rakshalla's Carpets" note="Rakshalla's Carpets" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Brightly colored carpets lie in stacks upon the floor of the shop, with narrow aisles between them to allow customers to browse through the goods offered for sale.  In the far corner of the shop, a young merchant stands behind the counter, ready to take your order (and your money) with a cheerful smile.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="Rakshalla's Carpets, Prayer Rugs" note="Prayer Rugs" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Incense burns in carved ivory holders shaped like scowling gargoyles or dainty nymphs.  The heady scent clings to clothing as well as the prayer rugs stacked in neat piles around the room.  Behind the counter, Rakshalla's daughter Imfini stands ready to take an order.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-210" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="North Turnpike, Meadow Trail" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Buffered by forest to the north, this meandering trail is shaded by towering deobar trees high overhead.  Sparsely laid out, the trees provide an attractive shelter to the homes nestled amidst the foliage, while a large meadow opens up away from the forest.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="North Turnpike, Meadow Trail" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The sporadic chiming of the nearby monastery bell rests, blanketing the area in silence.  Wildflowers twinkle in the light shed by nearby homes, giving their colorful tones an eerie cast.</description>
    <position x="90" y="-50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="North Turnpike, Meadow Trail" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Wooden pallets form an uneven trail through the thicker woods.  Massive blueberry bushes dot the area creating a dense canopy for small skittering woodland animals.  Tucked into the overgrowth, thatched cottages melt into their surroundings, creating harmony between habitation and the natural world.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="North Turnpike, Meadow Trail" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The soft babbling sounds of a nearby brook mingle with the occasional scuffling of small creatures and the ever present chirrups of local birds.  A pair of benches line the cobbled brick pathway that encircles a massive pagoda tree surrounded by tall grasses bent to either side from the traffic of local residents.</description>
    <position x="110" y="-50" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="256" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Monastery, Marble Hallway">
    <description>The long stretch of corridor bears windows on the right side and a set of doors on the left, and is sparkling clean as if washed and dusted very recently.  Sloping stone ceilings arch upward, supported by marble pillars that stand at even intervals.  The dark marble floor is covered with a rich mahogany carpet that runs the center of the room where the most traffic tends to tread.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow archway" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Monastery, Marble Hallway">
    <description>The long stretch of corridor bears windows on the right side and a set of doors on the left, and is sparkling clean as if washed and dusted very recently.  Sloping stone ceilings arch upward, supported by marble pillars that stand at even intervals.  The dark marble floor is covered with a rich mahogany carpet that runs the center of the room where the most traffic tends to tread.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go classroom door" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elaborate archway" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Monastery, Marble Hallway">
    <description>The long stretch of corridor bears windows on the right side and a set of doors on the left, and is sparkling clean as if washed and dusted very recently.  Sloping stone ceilings arch upward, supported by marble pillars that stand at even intervals.  The dark marble floor is covered with a rich mahogany carpet that runs the center of the room where the most traffic tends to tread.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cathedral door" destination="263" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Monastery, Classroom" note="Classroom">
    <description>Numerous small chairs with desks attached to them form neat rows on the hard wood floor, leading up to a teacher's desk at the front of the room.  A massive chalkboard graces the front wall, although it looks too old and cracked to be of much use in teaching now.  Several fresh potted plants stand in the corners of the room, bringing a hint of life to the old classroom.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-340" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go classroom door" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Monastery, Small Lounge" note="Small Lounge|Lounge">
    <description>With an unusually low ceiling for the monastery, the wide room appears to be a converted wine cellar.  Long couches and tables line the walls of the room, and a few free standing clusters make ideal areas for small meetings.  Numerous silver and red banners drape the walls of the room, covered with abstract patterns that defy a clear meaning.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-340" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go elaborate archway" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Monastery, Dusty Cathedral" note="Cathedral">
    <description>The arching ceiling of the cathedral rises high and comes to numerous points, with gothic spires and elaborate decorations carved directly into the marble.  Long pews line the sides of the long and narrow room, and high, narrow windows filled with plain glass cover both sides of the offset building.  Candles burn in the marble pillars that line the walls, filling the chapel with a soft ambiance.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-340" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cathedral door" destination="260" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Monastery, Cathedral Altar" note="Altar">
    <description>Though it is clear that the area was once used as the cathedral altar, any and all holy icons and symbols are missing.  In their place, a few chairs and a plain table rest on the small dais, and a few small gaethzen lanterns light up the area well.  A fresh coat of off-white paint covers the back wall, expertly covering up yet more religious paraphernalia.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-360" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go side door" destination="265" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Monastery, Stone Wall">
    <description>Blueberry bushes crowd the sides of the monastery wall, their scraggly appearance contrasting the lush green vines that cover its surface.  Though old and unrepaired, the wall stands high and sturdy, obviously built to last.  Nearly invisible among the bushes is a small side door, which looks rather disused and forgotten among the timeless stones.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-360" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go side door" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Birch Copse, Aevren Mod" note="Birch Copse|Aevren Mod|willow tree">
    <description>Towering above the shorter birch, the twisted limbs of the willow tree offer a breathtaking view of the landscape.  The leafless branches clatter and scrape against each other in the wind.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb willow tree" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Monastery, Quiet Library" note="Necromancer Library|Necro Library">
    <description>Plain white marble walls surround the rather large room, which is quite clean and free of dust.  Large bookcases stand in neatly spaced rows, while a ring of shelves line the walls, neatly packed with books from top to bottom.  Several wooden benches provide a place to read, and a simple return desk stands at the front of the library.</description>
    <position x="640" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble archway" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Brambles">
    <description>The bramble bushes aren't quite as dense in this spot, and there are a number of gaps big enough to slide through without doing too much damage to one's person.  This seems to be the intersection of a number of small trails, and judging by how churned and dug up the ground is, it sees a lot of use.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow trail" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide gap" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Brambles">
    <description>A few stray sunbeams shine through the branches of the trees scattered about the thicket, illuminating the grey-green leaves of the brambles, and gleaming on the needle-sharp points of their thorns.  Here and there a clump of tough grass manages to grow around the base of the bushes, but most of the dirt is trampled and dug up, making it impossible for less hardy plants to survive.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow trail" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Brambles">
    <description>The trail curves through the bramble thicket, past some bushes of a different variety.  Foliage presses close all around, spreading both out and up in the competition for resources.  Birds rustle in the bushes, hunting for berries and small insects.  Something else that sounds much larger than a bird rustles through the brambles somewhere close by.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Brambles">
    <description>Something large tore a gap in the brambles to the northwest.  Broken branches and oozing sap define the edges of a hole nearly an armlength across.  Broken and missing thorns testify to the toughness of whatever came crashing through -- the long, sharp spines weren't much of a deterrent.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="291" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Brambles">
    <description>Signs of a scuffle are everywhere.  The dirt underfoot is streaked and spotted with dried blood.  Patches of hide and broken spines lie scattered about, and there's a huge hole in the brambles to the southeast where something large went crashing through in a hurry.  The bark of a large tree is scarred by deep grooves the width of a finger or better, and drying sap streaks the wood in long, viscous dribbles.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Brambles">
    <description>Thick leaf litter covers the ground, making it both spongy and crunchy.  Shriveled berries and little round leaves from the brambles combine with long pointed leaves from the trees to form a dense insulating mulch.  Here and there in the mulch a few mushrooms show their pale heads, thriving in the moist decay.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Brambles">
    <description>Dense bushes grow in irregular mounds, throwing grotesque shapes across what little bare ground there is.  Bright orange berries nestle in the shadows among thorns as long as a finger.  Picking them would probably be painful, and would likely result in a certain amount of bloodletting, but they're not edible anyway, so it doesn't really matter.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tall trees" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Brambles">
    <description>A few tall trees grow in the midst of the thorny brambles, rising high above the bushes.  Long, pointed leaves filter out much of the sun, but the tough thorn bushes do fine all the same.  The soil is rich and loamy, and there's plenty of water, so the bushes and the trees manage to coexist quite well.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go thorny bushes" destination="277" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Brambles">
    <description>Palm-sized tracks pressed deeply into the ground stand out against the lighter colored leaf litter.  Broken branches and bruised foliage up to the height of a large Human's shoulder tell a tale of violence, as do the darkened spots and streaks of blood spattered about.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go web-choked trees" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Brambles">
    <description>Spiderwebs festoon the branches of the trees up overhead, draped and swagged like festival bunting.  The brambles below the trees are bare of webbing, although well-trimmed with long, sharp thorns.  Grey-green leaves spiral up the branches, large and round closer to the roots, small and oval at the tips.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="286" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go broken branches" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rising slope" destination="281" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Brambles">
    <description>There must be something good in the soil of the low rise to the northwest, because the brambles and other plants growing up there are lush and thick, forming an impenetrable barrier.  The thorn bushes spread across the slope in grey-green mounds, having penetrated into every available span of ground until they stand silhouetted against the sky at the top of the rise.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go downard slope" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Brambles">
    <description>Signs of a mighty conflagration are everywhere.  Scarred furrows in the ground make footing uncertain.  Blackened thorn branches wave like spiny skeletons, stripped of leaves and hardened by fire.  Heat-fused lumps of something unidentifiable lie scattered about -- driven into the ground, entangled in the brambles, flattened across the backs of raw wounds in the bark of trees.  Something unimaginably hot has burned a huge gap in the undergrowth to the south, like a white-hot poker sizzling through flesh.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="283" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Brambles">
    <description>Dense brambles grow on the slope to the northwest, protecting the low rise with a wall of finger-length thorns.  The track underfoot has been churned up by passing feet, the leaf litter thrown about to reveal the rich dirt beneath.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go downard slope" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Brambles">
    <description>A huge burned clearing, half a dozen long strides across, lies bare and blackened.  Even the tough brambles gave way before the heat of whatever came into this place, incinerated by the fire and now doubtless lying unidentifiable among the charred rubble and blackened dust crunching underfoot.  In the center of the consumed circle is a pit, a dark hole burrowed deep into the ground at a steep angle.  An acrid smell fills the air, sharp and sour, penetrating everything.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="Brambles">
    <description>The sound of calling birds blends with the rustles and crackles coming from all around the bramble thicket.  Thorny branches tremble in the breeze, dense living walls forming painful barriers in all but a very few directions.  Some scuffled tracks in the moist ground lead away to the north.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rising slope" destination="283" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="Brambles, Clearing">
    <description>Dense, thorny bushes press in from all sides, grabbing at hair and clothing and dangling straps.  A single tree spreads its branches overhead, filtering out the sunlight and casting dancing shadows on the foliage below.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="287" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Brambles, Clearing">
    <description>A huge oak tree stands sentinel in the center of a large clearing.  The bramble bushes stop suddenly around the edges, as though someone had drawn a wavering line across which they're forbidden to pass.  Short green grass grows here, although it's torn up in places, and a few flowers manage to bloom in spots and crannies.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="286" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="Brambles, Clearing">
    <description>The oak tree in the center of the clearing casts a large patch of shade here on its north side.  A few ferns grow at the base of the trunk, providing a feathery border to the expanse of green grass that covers the ground between the tree and the brambles.  Off on the eastern side of the clearing the brambles give way to dense, mounding berry bushes.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Brambles, Clearing">
    <description>Bright green berry bushes grow in rounded piles to the east of the oak tree, only gradually giving way to the brambles on the southern curve of the clearing.  Patches of bare dirt show dark against the lighter green of the grass, places where the ground has been torn up and smoothed over.  A few grey-green sprouts grow here and there in the grass, but none more than a couple of inches tall.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="288" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Brambles">
    <description>Crackles and rustles betray the presence of... something... moving in the brambles up the slope to the northwest.  The thorny bushes are so dense in that direction, however, that not even a Halfling child could manage to penetrate them.  Interspersed among the brambles are a few trees, spotted here and there, spreading their green canopies over the harsher undergrowth.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Brambles">
    <description>Tracks about the size of a large palm show clearly in the firmly packed dirt.  Grey-green leaves, liberally spiked with long, sharp thorns, spread out from either side.  The foliage casts deep shadows across the tracks, emphasizing their size and depth.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide gap" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Brambles">
    <description>The narrow game trail runs from the northwest to the southeast, winding round and about the bramble bushes.  A smaller track pushes into the undergrowth to the northeast.  Cracked and splintered branches and scarred ground make it look like the northeastern track is of recent creation.  Broken thorns suggest that whatever made the new trail probably didn't have a good time doing it.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go winding track" destination="299" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brambles" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Brambles">
    <description>A flowering vine twines through the tangle of brambles, winding its tendrils around the woody branches, uncaring of their sharp thorns.  Large green leaves shaped like arrowheads decorate the vines, swaying in the breeze.  Here and there a flower lifts its head, trumpet shaped, striped in pink and white.  The blossoms show a delicate contrast to the tough bramble bushes with their small leathery leaves.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go game trail" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Brambles">
    <description>Small round leaves, grey-green with a white streak down the middle, cover the branches of the brambles which form this thicket.  Although the leaves grow in dense masses, they're unable to hide the sharp thorns which protect the bushes.  A pleasant, spicy scent emanates from the leaves, and when the breeze dies down and the air is still, the smell is sharp enough to sting one's sinuses.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Brambles">
    <description>Dense brambles press in on all sides, giving this place a claustrophobic feel.  The few narrow gaps in the bushes are barely navigable, and from each branch and twig long, sharp spines threaten scratches and punctures.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="296" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden bridge" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow gap" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Brambles">
    <description>Tiny grey-green leaves grow in dense spirals around the branches of the brambles which surround the trail.  In actuality it's hardly a trail -- more a gap in the foliage, beyond which is another gap, and perhaps another.  The gaps are narrow, and look like they were made by animals rather than people.  This place belongs to its four-footed inhabitants, and the clinging, snagging thorns are a warning to all others who come here.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow gap" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="Brambles">
    <description>Something made its hurried way along this winding track, traveling northward as though driven by anger or fear.  The track has been forced through the brambles, and is none too wide.  Damaged bushes and blobs of hardened sap mark the passage of whatever did this.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go winding track" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Brambles">
    <description>A deep gouge in the tough bark of a tree, about four feet above the ground, marks the place where the track makes an abrupt change in direction.  The gouge, a furrow the length of a Human's hand marked with a deep hole the length and width of a finger, is on the south side of the tree, indicating that whatever hit it was traveling north at some speed when it hit.  It seems to have wrenched itself free and then thundered on to the northeast.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="299" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Brambles">
    <description>The trail, already narrow, comes to a stop here.  The bramble bushes grow more densely to the north, and although they show signs of splintering in places, they stand stout and firm.  There is little else here but a few bones, large enough to have survived the ministrations of temperature and weather and ants.  The ground has been churned up recently, so much so that no tracks are evident.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway" note="Daragrym|Risen Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Built into a former clock tower, the monastery's laboratories are set at regular intervals in a perpetual stairway that winds upward in a clockwise direction.  Freezing cold air wafts through the hallways, and bits of frost collect at the edges and corners of the walls and floor.  Very faint chanting and murmuring sounds drift upwards from the tower's basement, though the area is quite silent otherwise.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="308" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway" note="Kelasune" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Built into a former clock tower, the monastery's laboratories are set at regular intervals in a perpetual stairway that winds upward in a clockwise direction.  Freezing cold air wafts through the hallways, and bits of frost collect at the edges and corners of the walls and floor.  A steady 'drip, drip, drip' noise comes from one wall, as tiny runnels of a pale reddish substance trickle down it.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway">
    <description>Built into a former clock tower, the monastery's laboratories are set at regular intervals in a perpetual stairway that winds upward in a clockwise direction.  Freezing cold air wafts through the hallways, and bits of frost collect at the edges and corners of the walls and floor.  A small, frosty window looks out onto the monastery's northern courtyard, though sealed off with iron bars.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="311" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="312" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway">
    <description>Built into a former clock tower, the monastery's laboratories are set at regular intervals in a perpetual stairway that winds upward in a clockwise direction.  Freezing cold air wafts through the hallways, and bits of frost collect at the edges and corners of the walls and floor.  The steps narrow a bit, following the corners of the square-shaped tower.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="313" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="314" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway">
    <description>The top floor of the tower is colder than the rest, and a large device at the top of the stairs blocks off access to the top of the former clock tower.  Freezing cold air drifts downward from the device in even waves, spilling frost onto the carpeted stairs and down the hallway.  The area is very quiet, the only noise coming from the soft whirring of the strange magical device that seems to be generating the cold.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="315" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="316" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="310" y="-170" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="310" y="-190" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="350" y="-210" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="350" y="-230" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="303" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="330" y="-250" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="310" y="-250" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="290" y="-230" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="314" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="290" y="-210" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="315" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="315" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="316" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="325" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="317" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Brokerage Offices">
    <description>Heavy mahogany panels encase the walls of this small room.  The fireplace's curved brick opening reflects the arc of the arched brick entry directly opposite.  A rose velvet settee draped with a delicate white shawl sits below the front window.  Several tall-backed chairs are positioned near the settee, and a narrow refreshment table rests against one wall.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entry" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="318" name="Zoluren Royal Mews, Brokerage Offices">
    <description>This quiet, sparse office holds a simple desk and a couple of cushioned chairs.  Book-lined shelves cover one wall completely, with titles ranging from horse care to adventure stories relating to them.  A single window is covered by long emerald drapes embroidered with brown thread.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <label text="Badgers, Croff Pothanits">
    <position x="150" y="-550" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Badgers, Trollkins">
    <position x="0" y="-390" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="NTR">
    <position x="404" y="-102" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Crossing (North Gate)">
    <position x="160" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="To West Gate">
    <position x="10" y="60" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Granite Gargoyles">
    <position x="140" y="-200" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Skunks">
    <position x="40" y="-160" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pale Grey Death Spirits">
    <position x="0" y="-170" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zoluren Royal Mews">
    <position x="440" y="-80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Rugglestone Close">
    <position x="290" y="-240" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Brambles">
    <position x="159" y="-388" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="North Tower">
    <position x="260" y="-310" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Meadow Trail">
    <position x="20" y="-70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Book">
    <position x="405" y="-320" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Monks' Quarters">
    <position x="666" y="-305" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Graveyard">
    <position x="487" y="-207" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tynick">
    <position x="277" y="-108" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dining Hall">
    <position x="376" y="-238" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="exit (go path)">
    <position x="310" y="-70" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="scavenger giant">
    <position x="10" y="-310" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Jousting">
    <position x="560" y="-120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Stables">
    <position x="550" y="-50" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>