<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Under the Gondola" id="65">
  <node id="1" name="Dragon's Spine, Astrar's Sorrow" note="Map66_Shard_to_Gondola_Area.xml|STR|Shard">
    <description>The canyon terminates in frosty splendor, though the trail continues on, steeply switch-backing its way up the slick mountainside beside a stunning waterfall.  Hanging from a valley far above, Astrar's Sorrow descends as a glittering cascade of frozen water forming a pleated veil of icy tears that fall perpetually without movement to the solid river of ice below.</description>
    <position x="120" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Dragon's Spine, Behind the Waterfall">
    <description>Footing becomes quite treacherous here as each new step brings forth more uncertainty.  Tiny rivulets of icy water trickle down from the waterfall and freeze, adding to the already slippery sheet of ice on the ground.  The more adventurous traveler might either chance the dark woodlands ahead or ferret out some way to penetrate and attempt to swim the frozen river.  The less daring of souls will quickly retreat from whence they came.</description>
    <position x="120" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark woodlands" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small crack" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>A bitter chill lingers in the air and sends shivers to creep along your spine.  Dense clusters of mountain ash trees, heavily laden with icicles, line the rocky trail and bow reverently towards the earth.</description>
    <position x="100" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cleft" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Rows of spruce and fir trees rise neatly towards a pinnacle far ahead over the horizon.  Silence looms, marred only by the occasional skitter of some small creature foraging for the rare morsel of food beneath the ice and snow.</description>
    <position x="120" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Tiny pebbles crunch noisily underfoot as parcels of snow turn to patches of withered, brown grass.  Occasionally, your footsteps splash into a puddle of icy water, interrupting the solitude.</description>
    <position x="140" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>The soft chitter of a frisky squirrel quickly flitting from tree to tree overhead captures your attention.  Deep green ground ivy clusters in neat patches across the rocky path, grasping relentlessly for any feasible handhold on the earth.</description>
    <position x="140" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>A persistent tap-tap-tap and then another, deeper tap-tap-tap throbs at the temple as some unseen woodpecker overhead forages for insects deep in the bark of a rowan tree.  Fescue grasses grow tall around the base of each tree, vying for any available moisture.</description>
    <position x="160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Silverwood trees line the hard-packed rocky path, casting long pockets of shadow across the brush.  Red and black berries, in various stages of ripeness, dangle invitingly across the trail from the myriad of chokecherry bushes stealthily hidden in the brown grass.</description>
    <position x="160" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go moss-covered footpath" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Tamarisk bushes display their feathery tendrils, nearly as delicate as the web of a spider.  Each footfall creates a rather hollow sound upon the nearly dry earth.  Emitting a strange, phosphorescent glow, a decaying old log stretches itself full-length across the trail.</description>
    <description>Tamarisk bushes display their feathery tendrils, nearly as delicate as the web of a spider.  Each footfall creates a rather hollow sound upon the nearly dry earth.  Stretched full-length across the trail lies a decaying old log.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fallen log" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Dark Woodlands, Bulen Ond Alcas" color="#008000">
    <description>Ribbons of green surround a clear mountain lake to provide food and shelter for various fauna.  Nearby, the rugged mountain peaks carve out a majestic skyline against a pristine backdrop.  Footprints lead the way along the slender trail encircling the water.</description>
    <position x="120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Dark Woodlands, Bulen Ond Alcas" color="#008000">
    <description>Massive willow trees droop low to dip their feathery tendrils into the cool water beneath their feet.  Cattails and other various reeds line the banks of the lake and harbor a multitude of tiny insect larvae awaiting maturity.</description>
    <position x="120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Dark Woodlands, Bulen Ond Alcas" color="#008000">
    <description>Peering up from the edge of the trail, twin saplings lean gracefully into each other as if attempting to gain added strength as a single unit.  Bright pink and white water lilies glide leisurely across the faintly rippling surface of the lake, forming a perfect mirror reflection of themselves against the clear pool, some floating close enough to the shoreline to be captured by an admiring traveler.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Dark Woodlands, Bulen Ond Alcas" color="#008000">
    <description>By the edge of the narrow footpath, a mountain ash tree stands tall, keeping close watch over the creatures that inhabit the lakeside.  Painstakingly carved into its bark is the outline of a heart with an arrow through its middle.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Dark Woodlands, Bulen Ond Alcas" color="#008000">
    <description>Up ahead lies a lush garden of evening primroses, their golden yellow blooms fluttering softly with the slightest breeze off the lakefront.  Fragile moths glide from petal to petal imbibing themselves with the heavenly nectar.</description>
    <description>Up ahead lies a lush garden of evening primroses, their tiny heads bowed in protection against the rays of the sun.  Bumblebees flit lightly from stem to stem in their vain attempt to reach the heavenly nectar inside the closed blooms.</description>
    <position x="60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Willowy branches reach out from the low bushes lining both sides of the trail.  Slender fingers laced with thorns await any opportunity to snag an errant coat sleeve or a patch of bare flesh, claiming it for their own.</description>
    <position x="160" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb fallen log" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep embankment" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>The craggy incline abruptly becomes steeper and begins to take its toll on the calves of the hiker.  Perched overhead on a low-hanging branch, a tiny brown squirrel sits in death-like stillness, its cheeks nearly overflowing with the most recently acquired of provisions.</description>
    <position x="180" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock shelf" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Clusters of silverwood and spruce trees thicken to form a deeply shaded canopy and lengthen even further the encroaching shadows.  A rather ominous stillness settles over the ground, as if the creatures that normally inhabit the region are hidden in their burrows cowering in fear.</description>
    <position x="200" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky slope" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Rows of roughly hewn fir planks are lashed haphazardly together to form an obviously man-made ramp of sorts across a shallow creek.  Peering wide-eyed up from beneath the floorboards rests a pair of warty bullfrogs, mouths agape in an otherwise silent croak.</description>
    <position x="200" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ramp" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Any traveler desiring to avoid an ice-water bath in the chilly waters of the creek bed below must step very carefully over the decaying ramp's rotting planks.  Tall mountain ash trees cast long, dark shadows dimming the vision even further and making it quite difficult to distinguish the moldering logs from the intact ones.</description>
    <position x="200" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ramp" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Slippery green moss stealthily weaves its way in and out amongst the granite stepping-stones that lead further up the steep incline.  A single errant step may be all that is necessary to send one careening backwards head over heel towards the base of the cliff.</description>
    <position x="220" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stepping-stones" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Clusters of chicory crop up sporadically along the sides of the trail, their pale blue flowers bringing just a hint of a welcome glimmer of brightness to an otherwise shadowy landscape.  Off to the north, clumps of stems lie broken, recently trampled, and oozing their milky sap onto the ground.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stepping-stones" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail" color="#008000">
    <description>Towering silverwood trees sway silently with the slightest breeze, shadow-boxing with each other for dominance of their individual territories.  Competing in vain for space, tiny white-capped mushrooms spring up randomly at the base of each tall trunk.</description>
    <position x="240" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gap" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail">
    <description>Utter stillness and the grandiose play of nature settles across the landscape.  Wildflowers form an elegant multicolored drapery across the towering bluff and lend a sweet aroma to the cool mountain air.</description>
    <position x="240" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep embankment" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail">
    <description>Deep shadows begin to fall long across the hillside as the foliage grows denser.  Birds chitter softly back and forth to each other from the safety of the trees, as if signaling a quiet warning to all who traverse the woodlands.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Dark Woodlands, Rugged Trail">
    <description>Nature, with all its mysterious forces, works undisturbed in this remote wilderness.  The soft gurgle of nearby waters becomes welcome music to the ears, though the stand of towering silverwood and spruce trees on the horizon does not offer up the same invitation.</description>
    <position x="220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Undergondola, Narrow Path">
    <description>Widening and flattening out, the steep climb begins to level into a narrow path up the mountainside.  Tall purple lupine blossoms line the trail, their fragrance mingling with the crisp mountain air in a refreshing pause on an arduous journey.</description>
    <position x="220" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone wall" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Bright orange and crimson red paintbrush climbs stealthily in and out of the cracks in the rocks.  Guarding its abode, a large brown lizard blinks sleepily from its perch on a rocky ledge above.</description>
    <position x="220" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb slanted ledge" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Eroded by time and the elements into the seemingly impenetrable rock, a narrow rift provides a possible venue to further the perilous climb.  Mountain laurel lines the breach in the cliff face with just a hint of purple color.</description>
    <position x="220" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow rift" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>The climb grows ever steeper, dizzyingly high above the deep confines of the chasm below.  Chilly breezes caress your face, bringing a silent shiver as they brush lightly across your brow.</description>
    <position x="220" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow rift" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>The peak of the mountain comes into view above, though the shortage of suitable footholds along the way belittles all hope of attaining that goal at times.  Looming just ahead stands a huge boulder, heavily splattered with a dark red stain.</description>
    <position x="220" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb slanted ledge" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>A pair of mockingbirds perches leisurely along a slanted ledge.  Their soulless black eyes peer about, uncaring as to whether or not anyone joins them there.  Each new step up the face of the cliff tosses down a shower of rock fragments, leaving one to ponder even further just how advisable this journey may be.</description>
    <position x="240" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb slanted ledge" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>The forces of nature are constantly at work, slowly breaking down even the largest boulders only to deposit them elsewhere and build new ones.  Occasional lone branches of fir trees stick their arms out of the hard rock at random, possibly giving the climber an opportunity to progress further up the mountainside.</description>
    <position x="240" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky overhang" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Water trickles slowly in patches down the face of the cliff, making it even more perilous to obtain a firm grasp for the climb.  Polypody ferns grow thick and dangle leisurely from between any available crack in the stone wall, but quickly prove to be too frail to aid in the ascent whatsoever.</description>
    <position x="260" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky overhang" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Sweet alyssum pokes its tiny white-flowered blooms out in rounded domes from among the hard stone.  Skittering quickly back and forth along the rocks, a brown newt with red eyelids frantically searches for a suitable hiding place with the rustle of any footstep.</description>
    <position x="260" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock face" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Clusters of moss peek out in patches across the mountainside, vying with adventurers for a safe place to cling to the hard stone.  Nestled cozily on a slanted ledge, a large yellow-brown bull snake dozes, midline still bulging with evidence of its most recent meal.  An occasional contented hiss echoes softly across the summit.</description>
    <position x="280" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock face" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Firm handholds are hard to come by as clumps of what at first appear to be solid rock often crumble to the touch, leaving one to hang by mere fingertips alone.  From her well-appointed nursery in the small niche overhead, a mother chickadee warily surveys the area while guarding her cherished family.</description>
    <position x="280" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky crag" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Clay and limestone form distinctive layers in the strata and harden to take the shape of a steep cliff face on the side of the mountain.  Off to the south stands a small grove of spruce trees, their massive trunks standing guard over the earth.</description>
    <position x="260" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky crag" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grove" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>Heavy boulders leap out from the middle of the trail and hinder passage through the chasm.  Some stand proudly, reaching toward the sky, while others topple over to lean one against the other like a pair of drunks reeling home after a night at the tavern.</description>
    <position x="240" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>Off to one side of the faint trail through the chasm, a towering silverwood tree stands out amongst the otherwise barren and rocky landscape.  At its base is a stone marker etched with faintly visible lettering.  A lone chicory branch, withered and brown, lies next to the simple landmark.</description>
    <position x="240" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>Silence settles across the chasm, broken only by the occasional soft shower of pebbles down the cliff face.  Retreat continues to remain a viable option against whatever unseen foe might await in the blackness ahead.</description>
    <position x="220" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cave opening" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Chasm, Vertical Pothole">
    <description>A stand of tall trees comes into view overhead, further dimming the light and making it increasingly difficult to find a foothold up through the pothole.  Caution is absolutely necessary to prevent a case of vertigo from settling in and overwhelming the senses.</description>
    <position x="280" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb craggy niche" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb branch" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Chasm, Vertical Pothole">
    <description>The steep climb shows no signs of leveling out nor of providing any further assistance to a weary mountaineer.  Writhing gently inside a craggy niche, a large black snake attempts to wriggle out of a withered skin, its cloud-covered eyes both piercing and merciless.</description>
    <position x="280" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb craggy niche" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Chasm, Vertical Pothole">
    <description>Vegetation creeps in and out of the face of the rock.  One possible avenue for further exploration appears to be a narrow ledge, barely wide enough to place the toe of a boot-clad foot, that leads straight up the side of the deep chasm.</description>
    <position x="280" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone wall" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Obsidian Pass, Mountain Trail" note="Map62_Southern_Trade_Route_Part_2.xml|Crossing|Leth Deriel">
    <description>Cracks in the sides of the pass ooze a darkness flatter than the glassy black of the smoothed walls.  The silence here is disturbing.</description>
    <position x="260" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb branch" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Deep, narrow crevasses form a somewhat regular crisscross pattern across the sides of the chasm.  Quickly moving back and forth between a gap in the rocks here and a pocket in the cliff face overhead, a large grey vulture carries bits of food to her hatchlings tucked away in the small opening.</description>
    <position x="240" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb slanted ledge" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Undergondola, Cliff Face">
    <description>Pocketing the face of the cliffs are several eroded pits, ranging from the size of marbles to others large enough to hold two grown men.  Vegetation clings tenaciously to life, sending roots into mere cracks in the rocks.</description>
    <position x="240" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb pit" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Dark Woodlands, In the Gap" note="Gap|The Gap" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Silence settles its thickened fingers over the ever-darkening shadows of a large cluster of rowan trees.  Not even the lone cricket dares to venture forth a single chirp lest it awaken a larger and much more sinister being.</description>
    <position x="240" y="0" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest" note="Map62_Southern_Trade_Route_Part_2.xml">
    <description>The hollows and dips in the path are filled with rocks and muddy water.  Wagon-ruts leave indelible tracks in the dirt, insects and various unidentifiable things make their dark homes in the shallow pools that form.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Undergondola, Deep Pit">
    <description>An unusually rancid aroma rises to meet the nostrils.  Lying farther back in a dark corner are the remains of some poor beast, once covered with a white downy coat but now disemboweled as fodder for scavengers.  Small rocks are arranged in a rather crude circle near the carcass, but no ashes are to be found within its perimeter.</description>
    <position x="260" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb large opening" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Old bones lie in haphazard piles along the cavern floor.  In one far corner, a weathered and eyeless skull peers out from beneath the hood of a tattered grey cloak, its bony mouth agape in silent laughter at your courage.  Cold drafts creep along the floor, seeking out every gap in clothing or armor with a bone-chilling touch.</description>
    <position x="160" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb large opening" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Undergondola, Campsite">
    <description>A lush carpeting of mimosa grass forms a soft bedding for the brown canvas tent nestled cozily towards the center of the campsite.  Smooth, flat boulders are strategically placed to allow for friendly conversation.  The smell of a fresh kill slowly roasting over an open firepit further invites the weary traveler to obtain a brief respite from the burdens of an otherwise difficult survival.</description>
    <position x="260" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go canvas tent" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grove" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Undergondola, Canvas Tent">
    <description>Inviting welcome sleep and privacy, a small bedroll of downy snowbeast pelts dominates one side of the tiny alcove.  Various belongings of previous occupants lay scattered about the canvas floor, some obviously of great value and giving pause as to what manner of hasty retreat some poor soul had made.</description>
    <position x="260" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tent flap" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Every footstep, man-made or otherwise, reverberates through the cavern.  Hanging from the ceiling, flocks of bats rustle their wings as they slumber quietly.  Glistening webs, some still fresh and damp to the touch, fall in graceful swags against the walls, as if some lunatic decorator has tried to brighten the dark surroundings.</description>
    <position x="160" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" hidden="True" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" hidden="True" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Undergondola, Chamber" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Half-domed, a large underground chamber opens out, formed from eons of erosion through an ancient earthquake fault.  Water bubbles gently from an effervescent pool at the bottom of a towering cascade, accounting for the cool dampness of the grotto.  Diminutive cave fish, devoid of eyes, intermittently thrust sensitive whiskers into the air from the surface of the frothy waters.</description>
    <position x="140" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" hidden="True" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark tunnel" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb meander" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Tiny rivulets of ice-cold water drop from the ceiling to fall uncaring against the cool stone floor and exposed skin alike.  The dampness of the grotto seeps into your bones to make the cavern seem several degrees colder than it actually is.</description>
    <position x="140" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Darkness envelops all who venture into the dimmest recesses of the grotto.  A loud shriek, full of agony, echoes from deeper within the cavern.  The sound is distorted by distance, making it impossible to clearly distinguish whether it is produced by man or by some beast about to expire at a hunter's blade.</description>
    <position x="140" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" hidden="True" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Cool, dank air flows through the caverns, dampening fur and hair, and weighing heavily against skin and scale alike.  Shadows pool in the corners, making it hard to see, but an occasional wink of red eyes or the glint of a discarded longsword makes it hard to pretend you're all alone.</description>
    <position x="140" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto">
    <description>Rivulets of water trickle down the walls, causing a soft drip to echo throughout the cavern as the tiny droplets splash against the solid rock floor.</description>
    <position x="120" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb large opening" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>An unnatural silence settles across the chasm, broken only by the occasional soft shower of pebbles down the cliff face.  Retreat continues to remain quite the viable option against whatever unseen foe might await in the blackness ahead.</description>
    <position x="100" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cave opening" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>For centuries, feeble trickles of mineral-laden water have run down the walls of the cavern, leaving behind them voluminous calcite draperies.  Folding and curling back and forth along themselves, the shimmering curtains are carefully arranged by the hand of nature.  Even the most talented of artisans could not likely have painted such a display upon a mere canvas landscape.</description>
    <position x="140" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Disorientation begins to take a firm hold as the passages twist and turn in all directions.  Shimmering webs of silver lace dangle from the walls and ceiling, gently but firmly tangling the limbs of any who attempt to make their way through the caverns.</description>
    <position x="160" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" hidden="True" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Darkness envelops all who venture into the dimmest recesses of the grotto.  A loud shriek, full of agony, echoes from deeper within the cavern.  The sound is distorted by distance, making it impossible to clearly distinguish whether it is produced by man or by some beast about to expire at a hunter's blade.</description>
    <position x="160" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Masses of carrot-shaped stalactites descend from the ceiling, forcing one to weave precariously in and out to avoid a sharp welt on the head.  Columns make navigation even more difficult where the low-hanging stalactites flow into stalagmites rising up from the ground.</description>
    <position x="180" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Undergondola, Twisting Grotto" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Every footstep, man-made or otherwise, reverberates through the cavern.  Hanging from the ceiling, flocks of bats rustle their wings as they slumber quietly.  Glistening webs, some still fresh and damp to the touch, fall in graceful swags against the walls, as if some lunatic decorator has tried to brighten the dark surroundings.</description>
    <position x="140" y="480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Undergondola, Dark Tunnel">
    <description>Loud crunching noises underfoot reveal piles of old bones and carcasses in varying states of decomposition, littering the limestone floor and giving off a putrid stench.  The ceiling slopes ever closer to the ground as it ebbs further into the darker recesses of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="140" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb lit opening" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Undergondola, Dark Tunnel">
    <description>Ruthlessly unforgiving, the rough rock walls continue to narrow and squeeze any unsuspecting adventurer into a nearly prone position along the cold, damp ground.  Silken webs drape across the narrow opening in a thinly veiled threat to impede progress even further.</description>
    <position x="160" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Undergondola, Dark Tunnel">
    <description>Barriers of rough, solid rock line the passage and continue to embrace their helpless victims, scratching painfully at any bare patch of skin.  Nearly all sense of both time and space could be quite easily lost without careful concentration on each movement of arms and legs.  Inviting further inspection, a few bleak rays of light appear off in the distance.</description>
    <position x="180" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Undergondola, Dark Tunnel">
    <description>Layered strata form distinct ridges in the limestone walls and offer up nearly flawless impressions of plants and animals from eons past.  High overhead in the cavern ceiling is a small orifice through which stray beams of light alternate with periods of total blackness as a dark shadow intermittently obscures the tiny opening.  A narrow ledge juts out high above the floor along the far wall of the chamber.</description>
    <position x="200" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Undergondola, Fossil Outcrop">
    <description>The fantasy of any respectable paleontologist, all manner of plants and animals are fossilized within a deep pit and surrounded by scattered piles of petrified wood and ashes.  Small, rounded mounds of mostly intact bone and teeth fragments lie arranged in neat clusters that encircle the crater.</description>
    <position x="200" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Twisting Grotto, Meander above the Cascade" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>This slender, twisting passage offers a tight squeeze for even the leanest of travelers trying to make their way through.  Slippery green algae forms a filmy coating over the entire ledge, making footing risky at best.  A sullen grey mist hangs heavily in the air, shrouding the path in a glistening fog.</description>
    <position x="120" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cascade" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Twisting Grotto, Meander above the Cascade" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Clusters of hardened calcite crystals line the rocky floor and crunch loudly beneath each footstep.  Water gurgles nearby and a dizzying glance over the lofty ledge once more reveals a blue-green torrent hurriedly splashing down a cascade towards the grotto floor below.</description>
    <position x="120" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" hidden="True" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cascade" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Twisting Grotto, Meander above the Cascade" color="#FFBF00">
    <description>Fossilized plants and small animal bones are deeply entrenched in the hardened sandstone lining the walls.  A roughly carved depression in the rocky floor forms a primitive square-shaped basin.</description>
    <position x="120" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" hidden="True" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>Standing guard against heedless entry by less cautious explorers, heavy boulders loom large before a series of dark caverns ahead.  Distinct, sinuous markings that cross over themselves in the dirt floor of the chasm reveal the recent passing of those creatures that crawl along on their smooth underbellies alone.</description>
    <position x="100" y="460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>Now drab and browned by the sun, clusters of once-bright orange paintbrush ramble across the landscape.  Rolling and tumbling in the breeze, like dice in a chance game of hazard, the now tangled vines scratch mercilessly at any bare patch of flesh they may encounter as they flit swiftly past.</description>
    <position x="80" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>From its leisurely perch atop a rock-strewn crag, a small brown lizard lightly tastes the air with its tongue and then quickly scurries across the chasm floor with any encroaching footstep.</description>
    <position x="60" y="440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Undergondola, Chasm">
    <description>Boulders of all shapes and sizes litter the landscape, forcing one to have to weave and climb in and around the chasm.  Dust springs up in heavy swirls without warning, bringing tears to the eyes and evoking more than one fit of coughing.</description>
    <position x="60" y="420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Undergondola, Narrow Path">
    <description>From somewhere off in the distance comes the mournful hoot of an owl, awakened uneasily from its peaceful slumber.  The intermittent shadows overhead appear to have confused the otherwise nocturnal creature as to whether or not nightfall has, at long last, arrived.</description>
    <description>From somewhere off in the distance comes the mournful hoot of an owl in search of prey.  Dark shadows appear overhead at regular intervals, at times obscuring even a hint of the moonlight by which this nocturnal creature prefers to hunt.</description>
    <position x="40" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Undergondola, Narrow Path">
    <description>The occasional call of a lone eagle in flight through the abandoned canyon remains the only sound to break the solitude.  Steep slopes covered in loose rubble known as scree are too treacherous to climb, leaving only this twisting path for travelers to make their way through the canyon.</description>
    <description>The occasional clatter of a rock falling down the canyon breaks the stillness of the night.  Steep slopes covered in loose rubble known as scree are too treacherous to climb, leaving only this twisting path for travelers to make their way through the canyon.</description>
    <position x="20" y="400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Undergondola, Narrow Path">
    <description>The breeze echoes with a faint creaking sound as large, black shadows wheel and turn overhead.  Heavy boulders grow denser and crowd out the few sprigs of dry, brown grass that so valiantly attempt to rise from between them.</description>
    <position x="20" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Alongside the River, Narrow Path">
    <description>Parched grasses line the winding path and leave one to wonder how far away the river must be for these simple plants to unable to sustain any nourishment.  Rows of large boulders loom menacingly along the horizon.  Perched atop one of the heavy stones sits a scowling grey vulture, furtively scanning the area in search of the next tasty morsel to scavenge.</description>
    <position x="0" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Alongside the River, Narrow Path">
    <description>Settled unobtrusively beneath a lone spruce tree is a narrow bench of sorts.  Formed of two small boulders with a rough log placed across them, the rigid seating silently offers a welcome pause in an increasingly arduous journey.</description>
    <position x="0" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Alongside the River, Narrow Path">
    <description>Tiny brown saplings peer up from amongst patches of withered grass, fruitlessly attempting to gain some lease on life.  Clusters of rocks spring up across the path, rudely interrupting any view of greenery along the trail.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Alongside the River, Narrow Path">
    <description>Thick taffelberry bushes reach out along the sides of the trail, inviting further exploration deeper into the chasm.  Sparrows chirp noisily to their mates as they flit from bush to bush in their search for any of the dark, juicy berries to take home to their hatchlings.</description>
    <description>Thick taffelberry bushes reach out along the sides of the trail, their branches shrouding your view of anything beyond the path.  Crisp leaves rustle in the darkness as deer or some other unseen creature forages for the sweet, dark berries.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Alongside the River, Narrow Path">
    <description>Towering stands of silverwood and fir trees line the riverbank, their massive trunks dominating the earth and providing a welcome nest amidst their roots for the weary adventurer.  Peeking out from his burrow with beady black eyes, a furry mole cautiously plans an escape route to the water's edge.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Frozen River, The Shallows" color="#000080">
    <description>Currents begin to abate and footing is once more attainable as the waters shallow and the icy film floats away in ever-widening parcels.  A much-welcome rush of fresh air fills the nostrils and inflates the chest with sweet relief upon stepping up out of the deeper waters.  Tall clusters of cattails and fronds of eelgrass line the riverbank.</description>
    <position x="0" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>A quick glance upwards reveals a noticeable thinning of the heavy ice sheet across the water.  Light filters through in patches to reveal a school of tiny minnows attempting to conceal themselves among the hairgrass and coontails lining the silt floor.</description>
    <description>A quick glance upwards reveals an obvious thinning of the heavy ice sheet across the water as moonlight filters through in random patches.  Tiny minnows attempt to conceal themselves from the incandescence amongst the tall grasses lining the silt floor.</description>
    <position x="20" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>While the frigid water remains crystal clear, nearly impenetrable beds of bristly muskgrass and stonewart rise up from the river bottom.  Stealthily entwining their slender branches around arms and legs, they quickly become a nuisance making movement through the brisk currents even more perilous.</description>
    <description>While the frigid water remains crystal clear despite the darkness overhead, nearly impenetrable beds of tall bristly grasses rise up from the river bottom.  Stealthily entwining their slender branches around arms and legs, they quickly become a nuisance making movement through the brisk currents even more perilous.</description>
    <position x="20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>Dark shadows overhead take the form of an ice hut bored into place, quite likely the favorite hunting ground for some nearby fisherman.  Barely discernible beneath the shadow is a small, though perfectly formed circular opening, expertly carved into the ice sheeting above.</description>
    <position x="20" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>Maneuvering effortlessly along on the swift current, a bevy of large multi-colored trout dart in and out amongst each other.  Vision dims even further as the unrelenting frosting across the surface of the water thickens.</description>
    <description>Maneuvering effortlessly along on the swift current, a bevy of some large creature darts past, brushing delicate fins against your face.  Vision dims to near blackness as night settles across the unrelenting sheet of ice over the water.</description>
    <position x="40" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>The icy river takes on a mind of its own as the merciless waters become increasingly difficult to navigate.  Great care is required to suppress the instinctual urge to replenish the lungs with air.  Shivers crawl up and down the limbs of the weary traveler.</description>
    <description>The icy river takes on a mind of its own as the merciless waters become increasingly difficult to navigate.  Darkness abounds and only serves to perpetuate an already lost sense of direction.  Great care is required to suppress the instinctual urge to replenish the lungs with air.  Shivers crawl up and down the limbs of the weary traveler.</description>
    <position x="40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>Fingers and toes are numbed by the bone-chilling cold of the waters.  A large hatch of tiny, newborn salmon floats by, carried along by the ever-strengthening current.</description>
    <description>Fingers and toes are numbed by the bone-chilling cold of the waters.  Darkness obscures vision as a large hatch of some type of small fish floats by, carried along by the ever-strengthening current.</description>
    <position x="20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>Chilling currents grow ever stronger with further navigation along the river bottom.  Overhead, a solid sheet of ice covers the water, trapping you underneath.  One can only hope for the appearance of an occasional pocket of air near the surface.</description>
    <position x="20" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="93" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Frozen River, Beneath the Ice" color="#000080">
    <description>Icy fingers crawl up your spine upon entering the frigid waters.  The overwhelming desire to hold one's breath overtakes all other coherent thought.  A small hole in the thick blanket of ice overhead drifts just barely within reach.</description>
    <description>Icy fingers crawl up your spine upon entering the frigid waters.  The overwhelming desire to hold one's breath overtakes all other coherent thought.  Barely visible against the dark nighttime sky, a small hole in the thick blanket of ice overhead drifts just within reach.</description>
    <position x="0" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <label text="Red Leucros">
    <position x="80" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Yvhh La'tami">
    <position x="240" y="260" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="leads ^">
    <position x="204" y="-25" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Long way to STR, gives stun + head bleeder --&gt;">
    <position x="-20" y="-8" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="&lt;-- Quicker/difficult path to STR">
    <position x="270" y="90" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="To Dragon's Spine">
    <position x="80" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blade Spiders">
    <position x="60" y="360" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Frozen River">
    <position x="-40" y="200" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>