<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Tref Dinta" id="62b">
  <node id="1" name="Woodland Path, Brambles">
    <description>Thick brambles almost completely obscure the pathway, the runners twisting across the ground in a mesh of thorny vines.  Trunks loom above the massed heaps of foliage.  The air feels oppressive, almost as if it has physical weight.</description>
    <position x="100" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadow opening" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Woodland Path, Brambles">
    <description>Rustling sounds echo from the brambles although nothing can be seen except a few shaking leaves.  The thorny bushes have almost completely covered what was once a wide pathway through the woods.  Now all that is left is a twisting trail that soon will be engulfed by the forest.</description>
    <position x="120" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Woodland Path, Thorny Track">
    <description>The forest clears out a bit, allowing a gap in the tree cover that provides a glimpse of sky overhead.  Attached to one tree is a weathered plank with one lone nail still keeping it affixed.  Occasional sounds of running water can be heard in the distance, but the echoes within the trees prevent any idea of where they are coming from.</description>
    <position x="120" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Woodland Path, Thorny Track">
    <description>Gurgling sounds come from the west, perhaps from a stream or spring hidden within the dense forest.  The thorn bushes crowd close to the narrow track, grabbing at passersby almost as if they were alive and wanted to keep intruders out.</description>
    <position x="100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Woodland Path, Rutted Crossing">
    <description>What once was a bridge now lies collapsed across the stream, the beams and planks providing a slippery but passable crossing of the running stream.  The rotting stumps of the supports stand upright in the water, their lower reaches covered with moss that grows in the spray of the brook.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Woodland Path, Before the Gateway">
    <description>Crumbling stone walls end at a gateway inset into the dilapidated enclosure.  Formed from wrought iron bars set upright within a frame, the two panels of the gate have fallen off their hinges and lean drunkenly against the arched gateway.  The gaping space thus formed allows access into the courtyard beyond, while further progress on the pathway is blocked by a wall of thorn bushes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go derelict gate" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Tref Dinta, Courtyard">
    <description>Weeds push through the cobbles of the courtyard which lies within the enclosing stone walls.  An arched gateway pierces the enclosure, allowing egress through the ramparts.  Two gate panels lie off their hinges in the gateway, leaning against the walls like drunken soldiers sleeping off a late night drinking bout.  The grass-choked yard stretches to the west and north, while a tower rises to the northwest.</description>
    <position x="60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go derelict gate" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Tref Dinta, Courtyard">
    <description>Looming over the courtyard, a tall stone tower stands majestic and forlorn.  A few stones have begun to crumble, but the structure is still mainly intact and in good shape.  The wooden doorway into the keep is covered with thick iron bands and is mostly closed, although a small gap could allow entry for adventurers eager to see what lies within.</description>
    <position x="40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden doorway" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Tref Dinta, Courtyard">
    <description>A wooden stable stands in the northern section of the courtyard, its still sturdy doors barred and locked against intrusion.  The closed window shutters likewise prevent all entry.  An occasional rustle or other sound comes forth from within, but no way of access can be discerned.</description>
    <position x="60" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Main Floor, Entry">
    <description>Tumbled stones litter the entryway floor, fallen from the circular staircase that once led into the upper reaches of the structure.  Now the stairs end abruptly halfway up the wall although a gaping hole in the ceiling allows glimpses of the darkened spaces above.  Piles of dirt and debris brought in from the cracked doorway lie heaped in the corners.  Arches to the north and west offer further access to the building.</description>
    <position x="20" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden doorway" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Main Floor, Parlor">
    <description>Bits of wallpaper still cling to a few spots, but most of the walls are now bare stone with a some crumbling masonry between the blocks.  Piles of splintered wood and decaying fabric mark where once splendid furniture stood gleaming.  Belying the general air of decay, there are long trails through the dust on the floors, giving evidence that something still stirs within the tower.</description>
    <position x="0" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Main Floor, Dining Room">
    <description>Half of an enormous dining table lies canted on the floor, the rest of it lying in pieces and splinters around it on the scarred floorboards.  A few pieces of broken pottery are heaped in the corner, perhaps the last remnants of a long-decayed sideboard.</description>
    <position x="0" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Main Floor, Kitchen">
    <description>Standing against one wall is a long table that ends at a metal sink.  Amazingly, both are still intact, although covered with dust and grime.  A pump with a water spout perches on the edge of the sink, its handle halfway raised as if some kitchen maid was interrupted in mid-use and never returned to their task.  Opposite the sink is a circular opening leading to a staircase descending into the cellar.</description>
    <position x="0" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Main Floor, Pantry">
    <description>Odors of rot and decay overwhelm the senses, causing the eyes to water and the stomach to churn.  The noxious smells emanate from the corners where remains of various barrels and boxes spill their decomposing contents onto the wooden floor.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Main Floor, Library">
    <description>Shelves once lined the walls, but now only a few supports and boards still cling to the walls.  Miraculously, a couple of volumes still stand upright on some of the upper reaches, their spines dusty and covered with cobwebs.  Slime-covered trails snake across the floor, circling around a large pile that perhaps was once a desk, but is now just a heap of wooden scraps.</description>
    <position x="20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Cellar">
    <description>Vaulted ceilings of cut stone blocks loom overhead in the gloomy depths of the basement.  A long trail of slime twists through the dust and dirt on the floor, moving through the area and deeper into the cellar.  The broad steps of the circular staircase lead upwards towards the upper floors and escape from the dismal dank of the basement.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Cellar">
    <description>Heaps of coal lie abandoned here, spilling out from the rotting remains of large wooden bins.  Unlike most of the rest of the cellar contents, the coal lumps have not begun to disintegrate.  Dark dust from the coal mingles with dirt to hide the nature of the flooring underfoot.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Cellar">
    <description>A shelf holding casks has collapsed and spilled its contents across the floor.  Many of the containers broke up and the sticky residue from them mixes with the dust to create a gummy gunk on the floor that clings to footwear.  The very faint odor of vinegar permeates the area, further identifying the cask's contents as wine.  A single mage light high above provides fitful illumination for the area, beating back the dark gloom of the cellar.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Cellar">
    <description>Mysterious slime trails trace through the dust-covered floor, criss-crossing in wild abandon.  Little else remains in this corner of the cellar, just a few splinters of wood and piles of dirt to mark where stored items once stood.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Southern Trade Route, Alongside the Forest" note="Map62_Southern_Trade_Route_Part_2.xml|Southern Trade Route|STR|Shard|Leth Deriel">
    <description>A soft cooing echoes unbounded through the forest.  The road cuts a thick swatch through the brush, a pale shadow compared to the almost malignant ones surrounding it.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" />
    <arc exit="south" />
  </node>
  <label text="Gigantic Lachmate">
    <position x="10" y="-10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="To STR">
    <position x="72" y="14" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>