<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="DiSilveron" id="7c">
  <node id="1" name="Northern Trade Road, Farmlands" note="Map7_Northern_Trade_Road.xml|NTR|Crossing">
    <description>The scent of freshly-tilled earth rises from the farms on both sides of the road.  Heavily-loaded wagons and carts brimming with produce wend their way southward towards the walls of a city set near a glimmering river.  You note an amazing variety of races and types that are driving their goods into the town.</description>
    <position x="60" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go freshly-planted pathway" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="DiSilveron, Front Gate">
    <description>Several torches flicker from beyond a wrought-iron gate that makes its sudden appearance in a high, jasmine-scented hedge.  Two ominous statues, silhouetted against the lighter night sky, sparkle with faint traces of silver which glisten in the scant light.  Their eyes glow with an inner fire.</description>
    <description>Grand alabaster lions flank a regal wrought-iron gate that is accented in heavy silver leaf.  To either side of these gargantuan works of art are high hedges of jasmine intertwined with woodrose, which continue on for several yards before banking out of sight.  A silver-tinged, multi-gabled roof is visible just above the hedges.</description>
    <position x="120" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go freshly-planted pathway" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wrought-iron gate" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="DiSilveron, Topiary">
    <description>A corridor of emerald green grass passes between two upright rows of hedges trimmed in whimsical fashion.  Elegant Elvish workmanship is apparent in the living architecture of this most interesting garden border.</description>
    <position x="120" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wrought gate" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite pathway" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="DiSilveron, Topiary">
    <description>Neatly trimmed grass spreads from one shrub to the next, meticulously clipped to resemble an oak spreading out on the ground.  Aromatic cedar bark is loosely packed at the bases of a juniper shaped like a dancing fae and two entwined hedges formed into a fawn.</description>
    <position x="140" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="DiSilveron, Topiary">
    <description>Part of the charm of DiSilveron is this little stretch of garden which has been planted by generations of DiSilveron household members.  Miniature fruit trees, planted by the eldest son of each eldest son, line a narrow, dirdel carpet.  As the trees matured, each was shaped into the initial of the person who planted it.  It makes for an interesting jumble of alphabet which wafts its complex nectars on the wind.</description>
    <position x="100" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="DiSilveron, Chancellor's Gardens" note="Chancellor's Gardens">
    <description>To either side of a silver-flecked granite pathway lies the impeccable lawn which rolls and eddies gently over a vast tract of DiSilveron land.  The great, gabled manor stands like a castle in the midst of this extensive carpet of green, on a rise at the center of the property.  Tall, thick, primeval forest can be seen in the distance, bordering the horizon to which this lawn appears to stretch.</description>
    <position x="120" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite pathway" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="DiSilveron, Chancellor's Gardens">
    <description>Lovely dots and swirls of color make up the border garden which surrounds a large tract of lawn leading to the manor.  Bluebells compete with brilliant poppies and delicate violets for attention.  At regular intervals in the patterned plantings are stands upon which strawberry jars are nursing their next crop.</description>
    <position x="100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel pathway" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="DiSilveron, Chancellor's Gardens">
    <description>Great rose bushes create a spindly forest through which to pass.  A wide variety of propagations can be found here, from the delicate Faenella White Rose to the DiSilveron Black Rosette.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gravel walkway" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="DiSilveron, Chancellor's Gardens">
    <description>Almagarus blossoms in all their heady beauty crown lustrous alabaster pots along a graveled pathway.  These flowers, which resemble a cross between a rose and an iris, are arranged in an intriguing multicolored scheme and are in various stages of bloom.  At the base of the pots grows a delicate carpet of rare purple jernum.</description>
    <position x="120" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="DiSilveron, Chancellor's Gardens">
    <description>The garden takes on a particularly artistic look at this part of the pathway, as solid ground gives way to a great pond planted with an incredible array of aquatic florals.  Chief among the floating flora are various types of water lilies, with an array of irises, dustanjis and petapers.  Cultivated mosses and fresh-water grasses, some in bloom with sweet white flowers, provide protective cover for some tiny frogs and fish.</description>
    <position x="140" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dirt path" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="DiSilveron, Sanctuary" note="Sanctuary">
    <description>A great growth of woven woodrose vines creates a cool, quiet bower along the western fringe of the estate.  The bower, large enough to hold several dozen people, is furnished with chairs, tables and benches, and has a cleared area for performers.</description>
    <position x="60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="DiSilveron, Sanctuary" note="bird feeders">
    <description>This covered lane is actually a clearing in the midst of the high hedges of woodrose and jasmine which surround the estate.  Several rare species of birds are kept in this natural aviary, and their chirps and calls fill the air in a pleasant, drowsy chorus.</description>
    <position x="40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="DiSilveron, Sanctuary">
    <description>The pathway narrows substantially, squeezing between the high hedges of DiSilveron.  The scent of jasmine is strong, as is the scent of the composting materials which nourish the resident flora.</description>
    <position x="20" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="DiSilveron, Sanctuary">
    <description>Stray groups of summer holly and thistle grow below the neatly trimmed high hedges.  An ornate iron bench, painted white, is pushed to one side, providing a private sitting area for soft conversation.</description>
    <position x="0" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="DiSilveron, Sanctuary Garden">
    <description>Breaking out of the cover of the high hedges, this quaint garden of herbs is as welcome as the fresh air.  Gentle breezes ripple across the tangles of stems, vines, twigs and crowns, setting them to dancing.  A rugged poplar, planted in the southern corner of the garden, also marks a bend in the hedges which surround the estate.</description>
    <position x="0" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="DiSilveron, Outside Carriage House">
    <description>Meticulously white-washed, this large wooden structure is trimmed with flower boxes and supplied with a comfortable bench.  Several types of tack are visible through its windows, and there is an obvious smell of animal, but otherwise, it is so charming it could pass for a cottage.</description>
    <position x="140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go disilveron manor" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="DiSilveron, Promenade" note="Promenade">
    <description>Great columns of alabaster line a grand promenade surrounding DiSilveron Manor.  Exquisite iron furniture and an abundance of green plants are grouped to either side of the massive entry doors.  The floor planks, of expensive halmik wood, are covered in reed mats woven with the Sorvendig crest.</description>
    <position x="140" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entry doors" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="DiSilveron, Promenade">
    <description>Perfectly suited for afternoon tea or an evening rendezvous, the eastern promenade is furnished with several chairs surrounding an exquisite iron and glass table.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="DiSilveron, Promenade">
    <description>From this vantage point, the great copse of ironwood trees on the eastern border of the estate is visible.  As the wind parts the elegant branches, one catches a glimpse of the peaceful lake in its midst.  Northward, at the back of the mansion, is more lawnscape that stretches for miles until it reaches the forest.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="DiSilveron, Promenade">
    <description>The Chancellor's Gardens and a massive fountain are visible from this edge of the promenade.  Several books are stacked upon a set of nesting side tables, next to an ornate chaise.  There is a collection of new blossoms in a flower box that rests on the deck near an elaborate serving cart.  The coziness of the location, coupled with the refreshing breeze, make it easy to see why this spot is frequently used.</description>
    <position x="120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="DiSilveron, Grand Foyer" note="Grand Foyer">
    <description>Great urns of alabaster rest on marble pedestals before an ostentatious staircase which curls up both sides of the foyer to meet beneath a great crystal chandelier.  The polished marble floors continue to the east and west into smaller rooms, and north toward a great rotunda at the center of the home.  Ornate niches alternately bear intriguing sculptures in pewter and beautiful floral arrangements.</description>
    <position x="140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go entry doors" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="DiSilveron, Rotunda" note="Rotunda">
    <description>A shallow domed ceiling crowns this room, the setting for many a lavish gathering within the mansion.  Ferns and potted plants spill from hanging vases between a circle of alabaster columns that encompass the room.  Formal yet comfortable divans face each other across the marble floor, each with an ornate glass cocktail table accented with golden scrollwork.  A great mural in pastel colors wraps the rotunda's walls and wide etched glass doors lead to the lawns behind the manse.</description>
    <position x="140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go few steps" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="DiSilveron, Conservatory" note="Conservatory">
    <description>A love for music and the performing arts is evident in this cozy room.  Tapestries are hung along the walls, depicting actors and bards plying their craft before rapt audiences.  A violin is carefully stored in a halmik and glass case, and a harpsichord is tucked beneath a window.  Flutes and recorders are stored in mounted glass display cases, near shelves on which sit scripts for plays performed at the mansion in days past.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="DiSilveron, Library" note="Library">
    <description>Hundreds of books line shelves or rest decoratively upon tables, desks and the floor.  This long, narrow, corridor of a room looks more like a private club, with several groups of sofas creating sitting areas for whatever purpose they might serve.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go halmik doors" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="DiSilveron, Parlor" note="Parlor">
    <description>A cozy, quiet parlor connects to the mansion's library, more a source of solitude than a gathering place.  A marbled fireplace at one end provides just enough heat to be useful, and there is a plush throw rug underfoot.  A brocade divan and some wingback chairs surround a halmik cocktail table.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go halmik doors" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="DiSilveron, Formal Dining Room" note="Formal Dining Room|Dining Room">
    <description>A great dining table of hand-oiled taborwood gleams along the length of the room, accompanied by sixty-two high-backed chairs.  Light pours through a continuous wall of windows one one side, illuminating a series of rich paintings on the other.  Tall silver candelsticks rise confidently from the centers of floral arrangements at regular intervals along a beautifully crafted Elothean lace runner on the table.</description>
    <position x="140" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go few steps" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <label text="Front Gate">
    <position x="94" y="164" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="NTR">
    <position x="48" y="171" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dining Room">
    <position x="144" y="-8" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Conservatory">
    <position x="164" y="32" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Parlor">
    <position x="63" y="32" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Promenade">
    <position x="144" y="64" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="gardens">
    <position x="38" y="80" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>