<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Crossing East Gate" id="8">
  <node id="1" name="Eastern Tier, Middens">
    <description>The far-off scent of the sea-mingled river fades quickly here, as your nostrils are assaulted by a noxious odor borne by an eastern wind.  You are on the fringes of The Middens, a squatters' colony that houses newcomers to the outskirts of The Crossing.  Hovels of day laborers, itinerant tinkers and tradesfolk, sailors and petty criminals crowd against one another along the muddy paths and unpaved streets that lead off from the main road here.  The shadowy byways may hold danger, despair or discoveries.</description>
    <position x="200" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Eastern Tier, Outside Gate">
    <description>The eastern gate of the Crossing stands before you, an incomplete, but serviceable stone structure.  To the north are grey slate hills rising out of dense clumps of deobar trees and groves of tall almur poplars.  The land to the east is flat, and dips and rises almost imperceptibly into the distance.  A single, wide path winds through it, surrounded by ruins, debris and small huts.</description>
    <position x="140" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go eastern gate" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bush" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>The path here leads in a north-south direction.  Underfoot, crude paving gravel competes with mud and sand to sabotage your steps.  The sucking, squishing sound and the decaying smell of swampy soil fills the air, as you scrape the remains of some thick, blood-bloated worms off your boots and continue on.  To the south you notice a few sorry huts, and to the east, several tall structures dominate the horizon.</description>
    <position x="220" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>Rough sedges line the path, so matted and tangled that you could not leave the way and explore the undergrowth even if you were foolish enough to want to.  The road runs parallel to the town walls due west.  A glistening dragonfly glides alongside you and alights on a nearby clump of dark green viper's grass.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>The way turns here at a right angle, and paving pebbles mingle with soft, spongy moss that add bounce to your gait.  Tiny spikes of yellow and lavender flowers top the sedges along the shoulders of the road.  To the north, the land rises and you can barely make out a slate-colored hilltop, ominously devoid of trees.  To its southeast, a tall, tapering tower overlooks the land.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tall sedges" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>The north side of the path is almost a quagmire, clinging to your boots and making movement difficult.  From the north, you hear the clamor of toads and other less amiable bog dwellers.  Tiny, evanescent dots of light drift before your eyes, and flit off towards the sounds.</description>
    <position x="318" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Middens, Boggy End">
    <description>A very small, very scummy pond, covered with wrack and yellow-green algae, skirts the path here.  The air is thick with gnats and flies and the croaking of well-fed bullfrogs.  Aquatic plants compete with algae for space on the pond's surface, and provide a highway for all manner of creepy and crawly creatures.  Occasionally, sinister bubbles and ripples break the pond's surface and scatter the denizens.  The silence in the aftermath is not a comforting one.</description>
    <position x="318" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Middens, Boggy End">
    <description>You stand on the very verge of a black swamp.  The peat that forms the shore, if it can be called one, yields beneath your feet and could give way at any moment, casting you into the unknown terrors of the deep, silent bog.  Things seem to poke out of the mud, breaking the surface tension of the dark waters, and then disappear before you can make out their forms.</description>
    <position x="338" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Middens, Alerin Slade">
    <description>A wide junction greets you, and a daunting sight as well.  Here, along this soggy trail, slog all manner of races and professions, with one common air about them - all seem hopeless and downtrodden.  You have entered Alerin Slade, a squatters' quarter of wide ill repute.  There is a large proportion of Humans here, and you clutch your weapon as you pass through.</description>
    <description>A wide junction greets the eyes, and a daunting sight as well.  Here, along this soggy trail, slog all manner of races and professions, with one common air about them - all seem hopeless and downtrodden.  Entering into the area known as Alerin Slade, a squatters' quarter of wide ill repute that fosters a large proportion of Humans.</description>
    <position x="338" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Middens, Alerin Slade">
    <description>Some of the famed exports of The Slade hustle by you - thieves, mercenaries, brigands and press laborers - en route to or returning from the Crossing.  Stonefaced and purposeful, as shady as these characters appear, you cannot help but wonder if their grim determination is the product of hungry mouths huddled in squalid shacks somewhere nearby.</description>
    <position x="358" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>Very surly, very rank Gor'Togs shoulder by you, nearly knocking you to the ground in their melancholy haste.  You are accustomed to the brusque ways of their city-dwelling kin, but these squatters seem to be driven by some inner force, which you can almost see in their thick-lidded eyes.  Small children with swollen bellies trail after the grownups, pointing at you as they titter among themselves.</description>
    <description>Very surly, very rank Gor'Togs shoulder through the throngs of people nearby, a melancholy air encompassing the view.  Brusque in their haste as they move through groups of thick-lidded squatters that gaze about blankly as they idle about along the road.  Several small children with swollen bellies trail after grungy-looking adults as they move along the road.</description>
    <position x="358" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Middens, Bumboat Row">
    <description>This dead end smells like it.  It is dark, and hulking, cloaked figures lurk in the shadowy corners of the alley.  A river rat, big and sleek as a pampered house cat, skitters by and disappears down a cracked drainpipe.</description>
    <position x="358" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Middens, Alerin Slade">
    <description>Human children scurry by, laughing and teasing one another, looking for all the world like their more prosperous counterparts who dwell within the secure walls of the Crossing.  That is, until you notice one unfortunate straggler, hobbling after the group on crude wooden crutches.  Their high-pitched voices echo off the rising earthen mound to the east, and reverberate down the narrow lane to the southwest.</description>
    <position x="378" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Middens, Outside Ruins">
    <description>The low mud wall of the ruined Motte Fort affords no barrier to any living thing.  Snakes slither over it, among the vines growing on either side of the boundary.  A wren hops along its almost invisible crest, picking at worms who, in their turn, have feasted on the corpses of the long-buried defenders of the fort, their flesh mingled with the damp, dark soil here.</description>
    <position x="398" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low wall" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Middens, Bumboat Row">
    <description>You are in the heart of the Gor'Tog quarter, known as Bumboat Row.  Small pushcarts line the way, with hawkers selling cast-offs or rubbish gleaned from the garbage scows and trash heaps of the more fortunate townsfolk.  Unenthusiastic shoppers, laborers and loafers shamble by you.</description>
    <position x="378" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Middens, Bumboat Row">
    <description>Deep cart-ruts and pony tracks are evident here, hinting at the life and commerce of the gloomy Middens.  Water has welled up in the ruts, breeding grounds for gnats and mosquitoes.  You slog your way through the crowds of unwashed Gor'Togs, Humans and S'Kra Mur who stream to and from the north with patched leather buckets, warped wooden pails or broken clay jugs in tow.</description>
    <position x="398" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>Plodding inhabitants of The Slade and Bumboat Row meander past you, looking lost and aimless.  The river's distant lapping and a few shrill shorebirds provide welcome distractions from the smell and the oppressive closeness of the squatters' hovels and mean streets.</description>
    <position x="418" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Middens, Bumboat Row">
    <description>Swarms of horseflies and mosquitoes buzz around your ears, alighting on any exposed skin for a quick bite.  You try and fend them off, along with the undeniable stench arising from the open gutters here that carry the refuse of this Gor'Tog squatters quarter through the filthy lanes and out in the surrounding bog or straight to the river farther south.</description>
    <position x="378" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Middens, Goodworks' Plaza">
    <description>The sorry clearing here has been tamped down to produce a caricature of a Town Square.  A scraggly marsh tree stands forlornly in the middle of the open space, scraps of cloth and paper hanging from its bare branches.  To the west is a half-demolished well, the only remaining source of semi-potable water for all the squatters.</description>
    <position x="398" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Middens, Brackish Well">
    <description>The denizens of The Middens gather here at the only well to draw water for drinking, cooking and washing.  You feel a bit dry yourself, but a glance down the well shaft and at the sickly-looking crowd around you, and a sniff at the water, convince you that you are better off quenching your thirst elsewhere.</description>
    <position x="378" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Middens, Gravel Way">
    <description>The gloom in this portion of the Middens, deepened by the shadows of the Observatory to the east, and the low, ruined profile of the fort directly northwest, seems endless.  To the south lies the shanty community of Urrem's Bane.</description>
    <position x="438" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Middens, Swampy Junction">
    <description>A small, sodden crossroads here leads north down a murky track, southwest towards the Crossing, and east towards the ruins of Ulf'Hara Keep and the Observatory of the Southern Crossbow, which houses the Moon Mage Guild.  From the east comes the sound of raucous voices, and from the north an occasional eerie howl or wail.  It must be the wind whistling through the marsh grasses, nothing more.</description>
    <position x="478" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mud hovel" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Middens, Watershot">
    <description>This path lies between the mound of the ruined Motte Fort to the west, and the towering Ulf'Hara Keep due southeast.  Being in a natural basin and in the shadow of the two structures, the land underfoot is always damp, and marshlike.  You step cautiously through the unyielding wirgrass that covers treacherously soft, sucking mud.  Mosquitoes buzz about your ears, and slimy, leechlike slugs cling to your feet.  Little light penetrates to dispel your sense of utter gloom and calamity.</description>
    <description>This path lies between the mound of the ruined Motte Fort to the west, and the crumbled ruins of Ulf'Hara Keep due southeast.  Being in a natural basin and in the shadow of the two structures, the land underfoot is always damp, and marshlike.  You step cautiously through the unyielding wirgrass that covers treacherously soft, sucking mud.  Mosquitoes buzz about your ears, and slimy, leechlike slugs cling to your feet.  Little light penetrates to dispel your sense of utter gloom and calamity.</description>
    <position x="478" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Middens, Watershot">
    <description>You happen upon a long, broad ditch, excavated deep into the damp ground.  The ditch is filled with dark, slimy water, and its breadth and foulness make it impossible to cross.  The only exit lies back in the direction you came.</description>
    <position x="498" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Middens, Watchers Corner">
    <description>A few makeshift stalls selling dubious food, tepid ale and stale pipeweed cluster around both sides of the road here.  The path is wide and deeply rutted, bearing testimony to the many travelers and travailers who have passed through here.  Some have sought solace in viewing the heavens from the Crossbow Observatory to the south, while others bear witness to the ruins that was once Ulf'Hara Keep directly east, perhaps mourning the loss of those who died in its tragic destruction.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go warehouse" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Middens, Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins" note="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins">
    <description>The gravel way ends here at the smoldering ruins of a massive keep.  The once towering walls and fortified turrets of Ulf'Hara Keep now lies in a mass of devastation, portions of its blasted remains and fire-blackened granite littering most of the roadway.</description>
    <description>The gravel way ends here at the crumbled ruins of a massive keep.  The once towering walls and fortified turrets of Ulf'Hara Keep now lies in a mass of devastation, portions of its blasted remains and fire-blackened granite littering most of the roadway.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Middens, Crossbow Bend">
    <description>The gravel road merges with a well-kept cobblestone street here.  A firm surface underfoot permits you to pick up your pace.  To the southwest, you see the oddly-shaped Observatory of the Southern Crossbow.  Its sixteen-sided facade rises three stories above the flat river plain on which you stand.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Middens, Crossbow Bend">
    <description>Burly militiamen mingle with ethereal, robed figures, fresh-faced lads in pilgrim attire and maids of unworldly demeanor, all making their way to or from the Observatory.  Groups of Moon Mages walk by at a deliberate pace, and talk amongst themselves in low, dignified tones.  Those whose faces peek out of their hoods or cowls regard you with faraway, almost disdainful glances.</description>
    <position x="520" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver gateway" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Middens, Crossbow Bend" note="Moon Mage Guild" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Before you stands the Observatory of the Southern Crossbow.  It is a three-story edifice, its sixteen-sided walls capped with a crystal dome.  The top floor is also the nerve center of the Moon Mages' Guild, a most powerful and revered arcane circle throughout Elanthia.  All in all a rather quirky structure, it manages to inspire awe and curiosity at the same time.  A carved ivory door leads inside.</description>
    <position x="500" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silver gateway" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ivory door" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Middens, Urrem's Bane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Mildewed tangles of rope and precarious footbridges constructed of rotting wood straddle wooden platforms crowded with rickety shacks.  Stunted trees draped with long tendrils of moss shade a small cluster of buildings surrounding a thick cedar that squats in the center of the muck.</description>
    <position x="438" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Middens, Urrem's Bane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A stack of barrels half-sunk in the thick mud supports the center of a long plank leading from the edge of the deck to a ramshackle building nestled in the twisted branches of a stout cedar.  Taller trees hung with tattered shrouds of moss cast a dark pall over a huddle of tiny homes surrounding the cedar, which stands in the middle like the hub of a broken wagon wheel.</description>
    <position x="418" y="86" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go plank" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Middens, Urrem's Bane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>An ash heap behind the platform diminishes with each breeze, creating sooty clouds that hang in the humid air and tarnish everything a dull grey.  Pale light filters down through the moss-draped canopy and dances over the stolid forms of the small community.</description>
    <position x="438" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Middens, Urrem's Bane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A crudely carved pylon sits on the wooden platform underfoot, its surface decorated with strands of broken teeth and blood-red poppies.  A rope bridge lashed to two rotting beams leads down, and looks a good deal more stable than the broken planks of the wooden footbridge leading west.  The thin sound of trickling water giggles up from below.</description>
    <position x="478" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rope bridge" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Middens, Urrem's Bane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Tall wiregrass crackles in the occasional breeze and scratches the edges of the wooden footbridges, sounding like the scrabbling of thick-carapaced insects.  A trash pile nested in the high grass behind the rickety wooden platform fragrances the air with the sour smell of decay.</description>
    <position x="458" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Middens, Urrem's Bane" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Sinuous tendrils of dark shadow reach across the muck, pulling at the damp and splintered boards underfoot.  Sheets of hammered tin and uneven scraps of wood held together with rusting nails and frayed bits of rope huddle together in the limited space, looking like card houses ready to blow over at the slightest breeze.  A small rope bridge leads up to another ramshackle platform.</description>
    <position x="478" y="86" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rope bridge" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Middens, Alerin Slade">
    <description>This garbage-strewn alley leads into the heart of The Slade, the Human squatters' camp.  Filthy children play in the muck in front of hovels built of cast-off lumber, thatch and mud.  You see a group of heavily-armed Humans gathered in front of a stall that serves as a makeshift alehouse.</description>
    <position x="358" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Middens, Alerin Slade">
    <description>Obvious attempts have been made to keep this section of the alley clean and free of debris.  A few planks over the wet path make for easier passage, and lead up to an open area of dry land covered by a canopy.  Youngsters clad in hand-me-downs scamper by you, carrying books.  A hand-lettered sign affixed to a post driven into the soggy soil somehow manages to remain upright.</description>
    <position x="378" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Middens, Outside Ruins">
    <description>The byway leading here turns into a mixture of old rubble, mud and sodden peat.  Chunks of carbonized wood, rusty shards of metal and remnants of stone are strewn about, their density increasing to the southeast, where lie the ruins of an ancient fortification.</description>
    <position x="398" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go thick plank" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go breached wall" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Middens, Zehila" note="Zehila" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>This is the entrance to the most upscale of the squatters' quarters of the Middens, known as Zehila.  The inhabitants, all S'kra Mur, remain somewhat aloof from the other squatters' colonies, maintaining the pretense of social superiority.  When they do mix with the other downtrodden races of this area, at the Middens' only well, they pass through the junction here with purposeful haste.</description>
    <description>This is the entrance to the most upscale of the squatters' quarters of the Middens, known as Zehila.  The inhabitants, all S'Kra Mur, remain somewhat aloof from the other squatters' colonies, maintaining the pretense of social superiority.  When they do mix with the other downtrodden races of this area, at the Middens' only well, they pass through the junction here with purposeful haste.</description>
    <position x="220" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Middens, Zehila" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>This quiet alley is flanked on both sides by tidy hovels, freshly plastered with wattle and daub.  Some of the roofs are newly thatched.  The smell of cooking fires and home-brewed ale wafts to your nostrils.</description>
    <position x="240" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Middens, Zehila" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Several women are gathered around a large wooden tub in this dead-end street.  They are chatting in the hissing slang of the S'Kra Mur, their sibilant giggles punctuated by splashes of water as they wash their clothes at this communal laundry.  Long, white robes hang from ropes attempting to dry in the damp air, and a toddler stares at you shyly from behind one.</description>
    <position x="240" y="86" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Middens, Zehila" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A small clay statue stands in the corner of this tidy cul-de-sac.  Flowers and unfired clay vessels laden with fruit are set neatly before it.  An old S'Kra Mur, steadying himself with a tall staff, looks startled by your approach.</description>
    <position x="200" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="The Crossing, Eastern Gate" note="Map1_Crossing.xml|Crossing">
    <description>Camels, oxen and mules compete with Elves, Gor'Togs and Humans to pass through the Eastern Gate which leads to the Middens, and the Observatory beyond.  The lowing of animals and the bellowing of travelers become almost indistinguishable the more you listen.  After a few minutes, so do the mingled odors of unwashed sojourners and beasts of burden.  It begins to dawn on you why folks are anxious to pass through customs, whatever the cost, as quickly as possible.</description>
    <position x="120" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>The path winds in and out of a thick patch of stunted bushes near the exterior wall.  It emerges into an area of chipped rock where workers have dumped debris from the town wall's construction.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>Crumbling mud bricks and loose rock lay in a pile near the sturdy stone town wall.  A small field mouse nibbles at a crust of bread, perhaps discarded from the wall workers' lunch portion.</description>
    <description>Crumbling mud bricks and loose rock lay in a pile near the sturdy stone town wall.  Sounds of night-hidden creatures rustle in the weeds and nearby brush as they search for prey or leftover scraps.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>The path turns from the city ramparts and forks south and west.  Toward the north it runs along the town's outer wall, the stone structure within reach.  Sheltered from wind and sun, little vegetation except for stray weeds manages to thrive.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Eastern Tier, Footpath">
    <description>Thin-leafed sedges and weeds grow densely enough to hide partially buried stones that can jarringly catch the toe of a boot.  The hiss of wind across the field creates a background for the music of a small cloud of midges buzzing at head height.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Eastern Tier, Footpath">
    <description>Barely more than an animal track, this footpath can just be discerned through a field of sedge.  The weeds dull the sounds along the nearby road and city, leaving only the whisper of the wind all about.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>A smooth, flat slate-grey outcropping abuts the stone rampart, the same slates that compose the hills and terrain to the west.  Bits of the slab have cracked and chipped, but for a few yards the path is wide enough to be called a path.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>A gully eroded across the narrow way forces passage just next to the wall of the town.  Stagnant insect-infested water pools in muddy sections of the gully and a fetid odor of garbage saturates the air.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>The remains of a mudwren nest sits overhead in a rough section of the town's stone wall.  A newer nest is under construction just below it tucked within a chink of the wall.  Small birds dart through the tall brush, bustling as much as the citizens along the streets inside the gates.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Outside East Wall, Footpath">
    <description>Under the shadow of eastern section of The Crossing's stone town wall, this footpath serves as a shortcut.  Barely wide enough for one person, thick brambles and brush allow passage in single file.   A few crevices in the wall make adequate handholds as you squeeze your way along the uneven ground and past thorny branches.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Northeast Wilds, Outside Northeast Gate" note="Map7_Northern_Trade_Road.xml|Northern Trade Road|NTR|NE Gate">
    <description>You are before the Northeast Gate of the Crossing, surrounded by wayfarers and adventurers also in mid-journey.  Above, guardsmen stare down from the thick stone wall that encloses the city, wary for hostile visitors.  Whether they travel to destinations in town or farther west, or to the north and east, they all appear to be seeking something beyond themselves.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-154" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go footpath" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Observatory, First Level" note="Observatory1">
    <description>Airy strands of light waver about you on all sides of the alcove, soft filaments reaching out from within the milky observatory walls themselves.  At its northwestern corner, the square chamber gives way to an atrium of lush vegetation, flowers and exotic plants which reach upward into the sun's friendly glow.   A thin railing of intricately woven willow branches rises at the garden's edge, arcing gently to the south and northeast.  A carved ivory door leads outside.</description>
    <position x="680" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ivory door" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>The room is dominated by a massive ivory pillar rising from its center, barely leaving enough room for an armored human to walk through comfortably.  Life-sized likenesses of the eleven gods and goddesses ring the column, each clothed in garments of leisure with faces and bodies forever frozen in the reposed rigors of ease and kindness.</description>
    <description>The room is dominated by a massive ivory pillar rising from its center, barely leaving enough room for an armored human to walk through comfortably.  Life-sized likenesses of the thirteen gods and goddesses ring the column, each clothed in garments of leisure with faces and bodies forever frozen in the reposed rigors of ease and kindness.</description>
    <position x="680" y="126" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A vibrant orange carpet of rampant rusk invades the floor at the room's northwestern corner.  Patches of violets, somernot and widow's lace dot the palette, their purples, pinks and creams completing the collage with a beauty impossible for mortal hand to duplicate.</description>
    <position x="660" y="126" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>An oak pedestal erected in the southern corner of the room supports a large brass orb.  Flashes of light glance sharply from its surface as it spins and rotates, highlighting the uncountable engraved lines and figures that cross its face.</description>
    <position x="640" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A long, colorful mural spans the north and west walls from floor to ceiling, the dark figures of Damaris and Meraud cavorting with panthers and wolves beneath twin full moons.</description>
    <position x="620" y="126" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A somernot vine climbs along the atrium railing on the room's northeast side, its wispy pink flowers creating a painted lattice from rail to floor across the entire width of the room.  A thin layer of petals spreads over soil and floor where they meet, showing just how very stark and devoid of color the observatory proper can be.</description>
    <position x="600" y="126" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>An ornate staircase of mingled woods spirals into the ceiling and out of sight above the balcony floor.  A bright woolen runner ascends the stairs with nary a buckle or gap, nestled cleanly between vivid scenes of Everild leading his army into battle.</description>
    <position x="600" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go staircase" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A small jade sculpture of Eluned filling the oceans stands just inside the atrium railing on the room's eastern edge, nearly hidden beneath the draping fronds of a wylla fern.  Continuous silvery streams flow from the tines of the goddess' trident into a small, clear pool at her feet.  A thin furrow siphons trickles of water off into the garden.</description>
    <position x="580" y="86" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>Undulations of air and light permeate your mind, drum softly inside your head, and a subtle, undeniable sense of timing comes over you.  The tower's interior seems to throb, shifting from stark white to barely perceptible instantaneous pulses of translucent blue.  And then, like an instant of deja vu, it is gone.</description>
    <position x="600" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Observatory, First Level" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Occasional pillars of light slant down through a thinning in the flora on the room's southeastern edge.  Pools of brilliant gold dapple, coalesce and fade across the floor as Day passes on her merry way.  The northern wall bears a prominent inlay of variously-sized circular tiles.</description>
    <description>Occasional whispers pass among the flora in the dim darkness at the room's southeastern edge, an eerily familiar conversation lingering just out of mind's reach.  The northern wall bears a prominent inlay of variously-sized circular tiles.</description>
    <position x="600" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stair" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sweeping staircase" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A lunat bench, inlaid with fruit wood depictions of Glythtide surrounded by crowds of frolicking mortals, rests against the northern wall.  To the southeast, fluffy tendrils of dawn's breath sweep along the railing in draping strands of powder grey. </description>
    <position x="620" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A wide table, built into the room's northern corner, houses a brass model of the solar system--a thirteen planet ballet in which Elanthia dances part.   Frescos of Truffenyi grace the northeastern and northwestern walls, each framed by a braided willow pattern similar to that of the rail encircling the atrium.</description>
    <position x="640" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>Beneath the willow railing at the atrium's edge, a squat, fiery bush pours over onto the floor.  Deep red leaves spread in a dense, untamed mass, parted here and there by glossy orbs of even redder fruit.  Its lustrous skin shines enticingly in the light, luring the unaware to certain death.</description>
    <position x="660" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>The twining trunk of a large fig tree extends up out of sight to the southwest, its leafy crown hidden by the second level balcony.  Honeysuckle and various flowering vines cling to the curving wood, hanging in tangled bunches of pink, yellow and green.  An oak bench, upholstered in rich lime brocade, invites you to rest and admire the circle of Hodierna's beauty which occupies the tower's center, from ground to crystal dome far above.</description>
    <position x="680" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>The walls around you glow softly, casting the room in a subtly pulsing luminescence of milky blue.  The light engulfs you, seemingly permeating your skin, and seeps into your bones where it throbs hypnotically to the cadence of some arcane ritual long extinct.  An undeniable sense of power comes over you.</description>
    <description>At first glance, the material of which the tower is constructed appears to be nothing more than fine grade white alabaster.  But as day and the occasional flicker of shadow play over the surrounding surfaces, something strikes you as very odd about the substance.  The polar white seems to emit a subtle energy which you cannot wholly sense, and leaves you with a strange feeling of inertia.</description>
    <position x="680" y="66" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Observatory, First Level">
    <description>A scalloped jade fountain, set back to the west a small ways amid the atrium's vegetation, shoots intermittent crystalline arcs into the air above.  The water climbs, hanging for a second at its pinnacle, and then descends again to splash against the creamy green bowl and run in a slender rivulet through a groove in the fountain's lip.  Although you cannot see where the stream goes from this side, it seems probable that the water simply seeps off to dampen the surrounding soil.</description>
    <position x="700" y="86" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Observatory, Foyer" note="Map8a_Lost_Crossing.xml|Lost Crossing|Rolagi|Grazhir|Ways|Astral Plane">
    <description>A sweeping staircase draped with a royal blue carpet descends from the first floor of the observatory into this mahogany-walled foyer.  A long, velvet-padded bench runs along the wall beside a gilded archway to the east.  A narrower corridor opens to the north, the passage dimly lit by flickering torches.</description>
    <position x="580" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sweeping staircase" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Observatory, Second Level" note="Observatory2">
    <description>From up a spiral staircase, along the south and northwest corridors, a narrow, brightly-colored carpet splits the stoic white of the observatory floor.  Similar tapestries adorn the western wall, opposite a curved railing at the balcony's southeast edge.  Crowns of blossoming trees and all manner of flowers and vines spread across the atrium, eclipsed intermittently beneath skimming slivers of shadow.</description>
    <description>From up a spiral staircase, along the south and northwest corridors, a narrow, brightly-colored carpet splits the stoic white of the observatory floor.  Similar tapestries adorn the western wall, opposite a curved railing at the balcony's southeast edge.  Crowns of blossoming trees and all manner of flowers and vines spread across the atrium in a masterpiece vision of color, light and shadow.</description>
    <position x="478" y="206" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go staircase" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Protruding through a narrow slit in the room's southwestern corner, a crude wooden telescope trains its eye over the Middens to the horizon of the setting sun.  Students of the southern skies gather here in the early hours of the evening to behold the train of stars which follow the Shining Crucible to its nightly rest.</description>
    <position x="478" y="226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>A plush velvet rug of varying blue shades covers the floor of this narrow throughway.  From the southern wall, an olive-bordered taffeta portrait of Hodierna hangs, swaying gracefully with the air currents which sweep along the hall and throughout the observatory.</description>
    <position x="498" y="226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>The leather-bound tube of a telescope disappears in half through a small hole cut in the wall in one corner of the room.</description>
    <position x="518" y="246" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Sunny yellow carpets and sky-blue wall hangings swaddle the corridor in their soft embrace, radiating a warmth that washes over you and permeates your body to the bone.  Fragrant coriander and spikes of florid hanging poppies complete the scene, bringing summertime to your senses and ease into your mind.</description>
    <position x="538" y="226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Thousands of colored beads form geometric patterns about a telescope built into the alcove's southeast corner, giving the room a distinct feeling of festivity.  On clear evenings, near the edge of dusk, Glythtide's abode of mirth and music rises just off the southeasterly horizon, its varicolored spots and rings painted merrily against the darkening sky.</description>
    <position x="558" y="226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Along the eastern wall, a high stained-glass window twinkles in the daylight, its green, purple and blue panes forming a striking portrait of Eluned astride a living wave.  A slender pedestal of brushed pewter rises from the center of the floor, its stately finish flashing dully beneath colored rays.</description>
    <position x="558" y="206" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="none" move="touch brass handprint" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Extending through a slit in the eastern corner, a wooden telescope peels its eye to the horizon of the rising sun.  On clear mornings, schools of moon magi and other heavenly watchers gather to behold the stars which flee before the coming light of Dawn's Herald.</description>
    <position x="578" y="186" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Wild strands of ivy swirl along the balcony's railing to the southwest, tumbling in unfettered streams of rich green foliage to the atrium floor. Nearly hidden amongst the unruly vegetation, you notice what appears to be a large grey column, truncated in mid-growth, rising stalwartly from beneath its cover of soil.</description>
    <position x="558" y="166" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Spiders of light skitter across a dark metallic telescope protruding from a fixture in the room's northeastern corner.</description>
    <position x="558" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>A piece of rope dangles from the ceiling at its northeastern corner, gathering on the floor in a thick coil of muted green.  Intuition warns you away from the serpentine mass, but curiosity persists.</description>
    <position x="538" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Flanked on either side by a thin burgundy drape, a single pane of silvery glass spreads across the northwestern wall.  Standing careful vigil in front is a fine mother-of-pearl telescope, its pearlescent surface glimmering with each shift of the light.</description>
    <position x="518" y="126" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>A straight-grained length of railing continues its arc along the atrium's circumference to the southeast.  Standing at the balcony edge, your view is relatively unobstructed, and the true immensity of the atrial circle strikes you full force.</description>
    <position x="498" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>The room is solid white and completely bare, save for a copper-banded telescope extending through the northwest wall.</description>
    <position x="478" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>Almost entirely composed of deeply-stained glass, the western wall boasts a tremendous portrait of Kertigen standing casually in the doorway of the Traders' guild.  A large raven perches loftily upon his shoulder and a friendly smile splits his pudgy face.</description>
    <position x="478" y="166" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Observatory, Second Level">
    <description>When visible, Tamsine's ethereal abode wisps fleetingly over the imposing silhouette of East Mountain between dusk and dark.  A telescope, sheathed in a covering of softly tanned suede, strains its single eye beyond the western wall, as if in eager anticipation of Morleena itself.</description>
    <position x="458" y="186" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Urrem's Bane, The Hub">
    <description>This room is oddly spacious despite close-hovering shadows that embrace the pale cast of oil lamps hung from the large branches supporting the roof.  The thick smells of alcohol and burning tobacco hang in the warm air.  Tattered tapestries nailed to the walls and colorful wool rugs scattered around the dusty plank floor lend a hint of dignity to the shack.  A polished bar circles the trunk of the cedar in the middle of the room, kegs of ale and clay jugs stored in the tree's gnarled hollows.</description>
    <position x="398" y="106" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Middens, Near Ruins">
    <description>The smell of decaying peat, mixed with the unpleasant odor of rotting garbage, betrays this muddy sludge as an area for cast-off refuse.  At night, the odor is particularly foul.  A thick plank of wood crosses the soggiest portion of ground where someone attempted to create a bridge across the worst of the muck.</description>
    <description>The smell of decaying peat, mixed with the unpleasant odor of rotting garbage, betrays this muddy sludge as an area for cast-off refuse.  Flies dart and swarm as does the occasional dragonfly, looking for a spot to feast or call home.  A thick plank of wood crosses the soggiest portion of ground where someone attempted to create a bridge across the worst of the muck.</description>
    <position x="418" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go thick plank" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>The path climbs above the lowland middens and the soggy peat to the southwest, and heads towards a gently rising grassland.  Scrub brush dots the tall, coarse grass as darker blobs against the streaked land.  Birds nesting within take to the air when startled, their wings aflutter in confusion.</description>
    <position x="438" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="88" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>The path heads due east and west, faintly visible as a narrow ribbon of trampled grass.  With little to shelter this finger of land pointed to the east, storms and winds howl across it furiously whenever the weather turns ill.  Not a single tree is visible within the area.</description>
    <position x="458" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>The whisper of grass stirred by the ever-present sea breeze, or the wet sodden stalks beaten flat, are the only variety in view along this stretch of terrain.  The seasons make little difference, only the effects of mild or tempestuous winds leave a mark.</description>
    <position x="478" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>To the east the ground rises again, leaving behind the salt-tolerant grasses.  The path passes near one large dolmen, shelter in its shadow a welcome relief on blustery nights.  The wind is ceaseless and unrelenting.</description>
    <description>To the east the ground rises again, leaving behind the salt-tolerant grasses.  The path passes near one large dolmen, its shade a welcome relief on warm days.  The wind is ceaseless and unrelenting.</description>
    <position x="498" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tall dolmen" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>The ground climbs steeply to the east, and heavy boulders jut from the low ground.  The path threads its way among them in complicated switchbacks and curves.  A lighthouse, with peeling paint and stained masonry, stands above the shrubs and grasses that cover the terrain at the farthest tip of land.</description>
    <position x="518" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>Sparse patches of heather struggle to survive the frequent squalls.  As the elevation increases, glimpses of the sea to the north and south are visible in the occasional dips in terrain.</description>
    <position x="538" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Cape of Storms, Path">
    <description>More rock than living plant springs from the ground here, a landscape of hunched, splintered and bowed shapes.  The lighthouse towards the east is as drab as the boulders strewn about, clearly lacking in any recent exterior upkeep.</description>
    <position x="538" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Cape of Storms">
    <description>Winds from the northeast blow across the crags and stunt the growth of anything larger than the salt-tolerant bushes.  The ground is hard and packed along the path, but branches overhang it as the vegetation closes in the gap.</description>
    <position x="558" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shed" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Cape of Storms">
    <description>Disheveled shrubs claw their way around and over the boulder-littered peninsula of land.  Gusts of salty wind tug at the trailing stalks of tall grass interspersed among the rock and branch.  Intermittent cries of gulls rise in the distance and fade into the rustle of the grass.</description>
    <position x="558" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, High Cliff">
    <description>The back of the lighthouse stands atop a rocky cliff, far above the waves which crash against the jagged rocks at the base.  A sharp wind whips through the air, lashing a lone, young tree which tenaciously clings to a crevice.</description>
    <position x="578" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Entry Shed">
    <description>This shed has been built along the edge of the cliff and serves as a covered walkway to the ancient, crumbling E'erglim Lighthouse, now the sole responsibility of its mysterious keeper.  A large brass bell with a missing clapper perhaps once served to warn those of the nearby keep of gathering storms.  A few tools neatly line the walls, and although the dark oiled floor is in need of repair, it is swept clean of dust and debris.</description>
    <position x="578" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go masonry arch" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Ground Floor">
    <description>Within the tapering interior of the stark, ramshackle lighthouse, birds nest in the chinks of the masonry.  Narrow, unglazed windows open to the salty air of the sea and the shrilling of gulls beyond.  A spiral of stairs twists its way to the top -- a mere frame of thin iron bars welded together, the joints flecked with rust.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go masonry arch" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Spiral Stair">
    <description>The flimsy railing of the stair is hardly reassuring as the risers squeak and sway with every step.  An equally flimsy catwalk leads off to a small chamber built into the walls.</description>
    <position x="618" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="102" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flimsy catwalk" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral stair" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Spiral Stair">
    <description>The yellow glow of a blazing wood fire above plays on the round walls that taper inward toward the staircase.  Soot covers every surface, and a few embers float down from a small opening through which the stairway passes overhead.</description>
    <position x="618" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Beacon Room">
    <description>The heat and the smoke are almost unbearable here.  A huge brick firepit, resembling an open kiln, blazes with fire, its flames licking the blackened ceiling.  A highly polished, concave sheet of beaten brass is mounted on a pivot behind the fire, serving to focus and direct its radiance out of several glazed rectangular windows spaced at regular intervals in the curved walls.</description>
    <position x="618" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Fort Motte, Ruins">
    <description>A deep ditch separates you from the rising, weed-covered mound of earth that formed the refuge and rallying point of the ruined fort.  A rotting plank, charred and cracked, is all that is left of the bridge that spanned the moat here.</description>
    <position x="438" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rotting plank" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low wall" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Fort Motte, Ruins">
    <description>From this southwest corner of the ruined outer wall, you can easily look out over the byways of Alerin Slade to the west.</description>
    <position x="418" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Fort Motte, Ruins" note="Fort Motte">
    <description>The round, low ruin of the outer bailey here curves south and east as you stand amid the remains of the northwest palisade.  A burned-out shack here appears to have been the home of the Fort's Warden, who held the outlying lands by right as exchange for his service.  Charred furnishings and blackened bones are scattered about.</description>
    <position x="418" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mud wall" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Fort Motte, Ruins">
    <description>The southeast curve of the outer mud-and-plank bailey is barely distinguishable from the boggy turf beyond it.  Clumps of brambles and vines straddle the ruin, making it impossible to cross.  Looking over it, to the northeast, you see nothing but flat marshland, with dark green forests in the distance.</description>
    <position x="438" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>Suffused with brilliant light, the air beneath the observatory's cap seems to close in comfortably.  The crystal dome rises from the floor to the southeast, curving overhead and across the circle of trees and at the tower center.  In the middle of the corridor, a slender pewter pedestal stands amid the colorful tiles of a large mosaic.</description>
    <description>A large wooden tripod stands post at the room's eastern edge, watching endlessly over the lower eastern Middens and beyond.  Beneath its crux, a polished steel scope hangs, suspended within a harness of softened leather.  The copper eyepiece winks with every subtle shift of light, as if sharing a secret joke with the slender pewter pedestal nearby.</description>
    <position x="398" y="226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="none" move="touch brass handprint" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A large wooden tripod stands post at the room's eastern edge, watching endlessly over the lower eastern Middens and beyond.  In its crux sits a polished steel telescope, its silver eyepiece winking with every subtle shift of light.</description>
    <position x="418" y="206" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A massive lunat table dominates the room, its top covered by intricate inlays of planets, moons and stars in their uncountable configurations.  Flanked by upholstered benches, the grand piece plays host to heated debate as well as other, more official guild business.  At its head, a high-backed chair sits, stoic, and forever empty.</description>
    <position x="398" y="186" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>Nestled in a net of soft rope, a long, metallic scope hangs parallel to the floor, halfway up the crystal arc of the dome to its pinnacle.</description>
    <position x="398" y="166" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>Thick burgundy carpets span the corridor and cradle your feet, creating a warm feeling of satisfaction and comfort.  To the southwest, a narrow picket railing skirts the balcony's edge, a horizon above which rise the crowns of countless, indescribable trees.</description>
    <position x="378" y="166" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A looming skeleton overlooks the northern Middens with unflappable silence,  the bright finish of his brass joints and the slick sheen of his eye belying the all which he sees.  Centuries pass.  Mortals live, see, and give way to the visions of generations to come.  But Old Oak watches without bias, without fail, and never forgets.</description>
    <description>A looming skeleton overlooks the northern Middens with unflappable silence, the bright finish of his brass joints and the slick sheen of his eye belying the all which he sees.  Centuries pass.  Mortals live, see, and give way to the visions of generations to come.  But Old Oak watches without bias, without fail, and never forgets.</description>
    <position x="358" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="112" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Observatory, Third Level" note="GL Moon Mage|Kssarh|RS Moon Mage" color="#FF8000">
    <description>A soft sitting mat covers the floor entirely, save for a narrow strip of anti-color bordering starkly on all sides.  Painted onto the crystal hemisphere, a detailed star diagram spreads over your head, marking the constellations and their positions at various times of the year.</description>
    <position x="338" y="166" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Observatory, Third Level" note="Observatory3">
    <description>A twisted framework of oak timbers and brass machinery nearly fills the room.  At its center, the tremendous tube of a weer crystal telescope slants upward at a slight angle toward the dome's center, splitting the air like a precarious steel pillar gone askew.  A thick glass lens extends a small space beneath the scope's circular base.</description>
    <position x="318" y="166" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>The dingy collage of the Middens spreads north and westward, across sparse field and muddy road, to the Crossing wall in the distance.  Sporadic hovel clusters dot the landscape like afterthoughts of a lesser shade, their dirty tan cementing the picture's palette without a seam.</description>
    <position x="318" y="186" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>Mounted atop an ornate wrought-iron stand, a long wooden telescope peers out toward the western sky.  Flecks of light and shadow play over the figures of deities and astrological icons carved delicately into the wood, giving them the appearances of motion and life.</description>
    <position x="298" y="206" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>Situated at the balcony's edge, a long bench overlooks an ironwood tree spreading its branches just out of your reach.  The grey wood twists and folds into gnarled shapes which seem familiar, from life or thought, and yet strange and alien at the same time.</description>
    <position x="318" y="226" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A darkly-finished lunat tripod stands in the alcove's southwest corner, a polished brass telescope balancing lightly at its peak.</description>
    <position x="318" y="246" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A row of low hammocks extends along the room's southwestern edge, each net stretched loosely between wall and wooden peg.  The ropes sway hypnotically with waves of air that ebb and flow through the corridor, grasping your gaze and lulling you into shallow, walking slumber.</description>
    <position x="338" y="246" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A structure of crossed wooden planks and metal fittings supports a large telescope mounted loosely at its top.  Thin carvings of somernot and ivy curl delicately along the stand's base, undoubtedly the work of a master Elven craftsman.</description>
    <position x="358" y="266" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="122" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>Lustrous brass etchings twinkle intermittently above a long work table situated against the southeastern wall.  Scads of astrological charts and diagrams litter the wooden surface, the haphazard piles seeming indicators of someone's diligent study.</description>
    <position x="378" y="246" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Observatory, Third Level">
    <description>A long lunat telescope stretches from its base towards the transparent dome of the observatory.  The wooden tube reaches upward, the grains ribbing its sides pulled taut, as if straining to reach the light.</description>
    <position x="398" y="246" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Crossing, East Gate Battlements" note="Map1_Crossing.xml">
    <description>From this height, the ruins of Ulf'Hara Keep are visible in the far distance, and southward flows the churning Segoltha River.  Two of the wall's embrasures contain signal pots, an archaic backup should gwethdesuan or thoughtcast fail.  The cobbled walkway here is directly atop Crossing's eastern gate, overlooking the road into town.</description>
    <position x="119" y="11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb embrasure" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Crossing, East Wall Battlements" note="Map1_Crossing.xml">
    <description>The roof of a tall oak tower abuts the town wall's inner side, just feet below the cobbled walkway.  Scattered stones and feathers among the droppings dappling the roof suggest that a favorite pastime of the soldiers stationed here is chucking rocks at roosting birds.  From the crenellated outer wall the view is uninspiring: broken hovels and barren land marking the biting poverty of the Middens.  Northward, the cobbled walkway abruptly ends at the jagged rock of the unfinished wall.</description>
    <position x="119" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb break" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Crossing, East Wall Battlements" note="Map1_Crossing.xml">
    <description>Before becoming impassable, the cobbled walkway atop the town wall slopes south toward the Segoltha River.  A small stone guardhouse is set snugly against the outer battlement wall, offering those warriors not on watch a place to shelter from the elements.  Some whimsical soul has set a flowerpot and a doormat proclaiming Go Away! by the guardhouse door.</description>
    <position x="137" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb break" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb embrasure" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go guardhouse" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="E'erglim Lighthouse, Bartling's Quarters" note="Bartling">
    <description>Rumpled sheets rest in a heap on a single cot which occupies the entire far wall of this tiny chamber.  A battered sea chest serves as a desk and dresser in one, with a wax-encrusted candle holder perched precariously on its arched top.  The solitary broad bow window commands a breathtaking view of the river and Segoltha Sea beyond to the east.</description>
    <description>Rumpled sheets rest in a heap on a single cot which occupies the entire far wall of this tiny chamber.  A battered sea chest serves as a desk and dresser in one, with a wax-encrusted candle holder perched precariously on its arched top.  The solitary broad bow window reveals the lights of boats resting on the river below and the washing sounds of the Segoltha Sea beyond to the east.</description>
    <position x="618" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go flimsy catwalk" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Fort Motte, Ruins">
    <description>The central summit of the mound, where the regulars assembled to defend their turf, is littered with rubble, marl and weeds.  Little remains to honor those brave defenders of the first settlement here save a few crumbling brick outbuildings and some rusted weapons, rotted wagons and skeletal remains embedded in the weed-choked mud.</description>
    <position x="428" y="-44" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rotting plank" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Orphanage, Flower Garden">
    <description>Pale light from the multiple windows illuminates a cobblestone walk to a large stone building.  The soft scent of blooms scents the evening air.  Ironwood double doors, under the careful watch of two guards, lead into the orphanage.</description>
    <description>A lush garden, full of seasonal flowers, borders the cobblestone walk to a large, stone building and fills the air with a sweet fragrance.  Fat bumblebees buzz lazily about the garden, landing occasionally to partake of a drink of nectar.  Ironwood double doors, under the careful watch of two guards, lead into the orphanage.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doors" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Orphanage, Foyer" note="Orphanage">
    <description>The warm glow of oil lamps lights the foyer of the orphanage, giving the dark-stained wood floor a soft luster.  Small, cushioned benches outside the oak door to the office provide a place for visitors to enjoy a brief rest while they wait to be seen.  On either end of the hall, carved archways open onto the two lower wings of the complex, and a large staircase leads to the upper level.  Directly across from the main entrance, a walnut door set with a large window overlooks a courtyard.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-154" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Orphanage, East Wing">
    <description>The rough shapes of scarecrows can be made out in the dim light through the many large windows.  At the end of the hall stands a stout oak door.  A pine door leading to a darkened room has been left slightly ajar.</description>
    <description>The muted sounds of children echo through the long corridor.  Scarecrows can be seen through the many large windows, watching over their crops.  At the end of the hall stands a stout oak door.  Light shines across a pine door, a guide to the fun which lies beyond it.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-154" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Orphanage, West Wing">
    <description>The smell of baking bread lingers in the hallway.  Several windows looking out onto the courtyard, line the long hall, at one end of which stands a sturdy walnut door.  A pine door and an oak door can also be made out in the dim light.</description>
    <description>The smell of baking bread and the faint sounds of clanking pots and pans fill the hallway.  Several windows looking out onto the courtyard line the long hall, at one end of which stands a sturdy walnut door.  Dust specks seem to dance in the light that shines across the hall, bathing a pine door and an oak door in warm brilliance.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-154" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Orphanage, Library">
    <description>A comical painting of a large, green dragon wearing reading spectacles adorns the wall opposite a row of sturdy bookshelves.  A scattering of oversized pillows surround a leather chair, ready for reading lessons and storytelling sessions.  Oil lamps cast their glow down upon several books that litter the dense, blue-green carpet.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Orphanage, Playroom">
    <description>Plush, purple carpeting covers the floor of this expansive playroom, providing a soft and comfortable surface for the children.  A toy box has been tipped on its side, scattering its contents into one of the corners.  Large, bean-filled, stuffed animals double as toys and furniture.  One looks to have been slain by a particularly energetic orphan, causing it to spill its beans.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-154" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Orphanage, Vegetable Garden">
    <description>The sweet, rich smell of fertile earth is prevalent here.  The shapes of garden tools can be seen in the dim light from the windows of the building.  The sounds of an animal snuffling through a nearby vegetable plot can be heard.</description>
    <description>The sweet, rich smell of fertile earth is prevalent here.  Gardeners are busy tending to the vegetable plots, which border the way leading to the playground.  Nearby, several children gather and wash the harvested crops, gazing longingly at the playground to the north.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-174" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Orphanage, Playground">
    <description>A large climbing structure juts out of an enormous sandbox that provides a relatively soft landing for any who make a misstep.  A teeter-totter has been wedged down on the ground with a large block for safe travel in the dark.</description>
    <description>A large climbing structure juts out of an enormous sandbox that provides a relatively soft landing for any who make a misstep.  A teeter-totter balances precariously and a wide expanse of soft grass makes for the perfect place for a spirited game of tag.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-194" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Orphanage, Craft Room">
    <description>The sharp smell of paint and wheat paste lingers in the air, while the walls of the room have nearly been covered by the drying artwork of children.  The original color of the tile floor is nearly indiscernible, with a mosaic-like pattern created by the various spills and stains.  On the worktables, several paint-smeared palettes rest waiting to be cleaned, while others soak in a basin filled with soapy water.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-174" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Orphanage, Dining Room">
    <description>Several rows of dining tables with bench seating rest opposite the serving counter.  A large, colorful mural of an overflowing horn of plenty covers one of the walls.  The opposite wall is filled entirely with windows, which look out onto a beautiful flower garden.  A service door rocks slightly back and forth, sending the wonderful aromas from the kitchen spilling out into the room.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go service door" destination="139" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Orphanage, Kitchen">
    <description>Busy cooks are diligently preparing ingredients on the central granite countertop.  Several open windows fight a futile battle in an attempt to cool the massive, furnace-like kitchen.  The aroma of wood smoke and baking breads permeate the room amid the sounds of bubbling stews and chopping knives.  A bank of brick ovens and cast-iron stoves line the wall opposite the swinging door that leads to the dining area.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-154" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go swinging door" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Orphanage, Administrative Office">
    <description>A huge mahogany desk sits before two cushioned chairs.  Light from three candles of various heights cascades across its surface, which is practically covered with stacks of ledgers and neat piles of parchment.  A large window with burgundy curtains casts a soft light onto the flower garden outside.</description>
    <description>A huge mahogany desk sits before two cushioned chairs.  Light cascades across its surface, which is practically covered with stacks of ledgers and neat piles of parchment.  A large window with burgundy curtains overlooks the flower garden.  Outside, the chirping of songbirds and laughter of children can be heard, providing a relaxing background to the otherwise stressful task of overseeing the daily running of the orphanage.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Main Hallway, North">
    <description>Cream-colored tiles cover the floor of the rectangular hallway that leads from the large staircase towards some doors, which are spaced along its length.  A large glass skylight illuminates the area, creating shadows on the pale yellow walls.  A large gold-framed picture is placed in a perfect vantage point on the wall above the stairs.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cedar door" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Bedroom, Nursery Staff">
    <description>A large rug covers the wooden floor of the room.  A small window opposite the neatly made bed, looks out on to the courtyard and is framed by heavy, pale green velvet curtains which fall behind an overstuffed armchair.  A small dresser rests against the wall by the door.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cedar door" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Orphanage Nursery">
    <description>Pale lemon-yellow paint covers most of the walls.  The wall with a door has a mural of a woodland scene that extends onto a sky-blue ceiling.  Cribs are placed in an orderly fashion around the room with rocking chairs between them.  Snowy white curtains dress the windows and just reach the varnished wooden floor.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Nursery, Bathing Room">
    <description>A small sink with steel taps is situated under a small window.  Beside it is a long table covered in folded cotton towels of various colors.  Pale grey slate tiles cover the floor while all the walls are vividly painted with the image of a seascape.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-134" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Main Hallway, East">
    <description>Polished brass railings aid the younger children to keep from falling while on the walkway overlooking the ground floor.  Covered torches are mounted high on the wall to provide additional light when necessary.  A pale blue door leads off the main hallway into a large room.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Main Hallway, South">
    <description>The cream tiles of the floor are marred with tiny scratches.  Most of them are near a painted white door with a neatly nailed sign that leads to the clinic.  The hallway stretches an equal distance to the right and left.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Main Hallway, West">
    <description>A cream-colored door with a small rose-shaped plaque stands across the hallway from a plain birch door.  The faint sound of music drifts up from the ground floor, while the air is tinged with the slight scent of roses.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cream door" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Orphanage, Staff Bedroom">
    <description>Two beds dominate the room and flank the pine door to the hallway.  Matching trunks have been placed at the foot of each.  A large window, dressed with cream lace curtains, lets in light and overlooks the courtyard below.  Tucked into the corner is a wardrobe beside a small table.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pine door" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Boys' Dormitory">
    <description>From the pale walls to the much darker carpet, the dormitory is filled with various hues of blue.  The beds are lined up with almost military precision against the two longest walls and have small trunks at their feet.  Three large windows sit above one of these rows, while tucked away in the corner is a large open crate filled with toys.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue door" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Boys' Bathroom">
    <description>A large bath dominates the room and is encircled by sinks, each with a small cupboard over it.  Beside a narrow arch that leads back into the main dormitory is a table filled with blue towels.  Light is provided from small torches high on the wall.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Clinic Staff, Bedroom">
    <description>Pushed tightly against the wall, a bed sits under the room's only window.  A pale lilac rug covers the wooden floor, almost matching the color of the walls.  Sitting next to a mahogany door is a small writing desk with a straight-backed chair.  A light grey door that is slightly ajar leads to the infirmary.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go light door" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Orphanage, Clinic">
    <description>Stark white with pale grey tiling, the room is void of any variation in color.  Metal beds have been lined up against the walls, and there is a regimented feel to the room.  The scent of pine hangs heavily in the air.  A light grey door leads to a small room, and nearby is a desk with a plain chair behind it.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-74" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go white door" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey door" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Girls' Dormitory">
    <description>Pale pink walls complement the rose-colored runner between the two rows of beds in the room.  A small set of drawers is to the right of each bed. A bathing area can be seen through a tall arch, while a door leads back to the hallway.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cream door" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Bathing Area, Girls'">
    <description>Ceramic tiles cover the floor and surround the large bath.  The cream ceiling complements the pale white walls painted with delicate pink roses.  A large rose-colored rug rests on the floor between the bath and a large sideboard piled high with towels.  Next to it sits a small pedestal filled with soap.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-114" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Staff Bedroom, West">
    <description>Various shades of cream are scattered around the room, from the painted walls to curtains draped from the window.  A large, fluffy rug has been haphazardly flung over the floor near a bed covered in a cream woolen blanket.  A large trunk has been placed at the foot of the bed.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-94" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Warehouse, Office">
    <description>All of the office furniture, desk and chairs, have been blown to pieces.  The walls have scorch marks from floor to ceiling.  A large hole in the back wall leads to the warehouse storage area.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Warehouse, Storage">
    <description>The gut wrenching smell of sulfur and burnt flesh is thick in the air.  Scorched debris is scattered all over the building and the sky is visible through a badly damaged roof.  A large hole in one of the walls leads to the warehouse office.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-14" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go hole" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Stuff for Sale" note="Stuff for Sale" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A dirt floor, mud walls, and a smelly pile of straw are all that protect this tiny plot of land from the elements.  The floor is strewn with a mass of random garbage that looks freshly dredged from the swamp, and it is only the crudely scrawled price tags on each piece that indicates some optimistic soul hopes to sell them.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-34" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Cape of Storms, Cromlech">
    <description>Beneath the capped stones that form the dolmen, the air is cool and the ground chilly.  Silvery traces etched into the stones resemble a spider's web, but otherwise its purpose and pattern is mysterious and unclear.</description>
    <position x="518" y="-54" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Observatory, Library" note="Library Moon Mage">
    <description>Softly glowing sconces line the walls of this long library, where wooden shelves are polished to a dark luster and lined with dusty and arcane manuscripts.  A rounded archway leads out to the observatory walk.</description>
    <position x="338" y="146" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go arch" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Phelim's Shrine, Glade Path">
    <description>This gentle glade seems cloaked in perpetual twilight, nestled in a canopy of overhanging willows that threatens to blot out any light daring to filter through their dense branches.  Fireflies alight upon tall ferns, their syncopated inner lights twinkling like stars in a clear night sky.  A groomed, pebbled path runs east toward the front doors of the observatory, and northwest towards a small standing shrine.</description>
    <position x="480" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Phelim's Shrine, Exterior">
    <description>The pebbled path encircles a small shrine of dark marble erected within a tiny clearing.  Pale petals are strewn before the open archway, its surface polished so that the silvered veins within the ebon-hued stone glint even in the slightest remaining light.  Songbirds chirp and chitter all around, though they remain unseen within the shadowed branches of the surrounding trees.</description>
    <description>The pebbled path encircles a small shrine of dark marble erected within a tiny clearing.  Chamomile petals are strewn before the open archway, its surface polished so that the silvered veins within the ebon-hued stone shine brightly as the light catches them.  Songbirds chirp and chitter all around, their deep blue and crimson forms flitting through the trees.</description>
    <position x="460" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open archway" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Middens, Backend Holler" note="Backend Holler" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Rude huts comprised mostly of dung and filthy hay line this muddy unpaved road.  The derelict inhabitants here seem to cleave to their own kind, each race vying against one another for what meager scraps they might dredge from the mire of the Holler.  A canal of fetid runoff flows down towards the river, permeating the area with an acrid stench.</description>
    <position x="240" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Middens, Backend Holler" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A choking air of misery and desperation hangs over the Holler.  Muck squelches underfoot as the path narrows, veering through a shamble of long-abandoned tenements.  Only nominally remaining buildings, the bulk are largely collapsed, exposing crumbling planks like so many rotten teeth.</description>
    <position x="260" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Middens, Backend Holler" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The sodden path dead-ends here, deep in the festering bowels of the Holler, where rows of dilapidated hovels languish in a state of profound disrepair.  Vulgar Gor'Tog beggars pick through stinking mounds of refuse, bellowing at one another, some obviously drunk and others spoiling to fight.</description>
    <position x="280" y="26" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Middens, Backend Holler" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A sickly tree slouches over a putrid pond full of fetid runoff.  Crowds of screaming, feral Halfling children splash and cavort in the foul water.  Cheaply constructed shacks of rusting, corrugated metal dot the far side of the pond.</description>
    <position x="240" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="163" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Middens, Backend Holler" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The sick and diseased of all races queue in front of a rough stone and wood structure that has seemingly become a makeshift clinic amongst the surrounding shanties.  Screams, sobs and pleas for mercy filter out into the street.  A wheezing phlegmatic Gnome hobbles about in a geriatric dance of confusion.</description>
    <position x="260" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Middens, Backend Holler" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Behind the clinic an open expanse of sewage, sludge, goo, and filth span to the horizon.  Mangy animals ooze their way through the vast field of debris like zombies, dropping slobber and foam from their mouths as they go.  A massive pit filled with rotting flesh and festering corpses scars the landscape, serving, as a last resting place for the forgotten.  Odd-shaped shanties and lean-tos rim the pit, affording themselves a grim backyard.</description>
    <position x="280" y="46" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Phelim's Shrine, Interior">
    <description>Motes of dust sparkle in the warm air of this tiny shrine, the polished pebble floor glittering like diamonds in the twilight.  An ivory statue of Phelim stands behind the slender glaes altar, his stony form clad in a robe of twilight-hued velvet swept with silvered stars.</description>
    <position x="470" y="6" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Observatory, Celestial Gardens" color="#00FF00">
    <description>In a tranquil mingling of muted sound and sight, the river to the south continues on toward the sea, hushed in its ambition.  Darkness wraps the iron railing of the staircase in a cloak of shadow.  The night has brought with it a whispering urge to sit and contemplate the knowledge found in the sky and reflect upon the imperfect mirror of the river's surface.  A mosaic pathway leads on for those initiated interested in taking advantage of the Celestial Compact's private gardens.</description>
    <description>Sparkling to the south, the Segoltha River wends its way toward the sea, fringed by the long grasses nourished at the water's edge.  The crystal dome protecting the guild's central atrium rises behind the iron railing of the staircase, reflecting light from the sky.  A mosaic pathway leads on for those initiated interested in taking advantage of the Celestial Compact's private gardens.</description>
    <position x="280" y="266" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb staircase" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pathway" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Observatory, Celestial Cafe">
    <description>The mosaic pathway threads its way lazily through a lush grass courtyard.  Surrounding numerous billowy satin cushions, a series of crystal globes outline the center of the courtyard.</description>
    <description>Surrounding an open air cafe, crystal globes flicker in a vain attempt to drive off the shadows of night.  Eerily illuminated is a faint mosaic pathway leading through the grassy courtyard.</description>
    <position x="260" y="286" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go pathway" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Observatory, Celestial Herb Garden">
    <description>Composed of low hedges and filled with ground-hugging herbs, a geometric knot garden prominently occupies most of the area, leaving room around the outskirts for a mosaic pathway.  A heady aroma, intensifying at the slightest breeze, wafts through the air as if it were a living thing waiting to greet all who pass.</description>
    <description>Small points of light peek out from inside low hedges, revealing in their glow a mosaic pathway and a broad square knot garden filled with herbs.  A warm glow arises from the Crossing in the distance, a beacon amidst the enveloping darkness of night.</description>
    <position x="240" y="306" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Observatory, Celestial Flower Gardens">
    <description>Flower beds, contained within stacked stone borders, give rise to a riotous explosion of color and scent.  Several benches have been placed along the mosaic pathway that winds between the enclosures, affording a place to relax.</description>
    <description>Night leeches the color from the flowers nestled securely in enclosures of stacked stone, transforming them to shades of grey and white.  Several benches have been placed along the mosaic pathway that winds between the enclosures, affording a place to relax.</description>
    <position x="220" y="306" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Observatory, Celestial Water Gardens">
    <description>Diverting briefly around a small fish pond, the mosaic pathway continues its journey through plants that range in a barely tamed mass of ground-concealing greens and blues.  A brass heron stands on thin legs, poised as if to drink or perhaps capture one of the tiny fish swimming serenely under its gaze.</description>
    <description>Soft glimmers peek out from under a carpet of dense green foliage.  The mosaic pathway diverts around a small fish pond graced by a scultpure of a brass heron poised as if to strike at a hapless fish swimming lazily below.</description>
    <position x="200" y="286" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Observatory, Celestial Topiary Gardens">
    <description>Dense hedges clipped into animal shapes nearly hide a small vine-covered structure at the center of the garden, in turn surrounded by meticulously-shaped miniature trees.  A mosaic pathway skirts the edge of the observatory roof, affording an excellent view of the Segoltha in the distance.</description>
    <description>Tiny lights have been tucked into the clouds of foliage on each miniature tree, casting a soft glow over the surrounding garden.  Barely visible in the dim light is a small structure nearly hidden by hedges clipped into animal shapes.</description>
    <position x="180" y="286" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="175" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open archway" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Observatory, Celestial Garden Shop" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The air in this elegant garden shop is perfumed with the lingering scent of lilacs and roses.  Items of interest to members of the Celestial Compact are stocked here, the fragrant scent meant to appeal to customers.  A low herbal bench, a wicker clothing rack and a long ivory table are lit by small crystal globes while clerks stand by to attend to both the casual and wealthy shoppers.  An open archway leads out to the Observatory Gardens.</description>
    <position x="160" y="286" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open archway" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <label text="Sleazy Louts">
    <position x="140" y="36" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="">
    <position x="458" y="46" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moon Mage Guild, Level 2">
    <position x="230" y="200" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moon Mage Guild, Level 1">
    <position x="340" y="-40" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moon Mage Guild, Level 1">
    <position x="600" y="156" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="NE Gate">
    <position x="90" y="-164" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Lost Crossing">
    <position x="530" y="16" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The Crossing (East Gate)">
    <position x="-5" y="33" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins">
    <position x="544" y="-42" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Backend Holler">
    <position x="234" y="5" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Celestial Gardens">
    <position x="170" y="256" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moon Mage Guild, Level 2">
    <position x="460" y="256" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moon Mage Guild, Level 3">
    <position x="300" y="276" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>