<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Reshalia Trade Road" id="92">
  <node id="1" name="Shh'o'kumu Terrace, Sur'oson Gate" note="Map90_Ratha.xml|Ratha">
    <description>Tall timbers and rough-hewn stone form a giant gate in the great wall.  Standing open for the streams of wagon and foot traffic to pass through, the entrance to Ratha is carefully guarded by observant sentinels who watch every passerby with trained eyes.</description>
    <position x="340" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sur'oson gate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Ratha, Outside Sur'oson Gate">
    <description>Cloaked travelers slip in and out of the gate, wrapped up against the chill of the night and carrying torches and lanterns to light their way.  Although there are relatively few folk passing through at this hour, the gate guards seem particularly alert as they assess each person, keeping one eye on the shadows.</description>
    <description>All manner of travelers mill about the gate, either waiting their turn to enter or pushing through the crowds in the opposite direction if they're leaving.  Farmers pass through with wagonloads of produce and grain, fishermen with their catches, and rangers with bundles of hides.  The gate guards look on, watching everyone.</description>
    <position x="340" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sur'oson gate" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go large stable" destination="288" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Reshalia Trade Road">
    <description>The well-maintained gravel road connects the farmland to the northwest with the walled city to the southeast.  The city doesn't appear to cover much territory when viewed from this direction, but judging by the noise drifting this way it has to be quite a bit larger than it appears.</description>
    <position x="320" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Reshalia Trade Road">
    <description>The land near the city has been denuded of all vegetation save for weeds, and even the useful among their number have been rooted up and foraged into extermination.  All that's left are some scrubby grasses and a few patches here and there of a particularly ugly creeper.  An occasional insect creeps, hops or buzzes about its business, but even the bugs have largely sought more hospitable terrain.</description>
    <position x="300" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The land to the east and northeast lies under heavy cultivation.  Neither trees nor rocks mar the neatly rowed flatness of the fields, and even the occasional farmhouse huddles about itself, giving the impression of having pulled in its skirts so as to leave as much land as possible to the crops.</description>
    <position x="300" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The road runs close by the edge of the barley fields to the west.  On the opposite side of the way the land resembles a rural garbage heap.  The farmers apparently dumped stumps and boulders dug out of the fields across the road, and then continued dumping anything else they didn't want there in subsequent years.  Beyond the narrow strip of rocks and refuse the land rises in a steep slope, a berm covered with grass and weeds and loose-looking rocks.</description>
    <position x="300" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Rustling in the dark fields indicates that someone, or some thing, is doing some night harvesting, and it's probably not the farmer who crops this land.  The occasional barking of a dog identifies the source of at least some of the rustling, but dogs don't eat barley.</description>
    <description>Birds flutter back and forth, alternating between raiding the barley fields to the west, and hopping about the refuse piles to the east in search of whatever might be in there that is of interest to birds.  They seem to prefer the barley fields, but farm children with slings make raiding that particular cornucopia somewhat hazardous.</description>
    <position x="320" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The steep berm rising to the east blocks the view in that direction, but a cool breeze blowing down the slope bears the scent of water.  A narrow path winds through the rubbish on the east side of the road, past a rotting cart with no wheels and around an unstable pile of boulders, but there's no fixed path up the berm.  Its rocky slope is only partially anchored by foliage, and the rest looks very shifty.  The path continues to the west, disappearing into the barley.</description>
    <position x="320" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" hidden="True" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow path" hidden="True" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Flat, open fields stretch out to the west, broken occasionally by small farmhouses.  Beyond the fields rises a huge cindercone.  The volcano dominates the western skyline, tall and broad.  Its sides are old and weathered and craggy, with no sign of any lava or hot ash having flowed in this direction for quite some time.</description>
    <position x="240" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" hidden="True" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The dark fields along the west side of the road rustle softly in the night air.  A huge, dark mound looms over the scene as though watching over all under its looming eye.  At night, even more so than in the daytime, the volcano dominates the landscape.</description>
    <description>Rippling barley fills the fields to the west, from the road all the way to the base of the volcano.  The fields appear to be very fertile and the crop bountiful.  Children with slings run back and forth driving away hungry birds, while their elders move slowly through the grain, their concentration on their work.</description>
    <position x="220" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The crops in the fields change here, with barley to the south and kord to the north.  The barley fields are low, smooth and rustling, while the kord plants are taller, stringy and rather tangled looking.  Between the barley for beer and the kord for rope, this area is well suited to support ocean trade and its sailors.</description>
    <position x="200" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Night birds flap and squawk around a large farm wagon which was left out in the fields.  Judging by the calls and twitters, there are at least two kinds of birds out there, but it's too dark to see more than an occasional dark flutter of a silhouette against the starry black of the sky.</description>
    <description>Farmers work in the fields on the west side of the road, moving slowly along the rows with a wagon trailing them.  Someone is singing a slow song in S'Kra, and a number of farmers in one area are swaying slightly in time with the tune.</description>
    <position x="220" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>A small patch of orange flowers grows along the side of the road in the shadow of the stringy yellow kord plants.  More flowers, both the orange ones and some tiny white ones, grow scattered on the opposite side of the road, peeping out from between the discarded tree stumps and wagon wheels and bushel baskets.</description>
    <position x="200" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Stand">
    <description>A shuttered and empty stand sits in the bend of the road.  Judging by the scuffled footprints, and the deep ruts where wagons and caravans seem to have sat for some time, the stand enjoys a brisk flow of business in the daytime.  But in the night it's closed and still, just a boxy shadow in the dark.</description>
    <description>The children of a farmer have set up a little stand in the bend of the road.  Both farm folk and travellers gather here to have a cup of ale or a piece of bread and while away as much time as they can take from their labors, making this stretch of the track rather congested.</description>
    <position x="180" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go little stand" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland" color="#008000">
    <description>A scattering of daaknut trees grows haphazardly in the jumble of rocks and logs and refuse on the east side of the road.  Indigestible to humans, the nuts are believed to be particularly tasty by pigs of all sorts, and judging by the tracks in the dirt the farmers of the area take their pigs across the road to fatten up on the free largesse which falls from the trees at all seasons of the year.</description>
    <position x="200" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Just to the northeast the road is rutted, with an obvious track passing crosswise over it.  This is where the farmers usually cross with wagons of refuse, and take their pigs to feed on the daaknuts, often in depressingly large herds.  Depressing for any travellers caught on the wrong side of the stream of porcine livestock, that is.  The farmers are doubtless quite happy with the fertility of their pigs.</description>
    <position x="220" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Just to the southwest the road is rutted, with an obvious track passing crosswise over it.  This is where the farmers usually cross with wagons of refuse, and take their pigs to feed on the daaknuts, often in depressingly large herds.  Depressing for any travellers caught on the wrong side of the stream of porcine livestock, that is.  The farmers are doubtless quite happy with the fertility of their pigs.</description>
    <position x="240" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The tangled kord bushes bend and wave, although not in neat ripples as one would expect if it were the breeze moving them.  Something is apparently moving in there.  Whether it is children sneaking out in the darkness, though, or some sort of animal, one really can't say.</description>
    <description>The tangled kord bushes bend and wave, although not in neat ripples as one would expect if it were the breeze moving them.  Something is apparently moving in there.  Whether it is children hiding out, though, or some sort of animal one can't really say.</description>
    <position x="260" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Yellowish kord dominates the landscape from the road to the base of the volcano looming on the horizon.  The fibrous plant has never been known as a particularly valuable crop, but this near to a busy port town on the ocean there must be quite a steady demand for it.  Growing it is a sign of conservative responsibility in the farmers, rather than any dreams of being some day wealthy.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>A few scrubby trees and some low, tangled bushes are all that grow on the rocky berm to the east.  Rising high and steep above the long and narrow junk heap on that side of the road, it's regular enough to appear artificial.  The low call of water birds is heard from that direction, and every now and then a soaring shape appears in the sky.</description>
    <position x="260" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>It looks like someone discarded an entire stove on the east side of the road among the rotting stumps and shriveled kord stems.  Shaped like a flattened pyramid, it looks like it was originally of sturdy but unornamented construction.  The wrought iron is well rusted now, with gaping holes that were never made by the smith.  Some sort of small animal apparently nests inside, and twittering birds occasionally swoop down to perch and call.</description>
    <position x="280" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland" color="#808040">
    <description>The road takes a sharp turn here at the corner of a field.  The ground underfoot is soft and squishy, with frequent stretches that are downright slippery.  The smell of healthy, wet slime gives you a clue as to why this piece of road is so hazardous -- it's very muddy and oozy.</description>
    <description>The road takes a sharp turn here at the corner of a field.  The farmer who tends this land is a little overly enthusiastic about filling the drainage ditches, and water spills over onto the road somewhere to the northwest, making this stretch soggy.  A wide variety of slimes and mosses have taken over different ruts and corners, making all this mud most interesting for a dedicated natural philosopher, and a slippery nuisance for everyone else.</description>
    <position x="300" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland" color="#808040">
    <description>A pedal mill stands astride the irrigation ditch to one side of the road.  The surface of the road here is wet and muddy -- it looks like water slops over out of the ditch on a regular basis.</description>
    <description>Two large Gor'Togs, a male and a female, work side by side on a pedal-mill.  Constructed of old lumber lashed together, the rickety contraption lifts water out of the flowing irrigation ditch and dumps it into the smaller ditch leading off into the kord field west of the road.  One of the small buckets on the male's side of the machine is cracked, causing it to spill water onto the road whenever it comes around.</description>
    <position x="280" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland" color="#808040">
    <description>The occasional crunch underfoot is caused by gravel strewn in the road, apparently in an attempt to improve the footing in the muddy ruts.  It's a futile effort, however, since the gravel simply sinks into the mud and vanishes whenever it's walked on.  The road is wet and slippery, and the gravel only serves to bring to mind the likelihood of a few nasty cuts if one takes a spill, in addition to the inevitable mud on one's clothes.</description>
    <position x="260" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland" color="#808040">
    <description>To the west, in a corner where two kord fields meet at an angle, is a small rocky spot where the farmers have built a wooden shrine.  A path planted on either side with daisies and ornamental grasses leads to the cozy structure.  Two stone cows lie on either side of the path, their necks garlanded with wilted daisy wreaths, their carved eyes flat and glazed looking.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>A large pile of decomposing weeds lies fetid on the east side of the road.  Judging by the mound they rest on, the farmer across the way has been dumping weeds here for many years.  The pile is decomposing -- slowly -- and the ripe, earthy stench is overwhelming.</description>
    <position x="240" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The night has drawn its cloak over the quiet fields to the southwest.  You hear an occasional soughing of wind or rustling of vegetation, but other than that all is quiet.  It's too dark to tell what might be planted only a few armlengths away, or what stage of life the plants might be in.</description>
    <description>About a dozen farmers are doing something incomprehensibly farmish in the broad field to the southwest.  They're walking back and forth to and from a large cart loaded with something you can't quite make out, carrying baskets.  Scores of birds, black and brown and white and grey, wheel and swoop over the land, prevented from landing anywhere for long by a swarm of children with slings.</description>
    <position x="220" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Bees circle busily about a huge old oak tree on one side of the road.  Too big to dig out of the field, the farmer apparently thought it better to succumb to the inevitable and leave it.  There are signs that he's harvested honey from the hive, so he's reaped some benefit from his mercy, although the bees, were they capable of considering the matter, would most likely not see it that way.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb oak tree" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Two crops meet here at this bend in the road, which follows the boundaries of two different fields ploughed at a slight angle with each other.  The fields to the north are planted in beans, a tall, spreading variety which grows up twined stakes.  Those to the south are planted in kord, a shorter, fibrous plant, yellowish and tangled looking.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Shy columbines grow in the shade of a spreading elm tree, their nodding heads of cream colored blossoms surrounded by colorful spurs in red and yellow and purple, giving them a graceful delicacy.  Night breezes set the blooms to swaying, and the calls of night birds echo through the darkness.</description>
    <description>Shy columbines grow in the shade of a spreading elm tree, their nodding heads of cream colored blossoms surrounded by colorful spurs in red and yellow and purple, giving them a graceful delicacy.  A few bees buzz about, collecting pollen from the blooms, while songbirds hidden in the branches above sing the day.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The steep berm east of the road curves around from east to south.  The far curvature to the east is almost visible, but the smooth, grassy ridge disappears to the south too far for one to make out the southern boundary.  A narrow strip of wasteland runs between the base of the berm and the trade road, while across the road a wider strip of cropland spreads out all the way to the base of a large volcano just visible on the horizon.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>A large patch of field on the eastern side of the road grows what appears to be hops, while the larger spread of land on the opposite side is planted in pole beans.  The fields are well tended and appear to be flourishing.  A number of people, both adults and children, are working in the bean fields to the north, but you can't quite make out what they're doing.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Old Fields Road, Fields">
    <description>Rutted tracks wind between tumbledown stone walls overgrown with pigweed and nutgrass.  Periodic rumbles from the distant volcano continue to shake stones loose from crumbling mortar.  The fields beyond are full of grasses and weeds, choking out any remaining crops.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Old Fields Road, Fields">
    <description>Overgrown wagon tracks run between the road and a cluster of decaying buildings.  Granite rocks form heaps and piles alongside the tracks, vainly attempting to keep back the weeds.  The stones once formed fences, but now appear more like cairns in the tall grass.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Old Fields Road, Vacant Farm">
    <description>Bare ground is rapidly losing the battle against the weeds, with crabgrass runners and dandelions predominating.  Stumps of buildings rise waist-high here and there, their roof timbers collapsed inward or missing altogether.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Old Fields Road, Vacant Farm" color="#008000">
    <description>One lone building stands forlornly among the ruins of a farm.  Its walls and roof are heaped over with dirt and turf, turning the whole structure into a low hill.  A gaping doorway leads into the darkness of the interior, a small trickle of water seeping over the doorstep and oozing into the dirt.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gaping doorway" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Old Fields Road, Vacant Farm">
    <description>Weathered and battered, the walls of a barn lay collapsed beside the ruts of the road.  Another structure lies across the road, its form entirely shrouded in piles of wild kord.  Tendrils of kord cloak the skeleton of an oak tree that stood too close.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Old Fields Road, Idle Fields">
    <description>Corn stalks fight a losing battle with mallow and pigweed in the fields bordering the road.  Dandelions sprout in the center of the road, their yellow flowers doing little to relieve the desolate emptiness.  Low hills lie to the west and south, slowly rising in the distance to the base of the large volcano with wisps of smoke rising from its crater.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Old Fields Road, Idle Fields">
    <description>Boulder-strewn fields testify to the power of the distant volcano.  One large boulder landed on a stone wall, causing it to collapse.  The field within is bare of all but groundsel and thistle with not even one volunteer crop plant to tell what was once cultivated there.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills" color="#008000">
    <description>The roadway skims and dodges low rolling hills that climb out of the untended fields.  Several stumps stand stoically on the hillside while the grass and thistle sway in the wind.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills" color="#008000">
    <description>Scrub shrubs cling tenaciously to the sides of the hills, their very existence precarious in this desolate waste.  Cinder and rock covers much of the ground, mute testimony to the power of the looming volcano.  The remains of the road twist and turn between the hills as it travels through the scarred terrain.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills" color="#008000">
    <description>Steep hillsides rise to the south of the road as it follows the banks of a once-flourishing stream that is now a rock-choked trickle of water.  Rotted logs and broken stumps line the bends of the streambed.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills">
    <description>Cinder and ash completely obliterate parts of the track, leaving only patches of ruts between the barren hillsides.  Tiny shrubs cling tenaciously to the ground and are just about the only sign of life around.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills">
    <description>One side of a hill to the east has slumped down into the valley the roadway threads through.  The scar from the mudslide has softened somewhat, but no plant life yet grows on it.  Cinder and ash blow fitfully in the wind, and an occasional rumble from the volcano sends the stench of sulfur drifting on the breeze.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills">
    <description>The path twists here, snaking along the side of a hill from the top of a plateau down to a small valley below.  Scrawny grasses and a few battered weeds scatter in tufts on the ground.  A deep crack in the ground leads downward into shadow.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deep crack" destination="170" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills">
    <description>Tumbleweeds skitter back and forth in the wind, occasionally catching on a boulder or low-lying shrub.  The route is the barest hint of a path threading its way between the debris, revealing itself mainly as an absence of stones or rocks.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills">
    <description>Tufts of grass grow around an old post.  A comparative oasis in this barren area, the small patch of life only further underscores the bleakness of the landscape.  The sullen volcano rises to the west and dominates the countryside with rumbles and belches.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Old Fields Road, Low Hills">
    <description>The track traces its way over a small streamlet, crossing on the remains of a bridge.  A few ambitious juriweed plants tightly clench the ground near the stream, grimly clinging to life.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Old Fields Road, Bluff Edge">
    <description>Sheer cliffs fall away to the north, providing a panorama of the sea.  To the south, a large volcano rises out of a surrounding landscape of squat hills.  Vines creep up the cliffs from the base, seeking out all possible spots for growth.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Old Fields Road, Bluff Edge">
    <description>Steep bluffs, deeply eroded by gullies and washes, terminate the trail.  The ocean is visible below as a rolling, deep azure-blue field.  Mallow and groundsel spread about the dusty ground and cling to the edge.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go thin trail" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The howling and woofing of a number of dogs sound through the night, along with the rustle of things moving through the dark fields to the west.  It's too dark to see exactly where the dogs are or what they might be doing, but the occasional panicked cawing of a bird provides a clue.</description>
    <description>Ragged children divide their time between pulling weeds out of the rows of climbing bean plants, currently about chest high, and chasing off hungry birds with their slings.  Their elders follow a few yards behind them with a large farm cart, carrying baskets back and forth between the cart and the plants.  Judging by the smell, the adults are spreading fertilizer on the field.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>The large black blob on the eastern side of the road seems to be an anthill, although no ants are visible in the darkness.  A hunting owl hoots somewhere nearby, and swarms of fireflies dart and swoop about, lighting up the night like tiny torches.</description>
    <description>A large anthill sits to one side, between the trade road and the hops field to the east.  Tiny black ants scurry about, wandering back and forth in their winding paths.  Some carry bits of food, others seem to be in search of it, or of whatever else their little ant minds tell them they need just now.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="51" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Farmland">
    <description>Fields spread on either side of the road to the south, one side planted in pole beans while the other side is planted in hops.  The northern stretch of road is bounded by roughly cleared land, grass and weeds and wildflowers growing in a straggly fashion between the stumps of cut trees.  A few saplings have grown up here and there, but it'll be a long time before they're big enough to call trees.  A smaller dirt road runs to the east along the northern boundary of the hops field.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing" color="#008000">
    <description>The sweet scent of lilacs fills the air, blown in on the strong night winds.  The cawing and hooting of winged night hunters drift by, but for the most part the calls of the littlest birds are missing.  The smaller, weaker birds know better than to brave the blowing weather.</description>
    <description>Bright carpets of flowers grow around the squat treestumps on either side of the road.  Yellow and red daisies turn their faces up toward the sun, while little white starflowers cover the ground like snow.  Lilac bushes grow spotted about, their white or purple falls of blossom filling the air with a sweet scent.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing">
    <description>Tracks in the road show where at least two rabbits crossed not long ago.  Apparently the cutting down of the woods hasn't driven away quite all of the animals.  The deer and boar and bear are gone, but creatures the size of rabbits can still find shelter in the grasses and smaller shrubs left to dominate the land.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing">
    <description>When the wind blows just right, the sound of the ocean can be heard from here.  The crashing of the surf on the faraway shore sounds its endless rhythm, reminding one, even here a ways inland and several hundred feet up, that this is only an island, a speck of dirt surrounded by the mighty seas.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing">
    <description>The wind from the ocean blows in each night, making the slender young trees sway wildly and the grasses bow down flat in homage.  An occasional hysterical tweetering passes quickly from west to east as a small bird is blown by.  The night wind seems stronger on this stretch of road than any other, probably because the clear cutting of the trees has opened a path for the strongest gusts.</description>
    <description>Tiny birds dart here and there, singing their caroling songs and perching occasionally on the slender branches of the saplings which grow sparsely across the clearing.  The light weight of the little birds is enough to make the twiggy branches sway, as is indeed the breath of even a light breeze.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing">
    <description>Bare stumps stand irregularly around the clearing, like headstones in the graveyard of the forest.  The demand for lumber drives woodcutters ever farther north from Ratha in their search for more and ever more trees.  Ruts in the ground show where the rain, no longer softened by the leafy canopy of the trees, pounds directly into the dirt and runs off in rivulets, carrying soil with it.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing">
    <description>A few sparse bushes grow among the stumps and the spindly saplings, but the rest of the ground is either bare and rutted or covered with coarse grass.  Blue and orange and yellow wildflowers brighten the otherwise bleak scene, showing the nature will generally win out, if only she's left alone for a while.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Clearing">
    <description>Deep ruts in the road indicate where heavy carts loaded with logs trundled down south to Ratha, carrying away the forest.  The bare stumps mark civilization, with all its good and evil.  The woods to the north is still green and growing, but that won't likely last for long.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Tall, broad elm trees cast deep, cool shadows on the ground.  The road runs between the trees, straight enough to have been originally cut as a main road, rather than beginning as a winding track as do so many such thoroughfares.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Moonlight filters down through the leafy branches of the elm trees, painting gentle flickers on the loamy ground and the flowers and shrubbery.  Here and there stands a hewn off stump, marking where a tree has been felled, but for the most part the land here has been left in peace.  Birds call from the branches, insects buzz about, and all is tranquil.</description>
    <description>Sunlight filters down through the leafy branches of the elm trees, painting gentle flickers on the loamy ground and the flowers and shrubbery.  Here and there stands a hewn off stump, marking where a tree has been felled, but for the most part the land here has been left in peace.  Birds call from the branches, insects buzz about, and all is tranquil.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The rustle of leaves, the soughing of wind, and the tweetle-ee-ee-eep of birds all combine into a woodland symphony.  Far in the background is a rhythmic crashing that might be the ocean, although it's barely at the threshold of perceptible sound.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The gravel road runs through a pleasant wood composed mostly of grand old elms, with a few other trees scattered throughout.  Ferns grow around the bases of the trees, and shade-loving fuchsias thrive in the shadows.  Some kind of insect makes a chitter-click-click sound in the background, although it's well enough hidden that it can't be seen.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Suckers have sprung up all around the stump of a tree, roughly hewn with an axe a year or two ago.  In time the suckers will grow up into a ring of young trees, with the father stump decaying into a punky mound in the center.  Insects swarm over the rotting wood, some eating it, some making their home in it, and others preying upon the rest.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Shady elms grow on either side of the trade road.  The spreading trees cast shadows on the lower foliage, allowing ferns, columbines, fuchsias and other shade plants to flourish.  Here and there a stump shows where a woodcutter has taken a tree, dragging off the trunk and leaving the trimmed branches to decay on the loamy ground.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Reshalia, Abandoned Road" note="Silver Leucros" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>This branch of the road narrowly skirts a large gravel pit just to the north, but it shows no sign of through traffic by the gravel carts.  Tracks lead to the west, as if carts were sometimes stored here, but none continue down the road.  Instead, weeds and briars appear increasingly in the wheel ruts to the east.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Reshalia, Abandoned Road" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A rutted road stretches east and west, but it is so overgrown with weeds that it must be a long while since it has seen many travelers.  To the north yawns a great space -- the gravel pit, filled with the shouts of laborers by day, but now dark and silent.  A dark forest, thickly grown, lies to the south of the road.</description>
    <description>A rutted road stretches east and west, but it is so overgrown with weeds that it must be a long while since it has seen many travelers.  To the north yawns a great open gravel pit, filled with the shouts of laborers and the clatter of their tools.  A dark forest, thickly grown, lies to the south of the road.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Reshalia, Abandoned Road" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Low scrub covers the road and the broken wagon wheel that once traveled it.  The underbrush has returned, burying the traces of passage except to the west, where ruts can still be made out.  Gaps appear in the encircling trees to the north and northeast, although which of them was the road is hard to say.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Abandoned Road, The Briar Wood" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>From all around, both close by and deep in the woods, come strange sounds, sounds out of place in this wilderness.  One is caught in mid-step, even in mid-breath, by the very oddity of the noises -- clicks, a rasp of metal on stone, a half-liquid slither.</description>
    <description>Although trees and high underbrush line this crossing of what may be game trails, the ground looks more open to the southwest.  Shifting patches of light pierce the dense crown above, and a darker path heads east, deeper into the wood.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="72" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Abandoned Road, The Pit Edge" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>To the west is the unmistakable feel of a vast open space, threatening in its emptiness.  But if one yields to the pressure of the wilderness to the east and edges away from the hidden dangers of the wood, one false step could mean a stumble, a fall, and an unheard cry.</description>
    <description>The road, sunken from former traffic, stands well away from the edge of the massive pit to the west.  To the north, the road continues, obscured somewhat by dust rising from the gravel quarry.  A trail leads off through the foliage to the east.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Abandoned Road, The Briar Wood" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The path opens into a clearing that looks oddly regular in the darkness.  A musty scent like damp ash fills the air.  The smell is faint but fresh, as if something has recently been burned or scorched then doused.</description>
    <description>In the midst of thorns and briars, ringed by a high wall of dark cedars, lies a perfectly circular clearing.  Although weeds fill the center, footprints all around the edge of the clearing show where countless feet have beaten the ground cover to the bare earth.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Abandoned Road, The Briar Wood" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>The air in this maze of paths is still and heavy with a sharp medicinal odor.  The silence is broken from time to time by a falling drop, although the interlocked needles overhead shelter the area from all but the fiercest storms.</description>
    <description>Overhead the sky is nearly blotted out by the crowns of trees fighting for sunlight.  Some of the thorn bushes beneath them bear droplets of a clear liquid, thick and oily, with a scent vaguely like camphor.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Abandoned Road, The Pit Edge" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A vast, black emptiness stretches west and north.  With the yawning void on one side and the forest on the other, the sense of vulnerability is oppressive, as if the place offers no protection and no escape.</description>
    <description>The road curves to the northeast, avoiding a gap where the edge has collapsed.  From the pile of rock and rubble far below, the crumbling of the edge must have been spectacular.  Travelers on foot, perhaps giving the gap a wider berth, have beaten a shortcut through the dark briar wood to the east.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="71" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Abandoned Road, The Pit Edge" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>A misstep in the darkness at the edge of the pit would surely be fatal, and the traveler does well here to rely on the feel of the ground underfoot.  The wood to the east may offer more security -- or only danger of a different kind.</description>
    <description>More a path than a road, the way circles the gap where the pit edge has crumbled away.  The new face is almost vertical, eroded deeply and as yet untamed by plant or weather.  The gravel miners far down in the pit seem to avoid the area just below the gap, perhaps from bitter experience.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Abandoned Road, The Briar Wood" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>No description could be more appropriate for this small clearing than dead in dead end.  It's hard to say where the hint of death comes from, for the surrounding trees sound lively enough, shifting and rustling as if moved by a breeze.  Even when there is no breeze.</description>
    <description>A small clearing is encircled by a wall of dense undergrowth broken only by the path leading in.  Although the firm, dry area would make a fine campsite, there is no sign of visitors -- no empty bottles or wineskins, no discarded broken gear, not even the ashes of an old fire.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Abandoned Road, The Briar Wood" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Briars snag the unwary wayfarer at each pace, and thick, dark-green cedars limit vision except to the west.  In that direction, the path around the pit lies in plain view, although the watcher is well hidden by brush.  It seems a place made for waiting in ambush.</description>
    <description>This part of the wood, not far from the path around the gravel pit, sees few hunters, to judge by the wild growth of the brush on every side except to the west.  And it all seems to have thorns: if anything besides briars, nettles, holly, and thornbush grows here, it must be out of season.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Abandoned Road, The Briar Wood" color="#C0C0C0">
    <description>Even in the darkness, it's apparent this is an open area of some size.  From time to time spots of light appear, dim reddish dots.  They look to be about the height of a Halfling above the ground, showing up briefly, sometimes moving, then disappearing as quickly as they came.</description>
    <description>A secluded dell offers welcome relief from snagging thorns and tripping vines.  Thick grass cushions the ground and invites the weary to pause and rest.  The noise and dust of the gravel pit are only memories here, almost part of a different world.</description>
    <position x="620" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Slopes">
    <description>The road slopes gently down from the top of the plateau which comprises most of the southern end of the island.  The view to the north is spectacular if the weather cooperates.  Light glistens off the ocean to the north, east and west, all the way to the dim horizon, where the occasional sail is just visible.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" hidden="True" destination="80" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Slopes" color="#008000">
    <description>The sloping ground is moist and fertile looking.  A few trees grow here and there, but most of the vegetation here is lower, shrubs and grasses whose roots bind the soil and prevent it all from running down into the ocean.  Mushrooms grow in odd patches of shade under bushes and next to rocks.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Gravel Pit">
    <description>A huge black pit opens up in the ground to the southeast side of the road.  It's too dark to tell how deep it might be, but the vast, gaping maw might well go all the way down to the home of the world dragon, or so it seems.</description>
    <description>A large pit opens up in the ground to the southeast side of the road.  Sweating workmen labor bent over in the pit, some swinging pickaxes and others loading rock into carts with large shovels.  It looks like hard, dirty work and a miserable life for anyone to have to lead.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Gravel Pit">
    <description>This lonely piece of road runs between a thin stretch of wood to the northwest and a dark, wide hole in the ground to the southeast.  Ominous sounds come from both sides of the track, rustling and calling, with an occasional spine-shivering howl from the woods, and rattling and scrabbling sounds from the pit.  Neither is terribly comforting on a cold, dark night.</description>
    <description>The sounds of hard labor drift out of the gravel pit to one side of the road.  The whacking of pickaxes, the scrape and crash of rock being loaded with shovels, the ringing of sledge hammers and the rattle of gravel in sorting screens all blend into a chaotic din that assaults the ears.  The woods on the other side of the road are thin, with many stumps and few grown trees.  The wooden scaffolding and sheds and lean-tos down in the pit show where the wood likely went to.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Gravel Pit">
    <description>Gravel from the road goes rattling down into the pit every few minutes, returning to where it originally came from.  The road here is wide enough to be safe, despite the nearness of the pit on one side, but the huge black maw is frightening enough to send one to travel as far over on the opposite side as possible.</description>
    <description>Gravel from the road goes rattling down into the pit every few minutes, returning to where it originally came from.  The road here is wide enough to be safe, despite the nearness of the pit on one side, but one moment of inattention could cause a long fall into its depths.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Gravel Pit">
    <description>A dark pit opens up on the southeast side of the road.  It's impossible to tell how deep it is, but in the darkness of the night it looks bottomless.  The road runs perilously near the edge of the pit, and understandably most of the wheel ruts crowd the opposite side of the track, which runs near a wooded area.</description>
    <description>Workers swarm around a series of lean-tos and awnings down at the bottom of the huge gravel pit that gapes open on the southeast side of the road.  Carts move between the deepest areas of the pit and the awnings, and to a rickety wooden elevator standing near several huge hills of gravel.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Slopes">
    <description>A large granite boulder sits sentry on the side of the road.  A small gap at its base is too dark to see into, but the crusted piles of dirt in a half-circle around it suggest that something inside is having an addition put onto the back of the house.  The burrow has been cleverly placed on the downhill side of the boulder, so it's well sheltered from rain and water running down the slope.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="86" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Slopes">
    <description>The road meanders up a gentle slope, past acres of wildflowers and aromatic shrubs set amidst a grassy meadow that just happens to be somewhat tilted.  A cool, strong night breeze blows in from the ocean, just a mile or so west of here, carrying with it the scent of salt and the crashing of surf on rocks.</description>
    <description>The road meanders up a gentle slope, past wildflowers and aromatic shrubs set amidst a grassy meadow that just happens to be somewhat tilted.  Butterflies flutter from flower to flower, sipping from shy columbines and lillies of the valley nestled under larger bushes, and lilacs and poppies growing out in the sun.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The tiny leaves of birch trees shiver in the breeze, dancing against the background of their white and black trunks and greyish branches.  Sassy bluejays perch on the branches overhead, chattering with each other and swooping down upon occasion to see if you've dropped anything tasty.  Gravel combines with birch leaves and seed clusters to make the surface of the road crunchy.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Birch trees grow sparsely here, and the undergrowth is mostly grass, with a few small flowers and an odd succulent or two.  The sounds of the sea are clearly audible from this spot, as is the mournful call of the grey and black sea birds that swoop and circle overhead.  The air smells very slightly of salt, when the wind is from the west.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Trade Road, Cliff Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The road here runs within a few hundred feet of the cliff overlooking Slo'Tami Bay.  The sound of the surf below is plain, but twisted cypress trees block any view of the water.  The underbrush is dense, impassable except perhaps with a work crew wielding pickaxes.  A smaller road branches off to the east, curving around some trees and quickly out of sight.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Trade Road, Cliff Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The trade road curves around the northeastern point of the bay.  Cypresses press in on both sides, leaving scarcely room for two wagons to pass.  The underbrush is woody, tangled and dense.  No flowers grow nearby, nor even much grass save for a few yellowish tufts here and there.  The sound of the waves crashing on the rocks below is quite loud, but the trees are too dense to allow a view of the water.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="91" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Trade Road, Cliff Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The low spreading cypress trees cast deep shadows across the road.  The shade promotes damp, and the gravel spread regularly on the road sinks down into the mud beneath quickly enough that the road is muddy more often than not.  Birds screech and flap about in the dense foliage, but are only rarely seen overhead.  The air smells of sea salt and bird droppings.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="90" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="92" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Trade Road, Cliff Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Voices can be heard over the crashing of the waves, male voices mostly, calling to each other and laughing.  There must be a number of people about, somewhere on the bay side of the road, but the trees are impossible to see through, much less pass.  Flickers of firelight shine through the foliage, and a general glow comes from what's probably right around the edge of the cliff.</description>
    <description>Voices can be heard over the crashing of the waves, male voices mostly, calling to each other and laughing.  There must be a number of people about, somewhere on the bay side of the road, but the trees are are impossible to see through, much less pass.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="go" move="search go narrow gap" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Trade Road, Cliff Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Black and grey seabirds call and screech from an unpleasantly close distance.  A pair of them have made a nest in the cypresses right off the path, and they go hysterical whenever someone passes by, no matter how quietly.  Feathers, down and droppings litter the twigs and spot the ground, while forearm-long feathered bodies swoop back and forth across the road, complaining raucously.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Trade Road, Cliff Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The road hugs the edge of the bluffs here, forced right up to the brink by the twisted cypresses on the opposite side of the track.  To the west the land runs down a shallow incline, the cliffs stretching not quite so high as they do to the east.  The view to the southeast shows the Slo'Tami Cliffs in all their ruddy glory, while directly to the south and still over a hundred feet below lies the bay itself.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Trade Road, Cliff Meadow">
    <description>Few trees grow here on the slopes.  Tough grasses send fibrous roots into the soil where they cling tight against the gales which blow in off the ocean.  An occasional cypress shrub raises its gnarled branches toward the sky, and here and there a low-growing patch of sea anemone spreads, its succulent leaves looking like green fruit spears, surrounding the fleshy purple and pink flowers which give the plant its name.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Trade Road, Cliff Meadow">
    <description>The road slopes up to the east as the land rises toward the Slo'Tami Cliffs which curve around the inside of the bay of the same name.  A brisk wind smelling of salt and seaweed blows off the water, stirring the yellow fountains of grass and the bushes scattered about the meadow.  Hardy daisies nod in the shifting air currents, and dry leaves rustle.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="97" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow" note="Sirese" color="#00FF00">
    <description>An open meadow spreads out to the north, bounded a few dozen yards away by a wooded area composed of what look like elms, birch, and an occasional oak.  Flowers dot the meadow, in orange and yellow and white, along with a number of burrows of about the size to have been dug by rabbits.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" hidden="True" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow">
    <description>The road curves away from the bay to the northwest and toward the cliffs to the east.  It slopes very slightly to the south, and there are signs of water erosion in the ruts leading toward the cliff's edge.  If one looks closely, it's apparent that the road used to run right where the drop-off is now, but the receding cliff forced whomever maintains the road to pull it back for safety's sake.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" hidden="True" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="99" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow">
    <description>An old cart wheel lies decaying by the side of the road.  A short distance away the remains of half a dozen broken barrels litter the grass, their rusted hoops arcing up above their rotting staves.  A patch of oats grows all around the spot where the junk is scattered, with a few smaller tufts nodding in the light wind to the east.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow">
    <description>A huge oak tree grows hard by the side of the road, its rough-barked branches spreading grandly toward the sky.  The hooting of an owl is heard periodically, and fireflies swirl and dance in the night air, like a galaxy of stars come down to Elanthia to play.</description>
    <description>A huge oak tree grows hard by the side of the road, its rough-barked branches spreading grandly toward the sky on the side near the road, although the northeast side is rough and blackened and nearly flat.  Squirrels play up in the foliage, careless of the damage, chasing each other about and crunching on acorns.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow" color="#008000">
    <description>A few young oak trees, hardly more than bushes, grow in the meadow here.  The grass grows green and lush away from them, though, decorated by purple alyssum and sweet-smelling pink and purple stock.  An odd bowl-shaped depression in the center of the area is full of grass and flowers, but no trees grow there.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow">
    <description>Spreading bougainvillea vines snake across the ground, their blossoms like scarlet tissue resembling ruby rivers in the green grass.  One birch tree is nearly covered with the vines, and although the effect is very beautiful, the tree is being smothered and will likely die within a few years.  The grand old elms that border the meadow have likewise been trellised by climbing red roses, but these trees are old and established and seem to be bearing up well under the colorful invaders.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="101" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Meadow">
    <description>A large shadowed stone stands a few paces away from the road and near the indistinct border of the woods to the north.  Rising solitary out of the grass, its appearance is ominous and harsh, the focus of all that is dark and deathly in the night.</description>
    <description>A large stone stands a few paces away from the road and near the border of the woods to the north.  Made of red granite, its hard and solemn aspect contrasts with the cheerful appearance of the grassy meadow.  A large bouquet of field flowers, stocks and daisies and columbine and alyssum, with a spray of lilac to one side, lies before the stone.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Mature old trees grow on either side of the trade road, spreading oaks and sturdy elms and graceful birches.  The woods are well tended, with little underbrush clogging the ground between the treetrunks.  But sweet green grass grows, and shy, shade-loving plants.  Nodding columbines thrive in the shadows, their gracefully spurred blooms nodding above their pretty clover-like foliage.  Dainty violets peep out of nooks and crannies, while pink stock perfumes the air.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>A dark mound grows up against a sturdy elm, seemingly about to engulf its trunk.  The mound quivers and rustles, its reaching arms trembling.  The wind blowing off the ocean might explain the movement, but somehow the rhythm of the shaking seems wrong.</description>
    <description>A mound of wild blackberry vines grows beside the road, its spiny foliage surrounding plump, dark fruit.  The vines lean up against one of the elms, and a few more adventurous shoots have climbed high into the branches, much to the delight of the squirrels up above.  Bold bluejays swoop down to perch on the vines and peck at the berries, watching you with one eye as they feast.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="106" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>One of the huge elms has fallen to the southwest of the road, taking other trees with it on the way down.  The scorched wood seems to indicate a lightning strike.  The open space gives a clear if narrow view of the beach, and the ocean beyond it.  A few saplings have grown up around their dead elders, but it will be some time before the view is completely obstructed once more, and for right now this is a pleasant place for travellers to catch their breath and enjoy the scenery.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="107" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>The grass shivers in waves on the ground as the breeze from the ocean passes over it.  A ring of little brown-capped mushrooms is set in the shade of a tree, like a council room for tiny fae, gathered to discuss a coming moonlight dance or the flavor of this season's honeydew.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Reshalia Trade Road, Woods" color="#008000">
    <description>Elms, oaks and birches grow sturdy and well spaced here in the dark woods.  Points of glowing light hover and drift and zip about in an eerie display, while owls hoot their hunger on their nightly hunt.</description>
    <description>Elms, oaks and birches grow sturdy and well spaced, among cool green grasses and delicate shade flowers.  The trees are relatively young here at the edge of the woods, but this land is well cared for, with signs that someone clears brush and removes deadwood promptly.  Birds cheep and squawk and tootle and dreedle-ee-ee from the branches overhead, in a raucous, joyous cacophony of woodland sound.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go roadblock" destination="291" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Bay Cliffs, Trail">
    <description>This narrow trail through the woods is barely wide enough to walk sideways if you're bigger than a Dwarf.  Leaves obscure the line of sight in all directions, and branches and twigs poke from all sides.  Flying, crawling and hopping bugs are much closer than is comfortable, and there's no way to avoid them short of just leaving.  The foliage is denser to the south, but there are voices coming from that direction.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Bay Cliffs, Monument">
    <description>The trees and bushes have been cleared away from the rim of the cliff.  Halfway between the edge of the woods and the edge of the precipice stands a tall bronze monument.  A couple of young men are lounging around and chatting near torches stuck in the grass.</description>
    <description>The trees and bushes have been cleared away from the rim of the cliff.  Halfway between the edge of the woods and the edge of the precipice stands a bronze monument, tall and shining.  A couple of young men are lounging on the grass and chatting.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rock" destination="111" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Bay Cliffs, Projecting Rock">
    <description>The granite of the cliff thrusts out over the water, projecting far enough to give a clear view of the bluegreen water and jagged rocks directly below.  The young men and women here on the rock are all very wet, which is odd considering the only source of water is a truly appalling distance away, straight down.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grass" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Oak Tree" note="Bees">
    <description>Rough bark covers the huge branches of this venerable old tree.  From up here you can see clear to Ratha in the south, and the misty upper curve of Slo'Tami Bay to the north.  A few bees buzz around, busily bumbling back and forth between the fields nearby and their hive just overhead.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb down" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Shrine to Berengaria" note="Berengaria|shrine" color="#A6A3D9">
    <description>Although constructed simply and lacking any costly materials, it's obvious this shrine was built with deep devotion.  Finely fitted boards of elm form the walls of the small structure, while the plank floors are covered with a freshly woven oat-straw matting.  The murals on the walls are simple but painstakingly done.  Copper cowbells hang around the perimeter, and sound low clungs in the breeze that blows in the door.</description>
    <position x="260" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>The sandy soil shifts easily underfoot, sending small landslides down the uneven slope.  Straw-like tufts of grass grow from cracks in rocks and on any vaguely horizontal surface.  Above, a thin trail winds inland through the grass.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go thin trail" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>Protruding stones provide more solid footholds than the loose and sandy soil.  Further down the slope, the soft loam gives way entirely to large slabs of broken rock.  The soothing sounds of surf washes up from below, pierced now and again by the cry of a sea bird.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="116" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>Gulls reel and swoop through the sky, crying out soulfully to each other.  Occasionally, one dives and plunges into the sea and emerges triumphantly with a struggling fish in its beak.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="115" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>In the distance, great masted ships look like splinters of brown and white slipping over the horizon and out of sight while others emerge and gradually draw closer.  Long before the bluffs greeted the ships of mortals, it is rumored they were home to the island's fae.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>The wind ebbs and flows like the waves below, but with a rhythm all its own.  Sometimes the soft breezes sound like a ballad quietly whispered between the land and sea, while at other times the wind sings shrilly across the crags like a bitter song of mourning.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="119" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>The sheer bluffs soften to a sharply sloping talus of rock slabs either broken off of or dislodged from the cliff above.  Water seeps up between the large stones, creating calm tide pools where small schools of tiny silver fish dart about in search of food.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>Mist-laden air sprays and swirls around the stony bluffs, slicking the already slippery rock.  Pearly little crustaceans about the size of walnuts cling to the safety of a slim crevice in the rock face.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>Light and shadow play in the surf.  Moonlight catches waves as they grow from the sea and rides the crest above little pools of darkness that bob in and out of view.  As the waves crash against the stony shore, both are lost in a jubilant spray of white foam.</description>
    <description>Light and shadow play against the surf.  Sunlight catches waves as they grow from the sea and rides the crest above little pools of darkness that bob in and out of view.  As the waves crash against the stony shore, both are lost in a jubilant spray of white foam.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="120" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb downward path" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Egress Bluffs">
    <description>An algae-stained precipice littered with broken rock and shells reaches out from the bluff in a broad arm that seems to hover just above the waterline.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb upward path" destination="121" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark fissure" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Egress Bluffs, Fissure" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Briny water left by the receding tides fills the slim aperture in the stone.  Slimy strands of seaweed cling to the rock just above the waterline.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Egress Bluffs, Fissure" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The deep grey, mica-flecked stone walls have been worn smooth by ages of tides flowing through the narrow fissure.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Egress Bluffs, Fissure" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The uneven walls grow close, making the passageway more difficult to navigate.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="124" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Egress Bluffs, Fissure" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thin light glows vaguely above and diffuses shadows lurking within the fissure.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Softly fluorescing algae barely illuminates the capacious room leached from the island's foundation.  Twisted dripstone pillars seem to support a great canopy of stalactites hanging overhead like a frozen forest of weeping willows.  A thick stalagmite climbs out of the water and terminates near a ledge capping the limestone wall that skirts the cavern interior.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="126" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb thick stalagmite" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The cool water is shallow enough at the base of the wall to gaze at your footprints in the silt-dusted floor.  Soft light penetrating the limpid pool reveals an enormous cavern to the southeast looming beneath its diaphanous surface.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The surreal seascape of rainbow-hued dripstone formations is enrobed in soft light and the melodic burbling of running water.  Near the center of the cavern, the waters swirl with small whirlpools that dance across the glassy surface like frolicking sprites.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Diffused light washes the misty air a ghostly blue.  Gentle currents of air nudge aside the saline mist to expose pools of light that dance over the water and make small ripples gleam like polished platinum.  Darkness peeks from a narrow crevice in the limestone wall.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crevice" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The sandy floor of the cavern falls away from the surrounding wall and the cool waters beckon you to follow.  Crystalline pool spar lining the bottom glistens through the water like a mythic treasure trove.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Deep shadows hugging the periphery consume the walls and shroud the edges of the dark water, making the cavern feel infinitely larger.  Even the stout of heart would be moved to a startling feeling of insignificance in the center of the great mountain hollow.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Shapes move in the darkness below, making themselves felt among the shadows by causing shifts in the water's steady current.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="151" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The sound of water sloshing against the stone walls echoes through the cavern, occasionally punctuated by loud plops of moisture dripping into the pool.  Other, muffled sounds linger just beyond the reach of recognition before drowning in the steady rhythm of the water.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Shells speckling the cavern floor at the base of the wall paint the water with pinks and blues that swirl with colored minerals to form an amazing variety of hues.  Drafts of cool air descend from above and move through the area, pushing whorls of mist over the water's surface.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Deep shadows hugging the periphery consume the walls and shroud the edges of the dark water, making the cavern feel infinitely larger.  Even the stout of heart would be moved to a startling feeling of insignificance in the center of the great mountain hollow.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="150" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Long tendrils of sea vines hang from the ledge high above the water.  The milky drip of mineral-laden water frosts their deep green leaves, making them glitter in the shifting light.</description>
    <position x="0" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sea vine" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Like sharpened teeth dripping with spittle, stalactites pierce the shadows above and drip milky water into the water near the wall.  In places, stalagmites rise from the pool to meet them, making the cavern seem like the inside of some great creature's maw.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Gypsum crystals coating the rear of the cave sparkle like the first frost of winter and refract the light into millions of tiny rainbows that shower the wall with color.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The smell of brine makes the air feel heavy and dank in this dim corner of the cavern.  The granite wall to the east is oddly free of crystal or dripstone growth, but a series of shallow impressions in the stone weave a route up to the ledge above.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="138" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb limestone wall" destination="174" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Satha Cavern" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Two massive columns of red-swirled dripstone rise from the water and meet overhead in a gently curving arch that soars above the ledge.  Heavy droplets of water carrying dissolved minerals and flecks of mica glitter gaily as they roll slowly down the graceful curves.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb flowstone formation" destination="169" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Muffled echoes bounce along the stone walls from every direction, ebbing and flowing with the gently whirling currents near the center of the cavern.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Shellfish line the inside of a thin crease in the stone like pearly white peas in a deep grey pod.  They glow softly in the thin film of light in the water and seem to flicker when shadows pass overhead.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Broken curls of flowstone, shards of stalactites and shattered gypsum crystals litter the floor of the small stone shelf.  The piles occasionally shift with the currents, sending some pieces sliding off of the shelf into the black deep.</description>
    <position x="0" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A granite precipice looms overhead, but the umbrageous ceiling is paled by darker shadows stirring below.  Without a clear path to the surface, the grip of the water's depth seems stronger and closer.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Dusky water swirls against the stone, patiently wearing it away over the eons.  A thin vein of softer stone in the wall has all but dissolved, leaving a deep crevice that looks like a black scar in ebon skin.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thin light permeates the threadbare cloak of darkness near the water's surface and alights on crystalline pool spar growing on the cave bottom.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Shadows tint the waters in deepening shades of blue and violet, like veils of twilight lowered over evening.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Iridescent shells and yellowed splinters of bone collect in a small crevice in the stone, safe from the whirling current.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="151" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Only forty hands from the surface, the water cools considerably and descends another shade into darkness.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="151" name="Satha Cavern, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A thin layer of sand shifts across an ebon-veined basalt shelf below that refused to be dissolved by the relentless water.  Strong currents pull across the sliver of stone, carrying loose debris off into the inky deep.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="133" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The somber darkness swallows all light and color.  Everything, even one's own form, becomes one with the swirling black.</description>
    <position x="0" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Something reflective glints weakly through the darkness of the water below.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="159" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The quiet blackness seems to voice itself in the patient shushing of the currents.</description>
    <position x="0" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="153" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="162" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Visible through the thick darkness are the outlines of pale bones strewn across the floor below.</description>
    <position x="20" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>What light permeates the deepening shadow catches on flecks of mica and metallic debris caught up in the current to the south.  Through the clear water, it looks like a dust storm whirling through the nighttime desert.</description>
    <position x="0" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="148" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The swirling currents of cold water bear down on interlopers in their realm, seeking to impose their will.</description>
    <position x="0" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="155" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Chilling currents pull and push, stealing body heat and making navigating the litter-strewn cavern floor more difficult.</description>
    <position x="60" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="157" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A pile of rusting swords and armor sends a small tempest of ruddy flakes up into the whirling current.  Diminutive black fish dart voraciously through the maze of iron and steel, looking for smaller or slower kin to feed on.</description>
    <position x="40" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Shadows move with you in the darkness, accompanied by muffled barks and wails that bounce and warble through the depths.</description>
    <position x="60" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Lying broken and slightly askew like a large cracked egg, a pale white Gor'Tog skull gleams through the darkness.  The former braincase has become home to a group of eyeless black fish that weave placidly in and out of the jagged-edged hollow.</description>
    <position x="80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The tenebrous deep reveals little but the vague outlines of rusting armor and bits of their former owners scattered across the cavern floor.</description>
    <position x="60" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="160" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Satha Cavern, Itan Deep" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Silt deposited on the stone floor by the dancing currents lays in concentric ripples pointing in the direction of the water's flow.  The striated sand looks much like the gills of a giant sea creature.</description>
    <position x="60" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Narrow Crevice">
    <description>The slimy stone walls are close and the air is thick with the scent of briny seawater that fills the bottom of the crevice.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="130" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Narrow Crevice">
    <description>The slimy stone walls are close and the air is thick with the heavy scent of the briny seawater below.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>A rippling curtain of blue and green flowstone seems to dance along the edge of a granite mantle about ten hands overhead.  Shifting light reflected from the pool's surface casts pinks and yellows on the curtain, mixing new colors that fade and blend into others.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crevice" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>Patiently formed through eons of dripping water depositing layers of colorful minerals, flowstone blankets the walls with rainbow-hued folds and drapes.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb thick stalagmite" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>The sulfur-laden limestone walls of the large grotto glow a pale green in the ghostly blue light of the cavern.  The light pools in the wet sand and gravel deposited in ripples along the stone floor.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>In static waves, a red-swirled flowstone formation rolls down the ledge and into the water more than eighty hands below.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="168" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb flowstone formation" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Old Fields Road, A Deep Crack">
    <description>Thin light filters into the darkness of the deep wound in the island's foundation.  The narrow space is made more crowded by thick growths of sea vines flourishing in the warm, moist air rising from the shadows far, far below.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deep crack" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sea vines" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>Long tendrils of green vines hang from an aperture high above the shell-speckled cavern floor.  The milky drip of mineral-laden water frosts their dark leaves, making them glisten with crystalline brilliance.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb sea vine" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>Pale streams of light shift across the darkness from an aperture in the rock overhead, settling on no particular outline but glinting from the wet stone.  The dank salty-sour tang of wet stone and decaying algae permeates the cool air of the cave.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>Verdant sea vines crawl up the arching walls, finding welcome purchase in the crevices carved by rivulets of green-tinged water.  Thick and sinuous, the vines have wedged into small cracks and pried flakes of stone loose, littering the floor with shards of rock that crunch underfoot.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Tembat Nai Itan, Ledge">
    <description>The great slab of granite forming the wall is adorned with a series of fluidly twining designs and has a sense of permanence amid the dissolving limestone.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="173" />
    <arc exit="none" move="dive water" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Old Fields Road, Springhouse">
    <description>A constant drip, drip, drip echoes through the dank confines of the old springhouse.  A moss-covered stone slab lies halfway off of a small clear pool.  The overflow from the pool trickles across the floor and over the sagging doorstep.  Deep in one of corners, a lone cricket chirps and is answered from another corner.  An abandoned bucket hangs forlornly on the damp walls.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go gaping doorway" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Refreshment Stand" note="Refreshment Stand" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This crude little stand has been here for some time, judging by the weathering of the wood from which it's built.  Essentially a large table with a few boards nailed up on beams overhead to provide some shade from the sun or protection from the rain, it doesn't look as though it would get much business, but it's a favorite gathering place of the area and the three children behind the table grin as they hand over mugs of ale and rolls of bread and whatever else they might have today.</description>
    <position x="200" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Barley Fields, Farmer's Path">
    <description>Though the path widens and descends as it curves southwards, the other end crests over a hump of earth and dirt and vanishes.  The identifiable sounds of rural civilization leak over from the other side of the barrier, but all of the muffled noises dance just at the edge of earshot.  All around, waist-high lengths of barley sway gently in the wind.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow path" hidden="True" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Barley Fields">
    <description>A simple wooden plow rises from the rippling ocean of barley, contrasting as starkly as would a dark warship in a sea of crystal blue.  Nesting birds have built their homes in the joint where the handles meet the blade.  Even though the farmer has abandoned the plow to the weather, its usefulness shall not end.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai, Narrow Trace">
    <description>Green barley makes a miniature wall to the north as the path fades within the stalks of the waving crop.  Here, at the edge of the fields, the fine topsoil gives way to a stony and pebble-covered surface, the defining line nothing more than a mud-filled irrigation ditch.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>An odd series of rounded stones poke up from the dirt as the trail curves northwards, indicating that this path may have once been used frequently enough to be at least partially paved.  Except for the few stones still clinging to the vestiges of what was once a road, they've all fallen down the side of a steep slope.  Occasionally, one of the smaller stones bounces down the rock slide and vanishes from sight.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock slide" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>Tattered remnants of faded cloth shiver in the wind but are not pulled from their half-buried locations at the base of a rock slide.  Shifting any of the stones to discover what else may be hidden beneath the stones is naturally discouraged by the frequent crunching of the stones as they shift under the slightest provocation.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock slide" destination="180" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>Wind tears across the barren surface of the rocks, changing direction and force often enough to maintain a constant state of turbulent drafts.  A handful of sickly weeds find purchase in what little ash ridden soil the wind has failed to claim, unusually curved from their lives in the overbearing gusts.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="west" move="rt west" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>The deep scars of a washout gut the trail across the center, splitting the route into two halves before swallowing it completely.  Bits of black rock and tiny showers of grey dirt patter down the washout's slope, dislodged with every touch of the wind and every stray movement of a landing bird.  The peak of the volcano rises above the swirling wind, completely indifferent to the travelers braving its rocky routes.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb washout" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>Narrow to the point that it very nearly is non-existent, the trail clings tightly to the side of the volcano's slopes.  Glassy black rocks jut from their perches along either side as though they were hands reaching out to the sky for salvation.  Some of them have received their deliverance, having fallen to new resting places far below.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb washout" destination="183" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>All semblence of a proper path have vanished, and only the sharp angles of massive stones embedded in the surface of the volcano guide those who are not of avian descent.  A wispy grey fog curls serpentine-like around the bases of the blackened rocks, adding an even greater element of treacherous risk.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="south" move="rt south" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>The crumbling features of an obsidian rockface are nearly disguised by the tendrils of smoky mist that rise from below.  Though the grey twisting shape of the ever-present fog is hardly opaque here, it thickens quickly as one gazes off the edge of the sheer dropoff, hiding any and all things that may be lurking there.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="185" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb obsidian rockface" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>A dark mass towers above, its details masked by the heavy fog settled over the area.  Judging by the glossy black stones that are close enough to be unconcealed by the murky grey, the shape can only be that of one of the volcano's jagged obsidian rockfaces.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="rt southwest" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb obsidian rockface" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Tzgaa'lakh'adu'gai">
    <description>Gentle breezes from the nearby coastline carry the scent of brine, mingling it with the scent of dirt and stone for a hearty combination of natural smells.  The stirring of air also keeps the clouds of coastal fog from thickening, but a heavy bank of grey looms some distance away to the northeast.  The stones underfoot are not quite sharp enough to tear through a boot, but those that hide within the mist may have an augmented chance of doing just that.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt northeast" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky slope" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Trail's End">
    <description>Wisps of fog float gently up and over the cliff's edge, twining together, then separating and dissipating in the cold salty breeze.  Overhead, a lone albatross flies in never-ending spirals.  In the distance to the southeast, the outline of a lighthouse is barely visible through the fog.</description>
    <description>Like dancers at a ghostly midnight ball, wisps of fog float over the cliff's edge, twining together, then separating, twisting left, then right, and finally floating away towards the stars, following a song unheard, a path unseen.</description>
    <position x="340" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky slope" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough handholds" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Deadman's Confide, Rocky Path">
    <description>A knee-high rock wall lines the path on the cliff-side, blocking access to the edge.  Among the rocks, red and gold poppies bob in the sea breeze, nodding a merry Hello! to all who walk by them.</description>
    <position x="340" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Deadman's Confide, Rocky Path">
    <description>The cliff has crumbled away, taking part of the path and the rock wall with it.  A makeshift fence of old branches lashed together with stout fishing line leans precariously towards the edge, offering only the illusion of security from a sudden plunge into the murky fog below.</description>
    <position x="340" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="190" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="192" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Deadman's Confide, Rocky Path">
    <description>The path threads between some rocks and a lone acanth tree growing at the cliff's edge.  The constant sea breeze has limited growth on the seaward side causing the tree to lean inland.  Its long lean branches and sparse leaves flutter like streamers in the breeze.</description>
    <position x="340" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="193" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="Deadman's Confide, Prominence">
    <description>The rocky cliffs give way to a flat prominence covered in short grasses.  At the far eastern end of the prominence, a white lighthouse rises up against the pale blue sky.  Grey fog continues to obscure whatever lies at the bottom of the cliffs.</description>
    <description>The rocky cliffs give way to a flat prominence covered in short grasses.  At the far eastern end of the prominence, a pale lighthouse rises up against the dark night sky.  Grey fog continues to obscure whatever lies at the bottom of the cliffs.</description>
    <position x="360" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough handholds" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Deadman's Confide, Prominence">
    <description>Wild red roses are slowly overgrowing the remains of a greying picket fence.  Beyond the fence lies a child's playground, desolate and empty.  A gate, ripped from the fence, lies discarded in the grass nearby.</description>
    <position x="380" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go child's playground" destination="198" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Deadman's Confide, Prominence">
    <description>The prominence falls away sharply from both sides of the path, turning it into a thin dividing line between the grey foggy nothingness to north and the lively blue sea to the south.  A muted buoy within the fog murmurs endless mantras of no pain, no sorrow, no loss while the sparkling sea entices the senses with promises of hope, freedom, and laughter.</description>
    <position x="400" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Deadman's Confide, Prominence">
    <description>Make-shift gweldalmaen mark the site of three graves placed carefully on the southern side of the path looking towards the wide open sea.  A small mound of dirt lies next to a fourth, still open grave.</description>
    <position x="420" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="195" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Deadman's Confide, Prominence">
    <description>An alabaster lighthouse rises high against the backdrop of sea and sky.  A heavy wooden door leads into the base of the structure.  The roar of crashing waves rises up from below the promontory along with hearty scent of salt air.</description>
    <position x="440" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Deadman's Confide, Playground">
    <description>A picnic bench, a broken teeter-totter and flattened playhouse are lingering signs that a playground once existed here.  The playhouse looks like it might have been a child-sized version of the lighthouse to the east.</description>
    <position x="360" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Lighthouse, Entryway">
    <description>Pegs alongside the door are hung with the rotting remains of several woolen cloaks.  Through an arch to the east, there's a small sitting room.  A staircase, caked with years of grime and tarnish, spirals upward to the next level of the lighthouse.</description>
    <position x="400" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Lighthouse, Storage">
    <description>Oil to feed the beacon is stored in the large iron drums stacked here.  A thick black morass spills across the floor where one of the drums has split along its seam.  A confusion of muddled tracks follows the soft curve of the southern wall further into the storage area.</description>
    <position x="400" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Lighthouse, Basement">
    <description>A series of copper pipes, greenish-white with age, are poised over some oaken barrels.  The conduits angle upward and outward through the base of the tower in order to collect fresh rainwater for washing, drinking and bathing.</description>
    <position x="400" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="go" move="search go trapdoor" destination="211" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Lighthouse, Sitting Room">
    <description>This room was once homey and comfortable.  A decayed basket of knitting lies forgotten beside a light blue divan and upon the wall hangs a family portrait and a rack of hand-carved pipes.  A woman's touch is evident in the lacey curtains decorating a long window overlooking the sea.  That touch is long past, as dust lies heavily over the entire room.</description>
    <position x="420" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Lighthouse, Kitchen">
    <description>A cast iron stove remains untended, topped by a rusting teakettle.  Three chairs sit around a small table, the remains of the last meal uncleared.  A curtained alcove lies to the north and a narrow eastern window keeps watch over the ocean.</description>
    <position x="380" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb spiral staircase" destination="199" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Lighthouse, Pantry">
    <description>Shelves lining the walls once held cooking supplies but the perishables have long since collapsed into dust.  Flour spills across the floor where a canvas sack has burst and soft white bootprints leave tracks to the base of some stone steps leading upward into the spire.</description>
    <position x="380" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone steps" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Lighthouse, Bedroom">
    <description>A beautiful mahogany bed and wardrobe are carved with matching scenes of Lemicus spreading her arms in a benediction of protection over a raging sea.  A trundle bed is pulled out from one side of the larger, and upon it sits a toy galleon with a broken mast.  The ever-present eastern window overlooks the sea.</description>
    <position x="360" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone steps" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ladder" destination="206" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Lighthouse, Lamp Room">
    <description>In the center of the room stands a four-foot tall oil lamp on a low directable platform.  The lamp's reflector, an unblinking silver eye, keeps watch for ship and storm through the heavy glass walls of the spire.</description>
    <position x="340" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ladder" destination="205" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Lighthouse, Walkway East">
    <description>The sea spreads out from the base of the tower, chasing the horizon.  Seagulls ride the air currents, diving with a cry to grab shellfish from the shoals.  The promontory is scattered with debris where the gulls have smashed open their meals upon the rocks.</description>
    <position x="360" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="208" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Lighthouse, Walkway North">
    <description>Thick roiling mists cover the northern shore heedless of wind or weather.  Occasionally the mists thin and vaguely menacing forms can be made out stalking along the beaches.  Unearthly cries rise up from within the fog, the wailing lament of those lost forever on a foreign shore.</description>
    <position x="340" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Lighthouse, Walkway West">
    <description>Far to the west, a range of mountains peeks over the horizon.  A wide blue band of water meanders from near the base of the peaks toward the river delta.  Sailing hazards lie on either side of the promontory.  To the south, craggy rock formations peek from beneath the waves and to the north, dangerously shallow shoals could cause the unwary seafarer to run aground.</description>
    <position x="320" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Lighthouse, Walkway South">
    <description>Jagged rock formations jut from beneath the surface in the southern cove.  The danger is made evident by a schooner mast lying broken across the rocks.  The shoreline stretches southward them pulls back inland and out of sight.</description>
    <position x="340" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="207" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Deadman's Confide, Alabaster Passage">
    <description>The passage ends at a stone staircase leading dimly up to the gloom of the ceiling.  The muted sounds of trickling water come from somewhere above.  To the east, the passage runs off into darkness.</description>
    <position x="420" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="212" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone staircase" destination="201" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Deadman's Confide, Alabaster Passage">
    <description>A short passageway, smoothly crafted of fine alabaster stone, opens onto a shadowed room to the west.  The eastern wall is covered with an intricate set of gear and pulley mechanisms set within the faint outline of a door.</description>
    <position x="440" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="go" move="pull lever;go stone door" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Deadman's Confide, Drafty Passage">
    <description>Any further passage is halted by a vein of smooth alabaster stone cutting across the tunnel.  A slight breeze, redirected by the rough construction of the passage, comes from no particular direction.  A dwarven skeleton lies on the floor before the wall, a broken dagger still stuck between its ribs.</description>
    <position x="420" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Deadman's Confide, Dusty Tunnel">
    <description>Cobwebs are draped across the roof of the tunnel in a thick canopy.  The webs are occupied although the source of their builder's sustenance isn't obvious.  Hundreds of tiny black weavers scramble through the curtain of webbing alerted to the passage of potential prey.</description>
    <position x="440" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="215" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Deadman's Confide, Sandy Tunnel">
    <description>The ground here is much drier and covered with fine sand.  Small flecks of granite from the unfinished walls pepper the white sands.  A slight draft carries the tang of salt air.</description>
    <position x="460" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="214" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Deadman's Confide, Cliffside Chamber">
    <description>The high-ceilinged chamber is the collection point for a series of tunnels wandering yet deeper into the cliffs.  Ensconced torches flicker dimly, providing just enough light to reveal some dark markings along one wall.  A slow-moving stream of water meanders out of the southwestern tunnel.</description>
    <position x="480" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Deadman's Confide, Damp Tunnel">
    <description>A wall of coarse stone blocks is built across the passage.  Water trickles through the crumbling mortar of the wall in several spots, pooling at the base and wandering off as a small brackish stream.  The sounds of running water echo from behind the wall.</description>
    <position x="460" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite arch" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Deadman's Confide, Barracks">
    <description>Rotten wooden cots covered in moldering canvas fill the room with the scent of decay.  A wooden locker handcrafted from pine stands to one side of the room and a stained sea chest lies at the foot of one cot.</description>
    <position x="440" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go granite arch" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Deadman's Confide, Sloping Tunnel">
    <description>There's a marked downward slope to this tunnel as it delves further into the cliffs.  Phosphorescent lichens emit a wan green light, minimal and rather ghastly, but barely adequate for exploration.</description>
    <position x="480" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Deadman's Confide, Glowing Tunnel">
    <description>The tunnel sinks ever deeper into the bowels of the world to the southeast.  Glowing lichens festoon the walls and ceilings of the passage, bathing everything in a sickly greenish light, making the area surprisingly bright.</description>
    <position x="480" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="221" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Deadman's Confide, Brilliant Tunnel">
    <description>The light is blinding in contrast to the gloom of the other passages as the excavations pass through an exposed vein of quartz crystals.  Phosphorescent fungi, in a rainbow of hues, join the profusion of lichens.  Their light reflects off the gleaming crystals in kaleidoscopic patterns.  The effect is both awe-inspiring and nightmarish.</description>
    <position x="500" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Deadman's Confide, Dim Tunnel">
    <description>Light bleeds in from the northern passage providing just enough illumination to make out a rusted iron door in the southern wall.  To one side of the door, which has been frozen open by the passage of time, lies a broken stool.</description>
    <position x="500" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Deadman's Confide, Tunnel">
    <description>The passage dead-ends at a rockfall.  Part of the ceiling has collapsed blocking any further exploration eastward.  Two heavy doors, one of oak and one of mahogany, are solidly embedded in the walls to either side of the passage.</description>
    <position x="500" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="216" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Deadman's Confide, Dank Tunnel">
    <description>The sounds of the shore fade away as the dank walls close in and the passage wanders farther into the cliffside.  The dampness, darkness and close quarters combine for an atmosphere indistinguishable from a crypt.</description>
    <position x="500" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Deadman's Confide, Dank Tunnel">
    <description>A faint trickle of water can be heard through the gloom.  The walls of the tunnel are slick with moisture and small puddles collect to the sides of the passage.  The rushing tides whisper occasional warnings from a narrow gap in the stone.</description>
    <position x="520" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow gap" destination="233" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Deadman's Confide, Dining Hall">
    <description>A half dozen trestle tables stretch the length of the room.  Some wooden bowls and platters covered with petrified remains of an ancient meal are all that remain of interest.  At the northern end of the room, a smaller table has been raised upon a slight platform to oversee the forgotten banquet.</description>
    <position x="520" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mahogany door" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Deadman's Confide, Dining Hall">
    <description>A finely carved mahogany table oversees the rest of the dining hall and a skeleton occupies the captain's chair behind it.  The remains are pinned upright by a longsword jammed into its rib cage and through the rotting red velvet upholstery.  Moldering flags from various ships hang along the wall behind the table, the victims' identities long forgotten.</description>
    <position x="520" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Deadman's Confide, Galley">
    <description>A rusting iron stove sits in one corner of the room with an exhaust pipe leading up through a rift in the ceiling.  The stovepipe has split along one side and a soft moaning echoes through the tear as sea breezes wind their way down from the surface.  Bits of broken crockery lie scattered about, draped with veils of thick dust.</description>
    <position x="520" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Deadman's Confide, Prisoner's Hold">
    <description>There's an ever present chill here that's more atmosphere than temperature.  Devices of torture lie scattered about the room, ranging from an iron maiden to thumbscrews.  Several branding irons sit idle in a cold fire pit.  Three identical oak doors, with small barred windows, overlook the room.</description>
    <position x="520" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go second oak door" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go third oak door" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Deadman's Confide, Stone Cell">
    <description>The cell is completely barren except for a pair of manacles hanging from one wall.  An oak door with a small barred window looks to be the only means of escape.  </description>
    <position x="520" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Deadman's Confide, Stone Cell">
    <description>The cell is completely barren except for a pair of manacles hanging from one wall.  An oak door with a small barred window looks to be the only means of escape.</description>
    <position x="540" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Deadman's Confide, Stone Cell">
    <description>The cell is completely barren except for a pair of manacles hanging from one wall.  An oak door with a small barred window looks to be the only means of escape.</description>
    <position x="540" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="229" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="560" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="580" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="600" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="580" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="235" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="560" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="540" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="241" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="520" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="560" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="248" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="520" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="500" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the southwestern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough handholds" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="249" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the eastern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="500" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="250" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="520" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="251" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="460" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="480" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach" note="Large Rock" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="500" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="256" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the eastern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="520" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="560" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="256" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="520" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="263" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="500" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="252" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach" note="Fishing Net" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="580" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="560" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="261" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="540" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="262" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="520" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="263" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="500" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="257" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="265" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="500" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="none" move="southwest" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="271" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="520" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="270" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="560" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="270" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="266" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="267" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="275" />
  </node>
  <node id="273" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the western end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough handholds" destination="189" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach" note="Row Boat" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="285" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="283" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="281" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the northwestern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="281" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the northern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="282" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the northern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" hidden="True" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Every so often the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoed from every direction.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A thick, rolling fog blankets the beach, obscuring everything but the immediate area.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="285" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="286" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the northern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="286" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the northern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Every so the fog thins a bit, revealing shadowy outlines of uncertain origin.  Muffled sounds of surf, sea gulls, and tolling buoys sneak through the fog, echoing off the walls.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="285" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Deadman's Confide, Beach">
    <description>A cliff wall rises into the fog at the northern end of the fog-shrouded beach.  Though the surf breaks gently on the shore, the muffled sound of crashing waves drifts across the water through the fog.  Seashells, bits of driftwood, and clammy strands of kelp mark the high tide line.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="286" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" hidden="True" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="Ratha Stables" note="Stables|Joust" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Sheltered by the mass of the wall surrounding the city of Ratha, inside the stable the sound of the sea wind that is so constant outside sinks to a low murmur.  Soft straw covers the ground, muffling footsteps and the soft whump of hooves.  Unused bales are stacked ready, next to an open doorway leading into a supply room.  A small corral contains the horses currently for sale.</description>
    <position x="360" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open doorway" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Ratha Stables" note="Moritden">
    <description>Stretching off into dimness, rows of individual stalls line either side of a broad passageway.  Since this is the main stable for the city, a large number of horses are always present, along with workers scurrying about their duties of caring for them.</description>
    <position x="350" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="288" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Ratha Stables, Supply Room" note="Zodrov|Tack|Food" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Barely more than a large closet, the supply room is crammed with baskets, boxes, trunks, and other containers, all holding everything required for the basic care and feeding of horses.  An open doorway leads back to the main stable area.</description>
    <position x="360" y="310" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go open doorway" destination="288" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Pivilho Volcano, Base Route">
    <description>Large boulders of weathered ignimbrite dot the mountain face, and though the footing is precarious, the ground is partially hard packed by the traffic of local wildlife.  Scrub tenuously grows in what little shelter can be found, tufts of fur and feather mixing with the occasional scale in the clinging bushes.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go roadblock" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Pivilho Volcano, Base Route">
    <description>The bleached remains of a large ram are scattered along the pathway, heavily pitted from the warm sea breeze and elements.  Several cracks spider along the nearby boulders, and large chips of stone littering the area primarily around the skeletal form suggest the creature did not go down without a fight.  A swath of rippled igneous rock forms a causeway that has long since cooled and been worn down by the passing wildlife.  Seabirds soar offshore, coasting on the rising thermals and occasionally diving for the waters.  A ravine continues up the volcano.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="291" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ravine" destination="293" />
  </node>
  <node id="293" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fellgust Vale">
    <description>Naturally carved from millennia of rain and harsh winds, a wide valley cuts almost straight up the side of the volcano.  Nearly constant gusts of hot, humid air stream downward bringing noxious fumes reeking of sulfur.  A thin trickle of muddy water runs along the center of the valley, swirling with a thick yellow slime.  Bushes grow along the edges of the valley and the cliff walls, a significant distance from the slow stream.  A narrow path leads towards the base route.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fellgust Vale">
    <description>The valley curves slightly here, catching the prevailing ocean trade winds, and strong gusts push down the valley, mixing faintly with the ever present volcanic fumes.  Clinging bushes rustle along the valley walls, and a few stunted trees sprout along the cliff edges.  The ground is churned, crisscrossed by claw marks and littered with fractured stone shards.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="293" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="295" />
  </node>
  <node id="295" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fellgust Vale">
    <description>The valley branches here, bifurcating around a large outcropping.  Scoured by the winds and lashed with burn marks, the structure is heavily pocked and crumbling.  Merging as they are funneled around the rock, strong gusts of noxious wind howl and whip about chaotically.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="296" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="294" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fellgust Vale">
    <description>The air is powerfully charged with static, dry as a bone and sheltered from the sea breeze.  Quartz tinged with cinnabar and lapis lazuli deposits in the ravine wall occasionally flicker with a faint blue as they discharge sparkling electricity.  Large claw marks rake the walls and ground.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fellgust Vale">
    <description>The stream widens here, creating several pools lined with yellow-grey rings of accumulated sulfur deposits and salts.  These delicate rings demark bands of red and yellow, which deepen to greens and dark cerulean as the pools grow deeper.  Constantly churned by the strong winds, the waters within the pools are murky and bubble continuously as they are heated from below.  The air stinks of rotten eggs and worse.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="296" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fellgust Vale">
    <description>Rough boulders and chunks of stone torn from the walls of the ravine are scattered haphazardly, held in place by a muddy trickle of stinking water.  Large nests made of shredded timber and scrub packed with assorted bones peak over caves dug into the ravine walls.  The wind howls along the valley, buffeting the nests.  An open reinforced wooden barricade allows passage further up the ravine.</description>
    <position x="-100" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="297" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go barricade" destination="299" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="Pivilho Volcano, Summit Pathway">
    <description>Set into a bermed nook, a simple wooden lean-to provides shelter against the elements, and affords travlers an opportunity to rest in the shade.  The andesite ground is faintly rippled and scoured from the elements.  The path continues to the north, curving around a bend, and an open reinforced wooden barricade allows passage back down to the vale.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go barricade" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Pivilho Volcano, Summit Pathway">
    <description>Revealed by weathering, thin hexagonal columnar joints form an outcropping on an otherwise effectively sheer face.  Carved steps allow for an easy climb up to a series of quarried platforms set into the cliff.  The air smells of sulfur and hot ash.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="299" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="301" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Pivilho Volcano, Cliff Face">
    <description>Carved into the rock face, the columnar basalt has been rough hewn, resulting in numerous deep seated platforms.  Littered with large bones and lined with blackened fulgurite nodules spidering along the stone, the space appears to provide rest for more than just climbers scaling the cliff.  Further down the volcano, the waves beat against a black sand beach.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Pivilho Volcano, Cliff Edge">
    <description>A largely flat and even surface set into the volcano marks a short, rough plain.  Haphazard boulders are scattered around, shattered as if dropped from great height.  Heavy winds have swept the area of smaller debris, revealing hexagonal jointing with largely even elevation, exacting lines abruptly ending with the cliff edge.  The height and unobstructed view affords an excellent vantage of the ocean.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="301" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Pivilho Volcano, Cliff Edge">
    <description>A tall menhir made of weathered marble overlooks the ocean view and is set neatly between the hexagonal lines of the columnar ground.  Seabirds soar along the coast and the littoral waves are battered by the prevailing winds and tides.  The ground is swept clean, ending abruptly at the cliff's edge.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Pivilho Volcano, Rockslide Plain">
    <description>Set into the volcano's side, the flat plain appears to be caused by a rockslide, though the area has been largely cleared of debris.  The area is dotted with several large nests composed of thick branches and shredded wood.  The ground and wall face are crisscrossed with black and green glassy fulgurite spikes and droplets.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-480" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fumarole opening" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Pivilho Volcano, Fumarole Passage" color="White">
    <description>Sulfur crystals encrust the walls, shattered and scraped bare in places by deep claw marks.  The passage extends into the volcano at a modest downward angle, illuminated by a red glow.</description>
    <position x="-120" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fumarole opening" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Pivilho Volcano, Borehole Overlook" color="White">
    <description>Opening onto a glowing red abyss, a wide bell-like expansion stretches down into the depths.  Hot, dry, stinging air roars upward, a howling updraft that whistles along the walls and across the edge.  Riveted into the ground, a thick steelsilk rope allows for an easy descent to the chamber floor below.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="305" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steelsilk rope" destination="307" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Pivilho Volcano, Hav'roth's Bridge" color="White">
    <description>The wide causeway extends as a large semi-circle across the magma, the rippled, black stone curving gently between the north and south chambers.  To the north, billowing clouds of choking gas swirl malevolently with ash and streaking embers, the ground cracked and glowing red as magma flows beneath barely cooled crust.  To the south, a mournful melody echoes along the walls, the chamber darker and cooler.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-540" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steelsilk rope" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Pivilho Volcano, Peri'el's Calm" color="White">
    <description>The air is merely warm here, the tortuous heat diffusing harmlessly.  Jingling bells tinkle in the distance, a melody muffling the chaos to the north.  The dark banded rocks of the ground twist and kink, metallic inclusions glimmering in the faint light.  The walls and ceiling waver slightly.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-520" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="313" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="312" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Pivilho Volcano, Ushnish's Rage" color="White">
    <description>Howling winds blast all around, and crevices burst with yellow hot liquid stone.  Cooling bubbles fade to black, illuminated softly from within with a dull red, occasionally blistering and pushing forward slightly, hissing in a sibilant rumble as the ground shifts in a precarious and mesmerizing flow.  Visibility is limited as hot embers and ash swirl chaotically.</description>
    <position x="-160" y="-560" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="311" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Pivilho Volcano, Ushnish's Rage" color="White">
    <description>A large pit opens here, billowing lava welling upward, cooling as it hits the air to form a thin skin of stone that shifts with the undercurrent.  Crackling as it moves, the stone skin exposes lines of brighter red magma, jagged and constantly in motion.  Searingly hot air roars around chaotically, thick with noxious fumes.  The walls glisten with metal and gem formations.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="311" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Pivilho Volcano, Ushnish's Rage" color="White">
    <description>Several hollowed out boulders rise slightly from the ground, smoking and glowing with heat, but absent of the ever present magma.  Thick rock scales line the inside of the boulders, piled carefully around several egg-shaped black stones.  From deep within the swirling clouds and murky shadows echoes an angry hiss.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-580" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="309" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Pivilho Volcano, Peri'el's Calm" color="White">
    <description>The ground is littered with blackened seashells and the area resounds with an oceanic hissing, reminiscent of the surf.  As the volcano's cacophonous sounds vie for attention, something akin to soft vocals pierce the din, but its source remains elusive.  Glimmering deep within the vaguely transparent banded walls, gemstones flicker with luminescence.</description>
    <position x="-180" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Pivilho Volcano, Peri'el's Calm" color="White">
    <description>Striations of reds, yellows, lavenders, and blacks ripple along the floor, wall and ceiling, seeming to ebb and flow in the faint light.  Wafting through the area, a cool breeze gently carries a soft, soothing song.  A long, scorched gouge mars the wall, and a ragged chunk of stone is torn free.</description>
    <position x="-140" y="-500" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="312" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="308" />
  </node>
  <label text="Silver Leucros">
    <position x="530" y="-330" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="First Level">
    <position x="-20" y="20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Second Level">
    <position x="-10" y="140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Third Level">
    <position x="10" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Fourth Level">
    <position x="70" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Selkies">
    <position x="-20" y="-70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Crimson/Azure/Dark Merrows">
    <position x="0" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tembat Nai Itan">
    <position x="-140" y="-120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ratha 4th Tier">
    <position x="360" y="350" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Death/Dark Spirits">
    <position x="370" y="-10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Spectral Pirates">
    <position x="380" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Skeletal Sailors">
    <position x="380" y="10" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="A">
    <position x="300" y="210" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="A">
    <position x="240" y="340" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="B">
    <position x="570" y="-430" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="B">
    <position x="190" y="-190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="C">
    <position x="50" y="-380" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="C">
    <position x="120" y="-200" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="- Climb path to D">
    <position x="330" y="210" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="D">
    <position x="540" y="-180" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Razortusk Sow">
    <position x="20" y="-140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Razortusk Boar">
    <position x="-140" y="-240" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Gale Drakes">
    <position x="-140" y="-350" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Hurricane Drakes">
    <position x="-110" y="-460" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Magma Cobraa">
    <position x="-150" y="-560" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Researcher">
    <position x="140" y="-260" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Trelmik">
    <position x="140" y="-250" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>