<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Road to Aesry (Frostweavers, Snow Gobs)" id="98">
  <node id="1" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer" note="Dock">
    <description>Ocean spray soaks the wooden boards of the pier.  Cloaked in shadows, the main dock of the island extends to the west, surrounded by the forms of sleeping ships.  The sound of drunken laughter comes from the direction of the wooden ladder that leads to Denison's Pub.</description>
    <description>Ocean spray soaks the wooden boards of the pier.  Gulls and terns fly above the main dock to the west, their harsh cries mingling with the shouts of bosuns and captains ready to set sail.  Sailors walking along the pier glance longingly at the wooden ladder which leads to Denison's Pub.</description>
    <position x="20" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Harbor Docks, Aesry Surlaenis'a">
    <description>Sturdy oak planks stretch eastward towards the lights of the harbor and the shouting sailors in Denison's Pub.  Two beams of light pierce the darkness, emanating from a point high on the island's slope.</description>
    <description>Sturdy oak planks stretch eastward, leading to the harbor proper and the trail to the rest of Surlaenis island.  Twin points of light beckon from a point high on the island's slope, guiding ships through the dangerous shoals at the harbor's mouth.  A small pod of dolphins play a game of tag in the water below.</description>
    <position x="0" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go halasa selhin" destination="338" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>Weathered by the sun and the salty sea air, the wooden pier stretches to the south.  Ships of all types anchor for the night, though some small boats fish near the dangerous shoals at the harbor mouth.</description>
    <description>Weathered by the sun and the salty sea air, the wooden pier stretches to the south.  Ships of all types anchor near the pier, or sail away with sails billowing in the wind.  Several dolphins frolic in the water, leaping over the wakes of passing ships.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lybadel" destination="148" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>A few small boats are anchored away from the pier.  The waters below are alive with scores of fish that come to feed off of the trash that is dumped into the harbor each night.  The reek of decaying garbage rises from the water.</description>
    <description>Several small boats, each with several hundred yards of fishing net tied on deck, are docked to this corner of the pier.  A veritable swarm of gulls rest in the water as the fishermen clean their catch.  The reek of rotting fish guts rises from the water.</description>
    <position x="20" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>The ale-stained walls and shattered glass windows of Denison's Pub dominate this stretch of the wooden walkway.  A dented silver bell hangs above the remains of a bench broken in a brawl.  To the west, a wooden ladder leads down to the pier.</description>
    <position x="40" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go denison's pub" destination="300" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>A flurry of activity surrounds an elegant black building.  The crest of the Traders' Guild is carved into the surface of the white birch doors that lead into the foyer.  Across from the building, a wooden ladder leads down to the pier.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch doors" destination="316" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go warehouse door" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>Carved white birch columns support the blue tile roof of a prosperous shop on the eastern side of the street.  A sign hangs from the shop's tiled awning, painted with the words, Bariyu's Water Supplies.  Across from the building, a wooden ladder leads down to the pier.</description>
    <position x="40" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden ladder" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low-thatched hut" destination="314" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>A dingy shack perches precariously above the ocean waves.  Strands of seaweed hang from the front of the shack, drying in the sun.  On the far side of the house, a rickety ladder reaches down to the dark sand of the beach.</description>
    <position x="40" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety ladder" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cramped-looking shed" destination="315" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dingy shack" destination="335" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lezeni's Cove">
    <description>Gentle waves lap against the poles that support the pier and harbor buildings.  The salty sea breeze combines with the rhythm of the waves, creating a relaxing, hypnotic sound.  Several ropes hang from the shack above into the water beneath the pier.</description>
    <position x="40" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rickety ladder" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock jetty" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Above Lezeni's Cove">
    <description>A path winds up the cliffs from the sand of the cove, twisting around jutting rocks and shacks anchored into the rocks.  The wind whistles sharply through the crevices and the air is sticky with salt.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Above Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A wide shelf in the cliffs is packed with small dwellings, each one close to another, some abandoned, some noisy with the cries and shouts of the inhabitants.  The climb up the cliff continues to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Above Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A larger dwelling or two cantilevers over the face of the cliffs, no doubt with a nice view of Surlaenis Harbor.  As to how sturdy such structures are, however, there is definite question.  The wind thrums constantly and blows sand and bits of debris along the path and between the abodes.</description>
    <position x="100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Above Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The path levels out as it arcs around a promontory in the cliff.  A piece of sailcloth caught in a crack in the rocks whips in the wind like a flag, flapping and moaning with each lash of breeze.</description>
    <position x="120" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Above Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A hollow in the cliff provides a sheltered area for the collection of dwellings perched upon the level surfaces of the cliff.  Like the nests of some cliff-dwelling birds, they huddle together in available spaces on the precipice, some nicely maintained, some in squalid condition.</description>
    <position x="140" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Above Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A long, sloping path leads up to a higher section of the cliffs and down to the sand and rocks below.  A crumbling wood shack, roofless and decaying, barely remains upright in the gusty winds.  Prickly cocklebur grasses grow in pockets of sand all along the path.</description>
    <position x="100" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Near Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Sea oats and cocklebur grasses grow plentifully in the sandy soil.  To the southwest, the white wavecaps in the water reflect the light from the flashing beacons of the Sentinels above.  Salty wet air and spray blows on the wind from the damp rocky beach below.</description>
    <description>Sea oats and cocklebur grasses grow plentifully in the sandy soil.  To the southwest, the water sparkles from this higher viewpoint, the sunlight catching on the wavecaps.  A rocky beach below is damp and dark from the wet breezes and spray that blow across it.</description>
    <position x="60" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Near Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A wide, rocky beach, with grass-covered sand dunes to the east, borders the waters near Surlaenis Harbor.  The waves crash upon the pebbles, grinding the edges smoother as they scrape against each other.  Gulls wheel overhead looking for scraps of food, their keer, keer cry calling forlornly.</description>
    <position x="40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock jetty" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go sea" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Near Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A wide, rocky beach, with grass-covered sand dunes to the east, borders the waters near Surlaenis Harbor.  The waves crash upon the pebbles, grinding the edges smoother, the tide leaving seaweed to dry upon the wet rocks.</description>
    <position x="40" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Near Lezeni's Cove" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Sea oats and cocklebur grasses grow plentifully in the sandy soil.  To the southwest, the white wavecaps in the water reflect the light from the flashing beacons of the Sentinels above.  Salty wet air and spray blows on the wind from the damp rocky beach below.</description>
    <description>Sea oats and cocklebur grasses grow plentifully in the sandy soil.  To the southwest, the water sparkles from this higher viewpoint, the sunlight catching on the wavecaps.  A rocky beach below is damp and dark from the wet breezes and spray that blow across it.</description>
    <position x="60" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The water splashes playfully on the rocky beach, each ebb and flow grinding the stones against each other with a rasping sound.  A glint of a fish flashes in the wake of the waves, but quickly darts out of sight.  The small rocks shift underfoot as the water continues its constant advance and retreat upon the shore.</description>
    <position x="20" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go beach" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The depth of the water suddenly increases where the rock-littered shelf underfoot ends at a sharp demarcation, and the waves swell and dip before they break to the east.  To the south and west the deep water is rougher as it rounds a jutting finger of rock, while the distant docks of Surlaenis rise in the opposite direction.</description>
    <position x="0" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The depth of the water suddenly increases where the rock-littered shelf underfoot ends at a sharp demarcation, and the waves swell and dip before they break to the east.  To the south and west the deep water is rougher as it rounds a jutting finger of rock, while the distant docks of Surlaenis rise in the opposite direction.</description>
    <position x="0" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="149" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>Redolent with the salty scent of the sea, a fickle breeze ruffles the pennants hanging before the offices of affluent trading consortiums.  The wooden boards of the walkway are cool after the day's heat.  Shouts of sailors reveling in a night's shore leave come from the west.</description>
    <description>Redolent with the salty scent of the sea, a fickle breeze ruffles the pennants hanging before the offices of affluent trading consortiums.  The wooden boards of the walkway are warm with the day's heat.  Shouts of sailors unloading cargo and preparing for a night's shore leave come from the west.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer">
    <description>Salt-stained wooden boards echo with each traveller's footsteps.  Houses of black oak are supported by platforms made of sturdy ironwood, each with an entire tree trunk driven into the sand below.  The walkway stretches westward to the pier, and east to ascend the outer slope of the island.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Strong smells of tar and ocean air waft on the wind coming from the harbor to the west.  Vast expanses of white sand lie to the north and south, split in two by a wooden walkway rising up the slope of the island.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden walkway" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow trail" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Open Yard">
    <description>The grass-covered sand dunes piled at the base of the rocky sea cliff have been smoothed and flattened into a broad yard.  Hoofprints of all sizes crisscross the area around a grey-boarded barn and a low stable tucked against the base of the rocks.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low stable" destination="323" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go grey-boarded barn" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Winding Track">
    <description>A well-beaten track winds among the dunes, with a variety of jumps and obstacles placed at intervals along its landward side to create an exercise area.  Fences, a wooden gate, and a brick-painted wall provide jumping challenges, while a blue barrel and a red barrel mark the ends of the course.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Among the Dunes" note="jousting lists" color="#FF0000">
    <description>To the north, the dark bulk of the rocky sea cliff juts into the ocean, cutting off the palely glimmering expanse of sand and creating a semi-sheltered area where driftwood has accumulated from long-forgotten storms.  Against the cliffs, a broad area has been cleared and jousting lists built from the flatter planks that have been washed up.</description>
    <description>To the north, the rocky sea cliff juts into the ocean, cutting off the expanse of sand and creating a semi-sheltered area where driftwood has accumulated from long-forgotten storms.  Against the cliffs, a broad area has been cleared and jousting lists built from the flatter planks that have been washed up.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Path">
    <description>The narrow trail claws its way up from the harbor area and wends a long distance along the rocky breadth of the sea cliff.  The rim of Aesry Surlaenis'a looms high above, its massive weight seemingly impervious to the force of the sea beating against its foundation in a frothy rage.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow trail" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Path">
    <description>A small patch of crimson wildflowers has managed to take root where the trail merges into a slim ledge.  Bright heads nodding in the breeze, they provide a lively contrast to the stark rock and dizzying height.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Path">
    <description>Relentless in her onslaught, the sea has found a foothold and worn away at the very bones of the island, leaving the trail undercut and hanging far out over the restless waves.  Looking down, it's as if the trail floats upon the surface of the water and the blue-green roil is mesmerizing to behold.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Path">
    <description>The surface of the promontory is crazed as if slammed by a god's fist.  A web of cracks, thread-thin to foot-wide, spreads in all directions and the trail has eroded to mere inches in width making traversing it a hazard.  A constant sprinkling of dust rains down from the stressed basalt.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Path">
    <description>Running jaggedly from northeast to southwest, a massive fissure has cleaved the face of the rock like an old battle scar.  A warm damp breeze wheezes forth from the darkness, and faintly, the steady drip, drip of falling water can be heard from deep inside the stone.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="rt search;-2 go dark opening" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Path">
    <description>The winding trail, after one last twist and turn, abruptly ends its sojourn at the edge of an outcrop.  Small stunted bushes huddle together around the edge of the formation and rattle their branches at each intrusion of the wind.  Far below, a wave-swept cove lies in the lee of the surrounding promontories and a thin switchback trail hacked into the stone leads downwards.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb switchback trail" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cove">
    <description>The cool sea laps gently at the sands of the small cove as it settles beneath the cloak of night.  Tiny luminous sea creatures drift slowly in scattered tide pools, unconsciously imitating the glory of a starry sky, while feeding the misshapen bodies of the sand crabs that live amongst them.</description>
    <description>A crescent of warm black sand nestles at the base of the trail, softening the harsh lines of the towering escarpments.  The sea sends forth restless tendrils of aquamarine to wash at the sands, leaving behind foam-flecked reminders of its relentless energy.  Far overhead, a lone cypress clings stubbornly to the rock casting its cool shadow over a tangle of driftwood and debris.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb switchback trail" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cool sea" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Sea Caves, Tunnel" note="Map98a_Sea_Caves.xml">
    <description>Cool wind blows in from the sea and down into the tunnel.  Flecks of mica glitter in the walls, floor, and ceiling of the basalt passageway.  Green moss grows tentatively across the ground and partway up the sides of the tunnel where the late rays of sunlight fall before the sun goes to its rest.  The sound of the pounding surf echoes faintly down the hall.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="178" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide opening" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>To the west, the wooden walkway slopes downward to the dark wooden buildings of the harbor.  As it rises to the east, it follows the natural contours of the island, leading to a dark stone cleft far above.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden walkway" destination="25" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The salt-stained boards of the wooden walkway lead west from the base of a long stone ramp.  Gritty sand fills the spaces between the planks, blown by the wind from the far reaches of the island.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone ramp" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Sparse shoots of grass struggle to grow in the sandy soil where the beach ends and the rest of the island begins.  A large stone ramp leads down to the beach, its surface slick with spray from the ocean.  The dark wooden buildings of the harbor rise to the west, breaking the clean line of the sands.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone ramp" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The grass alongside the dirt path is well-nibbled by the wild sheep which roam in the grassy fields.  A strong breeze, redolent with the scent of ocean air, rustles through the grass.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dirt path" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Lush green hills surround the dirt road.  Delicate wildflowers dot the fields, their brilliant colors contrasting with the emerald grass.  Blades of grass bow in homage before the fickle breeze</description>
    <description>Lush green hills surround the dirt road.  Delicate wildflowers dot the fields, their brilliant colors contrasting with the emerald grass.  Blades of grass bow in homage before the fickle breeze.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dirt path" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Rising abruptly from the emerald grass is a cliff of dark basalt stone.  The dirt road ends at the base of a long switchback trail.  In the distance, tall waves lap against the white sand beach, their white foam gleaming in the light.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb switchback trail" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>A long switchback trail leads down a cliff of dark basalt stone.  To the northeast, a dense forest of silverwood and white birch stretches up the mountain's slope to the snowline far above.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb switchback trail" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The basalt road runs precariously alongside a steep drop, climbing upwards towards a dense forest.  Emerald green grass carpets the rolling hills below.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb basalt road" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Wide gaps between trees here at the forest's edge reveal the sparkling blue ocean below.  A basalt road leads downward, while a thin dirt path continues east into the trees.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb basalt road" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>White flowers grow in a small clearing away from the path.  One of the few varieties that bloom year round, the geshiloira petals are the exact color of winter snow.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Silverwood bark gleams in the faint light shining through the branches above.  A fallen branch, its surface covered in red-capped mushrooms, rests beside a narrow trail.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow trail" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Wafting on the air from beneath the trees is the aroma of decaying plants.  The rich brown earth of the forest is renewed each year by the falling leaves of the trees.  A narrow trail curves downward towards the beach.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow trail" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Gleaming silverwood mingles with white birch beside the path, the more fragile trees vying with their hardier cousins for the light.  A rocky trail to the east leads upward, towards the cleft in the mountain wall.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky trail" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Black velvet shadows fill the gaps between tree trunks.  The dirt path curves eastward from the rocky trail which leads downward.  Mournful hoots of hunting owls echo through the darkness.</description>
    <description>Black velvet shadows fill the gaps between tree trunks.  The dirt path curves eastward from the rocky trail which leads downward.  Faint birdsong fills the shadows.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rocky trail" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Dark green forest closes around the wide dirt path, the trunks of the trees partially blocking the view of the mountain pass to the north.  The trees thicken to the south and west, creating a tunnel of shadows.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Dark basalt towers above, the natural walls of the selhin dava rising several thousand feet above the path.  Brilliant white light shines from the Twin Sentinels of Aesry Surlaenis'a, guarding either side of the pass.  A narrow dirt path runs through the pass.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dirt path" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Selhin Dava">
    <description>Shadow and light paint a tapestry on the leaves of the forest below.  White birch mingles with silverwood, providing glimpses of color among the green.  Far below, the deep blue ocean waves caress the white sands of the beach surrounding the island.  Disrupting the natural line of the beach, the dark wood of the harbor juts into the sea at the end of Shadaer Jama.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dirt path" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep trail" destination="87" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Selhin Dava">
    <description>A tall basalt wall blocks the path eastwards, where the dip in the terrain creates a natural pass.  A great iron-reinforced gate, or Selhin Ilga, is the entrance through the wall, and is carefully guarded by specially trained soldiers to ensure no enemies breach the inner domain of Surlaenis.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go selhin ilga" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Selhin Ilga">
    <description>Here between the inner and outer gates of the great wall, the sun rarely shines.  The huge wall towers twenty feet overhead and is equally thick.  The cool damp stone echoes with the sounds of travelers, as the guards that man Selhin Ilga pace atop the wall, ready for any disturbance.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Selhin Dava">
    <description>The great inner gate, or ilga, and the huge basalt wall of the Selhin Dava protect the city from any unwelcome outsiders.  Sharp winds blow through the pass and gust over the birch woods that flourish to the east.  Here within the shadow of the wall, travelers check their equipment before journeying on to the city proper.  A pair of stone stairs hewn into the rock mirror each other as they climb to the south and north, leading to the top of the wall.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go selhin ilga" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Selhin Dava">
    <description>Spread below to the east is a view of the whole of inner Surlaenis.  The bowl-shaped interior of the island slopes back down to a mist-mantled blue lake, with a smaller island floating in its midst.  The city surrounds this lough and looks like a miniature model from this height.  The northern quadrant of the island is a steep rocky incline, while the southern slopes are greener and more lush with forest and meadowland.  Opposite, to the east, is a heavily forested slope, covered with dense dark trees.</description>
    <description>Spread below to the east is the dark basin of the interior reaches of Surlaenis.  A single misty light glows eternally in the center of the dark lake at the base of the inner slopes, surrounded by lights from the encircling streets and buildings winking far below.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb earthen stairs" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama" color="#008000">
    <description>Sound softens beneath the birch trees due to the thick mulch of old leaves that blankets the ground.  Small cones hang from the weeping side branches of the graceful trees, dripping moisture from their tips.  Split logs reinforce the earthen steps that climb up to the crown of the pass.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb earthen steps" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama" color="#008000">
    <description>Young birch woods line the upper slopes as the harbor road approaches the crest of Selhin Dava.  A few dry leaves scutter across the packed surface of the road and tumble with every breeze on the slopes beneath the trees.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama" color="#008000">
    <description>Birches border the road, their slender twiggy branches arching overhead and patterning the view of the sky.  Their attenuated trunks stand pale against the dark soil until they disappear into a shadowy blur in the distance.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama" color="#008000">
    <description>Wooden timbers reinforce the packed earthen stairs cut into the hillside.  The road's descent is steeper and longer than usual, and this group of steps has a smooth, polished handrailing for the weary to cling to and catch a breath.  The heathered slopes meet birch woods here, the eastern lower inclines covered with scrub and grasses, the birch climbing the higher terraces to the pass.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb earthen stairs" destination="73" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Birch Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The narrow path threads its way among the birches, with the steep slant of the hillside banking the western edge.  Young birches nevertheless manage to cling to the near vertical slope.  The rustle of leaves and twigs is constant as the drooping branches move with the slightest disturbance in the air.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadaer jama" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Birch Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The ground is soft underfoot.  Birch trees spread in all directions, their silvery-grey leaves whispering the language of trees in a soothing rustle.  Spots of greenish moss grow on some of the thicker trunks.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Birch Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The trees cluster so densely that it is difficult to be certain of the path.  One larger tree, with blackish-grey bark, stands like a mother to her smaller children, her crown well above the rest of the wood.  Fluttering leaves and flickering shadows dance in constant motion.</description>
    <position x="500" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, End of Path" color="#008000">
    <description>The path comes to an abrupt end at the top of a steep bank.  The tops of birch trees fill the view below and to the southeast, and tendrils of a dense mist float amongst the growth.  The bank of the dropoff is crumbling dirt, covered with many seasons' fallen leaves.  Each footfall rattles the dead foliage underfoot, loudly jarring the suddenly noticeable quiet.</description>
    <position x="500" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep bank" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>A leaf-covered hillside leads up to the west.  Some partially uprooted birches lean down the sharp incline --  many broken and dead branches prop one tree at a near horizonal angle.  To the east, smaller stunted trees with a green-grey moss coating the bark overlap their boughs to form a net of branches.  A faint, green-tinged mist creeps silently throughout.</description>
    <position x="500" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb hillside" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>Every tree within sight is splattered with a greenish-grey moss, a clinging growth that looks more like a disease than a co-habitant.  The leaves covering the ground are crusted with the same stringy substance, which perhaps emerges from the ground to grow up the trunks of the trees.  The branches are still as the fog twines about them, and the familar rustling of their twigs and leaves is absent.</description>
    <position x="520" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>Heart-shaped, dark green leathery leaves of wild ginger grow in a sweeping arc over the ground.  The spicy fragrance fills the air with a wet, warm odor.  Moss hangs from the birch branches in twisted strands like locks of hair.  Sounds still suddenly, except for a sourceless, arrhythmic dripping sound.</description>
    <position x="540" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>Five mature birches grew and died here -- nothing stands now but their skeletons, thoroughly coated in the moss.  An unpleasant green-tinted mist fills the air, as a steamy vapor evaporates from the mossy surfaces.  Brittle broken twigs thatch the soggy ground.</description>
    <position x="520" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="70" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>The wall of the hillside blocks the view west.  Small saplings grow along it except near a dark vertical gash.  Sathramoss covers most of the hole, and in one more season, will completely cloak it.  A vaporous mist hovers about the moss, forming along its edges.</description>
    <position x="520" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>A dress woven of grass and leaves hangs caught on a broken branch, as if someone had left it behind in a desperate escape.  The ground is very boggy here, and footprints fill quickly with green water.  Sound is deadened by the birch growth, voices muffled by the heavy misty air.</description>
    <position x="540" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Lower Birch Wood" color="#008000">
    <description>A dip in the terrain houses a shelter where the infrangible barrier of trees prevents further movement into the wood.  Beneath a canopy of tangled boughs hangs a hammock, woven from the living branches of two white-barked birches.  Although the moss spreads over the ground like embroidery, the trees here are as yet untouched by the blight.  The mist is thinner, but lingers heavily within the surrounding forest.</description>
    <position x="560" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama" color="#008000">
    <description>Wooden timbers reinforce the packed earthen stairs cut into the hillside.  The high stair climb may have created the need for the wooden handrail which gives the weary a place to cling to and catch a breath.  A line of birch trees grows up the western slopes as the heathery moorland yields to the slender shapes of silvery forest.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="74" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb earthen stairs" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>A burbling sound betrays the presence of running water somewhere nearby.  Patches of heather and surlaenis knotweed conceal any springs or small streams that might be the source, but lusher growth does clump around a gouged indentation in the hillside.</description>
    <description>A burbling sound betrays the presence of running water somewhere nearby.  The dark and the overgrowth of heather conceal any springs or small streams that might be the source.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go overgrown indentation" destination="288" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>A whiff of a sour scent drifts from somewhere nearby.  Scraggly groups of wild plum trees just to the north of the road are the tallest trees in the rather moor-like terrain.  The hard packed surface of the dirt road continues up and down the slope in a straight east-west direction.</description>
    <description>A whiff of a sour scent drifts from somewhere nearby.  Scraggly groups of trees to the north are silhouetted against the night sky.  The dirt packed surface of the harbor road continues up and down the slope in a straight east-west direction.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The chirring of hidden insects vibrates within the tall wild grasses and low shrubs that border the road.  Dark rocks emerge above the heath and jut out erratically from the steeply sloping ground.  An occasional black-brown rabbit streaks over the gabbro boulders before diving safely out of sight into the rough terrain.</description>
    <description>The chirring of hidden insects vibrates within the tall wild grasses and low shrubs that border the road.  Dark shapes emerge above the heath and jut out erratically from the steeply sloping ground.
	</description>
    <description>The chirring of hidden insects vibrates within the tall wild grasses and low shrubs that border the road.  Dark shapes emerge above the heath and jut out erratically from the steeply sloping ground.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="75" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="77" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Approximately halfway between Selhin Dava and the shore of Cha'walkas, the road widens to a circular, level area enclaved by heather and tall grass.  Many travelers use this point as a resting place, if not a spot to survey the surrounding view.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>This section of the road is paved with the bedrock of a stone outcropping.  The stairs are solid rock, and hewn from the same granite vein.  Each broad step is smoothly cut, but undulating lines like abstract ocean waves decorate each tread.  A single jutting boulder walls off a portion of the view to the north, and its flat facing surface is decorated with the abstract carving of a dragon-like monster.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairs" destination="79" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>This section of the road is paved with the bedrock of a stone outcropping.  The stairs are solid rock, and hewn from the same granite vein.  Each broad step is smoothly cut, but undulating lines like abstract ocean waves decorate each tread.  Some tangling blackberry brambles cover the hillside slopes on both sides of the road.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb granite stairs" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The road slopes gently at an angle down to the east before pausing at the brink of another set of stairs cut into the hillside.  Off to the south, farmland fields lie in curving narrow strips, some fallow, some planted, in a rhythmic rotation of life and rest.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>Some large granite stones protrude from the packed dirt surface of the road, aligned like the vertebrae of an animal crouching beneath the soil.  The bulges aren't great enough to trip a traveler, but resound like cobblestones when trod upon.  Knee-high grasses wave along the sides of the road, the cultivated fields to the north deteriorating to the rockier slopes covered with more of the tall wild grasses.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb terrace stairs" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama" color="#008000">
    <description>Dark granite stone reinforces the steep stairs cut into the hillside.  A group of birch trees shelters this section of dirt road.  Given the constant twittering and rattling branches, the cluster of trees is a popular perch for local songbirds which dart in and out of the branches.</description>
    <description>Dark granite stone reinforces the steep stairs cut into the hillside.  A group of birch trees shelters this section of dirt road, their branches reaching upwards towards the night sky.</description>
    <position x="620" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone stairs" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The moderately sloping trail from the east ends abruptly at an earthen and stone stairway carved from the hillside which leads up towards the pass.  Low hedges of dark green shrubs divide the bordering fields into protected terraces, creating a crazy-quilt of farms.</description>
    <position x="640" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone stairs" destination="82" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Shadaer Jama">
    <description>The hard, packed surface of the road which leads up over the pass to the west begins its climb here.  Eluned's prayer gate lies a short distance further east.  Tilled fields border either side of the road, the air fragrant with rich soil and cultivated vegetation.</description>
    <position x="660" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="83" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go lone stable" destination="286" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Eluned Prayer Gate">
    <description>Gentle terraces of tilled earth rise to the west, leading towards the Selhin Dava.  A large prayer gate, watched over by two guards, stands as the only demarcation between the inner slope and the city.  Dedicated to Eluned of the Waters, the prayer gate bears an anloral sculpture of a leaping dolphin at its peak.</description>
    <position x="680" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="84" />
    <arc exit="go" move="bow dolphin;go prayer gate" destination="86" />
  </node>
  <node id="86" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Beneath the Prayer Gate" note="Map99_Aesry_Surlaenis'a.xml|Town|Aesry Surlaenis'a">
    <description>Smooth mother-of-pearl walls rise to form a gentle arch above.  Mosaics of interlocking shells form images of life beneath Elanthia's oceans.  Blue-grey dolphins frolic among sea-green waves as gentle merfolk herd schools of fish into nets of woven kelp.  To the east, the Staho Pivo'hrr'schu'Mus leads into the city proper.</description>
    <position x="700" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="85" />
  </node>
  <node id="87" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme" note="Bobcats|Blood Wolves">
    <description>The trees begin to thin as the trail climbs at a steep angle up the mountainside.  Young stands of fir and modwir crowd the slender birch trees as both compete on the rocky soil.  Winding through the dark tree trunks, the path is cushioned by a layer of decaying reddish-brown pine needles.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep trail" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="88" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Slender shapes seem to dart from shadow to shadow beneath the sheltering branches of the trees, only to vanish before you can turn your head.  The dark wood and leaves are surprisingly healthy, given the altitude and the cold.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="87" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="89" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Thin strands of milkweed drift past, lofted from a bird's nest by an errant breeze.  The path branches here to the north and west, making its way around the impenetrable tangle of briars which form a nearby thicket.  A hole, half-hidden at the base of the brambles, emits the pungent, musky scent of a badger or skunk.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="88" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="90" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Branches tangle overhead, caught by tendrils of ivy that mingle with the brambles in a nearby briar patch.  The thicket is home to a variety of wildlife -- chittering squirrels, shy rabbits and raucous crows are but a few of the more easily identified residents.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="89" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="91" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="96" />
  </node>
  <node id="91" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>The path ends at the top of a dropoff, leaving no choice but to turn back the way you came.  The ocean is visible to the south -- sparkling blue water capped by white foam as the waves crest and roll toward the shore.  A pod of dolphins leaps into the air, racing before the prow of a ship just entering the island's western harbor.</description>
    <description>The path ends at the top of a dropoff, leaving no choice but to turn back the way you came.  The ocean is visible to the south -- sparkling moonlit water capped by white foam as the waves crest and roll toward the shore.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="92" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Leaves rustle softly as some unseen animal stalks within the thicket.  Evidently the creature poses little threat to the denizens of the briars, as birds' songs continue, unabated by the disturbance.  A faint musky scent wafts through the air.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="89" />
  </node>
  <node id="93" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>The air is cool beneath the overhanging branches of the modwir trees that line the path.  Soft green moss clings to tree trunks, and the fragrance of leaf mold mingles with the sharp scent of fir needles.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="92" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="94" />
  </node>
  <node id="94" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>A flash of red disappears into the darkness as a cardinal darts down to land in the nearby thicket.  Deep green vines bearing dark purple berries twine among the brambles, lending a splash of color against the thorny brown backdrop.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="93" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="95" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Dark grey tufts of matted fur dangle from the branches of a briar patch, pulled from the pelt of a wolf or other creature.  Sunlight filters through the leaves to paint the ground with shifting shades of green.</description>
    <description>Moonlight filters through the leaves, illuminating tufts of dark grey fur caught on the thorns of a nearby briar patch.  Deep within the tangled underbrush, unilluminated by the pallid light of the moons, leaves rustle and branches break with a sharp *snap* as some unseen creature makes its way, padding softly through the thicket.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="94" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="96" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="96" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Half-hidden beneath fallen pine needles, a patch of dried mud captures the paw prints of some large animal.  The wind blows strongly on the mountainside, carrying with it the scent of pine needles intermingled with the sharper musky scent of a fox den.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="90" />
  </node>
  <node id="97" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>A rustling cushion of dried leaves covers the path as it skirts a small pond.  Runoff from the snow fields high atop the mountain trickles down the cliff face on the far side of the pond, and collects here, leaving the water icy-cold on even the warmest summer days.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="95" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="98" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="98" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>A boulder juts up through the ground cover, the surface dappled with darker pockets where erosion has worn away the basalt.  Tiny peridot chips embedded in the rock sparkle as the light refracts through the crystals.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="95" />
  </node>
  <node id="99" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Twisted roots stretch across the path, catching the feet of unwary hunters as they pass beneath the shelter of the modwir trees that line the trail.  A spider industriously spins her web from tree branch to trunk, the pale grey strands glistening in the light.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="100" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>The path comes to an abrupt end at the base of a tall cliff.  Gnarled roots and crevices mark the surface, providing purchase for the agile to scramble up the slope.  Narrow rivulets of frigid water trickle down the cliff face from the snow fields above, collecting in a nearby pond.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="99" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="101" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tall cliff" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide crevice" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="101" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Falachui Ikeme">
    <description>Stunted modwirs cling with gnarled roots to the thin patches of dirt that nestle between the rocky outcroppings beside the path.  The wind is chill, cutting through layers of clothing and armor alike.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="100" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="98" />
  </node>
  <node id="102" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Chedirnan">
    <description>The deep, still water of the pool reflects the sky and the surrounding trees with crystal clarity, disturbed only along the cliff edge where multiple tiny waterfalls eddy the surface.  Huge boulders that have separated from the cliff face lie scattered here and there, surrounded by rhododendron and ferns.  Behind one immense block that fell within inches of the cliff face, a rough stairway leads upward in a narrow gap.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="97" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough stairway" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="103" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Snow covers the rocky ground at the highest reaches of the island, nestling in the angular hollows between jagged basalt stones.  The trade road leading to the city of Aesry Surlaenis'a winds around the mountainside about a thousand feet below.  Rivulets of frigid water trickle over the side of the cliff, falling into a pond far, far below.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="104" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb tall cliff" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="104" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Gusts of wind dance between the jagged rocks strewn across the mountainside.  Rivulets of ice mingle with lighter trachytic flows, winding against the dark basalt backdrop like an eternally frozen river.  While it would be a difficult climb, it might be possible to scramble up the ice to the trail above.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="105" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="103" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall ice" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="105" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Olivine deposits form dull green streaks through a dark basalt boulder on the upper side of the trail.  Though cold now, once this area must have burned with the volcano's fiery rage.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="106" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Snowdrops bloom between the rocks which line a sheltered hollow along the trail.  When open, the pale blue, almost white, petals reveal the flower's crimson heart.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="105" />
  </node>
  <node id="107" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>A cold wind howls along the stark rocks of the trail, chilling the body as it depresses the spirits.  Local legend holds that the spirits of animals slain by the volcano still roam the hillsides, unaware of their demise.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="106" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="108" />
  </node>
  <node id="108" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>The skeleton of a horse or other large animal lies in a tumbled heap a short way down the slope.  One leg is obviously broken, and the iron head and curved brass flights of a crossbow bolt are visible nearby.  The bones gleam whitely, picked clean by the scavengers who roam the mountainside, ever hungry for their next meal.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="107" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="109" />
  </node>
  <node id="109" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Icy tendrils of mist sway along the snow-covered surface of the mountainside.  High above the treeline, the wind blows cold and strong, making the already low temperature seem even worse and lending credibility to the S'Kra Mur notion of hell as a place of ice and frost.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="108" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="110" />
  </node>
  <node id="110" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Frozen rivulets of ice tumble over the side of the mountain, reflecting the sunlight in a spectacular display.  The rocky trail is slick underfoot, making travel hazardous.  It might be possible to scramble down the ice to the trail below, but the climb would almost certainly be treacherous.</description>
    <description>Frozen rivulets of ice tumble over the side of the mountain, reflecting the moonlight with a soft glow.  The rocky trail is slick underfoot, making travel hazardous.  It might be possible to scramble down the ice to the trail below, but the climb would almost certainly be treacherous.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="109" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall ice" destination="104" />
  </node>
  <node id="111" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Beneath the shelter of an overhanging rock, an irregular circle of blackened rocks outlines the charred remains of a long-extinguished campfire.  Outside, the wind whistles about the area in a disconsolate howl, as if bemoaning the loss of its victims.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="110" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="112" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Glassy bands of obsidian streak the surface of the mountainside, reflecting the light with a painful glare.  Gusts of wind drive the snow before them, forming deep drifts that nestle in the hollows between the rocks.</description>
    <description>Glassy bands of obsidian reflect moonlight, shining softly as if Katamba bathed the mountainside in its eerie dark glow.  Gusts of wind drive the snow before them, forming deep drifts that nestle in the hollows between the rocks.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="111" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="113" />
  </node>
  <node id="113" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Icy spears dangle from a rocky overhang, the arm-thick icicles catching at hair and clothing of careless travelers.  Pale grey fragments of ash crunch underfoot, providing a bit of traction on the treacherous surface of the path.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="114" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="112" />
  </node>
  <node id="114" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Bundles of wood and kindling tied with string are stacked outside the burnt-out shell of a waystation high on the mountainside.  No trees grow nearby, so all wood must be carted up the trail from the forests below, a laborious process required to keep the station stocked for emergencies.  A faint scent of smoke lingers in the air from the charred timbers.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="113" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="115" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Far below, the warm waters of the ocean glisten in the sunlight.  Ships' sails billow in the breeze as they skip across the surface of the harbor.  The same wind, at this altitude, chills the traveler to the bone.  The sunlight that warms the waters below seems merely to accentuate the cold.</description>
    <description>Far below, the warm waters of the ocean glisten in the moonlight.  Ships' sails billow in the breeze as they skip across the surface of the harbor.  The same wind, at this altitude, chills the traveler to the bone.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="114" />
  </node>
  <node id="116" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>A faint mist hovers over the ice and snow, swirling about in an uneasy dance.  Rounded boulders, smoothed by exposure to the elements, are scattered across the snowfield like a child's discarded marbles.  Swirls of olivine streak the glossy black surfaces, heightening the impression.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="117" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="115" />
  </node>
  <node id="117" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>Snow drifts down from an overhanging ledge about fifty feet above.  Travelers must move quietly to avoid vibrations that might trigger an avalanche.  Further up the trail you can see the outline of a cabin.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="116" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="118" />
  </node>
  <node id="118" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>The path slopes sharply upward as it nears the end, reaching the summit after a strenuous scramble over the rock-strewn trail.  Gusts of wind further unbalance those who attempt to make their way, howling about to catch at clothing and hair impartially.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="117" />
  </node>
  <node id="119" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshi'selhin Chui">
    <description>The trail ends at a rocky promontory on the rim of the mountain.  From this point, balanced on a ledge about twenty paces across, there is a view of both the ocean at the base of the mountain, and the town nestled in the crater.  A cabin stands here, providing shelter for the guards who maintain the watch, and a signal fire beside it stands ready to be lit to warn the town of the approach of invaders from the sea.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-420" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="118" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go log cabin" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="120" name="Mountain Cabin">
    <description>Mud and moss chink the gaps between the logs in the cabin's walls, and colorful woolen blankets are hung along the interior to further reduce the drafts.  A sturdy wooden table is placed over a trap door in the floor beside the brick hearth.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-440" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="119" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trap door" destination="121" />
  </node>
  <node id="121" name="Mountain Cabin, Cold Cellar">
    <description>Dried hams and sausages hang from the rafters of the cold cellar, safely out of reach of rodents.  Along the walls, metal-lined wooden bins filled with sand hold carrots, potatoes, apples and pears, while other bins hold various grains.  Wax-sealed terra cotta urns filled with oil rest within a sand-filled pit, cushioned against breakage.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-460" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trap door" destination="120" />
  </node>
  <node id="122" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Amakra">
    <description>Atop the boulder, a narrow ledge climbs the cliff face upward.  Tiny yellow flowers sprout from cracks in the sheer rock, clinging tenaciously in any tiny bit of soil that accumulates.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="123" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough stairway" destination="102" />
  </node>
  <node id="123" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Amakra">
    <description>The ledge widens slightly, creating a resting spot and a high vantage point.  To one side, a very steep slope formed of tumbled gravel forms a precarious path upward.  Far in the distance, tiny ships and fishing boats move in and out of the harbor, their crews too far off to make out.</description>
    <description>The ledge widens slightly, creating a resting spot and a high vantage point.  To one side, a very steep slope formed of tumbled gravel forms a precarious path upward.  Far in the distance, tiny golden lights glide on the shimmering black expanse of ocean, creating streaks of brightness on the night-lit water.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep slope" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow ledge" destination="122" />
  </node>
  <node id="124" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Bu'amakra">
    <description>The slope ends abruptly at a wall of dirty grey that breathes cold even more intense than the thin chill air.  Faintly visible under the streaks of grit is a hint of pristine white.  An occasional loud cracking sound bears witness to the ponderous, imperceptible movement of the glacial ice.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small fissure" destination="125" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep slope" destination="123" />
  </node>
  <node id="125" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger" note="Safe Room|Fissure" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>The interior of the underground compartment is slick with ice crystals and powdery frost.  Cold air wafts from deeper within the small space, seeping through unseen cracks and a larger crevice.  Oddly, the back of the cavern seems no darker than the front.</description>
    <description>The interior of the underground compartment is slick with ice crystals and powdery frost.  Cold air wafts from deeper within the small space, seeping through unseen cracks.  Oddly, the back of the cavern seems no darker than the front.</description>
    <position x="360" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="124" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="126" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Huge boulders and bands of jumbled rock hang suspended in solid blue-green ice.  Sharp slices of frigid air cut with every breath, and in the pale light, clouds of foggy mist churn as warm air collides with the cold.  The floor of the passageway is crisp with tiny snow-like particles, collected as condensation froze and fell.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="127" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="125" />
  </node>
  <node id="127" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A deep gash cuts across the floor of the passageway -- a misstep would plunge the hapless wanderer to immeasurable depths and a hopeless doom.  Chunks of fallen boulders, all coated in powdery frost, create an obstacle course requiring careful navigation.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="128" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="126" />
  </node>
  <node id="128" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>The long, narrow tunnel snakes deeper into the glacier, the low ceiling requiring all except the shortest races to bend to avoid protrusions of ice flow hanging from the ceiling.  Ice so cold that touching it sucks the very strength from the living threatens to entomb any attempting this journey -- only sheer will prevails.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="129" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="127" />
  </node>
  <node id="129" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>The narrow passage to the south opens out into a large echoing cavern, with icy walls soaring into darkness.  The soft brushing sound is that of falling particles of frozen mist -- it whispers as it touches the floor, the chunks of fallen rock, or your face.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="128" />
  </node>
  <node id="130" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>The dimensions of the cavern are hard to judge, as the walls soar into darkness.  Softly whispering frozen mist continues to fall from the air, coating everything it touches with a fine, white powder.  The floor slopes at a sharp angle to the north.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="131" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="129" />
  </node>
  <node id="131" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Near the northern end of the cavern, the walls and floor converge to form an alcove.  A vertical crevice, barely wide enough to squeeze through, leads deeper into the rock.  Overhead, icicles hang like pointy teeth in a gaping maw, glistening hungrily and shedding a glowing blue-green light through the massive layers of ice.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="130" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="132" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>This high chamber appears to be carved out of solid ice.  Icicles of tremendous proportions hang overhead like stalactites from a dim, invisible ceiling.  Cubical chunks tumble about the floor and emerge from the wall, stuck fast.  Although the cold air penetrates all, closer examination reveals the crystalline structure is not frozen water, but clear quartz-like rocks that will never thaw even should the cold be banished.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="135" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go crevice" destination="131" />
  </node>
  <node id="133" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Ice-clear rock lines the winding passageway that slopes deeper into the mountainside, allowing light from the surface to filter through and dimly illuminate all.  Northwards, warmer air brushes through, a sweet scented air that speaks of hope.  The floor is still slick underfoot with a sheet of ice.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="134" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="132" />
  </node>
  <node id="134" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A webbing of dripping spun-ice bars the passageway.  The barrier appears to melt and reform as tendrils creep from the floor and walls to join, and then dissolve into a dripping puddle.  Warm air seeps past it, though a frigid wind sails through the turns of the corridor to the south.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="133" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ice barrier" destination="287" />
  </node>
  <node id="135" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>The cold of the void, a cold no life could survive for long, fills the tunnel.  Bits of crystal glint where light touches them, the hard cold rock speaking of the unforgiving state of eternal winter.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="132" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="136" />
  </node>
  <node id="136" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>The cold blue-green glow filtering through the mass of ice and tumbled rock casts a weird dead light on everything it touches.  No sound echoes -- the very vibrations freeze as if in the void.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="137" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="135" />
  </node>
  <node id="137" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A thud of sound thrums through the rock walls, the purpose and rhythm mysterious.  From time to time, a swirl of air picks up the frozen particles littering the floor and spins them about in a small tornado storm.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="136" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="138" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A cathedral of ice rises around you, the ceiling lost in shadowy darkness.  The floor is smooth and slick underfoot, like polished marble.  Large sections of the side walls have peeled off under the enormous pressure, and an occasional echoing crack bears testimony to the slow movement of the ice.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="137" />
  </node>
  <node id="139" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>The cavern narrows slightly, with the floor ankle deep in piles of dry, powdery ice crystals.  Its walls, frosted like the sides of a cake, round and swell with the swirling formations of rime.  Light bounces off the tiny granules to sparkle like distant stars or diamond fragments.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="140" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="138" />
  </node>
  <node id="140" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Deep inside the cavern, only blue light filters in through the frozen ice mass.  The corners and niches are a deep, pure indigo, shading almost to azure on the more exposed surface of a pile of ice crystals.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="139" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="141" />
  </node>
  <node id="141" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A skeleton of white bones hangs caught on a shelf of rock above.  Coated in a light dusting of icy powder, it is fast becoming one with the bitter cold frost and rock that surrounds all.  Drifts of brittle ice particles hug the base of the walls.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="142" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="140" />
  </node>
  <node id="142" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A waterfall once fell through a crack in the rock overhead, but is now frozen in frothy turmoil into a solid chunk of hard glacial ice.  Only the imagination can recall the roar of sound such a torrent would have made as it flowed.  Underfoot, ice smooth as a mirror levels the floor.</description>
    <position x="520" y="-300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="141" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go vertical slit" destination="143" />
  </node>
  <node id="143" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Smooth, slick ice lines the walls of the small cavern, and the air seems dead and lifeless.  Buried deep within the glacier, only a narrow passageway leads out to the east.</description>
    <position x="560" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="144" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark slit" destination="142" />
  </node>
  <node id="144" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Within the cold ice cave, strange swirls and angular cuts sliced into the glassy walls speak an indecipherable tale.  Piles of ice-dust glimmer like anthills of diamond slivers, curiously scattered about the chamber.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="143" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="145" />
  </node>
  <node id="145" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A ridge of packed ice creates a slippery slope to traverse.  Small holes bored into the frozen material emit a nasty-smelling odor, exhaling tendrils of smoky fog that freeze to tiny crystalized grains.</description>
    <position x="580" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="146" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="144" />
  </node>
  <node id="146" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Crystalline stalactites of purest ice hang from the ceiling in fang-like rows.  The dim blue light casts weird shadows and creates an alien landscape where nothing appears as it did on the surface under the sun and moons.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="145" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="147" />
  </node>
  <node id="147" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>This deep within the glacier, the light dims and shadows fill all corners and crevices.  Tiny ice particles swirl in the soft breezes created by any movement, creating the shapes of creatures flickering in the darkness, gone before one can put a name or fear to them.</description>
    <position x="600" y="-340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="rt lie; northeast" destination="152" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt stand; up" destination="146" />
  </node>
  <node id="148" name="Lybadel, Main Deck" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>In the middle of the ship, the main deck is closest to the water of all the open decks, and on a hard heel the waves can wash over the exposed planks.  For this reason, everything is securely fastened down to keep it from sliding or being washed away, and the hatches are tightly dogged shut.  Forward lies the forecastle and an oak door leading to the galley, while aft rises the quarterdeck and under it, a cabin door.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go surlaenis" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go riverhaven" />
  </node>
  <node id="149" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The farther from shore, the rougher the surf.  Huge swells of saltwater sweep any flotsam great distances in a flash, all adrift in ceaseless motion.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="150" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Though hardly calm, the cove is still sheltered and the waves gentle enough to avoid the dangers of a lonely death, dashed against the rocks.  The water is very deep, the bottom unseen in the dark below.  Upon its surface, the swells set all afloat drifting.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="154" />
  </node>
  <node id="152" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>Tunneling through walls of ice, this passageway slopes downwards to the southwest.  The colorless, hard surrounding surfaces show no sign of mortal passage, and no sign of thaw.</description>
    <position x="620" y="-360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="rt southwest" destination="147" />
    <arc exit="up" move="rt up" destination="153" />
  </node>
  <node id="153" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Geshiger">
    <description>A vertical tunnel of ice penetrates into the dark below.  What appears to be a plant, slicked with ice, protrudes from a small ledge on one side, the leaves coated and preserved with a sheeting of glassy frost.</description>
    <position x="620" y="-380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="rt lie; down" destination="152" />
  </node>
  <node id="154" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, West of Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Beyond the gentler swells of the cove, the waters grow rough and cold as the northern ocean current curls around Surlaenis.  The angle of the island's ascent is apparent from this distance, its conical shape recalling a long dead volcano.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="149" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="150" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="156" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="155" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, West of Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Boats traveling the Reshal sea shift upon the swells, rising and falling from view as they enter the distant harbor.  Closer by, harbor seals bark from the rocky shores of a narrow inlet to the southeast.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="156" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Inlet" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The inlet narrows to a finger as it slices towards the shore.  The sea pounds against a rocky promontory to the south, but the waves look less perilous closer to land.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="154" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="155" />
  </node>
  <node id="157" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Inlet" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The water is deep and cold, the currents swift.  A dangerous rock cliff cuts the inlet off from the rest of the open sea, but does little to shelter it from the rough seas.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="156" />
  </node>
  <node id="158" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Inlet" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The waves slosh against the rocks with salty spray ever present in the air.  The large sheer cliff cuts off the view to the south and is uninhabitable except by the seabirds that fly in sweeping curves to nest there.  A boulder on the slope of the island is within reach, however.</description>
    <position x="0" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="157" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="159" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb boulder" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="159" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>Salt water churns all about as the sea drives against the submerged rocks.  Strands of seaweed caught in the cracks swirl in a fantastical dance as the motion surges and retreats.  Below is only dark, deep water.</description>
    <position x="0" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="158" />
  </node>
  <node id="160" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff Boulder">
    <description>This large boulder rises above the spray and slosh from the waves of the cove below and forms the first step up a severe climb along the island's western edge.  The frothing waves beat upon the wet rocks emerging from the sea water with a constant thrumming and roar.</description>
    <description>This large boulder rises above the spray and slosh of the waves from the cove below and forms the first step up a severe climb along the island's western edge.  The frothing waves beat upon the wet rocks emerging from the sea water with a constant thrumming and roar, but the light glints off the wave caps with a sparkle and wink.</description>
    <position x="0" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="158" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock shelf" destination="161" />
  </node>
  <node id="161" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff">
    <description>A ledge runs along the face of the cliff, rising upwards to the south.  Salty wind presses the shrubs clinging to patches of soil against the vertical face, but the ledge is wide enough to traverse safely.</description>
    <position x="20" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="160" />
  </node>
  <node id="162" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff">
    <description>The ledge is wide enough to make the shuddering sea breeze less risky, but cracks in the rock squeal in torment every time a harsh gust blows across.  A passage upwards leads safely away from the pounding waves below.</description>
    <position x="20" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="161" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="163" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff">
    <description>A gouge in the cliff overhead looks like a difficult climb.  Trees and shrubs trail down the side of the palisade from the wooded growth there -- quite a pleasant spot if one can attain the heights.  Below, the ocean waves thunder on the partly-submerged rocks.</description>
    <description>A gouge in the cliff overhead looks like a difficult climb.  Trees and shrubs trail down the side of the palisade from the wooded growth there -- quite a pleasant spot if one can attain the heights.  Below, the ocean waves flicker with white caps as flecks of foam cling to the partly-submerged rocks.</description>
    <position x="40" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="162" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb cliff gouge" destination="164" />
  </node>
  <node id="164" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Cliff">
    <description>This area gouged in the cliff is abundant with trees and vegetation, beginning a long curving path into a forest.  A flat, barren patch of stone hangs over the cliff face like a diving platform -- one for the fearless or insane.</description>
    <position x="60" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="165" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb slanting shelf" destination="163" />
  </node>
  <node id="165" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path">
    <description>Birch, rowan and willow trees cover the slope upwards to the east.  The soil is rich, almost black, wherever the leaves do not dance in a light blanket over the ground.  Salt air still whispers in a stinging wind, but the trees sing along with a cheerful reply to each gust.</description>
    <position x="60" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="164" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="166" />
  </node>
  <node id="166" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path">
    <description>The path winds through the trees in a pleasant amble, the further from the sea cliffs, the quieter the churn of ocean and wind.  A distant owl hoots incessantly, comparable to the tolling of a soft bell.</description>
    <description>The path winds through the trees in a pleasant amble, the further from the sea cliffs, the quieter the loquacious ocean and wind.  A bird sings out occasionally, its melody soft and sweet over the rustle of tree branches.</description>
    <position x="80" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="167" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="165" />
  </node>
  <node id="167" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path">
    <description>The path ends here at a ravine -- like a crack in a glacier, or a deep cleft scar, the ground falls far, far away to a distant bottom.  Trees border the path and grow along the gap in a line.  The width of the gash is too far to jump, but... perhaps a way can be discovered across it.</description>
    <position x="80" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="166" />
    <arc exit="none" move="rt search;go fallen log" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="168" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path">
    <description>The trees grow tall here south of the ravine that divides the forest into two halves.  Deeper into the woods, large rowans grow along the sloping ground and shade the plentiful shrubs and herbs thriving on the damp leaf-strewn floor.</description>
    <position x="80" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go fallen log" destination="167" />
  </node>
  <node id="169" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The night air has a fresh coolness to it, and the branches of the trees sway overhead in dancing patterns.  Sometimes a branch pops loudly, breaking the deep quiet.  Startled, birds singing or creatures rustling in their hidden shelters grow still and alert.</description>
    <description>The air has a fresh crispness to it, and the light filters through the trees in dancing patterns.  Sometimes a branch pops loudly, breaking the deep quiet.  Startled, birds singing or creatures rustling in their hidden shelters grow still and alert.</description>
    <position x="100" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="168" />
  </node>
  <node id="170" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Although the slope of the ground is severe, the narrow path winds along a flattened ridge.  Broken twigs on a bush near the trail betray the earlier passage of an explorer or an animal.</description>
    <position x="100" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="169" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="171" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The path runs past a log building, simple in construction but large enough to hold many gatherers.  An old willow tree guards the entrance.  The area otherwise looks undisturbed, and without careful observation, the building might well have never been noticed.</description>
    <position x="120" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="172" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="170" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go log building" destination="175" />
  </node>
  <node id="172" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A stand of towering rowan trees spreads in all directions.  The sweet scent of mint and damp earth mingles with composting leaf mould enriching the already thick soil.</description>
    <position x="120" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="171" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="173" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Young aspens that quiver with each breeze grow in the space beneath the towering rowans.  The smaller growth screens and shelters the area from the forest beyond, forming a natural sanctuary.</description>
    <position x="140" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="174" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="172" />
  </node>
  <node id="174" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Wooded Path" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The leaf-covered slope is broken at one point by rocks where the soil has worn away.  A single slate beneath it is wet with the splash of spring water that spills from the rocky ground.  The patter of water counterpoints the shivering rowan and aspen trees that continue into the distant forest.</description>
    <position x="160" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="173" />
  </node>
  <node id="175" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Hart Hall">
    <description>The high rafters of the hall make the building light and spacious, and the planked floor and walls are smooth from years of use.  Boards placed over trestles form a long table down the center of the room, and similar planks line the walls to form bunks for bedding.  A fire at one end of the hall burns brightly and warms a pot of stew.  At the opposite end, a huge rack of antlers hangs over the doorway.</description>
    <position x="140" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go doorway" destination="171" />
  </node>
  <node id="176" name="Waters of the Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The onslaught of the sea is lessened within the protective borders of the small cove.  Black sand embraces the water's edge in sun baked warmth, its heat quenched in the cool caress of the ocean as it glides its foamy, green fingers softly over the shore.  Each wave thrusting lightly over the beach steals a precious cargo of sand, yet deposits its own seeds of marine life upon the warm, receptive land.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="177" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shore" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="177" name="Ocean, Near the Cove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Among sheer towering cliffs is nestled a small sandy cove, a picture of bliss next to the fury of waves breaking on the massive wall of stone.  The water, here at the mouth of the cove, bobs gently with the incoming waves, lifting swimmers on its rolling crest.  The wide, sweet sea spreads out to the north and west, its swells rising and falling with its own secret rhythms.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="176" />
  </node>
  <node id="178" name="Sea Caves, Tunnel">
    <description>The surging of the sea registers as a slight throbbing in the earth and a faint tickle of salt in the air.  The sparkling passage leads smoothly and directly away from the trail and ocean into the hard rock of the seaside cliffs.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="179" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="179" name="Sea Caves, Tunnel">
    <description>A slender path winds its way through the chamber, the floor to either side rising gradually until it meets the shallowly arched roof.  Short stalactites crowd the ceiling, dripping lonely drops of water.  The floor, aside from the worn path, is pocked with puddles and tiny pools.  As water drips into the higher pools they overflow their small banks and send a miniature stream running down to the next pool where the event is repeated until the overflow has dribbled out onto the path.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="178" />
  </node>
  <node id="180" name="Crystal Cave">
    <description>An outcrop of clear crystals bursts from a red and gold rock formation like the morning sun rising over a forest of stalagmites growing thickly on the cavern floor.  Several long stalactites glisten from where they hang on the ceiling, letting fall an occasional drop of water.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="179" />
  </node>
  <node id="181" name="Sea Caves">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Water cascades down the glistening walls of the large cavern and drips rapidly from many long stalactites.  Rivulets of water meander across the uneven floor pooling in a depression near the center of the room.  Flecks of mica glimmer like thousands of tiny stars through the thin sheets of water.  Numerous stalagmites jab upwards, dribbled spires and towers of some god's languorous dream.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="180" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="187" />
  </node>
  <node id="182" name="Sea Caves, Passageway">
    <description>The long passageway is cramped and close.  Damp walls press in from the sides and great care must be exercised to avoid smashing one's head against the ubiquitous stalactites or barking one's shins on the solid stalagmites which seem to move to get in the way.  The glittering speckles imbedded in the rock do very little to banish the stark shadows which grow blackly behind the hanging rock and across the obstacle-studded floor.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="181" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="183" name="Sea Caves, Passageway">
    <description>Warm light glows from a thick vein of clear crystal intersecting the tunnel.  The vein must break through the surface somewhere above and reflect the sunlight down.  Green metallic tendrils cobweb the walls, forked lightning forms frozen forever in the rock.  A small garden of mushrooms has taken up residence on a shelf in the basalt walls which has managed to accumulate enough soil to support the little forest.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="184" name="Sea Caves, Large Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A damp rock curtain glitters like a grey-green waterfall tumbling down the southern wall of the cavern to spill out across the floor in an uneven carpet of stone.  A tall column reaches up into the dark recesses of the stalactite studded ceiling.  The sound of water splattering as it hits the floor or a receiving stalagmite echoes weirdly in the chamber.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="183" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone column" destination="193" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock curtain" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="185" name="Sea Caves, Hot Spring">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A small pool burbles and steams in the lower end of the small cavern, a wide ledge running about its edge.  The walls are smooth and damp, intermittently adorned with a fragile blue and green fungus.  A sweet, floral scent wafts from the pool.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="182" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small pool" destination="186" />
  </node>
  <node id="186" name="Hot Spring">
    <description>The water is almost too hot to endure but is strangely relaxing.  The sweet scent of the steam eases the mind, soothing away worries as the rejuvenating water loosens stiff muscles.  Each inhalation clears the head with a startling sharpness while inducing a wistful sleepiness.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wide ledge" destination="185" />
  </node>
  <node id="187" name="Sea Caves">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>No water glistens here.  The small room's floor is uneven and covered with rocky dust.  Multi-colored layers of rock are exposed in the ceiling where chunks have recently broken off and fallen.  Gouges and long scrapes mar one wall where something frantically scratched it some time ago.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="181" />
  </node>
  <node id="188" name="Sea Caves, Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A small waterfall pours from the low ceiling into a long shallow pool running along one wall of the elongated chamber.  Rocks and stalagmites crowd its banks almost like a dam.  Several stalactites reach their long points down nearly to the surface of the pool.  Where free from hanging rock formations, the ceiling is covered with a blue-green fungus tinged with yellow.  The basalt wall opposite the pool is streaked with yellow, red, and green veins like wisps of colored smoke against a midnight sky.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="187" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="189" name="Sea Caves, Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A ledge skirts its way about this huge chamber.  Between the ledge and the wall rises an enormous pile of rubble which has fallen from the ceiling above.  The caved in portion of the roof is as flat and round as a plate, and the coloring of the exposed rock forms an image which resembles a large shark.  On the other side of the ledge, the floor tilts steeply down among large bits of rock debris, broken stalagmites and shattered stalactites before reaching the far side of the cavern.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="188" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rubble" destination="190" />
  </node>
  <node id="190" name="Shrine of Drogor">
    <description>The top of the pile of rubble is just out of reach of the ceiling of the chamber, where the image of a ferocious shark is clear on a barren circle of stone.  Small bones litter the top of the rubble pile, and offerings lie scattered about the loose stone.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rubble" destination="189" />
  </node>
  <node id="191" name="Sea Caves, Passageway">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The passage narrows enough that a Gor'Tog would have to squeeze to get its shoulders through, but the ceiling is lost from sight as a crevice extends far above into the darkness.  The walls are smooth and straight rather than uneven and rough, as is the case elsewhere in the caverns.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="192" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="184" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crevice" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="192" name="Sea Caves, Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A host of slender stone columns join the ceiling and floor, giving the glimmering cavern the look of a palace ballroom.  The ropey veined basalt, glistening with dampness, is a polished marble dance floor.  The long stalactites are glittering chandeliers.  The elegant stalagmites, clustered in tight knots, are indolent courtiers.  A low shelf skirts the northeast side of the chamber, wide and smooth.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="191" />
  </node>
  <node id="193" name="A Nook">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A large lip of rock forms a pocket in the ceiling within easy reach of the thick stone column.  The nook is amazingly dry and feels a bit cooler than the chamber below.  A bed of fresh rushes lies invitingly in the rear of the cavity.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone column" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="194" name="Above the Curtain">
    <description>A wide ledge spreads out across the top of the rock curtain.  The air feels warm and moist, and it smells slightly of rotten eggs.  A few stalactites hang near the edge of the ledge above the curtain, but otherwise the ceiling and floor are barren of rocky growths.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="196" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rock curtain" destination="184" />
  </node>
  <node id="195" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>The air is warm and humid.  Beads of water cover the walls and roof, dripping down with inexorable slowness.  The rock is patterned with holes and vents of all sizes, and no stalactites or stalagmites grow.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="210" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="196" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Odd holes and vents riddle the walls of the passage.  Some are too small to poke in a finger, others are larger than a Gor Tog's head.  The unusual construction gives the rock a soft, spongy look, but it is quite firm and warm to the touch.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="200" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="197" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="194" />
  </node>
  <node id="197" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Steam gushes into the small chamber from several flues in the walls and floor.  Some of the dense clouds escape through small shafts in the ceiling, leaving a light mist blanketing the room.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="199" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="198" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="198" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The walls have the oozy appearance of mud, piling in soft-looking folds towards the floor.  Several fist-sized holes line the top of the walls around the chamber, shooting gouts of steam and spitting out hot mud.  Wisps of steam linger about the walls and floor in smoky tendrils.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="199" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>Sharp crystals sprout all about the chamber.  Black, clear, crimson, and azure spikes thrust up to snag the unwary.  Rather than sparkling beautifully, the crystals radiate a dim, unhealthy green glow.  Steam swirls sluggishly around the room of the cavern, shrouding some crystals in a thin veil.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="197" />
  </node>
  <node id="200" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The walls of the small chamber are oddly shaped with bulges and strange eruptions in the rock.  The ceiling bows down in the center as if tired of holding up the tons of rock overhead.  Tiny holes riddle the undulated floor of the chamber.  The air is thick and hot with a halo of steam floating around the edges of the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="202" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="201" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="196" />
  </node>
  <node id="201" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The tunnel comes to an end in a small chamber, the floor sinking down to a narrow shaft in the floor.  Gurgling sounds echo up the shaft, and geysers of steam blast intermittently from the hole.  Above the pit, the ceiling is blasted smooth.  Water condensation runs down the pock-marked walls from the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="202" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The jagged entrance opens into a smooth black-glass oval.  The surface is nearly unmarred, only minor blemishes interrupt the dark reflective walls.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="200" />
  </node>
  <node id="203" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The uneven floor and bulging walls of the moderately sized chamber are pocked with eerie dark mouths, vents, wells, and holes.  Some of the orifices emit tendrils of hot steam, other release nauseous fumes, a very few intermittently burp out scalding water.  The smells and sounds are sickeningly remniscent of a sour stomach.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="204" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="194" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="204" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>Thick clouds of steam make for terrible visibility in the narrow passageway.  Hot air blows through the cramped confines, tugging at loose articles of clothing and nearly blistering the skin.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="206" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="205" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="203" />
  </node>
  <node id="205" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>The large cavern is honeycombed with vents and fissures of all sizes.  One would need to step carefully to avoid turning an ankle on the uneven and pit-strewn floor.  A loud hissing noise fills the room.  Steam billows from several sunken orifices about the chamber, and the walls sweat heavily.  A glassy-black basalt outcropping gleams in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="206" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>Small fissures split the floor and walls, allowing blasts of hot air and steam to shoot up from somewhere below.  The air is heavy with the stench of rotting eggs and has a sharp quality which makes eyes water and heads pound.  Beads of water drip down the slick green walls.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="204" />
  </node>
  <node id="207" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>A large puddle of muddy water burbles slowly in the lower portion of the small chamber.  A couple of stalactites drip sadly into the puddle, looking as if they are about to melt away.  The floor has a treacherous, slimy feel to it and the walls and ceiling glisten damply.  In the wall behind the pool of muck is a small hole.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="208" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="203" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="209" />
  </node>
  <node id="208" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>Three strange mounds rise from the floor of the small cavern.  An ash-grey mud burbles out of one of the mounds, and the other two belch out putrid smelling fumes and steam.  The vents and holes in the wall are all very small, giving the appearance that the tunnel is covered with a huge mud dauber's nest.  Jets of steam spray occasionally from the holes.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="209" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The passage is blocked by an old cave-in -- tons of rock cut off movement into a smaller side passage.  Steady streams of hot steam billow from several chinks around the edges of the rock pile.  The vents in the wall are all very small, giving the appearance that the tunnel is covered with a huge mud dauber's nest.  Jets of steam spray occasionally from the holes.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="207" />
  </node>
  <node id="210" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Glassy basalt glitters darkly on the walls, ceiling, and floor.  All surfaces have a peculiar scalloped appearance, the small depressions varying between smooth and glassy or rough and pitted.  The small ridges are sharp and jagged.  A fall or misstep would likely rend flesh from the unlucky fumbler.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="211" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="212" />
  </node>
  <node id="211" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>A black tarry substance coats the walls of the miserably horrid-smelling dead end.  A thick crack in the floor, crusted with black scabrous material, releases foul emissions into the air.  The vents in the wall are all very small, giving the appearance that the tunnel is covered with a huge mud dauber's nest.  Jets of steam spray occasionally from the holes.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="212" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>The passageway ends at a deep pit which belches forth great clouds of steam and scalding water.  The heat is almost unbearable.  The vents in the wall are all very small, giving the appearance that the tunnel is covered with a huge mud dauber's nest.  Jets of steam spray occasionally from the holes.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="210" />
  </node>
  <node id="213" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Wisps of steam rise from the holes and pits in the walls.  The air is hot, muggy, and foul smelling, making breathing difficult.  A roiling cloud of steam churns against the high roof of the wide chamber.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="214" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="195" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="215" />
  </node>
  <node id="214" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The tunnel dwindles and separates into three large vents which sink into the rocky floor.  The vents in the wall are all very small, giving the appearance that the tunnel is covered with a huge mud dauber's nest.  Jets of steam spray occasionally from the holes.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="215" name="Steam Vents">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The tunnel comes to a gradual end here, the passage diameter narrowing abrupty to a small cone with a dark hole at its end.  The vents in the wall are all very small, giving the appearance that the tunnel is covered with a huge mud dauber's nest.  Jets of steam spray occasionally from the holes.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="213" />
  </node>
  <node id="216" name="Sea Caves, Crevice">
    <description>The top of the crevice ends at a slender opening in the wall.  A faint breath of warm air caresses the flesh on its way up the natural chimney.  The walls and ceiling are much drier and the air less humid than down below.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crevice" destination="191" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slender opening" destination="217" />
  </node>
  <node id="217" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A huge flat slab of rock serves as a floor in this shaft, ending at a dark slot-like opening splitting the north wall horizontally.  The low ceiling and walls are likewise even and flat, although the texture is rough to the touch.  A fine grit of pulverized rock is scattered across the peculiar chamber.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="218" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark opening" destination="216" />
  </node>
  <node id="218" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>The small dome-shaped chamber is unremarkable except for the smoothness of its surfaces.  The floor is even and level with only a light coating of rock dust.  The walls slope gently inward and upward to the apex of the hemisphere of black stone.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="217" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="219" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>Passages lead out of the large chamber like spokes from the hub of a wagon wheel.  Dust and rubble cover the floor in cluttered disarray.  The ceiling is lost behind many layers of webbing, old and new, as if to hold back the falling stone of the roof.  A small cairn stands in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="280" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="220" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="218" />
  </node>
  <node id="220" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>A thick black ichor creeps down the southern wall of the chamber from a thin crack where the smooth wall slab meets the rough rock of the ceiling.  The excretion has built up at the base of the wall and solidified into a scabrous crust.  Remarkably, the room is free of the ubiquitous dust and rubble encountered elsewhere.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="221" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>Sloping steeply down to the northeast, the floor is pocked with numerous pits and festooned with fallen rock.  The extreme southwest end of the room is flat and even for a couple of paces before the ground begins its descent.  A couple of out-of-place boulders are worn down and polished on their tops.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="222" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>The upper reaches of the chamber are cloaked in deep shadows.  Strewn among the unusually large stones and rubble are a litter of cracked bones and other less savory detritus of death.  One wall is cloven with an ominous crack running from the floor up into the darkness above.  Many smaller spidery lines fork off from the main split.</description>
    <position x="300" y="0" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="223" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="220" />
  </node>
  <node id="223" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A deep crevice splits the cavern in the east.  A narrow bridge of stone arches over the abyss to a small landing.  The sound of running water echoes loudly through the chamber, reverberating off the high ceiling.  Heaps of rubble litter the expansive floor.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="222" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="221" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone bridge" destination="279" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deep crevice" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="224" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>A large clump of webbing obscures and fills a man-sized nook in one wall.  Crisscrossing the high ceiling is a multitude of webs.  Clouds of fine dust sift down occasionally through the thick strands with a dry rasping rustle.</description>
    <position x="320" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="222" />
  </node>
  <node id="225" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>The intersecting tunnels form a small chamber only a few paces across.  The foot of one of the corner walls forms a low shelf worn smooth by use.  The rubble and loose stones in the area are swept aside forming a low ring of debris which passes in front of the passage openings -- a formidable barrier to marauding mice, but naught else.</description>
    <position x="340" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="226" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="226" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Columns of stone sprout from the floor and tower up into the web-veiled reaches of the high ceiling.  Nine of the mammoth shafts connect floor and ceiling like living fibers stretching between rent flesh.  The cavern is easily fifty paces across at its widest point and at least half as high.  Ropes of webbing connect the upper reaches of the pillars in intricate patterns which shift and glimmer with each vibration.</description>
    <position x="360" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="stone column" destination="235" />
  </node>
  <node id="227" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>A disturbingly large pair of disembodied chelicerae lies haphazardly against a wall.  Poking out from beneath a large rock fall are several long slivers of chitinous plate.  Trailers of aged webbing dangle in silver-grey patches from the walls and ceiling.</description>
    <position x="300" y="40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="224" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="228" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="219" />
  </node>
  <node id="228" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Thick gouges evidence an effort to widen the narrow passage here.  Knobs of rock protrude from the irregular walls and thrust into the room to crowd the small space.  Dust and flakes of rock litter the ground, crunching sharply when trod upon.</description>
    <position x="320" y="60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="225" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep staircase" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="229" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>A dark cut slices through one wall of the chamber running from a gaping hole in the ceiling down through a narrow slot in the floor.  A thin stream of water runs along the channel, falling through the hole from somewhere above only to disappear into the rocky earth.  The gurgling sound of running water is a pleasant diversion from the unnatural silence of these dry caverns.</description>
    <position x="280" y="60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="227" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="230" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="231" />
  </node>
  <node id="230" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>A thin coat of ashen dust covers everything in the wide cavern.  Strange scuffling marks are etched in the dust as if someone tried sweeping the room with the wrong end of a broom.  Thick webs shroud the roof of the chamber from view, glinting the same silvery-greyness as the fine layer of grit below.</description>
    <position x="280" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="231" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>The misshapen ceiling hangs down in several banded layers.  Parts of the great rock plates have fallen, leaving black gaps like missing teeth grinning down from above.  Piles of rubble lie in chaotic disarray beneath the gaping holes.  At infrequent intervals, fountains of dust rain down from the pits and scatter on the rocks below.</description>
    <position x="260" y="40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="229" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="232" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The floor lies like a rumpled blanket in untidy folds of rock and makes for precarious footing.  Loose stones, pebbles, and dust do not help the matter.  A long slab of stone leans tiredly against the wall, forming a small niche beneath.</description>
    <position x="240" y="60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="234" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="230" />
  </node>
  <node id="233" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>The small chamber is little more than a widening of the connecting passages.  A web of cracks spreads across the otherwise flat and featureless floor.  The ceiling is also afflicted with cracks, and wide slates of rock appear on the verge of releasing their tenuous grip and dashing to pieces below.</description>
    <position x="240" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="219" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="231" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="234" />
  </node>
  <node id="234" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>A long tube has been cut into the rock with great force.  The rounded walls are rough and uneven, but the shaft runs in a nearly perfect straight line, a testament to the power of the earth.  Shards of mica sparkle in the dark surfaces of the stone.  Looking down the tunnel is like gazing into a well of stars.</description>
    <position x="220" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="233" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="232" />
  </node>
  <node id="235" name="Lofty Perch">
    <description>A small ledge juts from the side of the column near the ceiling, just wide enough to stand on comfortably.  Instead of walls, the ledge is ringed by the complex webs built all about the upper portion of the cavern.</description>
    <position x="380" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="236" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stone column" destination="226" />
  </node>
  <node id="236" name="Upper Caverns, On the Column">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The ledge curls its way up and around the wide column.  Thick strands of silk, anchored to the sturdy stone, create difficult obstacles.  Several planes of webbing stretch across the upper reaches of the high cavern, providing easy access to all areas by whatever creature fashioned them.</description>
    <position x="380" y="0" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="237" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="235" />
  </node>
  <node id="237" name="Upper Caverns, On the Column">
    <description>The ledge curls its way up and around the wide column.  A vast network of thick webbing spans the upper reaches of the high cavern.  Anchored on the stone column, stalactites, and the rock walls, the strands create easy access paths for the creatures dwelling therein.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="238" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="236" />
  </node>
  <node id="238" name="Upper Caverns, On the Column">
    <description>The ledge curls its way up and around the wide column.  Thick strands of silk, anchored to the sturdy stone, create difficult obstacles.  Several planes of webbing stretch across the upper reaches of the high cavern, providing easy access to all areas by whatever creature fashioned them.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="239" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="237" />
  </node>
  <node id="239" name="Upper Caverns, On the Column">
    <description>The ledge curls its way up and around the thick stone column.  Enormous webs cast their strong silken strands across the upper reaches of the cavern, connecting pillar to wall to stalactite in a dazzling pattern of intersecting and concentric silver lines.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="240" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="238" />
  </node>
  <node id="240" name="Upper Caverns, On the Column">
    <description>The ledge curls its way up and around the rock column.  Long, thick silk strands sweep across the upper reaches of the chamber, shimmering silver rays as the threads stir in the dim reaches of the cave.  Above, the ceiling is visible through a few more layers of webbing.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="239" />
  </node>
  <node id="241" name="Upper Caverns, On the Column">
    <description>The ledge curls its way up and around the wide column.  A vast network of webs fans across the upper reaches of the cavern, glistening damply from water caught falling from small stalactites above.  Only a sparse layer of thick grey strands spans the space between this ledge and the roof of the high chamber.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="242" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="240" />
  </node>
  <node id="242" name="Upper Caverns, Top of the Column">
    <description>The narrow ledge ends near the rough ceiling of the huge cavern.  A single horizontal plane of webbing stretches across the area below the roof at the level of the ledge.  The many layers filling the nether region create the impression of clouds or fog floating below.  Nearly out of reach, where the thick column joins the vaulted ceiling, is a faintly illuminated, rough hole.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="241" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb rough hole" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="243" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>Very faint illumination is provided by a flaking patch of glowing fungus clinging to a fallen rock.  An enormous cavern spreads out of sight into the darkness, stony floor and soaring walls fading into the unlit areas beyond.  Nearly hidden behind some crumbling stalagmites, a narrow opening sinks into the floor near the wall of the wide cavern.  A huge stalagmite and stalactite pair occupy the center of the chamber.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="244" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb narrow opening" destination="242" />
  </node>
  <node id="244" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>A pile of rubble litters the area where a falling stalactite or roof plate has shattered on the ground.  The walls at this end of the long cavern are smooth and dry.  Silver-grey dust coats everything in a soft film.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="243" />
  </node>
  <node id="245" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Smokey quartz and fool's gold gleam from a multitude of small outcrops in an ancient rock curtain draped down the wall.  Like dripping candle wax, the sediment crawled down the wall millenia ago and solidified in odd lumps and long streams, even pooling on the floor in a thick, rippled mass of stone.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="246" />
  </node>
  <node id="246" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>Luminous lichens grow on the rocks, stalagmites and walls, providing a dim yellow glow.  In the shadows of a pile of rubble, a narrow hole cuts down into the earth, its smooth sides providing little purchase.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark hole" destination="253" />
  </node>
  <node id="247" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Occupying this dark corner of the huge chamber is a heaping stack of bones.  Small insects skitter in and over the gleaming white remains.  The sweet scent of decay tickles the nose faintly in the otherwise dank air.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="248" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Numerous small stalagmites crowd the space between the base of the great fang in the center of the chamber and the jagged wall of the cavern.  The floor is dry and dusty, the thick layers of webbing strewn across the upper cavern catching any water droplets which might have fallen from stalactites hidden above.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="247" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="251" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="244" />
  </node>
  <node id="249" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Puddles of dust dot the uneven floor.  Bits of fractured stone lie scattered about the area.  Carved into the wall of the chamber is a skeletal fish.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="250" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="251" />
  </node>
  <node id="250" name="Wide Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>Blanketing the area is a thick carpet of fine-textured black pumice.  A few short stalagmites poke up through the layer of powder.  The huge, echoing chamber expands to the north and west where an awe-inspiring paired stalactite and stalagmite reach towards each other in a much awaited embrace.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="245" />
  </node>
  <node id="251" name="Wide Cavern, The Fangs">
    <description>A gigantic stalagmite erupts from the floor, reaching high up towards the point of an equally massive stalactite.  Hanging from the web-shrouded ceiling, the stalactite is an awesome reflection of the lower fang on a silvery pond of silk.</description>
    <position x="420" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="248" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="249" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="245" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="243" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stalagmite" destination="252" />
  </node>
  <node id="252" name="The Fangs, The Pinnacle">
    <description>The irregular surface provides many tiny ledges and hand holds near the tip of the stalagmite.  Only a few feet above, a drop of water slowly forms at the slender tip of the fang, gradually growing in size until gravity finally wrests it away to fall upon the rock below.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stalagmite" destination="251" />
  </node>
  <node id="253" name="The Chimney">
    <description>A split in the rock provides a thin lip of stone on which to rest above the dark hole descending below.  The narrow chimney rises steeply above, smooth and barren of handholds.  The crumbling remains of glowing lichens on the wall provide poor illumination to the cramped spot.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb chimney" destination="246" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark hole" destination="254" />
  </node>
  <node id="254" name="The Chimney">
    <description>A split in the rock provides a thin lip of stone on which to rest above the dark hole descending below.  The narrow chimney rises steeply above, smooth and barren of handholds.  Weak light from far above drives back the nearly palpable darkness.</description>
    <position x="400" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb chimney" destination="253" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark hole" destination="255" />
  </node>
  <node id="255" name="The Chimney">
    <description>A slight change of the shaft's orientation provides a thin ledge of stone on which to rest above the dark hole descending below.  The narrow chimney rises straight up above, smooth and barren of handholds.  The barest trickle of light reaches down from what seems an infinite distance above, providing just enough illumination to question the darkness.</description>
    <position x="400" y="0" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb chimney" destination="254" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark hole" destination="256" />
  </node>
  <node id="256" name="The Chimney">
    <description>A split in the rock provides a thin lip of stone on which to rest above the dark hole descending below.  The narrow chimney rises straight up above, smooth and barren of handholds.  The darkness thickens like a shroud.  The memory of light gleaming within provides more sight than the pale wraith of illumination above.</description>
    <position x="400" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb chimney" destination="255" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark hole" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="257" name="The Chimney">
    <description>A slight change of the shaft's orientation provides a thin ledge of stone on which to rest above the dark hole descending below.  The narrow chimney rises steeply above, smooth and barren of handholds.  A light so faint it can only be called such in comparison to the dark below illuminates the area, its source unidentifiable.</description>
    <position x="400" y="40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb chimney" destination="256" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb dark hole" destination="258" />
  </node>
  <node id="258" name="Small Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The walls and floor of the chamber are smooth with barely a chisel mark to betray the skilled hand of whatever worked the stone.  Overhead, however, the walls curve to the domed ceiling in the usual rough way of caverns.  A narrow hole, chimney-like bores its way out through the roof.</description>
    <position x="420" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="259" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb chimney" destination="257" />
  </node>
  <node id="259" name="Small Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The walls and floor of the chamber are smooth with barely a chisel mark to betray the skilled hand of whatever worked the stone.  Overhead, however, the walls curve to the domed ceiling in the usual rough way of caverns.  A smooth-walled alcove, slightly larger than a burly dwarf, cuts into the wall.</description>
    <position x="420" y="60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb steep staircase" destination="228" />
  </node>
  <node id="260" name="Small Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The walls and floor of the chamber are smooth with barely a chisel mark to betray the skilled hand of whatever worked the stone.  Overhead, however, the walls curve to the domed ceiling in the usual rough way of caverns.  Slicing out of the east wall is a small passageway.</description>
    <position x="440" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="261" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="261" name="Small Cavern">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <description>The walls and floor of the chamber are smooth with barely a chisel mark to betray the skilled hand of whatever worked the stone.  Overhead, however, the walls curve to the domed ceiling in the usual rough way of caverns.  A wide ledge of stone, cluttered with shards of pottery and ceramics, juts from the wall.</description>
    <position x="440" y="60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="260" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="258" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="259" />
  </node>
  <node id="262" name="Narrow Passage">
    <description>The entire passage is finely cut through the black rock, though it is a bit narrow for 'Togs.  It is impossible to tell where chisel may have touched stone in its creation.</description>
    <position x="460" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="263" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="260" />
  </node>
  <node id="263" name="The Rift">
    <description>A narrow passage ends at a tall crevice which runs north and south through the cavern.  A ledge, wide enough for safety, protrudes into the rift and overhangs the deep gash.  The sound of rushing water reverberates through the space.</description>
    <position x="480" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="262" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb crevice" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="264" name="Underground River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A swift river blasts through the narrow chasm, roiling madly in its stoney bed.  Glowing lichens growing on the high walls cast a dim illumination on the raging torrent.  High above, a wide ledge protrudes from the wall, hanging out over the river.</description>
    <position x="500" y="80" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="268" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wall" destination="263" />
  </node>
  <node id="265" name="Underground River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Strong jets of water from underground streams emptying into the river below the surface cause powerful swirls and chop.  The deep waters move swiftly between the sheer walls of the high crevice.  Glowing lichens cast their dim illumination on the river below.</description>
    <position x="500" y="100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="264" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="266" name="Underground Streams" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Glowing lichens, high above, cast a dim illumination on the gushing streams below.  Water cascades in frothy veils and powerful sprays from large holes in the sides of the fissure.  The torrent swells to several feet in depth, churning mightily as it tumbles away.</description>
    <position x="500" y="120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="265" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="267" />
  </node>
  <node id="267" name="Underground Streams, Source" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Hundreds of fountains of water pour from holes in the rock walls at the end of the crevice.  The water gathers in an ankle deep pool before rushing away to the north.  Glowing lichens, high above, cast a dim illumination on the streams below.</description>
    <position x="500" y="140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="266" />
  </node>
  <node id="268" name="Underground River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A swift river blasts through the narrow chasm, roiling madly in its stoney bed.  Glowing lichens growing on the high walls cast a dim illumination on the raging torrent.</description>
    <position x="500" y="60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="269" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="264" />
  </node>
  <node id="269" name="Underground River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A swift river blasts through the narrow chasm, roiling madly in its stoney bed.  Glowing lichens growing on the high walls cast a dim illumination on the raging torrent.</description>
    <position x="500" y="40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="270" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="268" />
  </node>
  <node id="270" name="Underground River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The crevice comes to an abrupt end, but the river punches through the rock, rushing noisily through a wide opening in the wall of stone.</description>
    <position x="500" y="20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="271" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="269" />
  </node>
  <node id="271" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="0" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="272" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="270" />
  </node>
  <node id="272" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-20" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="273" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="271" />
  </node>
  <node id="273" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-40" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="274" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="272" />
  </node>
  <node id="274" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-60" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="273" />
  </node>
  <node id="275" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="274" />
  </node>
  <node id="276" name="Chasm River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The deep water rushes wildly between the craggy walls rising to either side.  High above, the bridge arches over the chasm, its underside dimly lit.  Water splashes high up the wall as it tumbles through, bashing against the rough stone.  Debris in the water, propelled by the swift current, strikes swimmers with great force.  Water gushes from a low opening in the south wall.  A strange luminescence glows faintly from under the water.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-120" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="275" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb craggy wall" destination="279" />
  </node>
  <node id="277" name="Chasm River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The deep water rushes wildly between the craggy walls rising to either side.  High above, the bridge arches over the chasm, its underside dimly lit.  Water splashes high up the wall as it tumbles through, bashing against the rough stone.  Debris in the water, propelled by the swift current, strikes swimmers with great force.  A strange luminescence glows faintly from under the water.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-140" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="278" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="276" />
  </node>
  <node id="278" name="Chasm River" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The deep water rushes wildly between the craggy walls rising to either side.  High above, the bridge arches over the chasm, its underside dimly lit.  Water splashes high up the wall as it tumbles through, bashing against the rough stone.  Debris in the water, propelled by the swift current, strikes swimmers with great force.  The swirling waters drain out through a low tunnel in the wall.  A strange luminescence glows faintly from under the water.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-160" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="277" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go low tunnel" destination="280" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb craggy wall" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="279" name="Upper Caverns">
    <description>It's pitch dark and you can't see a thing!</description>
    <position x="480" y="-100" z="1" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deep crevice" destination="276" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone bridge" destination="223" />
  </node>
  <node id="280" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-180" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="278" />
  </node>
  <node id="281" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-200" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="280" />
  </node>
  <node id="282" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="500" y="-220" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="281" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="283" />
  </node>
  <node id="283" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-240" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="282" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="284" />
  </node>
  <node id="284" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#000080">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="460" y="-260" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="283" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="285" />
  </node>
  <node id="285" name="Underground River, Underwater" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A torrent of water rushes through the wide tunnel dragging all along with it.  Scouring the rock as it goes, the river wears down the stone, occasionally tearing off a chunk and pushing it along in the flood.</description>
    <position x="440" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="284" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="177" />
  </node>
  <node id="286" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Kregkeirel Stable">
    <description>Whitewashed wooden stalls line the room, customized to suit the needs of the native creatures of Surlaenis.  Long-eared and camel-faced, the kregkeirels peek over their pens with bored interest, using their long necks to get a good view of the hay-filled surroundings.  Along one wall is a row of panniers, large woven baskets shaped to fit comfortably on the back of the beasts.  Stablehands come and go as they see to their work, sometimes stopping to offer the beasts an affectionate pat.</description>
    <position x="660" y="-180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stable door" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="287" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Chamber">
    <description>Soft, bluish light pulses from the walls of this chamber, a vein of precious anloral.  The air is cool and fresh, not a trace of the life-sucking cold seeping through the passageways or stone.  The walls are sheer and smooth, soaring high overhead to merge into a boundless glow.</description>
    <position x="480" y="-400" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="134" />
  </node>
  <node id="288" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Beside Shadaer Jama">
    <description>In an overgrown indentation not far from the road, the ground is covered with shattered rock and fallen pebbles.  Within one crevice, water bubbles up from an underground spring and tumbles over the stones in a gushing gargle of swift water as it heads down the steep slope below.</description>
    <position x="540" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadaer jama" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="289" name="Builder's Warehouse, Interior" note="Furniture Shop">
    <description>An entry area to the warehouse lies just inside the door.  As the space stretches away from the docks, rice paper screens partition it into private sections that shopkeepers rent to display their wares.  Fluttering overhead, a paper mobile hangs out of reach and dances wildly in the breeze each time the door opens and closes.</description>
    <position x="100" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go exit door" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="292" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ricepaper screen" destination="294" />
  </node>
  <node id="290" name="Builder's Warehouse, Sectioned Corridor">
    <description>The screens form a passageway to move deeper into the warehouse.  A sisal runner covering the wood planked floor and the scent of burning sandalwood lends warmth and comfort to the practical space.  The muted shouts of workers on the dock drift into the interior through partly-open windows high overhead.</description>
    <position x="120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="291" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="289" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go silk-curtained arch" destination="295" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ricepaper screen" destination="296" />
  </node>
  <node id="291" name="Builder's Warehouse, Sectioned Corridor">
    <description>Several open screens lead into various sections providing wares for the homeowner or builder.  From somewhere in the farthest reaches comes the soft cry of an infant and his mother's singing coos to calm him as she works.</description>
    <position x="140" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="290" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go curved arch" destination="297" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide doorway" destination="299" />
  </node>
  <node id="292" name="Smoque's Screens" note="Walls" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Translucent ricepaper screens in neutral and pastel colors are on display along the walls of the shop.  A sliding arrangement near the door allows the purchaser to judge the colors in the light when selecting furnishings for their home.</description>
    <position x="100" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="293" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="293" name="Where There's Smoque, There's Fyere!" note="Stoves" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Fires burn in small braziers and stoves, each carefully screened to protect the ricepaper screens which form the walls of the shop.  Designed to sit upon the floor, the low braziers provide a surprising amount of warmth for their size.</description>
    <position x="120" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="292" />
  </node>
  <node id="294" name="Thymes' Tables" note="Tables" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The fragrance of freshly carved sandalwood doesn't quite mask the sharper smells of the lacquer used to provide the glossy finish so popular on the island.  An assortment of tables and desks are on display, providing the homeowner with a good selection of both traditional and modern styles.  From the abstract shesegri design of the meditation table to the more representative floral images on the rose and lotus tables, the shop bespeaks fine craftsmanship and careful attention to detail.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="289" />
  </node>
  <node id="295" name="The Lap of Luxury" note="Cushions" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pale gold ricepaper screens enclose the small shop.  Within, piles of cushions in various fabrics and colors are scattered upon the floor.  Traditionally, local homes use these cushions in place of the mainlander's chairs to offer a comfortable place for guests to sit or recline while eating dinner at low tables.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="296" name="Fenwycke's Floormats" note="Floors" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Samples of the local floormats -- woven reed or grass floor matting which conceal the floor of a home -- are on display along the walls of the shop.  The shopkeeper, Fenwycke, plies his trade as he works, waiting for customers to make their decisions.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="290" />
  </node>
  <node id="297" name="Tredwynne's Bedding" note="Beds" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Translucent ricepaper screens line the walls of the shop, the austerity complementing the black stone columns as well as the neutral color of the woven reed floormat.  Against the understated neutrality of the background decor, the sleeping mats on display around the shop provide bright splashes of color.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="291" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go back room" destination="298" />
  </node>
  <node id="298" name="Tredwynne's Bed Linens" note="Blankets" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Stacks of quilts and blankets fill the cabinets which line the shop, leaving little room for the pillows and other objects on display.  Tredwynne's prides itself on offering a complete line of bedding and accessories for the home.</description>
    <position x="160" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="297" />
  </node>
  <node id="299" name="A Room With A View" note="Windows" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Thin metal chains hang from the ceiling, supporting metal-framed frosted and stained glass windows.  The windows are more decorative than functional, keeping insects out and allowing light to filter through the cut glass surfaces.</description>
    <position x="140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="291" />
  </node>
  <node id="300" name="Denison's Pub, Common Room" note="Denison's Pub|Pub|Bar" color="#FF0000">
    <description>A long bar curves around the eastern end of the room, the imposing figure of Denison guarding the casks along the back wall.  Several wooden tables surrounded by rickety chairs in various states of repair crowd the small room in front of the door.  Along the north wall are a couple of slightly more private, and less clean, booths.  The dingy interior is lit by a couple lanterns hanging from support beams burning smelly lamp oil and filling the room with a foul smoke.</description>
    <description>A long bar curves around the eastern end of the room, the imposing figure of Denison guarding the casks along the back wall.  Several wooden tables surrounded by rickety chairs in various states of repair crowd the small room in front of the door.  Along the north wall are a couple of slightly more private, and less clean, booths.  The dingy interior is lit by the sunlight streaming in the broken windows on either side of the entryway.</description>
    <position x="60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="301" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="301" name="Denison's Pub, Stairwell">
    <description>A flight of stone stairs leading up to the second floor takes up most of the space in this small room.  A narrow hallway leads off to the west.  A little used broom and dustpan sit in a dark corner next to the steps.</description>
    <position x="80" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" destination="302" />
  </node>
  <node id="302" name="Denison's Pub, Upper Stairwell">
    <description>A narrow hallway leads away from the stairs and into the dark recesses of the pub.  A grimy window allows a little light to illuminate the steps and hallway.  An occasional burst of laughter erupts from the common room, and a low buzz of conversation murmurs in the hallway.</description>
    <position x="100" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow hallway" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairs" destination="301" />
  </node>
  <node id="303" name="Denison's Pub, Narrow Hallway">
    <description>A dim stairwell lies at one end of the hallway.  The passage takes a sharp turn west away from the stairwell and comes to a dark dead end.  An ebony door on the north wall and a darkly stained walnut door directly across from it are barely discernable in the poor light.  Soot and debris litter the hallway, loose trash rustling underfoot.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dim stairwell" destination="302" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="304" />
  </node>
  <node id="304" name="Denison's Pub, A Back Room">
    <description>Well-crafted tapestries cover the walls, and a thick rug carpets the floor.  An intricately carved liquor cabinet stands against one wall.  Plush cushions issue a tempting invitation, and a low hammock, upheld by two granite statues of dancing maidens, swings near the wall opposite the door.  The ceiling is also draped with small tapestries to keep out drafts and absorb leaks.</description>
    <position x="140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="303" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small doorway" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="305" name="Denison's Pub, Dark Passage">
    <description>A single door opens into this short, unlit hallway.  Dim light filters in from an opening at the end of the hallway, enough to see the walls have been paneled and a thick red carpet put down on the floor.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="304" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go opening" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="306" name="Denison's Pub, Back Hallway">
    <description>The narrow passage runs in a straight line along the back of the pub, a smaller hallway branching off in the middle.  A pair of small grimy windows high in the east wall allow the barest bit of light to illuminate the refuse-scattered way.  The back stair is littered with cast off clothing, broken plates, and spilled food and drink, contributing a memorable scent to the location.</description>
    <position x="180" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red door" destination="307" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebony door" destination="308" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="310" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="312" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go small hallway" destination="305" />
  </node>
  <node id="307" name="Denison's Pub, Curtain Room">
    <description>Thick red velvet curtains hang from a wooden beam, shrouding a makeshift bed of heaped cushions and furs in near darkness.  A burning wick floating in a bowl of lamp oil provides meager illumination from its perch on a low table opposite the bed.  Woven mats cover the floor and prove to be remarkably comfortable.</description>
    <position x="180" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="308" name="Denison's Pub, Upper Chamber">
    <description>Three thin windows covered in grease paper cast a dim glow over the room.  Variously sized tables and chairs crowd the close chamber, creating a veritable obstacle course.  A badly torn fishing net covers one whole wall, gathering dust even as it slowly rots away.  Herds of dust bunnies stampede across the bare wood floor when the door opens and stirs the thick air.</description>
    <position x="200" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebony door" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide archway" destination="309" />
  </node>
  <node id="309" name="Denison's Pub, Sitting Room">
    <description>A wide hearth occupies the south wall with its stone hulk.  Scattered about the room are pairs, trios, and larger groups of chairs arranged for comfortable dialog, intimate discussions, or group arguments.  A colorful Therengian carpet covers the floor, underlying several fine tables which stand available to hold drinks and food.  Shiny brass lamps burn at regular intervals around the walls, providing a sweet scent and little smoke.</description>
    <position x="220" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide archway" destination="308" />
  </node>
  <node id="310" name="Denison's Pub, Table Room">
    <description>A long oak table, the finest piece of furniture in the pub, demands most of the space in the room.  A slew of mismatched chairs encircle the table, eating up the remaining space.  Two rusty iron lamps spread their glow from atop the table.</description>
    <position x="200" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="306" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go battered door" destination="311" />
  </node>
  <node id="311" name="Denison's Pub, Rattan Room">
    <description>The deteriorating floorboards are mostly covered with an elaborate patchwork of threadbare throw rugs.  A frame of curved rattan supports a thick mattress clothed with linen sheets which may have once been white.  Pushed into a dim corner of the room is a roomy circular chair, also of rattan.  Above a tarnished brass lamp is a black triangle of soot, dirtying the fading white wash.</description>
    <position x="220" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go battered door" destination="310" />
  </node>
  <node id="312" name="Denison's Pub, Closet">
    <description>Several shelves hold stacks of folded sheets, towels, spare bar glasses, lamps, casks of oil and other supplies a pub might need.</description>
    <position x="200" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="306" />
  </node>
  <node id="313" name="Denison's Pub, Cellar">
    <description>The cellar is packed with beer barrels, wine casks, tuns, and crates of staples and foodstuffs.  Narrow aisles pass between the high stacks.  A rack supports several tapped barrels and kegs for the lesser ordered beverages carried by the pub.  Bags of flour, sugar, and other dry ingredients are piled on shelves and atop tuns to prevent the damp floor from damaging them.  It is a wonder Denison or his staff can find anything in the clutter.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden steps" destination="300" />
    <arc exit="none" move="rt search;go door" destination="336" />
  </node>
  <node id="314" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Willowbee's Pelts and Spinners" note="Tanner" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Crates of furs and piles of tightly wrapped spinnerets are stacked in the room, many of them tagged with the names of far away places -- the destinations where the furs are bound.  A spindly male elf, Willowbee himself, is often seen bustling around the shop and preparing orders while keeping an eye on the door for hunters, trappers, and traders to bring him business.</description>
    <position x="60" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="315" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Sheds and Shacks" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The small building is crammed with a variety of new and used building materials, but most of it looks scavenged at best.  There is hardly room to turn around, much less closely examine anything, but the merchant is delighted to see any potential customer and eagerly awaits an order.</description>
    <position x="60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="316" name="The Traders' Guild, Grand Foyer">
    <description>Richly veneered cherrywood beams climb the polished marble walls, peaking to form the arch of the high vaulted glass ceiling.  Evening light casts a dim glow upon the stone floors, lengthening the shadows beneath a wide deobar staircase that leads to an open hallway above.  The sounds of thrifty commerce seem enhanced in the echo -- every footstep, every jingle of coin and every barter from the nearby Exchange fill the air with promises of exciting ventures and profitable returns.</description>
    <description>Richly veneered cherrywood beams climb the polished marble walls, peaking to form the arch of the high vaulted glass ceiling.  Light filters down and warms the cold stone floors, casting shadows beneath a wide deobar staircase that leads to an open hallway above.  The sounds of thrifty commerce seem enhanced by the echo -- every footstep, every jingle of coin and every barter from the nearby Exchange fill the air with promises of exciting ventures and profitable returns.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="317" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone ramp" destination="318" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deobar staircase" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="317" name="The Traders' Guild, Surlaenis Customs Exchange" note="Fish Buyer|Buyer" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Like a great melting pot of chaos and order, the Exchange is constantly filled with traders and dock workers, hauling in imports and trying to strike up profitable deals with other merchants.  Numbers are tossed through the air, handshakes are made, and crates are bought and sold -- all for the neverending, energizing grind of trying to seize the perfect bargain.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="316" />
  </node>
  <node id="318" name="The Traders' Guild, Private Dock">
    <description>Crates and barrels line the docks, all properly tied and marked as they wait for shipment abroad.  Dockhands and guild clerks mill about on the dock as they unload, sort and load -- their heavy boots making a rhythmic plodding sound on the wooden surface.  Wheeled carts are filled with goods and readied for the short trek up the ramp and into the Traders' Guild.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="319" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone ramp" destination="316" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="320" />
  </node>
  <node id="319" name="The Trader's Guild, Lower Deck" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Shadowed by the decks above and hanging over the deep, rolling ocean, the lower deck provides a delightful view of the sea.  Every now and then the tumbling waves crash against the dock and spray the deck with water, leaving it constantly damp and glistening.  Deck chairs have been lined up between the doors on the south side of the guildhall, keeping them fairly dry for those wishing to relax and enjoy the salty air.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="318" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden stairway" destination="321" />
  </node>
  <node id="320" name="The Traders' Guild, Surlaenis Shipping Office" note="Trader Shipping|Clerk" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Stacked crates fill the office, some of them towering up to the ceiling, each one clearly tagged and marked with such precision that only a third of the crates marked topside are upside down.  Nearly buried in the room is a small stand, filled with ship schedules and paperwork haphazardly stacked in chaotic piles in attempt to keep the area tidy.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="318" />
  </node>
  <node id="321" name="The Trader's Guild, Middle Deck" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Sandwiched between the other decks, the Middle Deck provides a sheltered view of the sea, far above the rolling waves.  Footsteps can often be heard from above and below, along with the occasional squeaking of the rope-service.  Tantalizing aromas of hot, freshly cooked meals fill the air any time the box to the rope-service passes by.</description>
    <position x="20" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb wooden stairway" destination="319" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb creaking stairs" destination="322" />
  </node>
  <node id="322" name="The Trader's Guild, Upper Deck" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The upper deck provides an unobstructed view of the sun and the sea.  Deck chairs provide residents with a comfortable vantage point from which they can take in the sun or enjoy the view while sipping drinks delivered by the rope-service.  To the north above the Mariner's Deck and surrounded by the rough, wooden awning of the roof is a lone balcony, where a narrow door, much like one designed for a ship, has been shut tight against unwanted visitors brave enough to try to get in via that route.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb creaking stairs" destination="321" />
  </node>
  <node id="323" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Kregkeirel Stable">
    <description>Whitewashed wooden stalls line the room, customized to suit the needs of the native creatures of Surlaenis.  Long-eared and camel-faced, the kregkeirels peek over their pens with bored interest, using their long necks to get a good view of the hay-filled surroundings.  Along one wall is a row of panniers, large woven baskets shaped to fit comfortably on the back of the beasts.  Stablehands come and go as they see to their work, sometimes stopping to offer the beasts an affectionate pat.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stable door" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="324" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Barn" note="Stable" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Weathered grey boards muffle the ever-present sound of the sea just over the dunes to the west, creating a cozy and secure haven from the elements.  From their individual stalls come the faint sounds of horses stamping their hooves or swishing their tails at a bothersome fly.  In one corner is a holding pen with several horses and ponies offered for sale.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="325" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="326" />
  </node>
  <node id="325" name="Aesry Surlaenis'a, Barn">
    <description>Carefully maintained horse stalls line both sides of a broad, straw-covered passage.  Pungent smells rise around you -- the sweetness of hay, the earthiness of manure, leather, oil, and sweat.  Bales of fresh straw are stacked along the far wall, ready for use.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="326" name="Tack and Feed Room" note="Tack|Feed" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Stableman Sy'ilar stands behind a rough counter formed by a broad board laid across two barrels.  Surrounding him are old trunks, boxes, and baskets holding all the many things needed to properly care for a horse, including feed, tack, and grooming tools.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="324" />
  </node>
  <node id="328" name="The Traders' Guild, Hallway">
    <description>Separated from the lower foyer by an open wooden rail, the narrow hallway provides an excellent view of the room below -- as well as an acoustical ear into any conversations carelessly spoken under the wide, vaulted ceiling.  Open glass doors to the west lead out onto an elevated wooden deck, while a large, finely carved door leads into the only room on the second floor, the guild leader's office.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="329" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb deobar staircase" destination="316" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go birch door" destination="330" />
  </node>
  <node id="329" name="The Traders' Guild, Mariners' Deck" note="Waiter" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Taking full advantage of the panoramic view of the docks, this finished wooden deck has been constructed upon the lower roof of the Guild Hall, looking out towards the sea.  Tables and chairs have been placed about the area, somewhat protected from the elements by a large wooden awning that overhangs the deck.  Elderly mariners and traders gather in groups around the tables, boasting of good deals or telling tales of dangers on the high seas as they puff on pipes and gaze down on the lights of the harbor.</description>
    <description>Taking full advantage of the panoramic view of the docks, this finished wooden deck has been constructed upon the lower roof of the Guild Hall, looking out towards the sea.  Tables and chairs have been placed about the area, somewhat protected from the elements by a large wooden awning that overhangs the deck.  Elderly mariners and traders gather in groups around the tables, boasting of good deals or telling tales of dangers on the high seas.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="328" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding stair" destination="337" />
  </node>
  <node id="330" name="The Traders' Guild, Seranda's Office" note="GL Trader|Seranda|RS Trader" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Memoirs gathered from countless journeys on the high seas are decoratively placed around the room, some clustered on small tables and some hanging along the walls.  A low cherrywood desk stands in front of an open window that faces the guild's private dock, providing a view of the activity.  Placed beside it is a high-backed wicker chair of local craftsmanship, filled with watersilk cushions and pillows, custom-made to suit the Guild Leader's taste and comfort.</description>
    <position x="0" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="328" />
  </node>
  <node id="331" name="Ranger Guild, Cave Mouth">
    <description>In the mouth of the cave, pale daylight flickers through the dangling roots like faeries at play.  An exquisitely carved mahogany case on the eastern wall looks oddly appropriate for the area.  Despite the recent furnishings, time marks this rocky shelter by the endless coat of moss that covers the rock surfaces.  A few scattered stones protrude from the brown sand underfoot.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-280" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wide crevice" destination="100" />
  </node>
  <node id="332" name="Ranger Guild, Tunnel">
    <description>Halfway through the torch-lined tunnel, the ceiling begins to bloat downward, forcing all but the smallest of races to stoop over.  Above a small, unattended fire pit, the contents of an iron pot slowly simmer.  Gradually the smell of onions, garlic, and some sort of fowl become recognizable, masking the otherwise dank, musty smell of the cave.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-300" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="333" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="331" />
  </node>
  <node id="333" name="Ranger Guild, Main Area" note="GL Ranger" color="#FF8000">
    <description>The low tunnel opens into a magnificent cathedral of stalagmites and stalactites veiled in a thin mist of moisture.  Amplified by the acoustics of the cavern, water droplets and their echoes perform a natural symphony.  To the north, a natural formation of rocks bridges the chasm.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="332" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go bridge" destination="334" />
  </node>
  <node id="334" name="Ranger Guild, Northern Cavern">
    <description>Mushrooms and colorful lichen anchor their roots throughout the crystal formations within the walls, which magnify the natural light in this area.  Small boulders allow the visitors to sit quietly and enjoy the beauty of the caves, while a natural spring offers the perfect solution to soothe aching bodies.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-320" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rocky bridge" destination="333" />
  </node>
  <node id="335" name="Fyne's Fishing Supplies" note="Fishing Supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Built out over the harbor on stilts, the floor of the shack is pierced in several places by open trap doors, each of which has a rope slung through it.  The walls have apparently been built of whatever driftwood washed ashore, and the sky is clearly visible in several spots through the loosely thatched roof.  Barrels filled with water are lined against the walls, emitting odors that only a shark could love.  On top of the largest barrel is perched a battered catalog.</description>
    <position x="60" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="336" name="Denison's Pub, Bolt Hole">
    <description>The small room is obviously designed for hiding persons or objects.  Occupants can peer out the door without being seen on this side of the hidden door.  The room is sparsely furnished with only a table and a few chairs.</description>
    <position x="80" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="313" />
  </node>
  <node id="337" name="The Traders' Guild, Kitchen">
    <description>Arranged in a fashion much like the galley of a ship, this private kitchen serves not only the private needs of the Guildleader and her staff but also provides the food and menus for the restaurant and rope-service.  Crates of goods line the back wall along with dangling dried meats and seasonal fruits, filling the kitchen with a constant, spicy aroma.  A chipped cat dish has been placed below the heavy wooden prep table in the center of the room.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding stair" destination="329" />
  </node>
  <node id="338" name="The Halasa Selhin, Main Deck" note="Map998_Transports.xml">
    <description>After years of varnishing, the main deck of the Halasa Selhin glistens like a becalmed sea.  Holding the crisp yards of her mainsail, the mainmast rises skyward to a dizzying height with the sweeping length of the boom spreading her canvas skirt to the wind.  Brightly colored pennants flutter from the halyards.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="20" z="0" />
  </node>
  <label text="Moss Meys">
    <position x="540" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blood Wolves">
    <position x="320" y="-170" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Snow Goblins (3)">
    <position x="560" y="-330" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Sea Caves">
    <position x="110" y="-190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Frostweavers">
    <position x="250" y="-370" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Snow Goblins (1)">
    <position x="370" y="-210" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Aesry Town">
    <position x="660" y="-150" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dock">
    <position x="-20" y="30" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Nipoh Oshu">
    <position x="190" y="-250" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Nightweaver Unyns">
    <position x="60" y="-110" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Nightreaver Unyns">
    <position x="130" y="30" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Nightstalker Unyns">
    <position x="350" y="-220" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Elba Darvagers">
    <position x="380" y="90" z="1" />
  </label>
  <label text="Bull Sharks">
    <position x="-40" y="80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Snow Goblins (2)">
    <position x="450" y="-370" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>
