<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Basalt Isle and Jeihrem's Barrow" id="90f">
  <node id="1" name="Basalt Isle, Cliffs of Ruin">
    <description>The harsh sound of the ocean waves breaking on bare rock echoes through the chasm, and the towering basalt makes strange geometric shapes that look ready to give way at any moment.  Huge basalt boulders are scattered here and there, indicating that a few chunks have already fallen.  A few stubborn scrubby bushes cling to either side of the cavern walls, their thin branches parched and bleached by the salty sea air.</description>
    <position x="20" y="29" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone dock" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Basalt Isle, Stone Dock" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>The roar of the ocean waves constantly fills the air, and the foamy saltwater coats everything with a tangible dampness.  Evenly spaced stone pillars offer a crude place to tie a boat, their metal hooks badly rusted from the salt-filled air.  Sheer cliffs made from thousands of basalt columns rise tall at the water's edge, their outlines shrouded by the darkness of the night.</description>
    <description>Waves constantly whip at the edges of the desolate stone dock, occasionally sending splashes of foamy saltwater high into the air.  Evenly spaced stone pillars offer a crude place to tie a boat, their metal hooks badly rusted from the salt-filled air.  Sheer cliffs made from thousands of basalt columns rise tall at the water's edge, their jagged shapes standing tall against the battering waves.</description>
    <position x="0" y="29" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow gap" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Basalt Isle, Cliffs of Ruin">
    <description>Towering basalt pillars interlock tightly with each other, forming huge cliffs that rise tall on either side of the narrow gap in columns of dark grey and black.  Broken bits of rubble line the bottom of the chasm, the scattered pieces forming geometrical patterns in the sharply angled ravine.  Nothing grows here, the desolated environment not even affording purchase for plants or insects.</description>
    <position x="0" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Basalt Isle, Steep Approach">
    <description>Enormous basalt columns hang toothlike at this incline, worn away at the bottom by erosion and leaving the bottoms of the geometrical pillars exposed and jagged.  Small clumps of moss and grass cling to the sides and underside of the basalt columns, somewhat sheltered here from the harsh wind and salty air.  The cracked path is quite steep, wending its way between the jagged cliffs.</description>
    <position x="20" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Basalt Isle, Steep Approach">
    <description>Darkness makes the wide hexagonal columns rather treacherous to traverse, the natural stairway offering little purchase or protection against a fall.  The dim silhouettes of pine trees crown the top of the basalt cliffs, standing silent sentinel over the crack between the pillars.  The night wind constantly blows through the chasm, howling its mournful dirge to the ruined island.</description>
    <description>Wide hexagonal columns of basalt form a natural stairway, steeply inclining from the direction of the sea and following the crack in the basalt pillars.  Tall pine trees crown the top of the chasm's cliffs, most severely withered but still surviving in the harsh environment.  Wind constantly blows through the chasm, making strange sounds that sound unnatural and otherworldly.</description>
    <position x="40" y="-11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go dark cave" destination="76" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Basalt Isle, Harrowed Chasm">
    <description>Basalt columns bend and fold at odd angles, molded at a diagonal by some enormous geological pressure so that the top-most layer has become nearly horizontal.  Bits of rough crab grass grow here and there between the harsh grey stones, tiny oases in between the dry and lifeless desolation.</description>
    <position x="60" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb basalt cliff" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Basalt Isle, Harrowed Chasm">
    <description>The chasm forms a dead end, surrounded on most sides by the rough tablerock basalt.  Rough wind blows through the chasm, whispering a thousand secrets in a language understood by none.  Huge holes in the basalt cliffs above are marred with dry rusty streaks, indicating the odd stream of water once managed to trickle through and wet the stone before draining away.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb basalt cliff" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Basalt Isle, Stained Plateau">
    <description>Huge streaks of dark rust mar the top of the weathered plateau, the rock worn nearly smooth by the endless ages of erosion by the salty wind.  The sound of the ocean waves roaring against the island's edge can be heard coming from far below the plateau.  Any usual night sounds are all but nonexistent, making the island feel barren and lifeless.</description>
    <description>Huge streaks of brownish rust mar the top of the weathered plateau, the rock worn nearly smooth by the endless ages of erosion by the salty wind.  Dark and dangerous water can be seen far below the plateau's edge, churned continuously by the rough waves in this part of the ocean.  No birds fly through the air or sing their songs, making the island feel barren and lifeless.</description>
    <position x="80" y="29" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb basalt cliff" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Basalt Isle, Stained Plateau">
    <description>Odd geometrical patterns form this bleak and arid plateau, with occasional bits of weedy foliage sticking up between the rocks of the natural formation.  Rusty markings of varying age litter the ground randomly, permanently soaked into the flat surface of the bleary stone.  The air is very dry despite the salty spray from far below, smelling of metallic dust mixed with the sharp scent of the sea.</description>
    <position x="100" y="49" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Basalt Isle, Stained Plateau">
    <description>Occasional thin, withered trees grow at the eastern edge of the wide plateau, affording a small amount of respite from exposure to the elements.  Hairline cracks in the stone are stained an orangeish red with many layers of rust, settled in vague spiderweb patterns.  The trail slopes steeply upward to the north to lead to a small overlook, while another drops dramatically to the east to follow the treacherous cliffside.</description>
    <position x="120" y="29" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Basalt Isle, Overlook">
    <description>The entire island is visible from this small overlook, the jagged basalt spines jutting from the sea to the east while huge cracks run through the island's center to create dark, gaping chasms.  An ominous-looking castle can be seen far to the west at the top of a towering cliff, while a small fishing village huddles far below it.  Very little greenery pierces the flat grey landscape, and the sea appears harsh and unforgiving at every horizon.</description>
    <position x="120" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Basalt Isle, Towering Pillars">
    <description>Dark grey spines frame the eastern edge of the steep cliffside path, following the edge of the plateau and forming a measure of protection against falling.  Jagged rocks jut from the ocean below, splitting the roiling waves and creating a calmer area.  The silhouette of a rocky reef rises out in the far distance, with two visible shipwrecks jutting their ruined masts at odd angles against the dark sea.</description>
    <description>Dark grey spines frame the eastern edge of the steep cliffside path, following the edge of the plateau and forming a measure of protection against falling.  Jagged rocks jut from the ocean below, coated thick with red algae and splitting the roiling waves.  A rocky reef rises out in the far distance, two distinct shipwrecks splintered apart on their treacherous edge.</description>
    <position x="140" y="49" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Basalt Isle, Stained Plateau">
    <description>The sheer basalt cliff drops off to the west, forming a completely vertical drop to the rocky ocean hundreds of feet below.  Random piles of broken columnar basalt litter the plateau here, resembling chopped stone logs from a nightmare's forest.  Harsh salty wind blows constantly through the air and wears the stone surface clean, ensuring nothing grows on this side of the plateau.</description>
    <position x="80" y="69" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Basalt Isle, Towering Pillars">
    <description>Strange rock formations make up the cliff wall, needle-like basalt columns interspersed with harder crystals and softer limestone.  Runoff from rainwater has formed a sunken basin to the west, while the rocky trail follows the cliff to the southwest.  Huge fang-like rock formations jut directly from the ocean to the east, rendering the terrain there unnavigable and suicidally dangerous.</description>
    <position x="160" y="69" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Basalt Isle, Sunken Basin">
    <description>A small pool of stagnant water has formed in a small indentation in the cliffside here, smelling heavily of algae.  Small cracks in the pool's surface are filled with foam, spiderwebbing across the dark water in a vivid contrast.  Strange fuzzy shapes poke through the surface of the water, unmoving but playing tricks with vision in the night's darkness.</description>
    <description>A small pool of stagnant water has formed in a small indentation in the cliffside here, slicked thick with red algae.  White foam cracks in its surface show the water's heavy salinity, allowing the slick scum to thrive in this wet basin high in the rocks.  Rocks and boulders poke through the sludge, their surfaces coated a rusty crimson from the heavily infested water.</description>
    <position x="140" y="69" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Basalt Isle, Desolate Beach">
    <description>The relentless pounding of the ocean waves has slowly worn away a small portion of the cliffside into a thin strip of dark grey sand, forming a poor excuse of a beach.  Scattered boulders and large stones litter the sand here and there, many worn smooth by the pounding ocean waves.  An eerie quiet reigns over this patch of desolation, the air completely empty of the usual seabirds.</description>
    <position x="140" y="89" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go decaying dock" destination="48" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Basalt Isle, Desolate Beach">
    <description>The skeletal remains of a large beached animal lie washed up on the sand, picked clean and bleached by the harsh environment.  Eddies of salty sand pool around it in a slow and uncaring manner, preserving the creature's death throes in the salty brine.  The towering basalt cliffs rise sharply at the northern edge of the beach, dwarfing the creature's remains and making them seem small and insignificant.</description>
    <position x="120" y="109" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Basalt Isle, Desolate Beach">
    <description>At the western end of the lifeless grey beach is a gaping maw of a cavern, carved into the basalt columns by the sea's relentless waves.  The jagged interior is pitch black inside, greedily swallowing all light that enters it.  Water rushes into the huge opening with each wave, then slowly drains back out again, undulating in dangerous swells, though a thin strip of sand allow safe passage at its very edge.</description>
    <position x="100" y="109" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cave" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Basalt Isle, Salt Deposits" note="salt golems">
    <description>This portion of the island has sloped into a vague bowl-like shape, framed with spiked points to the east while huge basalt columns rise tall to the west.  Harsh white deposits of salt cover the area almost completely, contrasting the dark grey rocks with large rectangular crystals.  Jagged points rise here and there among the scattered stones, though the majority have broken free and cover the ground in a relatively even layer of rubble.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb basalt cliff" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Basalt Isle, Salt Deposits">
    <description>Crusty layers of salt thoroughly coat the walls and floor of this partially sheltered side of the basin, save for a single chunk of raw obsidian lying on its side.  The black rock is a stark contrast, its surface worn almost mirror smooth by the last eddies of ocean wind.  Deposits of white crust the boulder's base, as if threatening to swallow this last holdout and make the landscape uniform.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Basalt Isle, Needle Passage">
    <description>The ocean meets the edge of the island here, dark pillars continuing out further into the water but gradually disappearing into the murky black waters.  Piled rock forms a safe walkway across the hazardous terrain, made from loose rubble.  The dim silhouette of a reef can be seen edging the island, barely visible pieces of wood marking a splintered shipwreck in the darkness.</description>
    <description>The ocean meets the edge of the island here, the jagged pillars continuing out further into the water but gradually disappearing beneath the waves further out.  Piled rock forms a safe walkway across the hazardous terrain, made from loose rubble.  A reef can be seen edging the island and only occasionally breaking the waterline, splintered ship pieces proving passage to the island as very treacherous.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-71" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go path" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Basalt Isle, Needle Passage">
    <description>A single huge, toppled pillar of basalt lies on its side in among shattered grey stone, providing safe passage through an otherwise treacherous terrain.  The ground underneath the pillar is thoroughly soaked, the occasional waves from the island's edge finding their way through and dampening the broken stones.  Dark red moss speckles the underside of the column, thriving on the salt-saturated water.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Basalt Isle, Needle Passage">
    <description>Runnels of salty water have formed shallow pools, fresh water mingling with the salt deposits and becoming trapped between the jagged rocks.  A few plants and beds of moss tenuously make their home in the patches of soil, speckling the ground here and there.  Several of the grey needle-like pillars have been forcefully toppled and shattered, forming a makeshift way through the treacherous terrain.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Basalt Isle, Salt Deposits">
    <description>The island's huge basalt cliffs shelter the salt-crusted basin, trapping the sea's deposits in large crystal formation and trapping eddies of brown and red in among the pale grey stone.  Jagged rocks make passage here treacherous, jutting from the bedrock and worn into sharp shapes by the harsh wind from the east.  Loose, broken rubble lies underfoot, underscoring the desolation and hostility of the island.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Basalt Isle, Salt Deposits">
    <description>A break in the jagged rocks offers a clear view of the ocean, though further passage is impossible due to a sheer cliff dropping a hundred feet down to the ocean waves washing through a thousand points of jutting rock.  Salty wind constantly whips in from the ocean, amplified by the shape of the strange rock formations.  Reef formations can be seen far in the distance out over the ocean, offering glimpses of a shipwreck trapped by the treacherous rocks.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Basalt Isle, Field of Rubble">
    <description>Crumbled stones worn somewhat smooth lie in scattered piles, indicating the vague outlines of what used to be stone buildings.  A few are stripped bare down to their foundations, revealing shallow basements and storm cellars.  A small number of hardy trees edge the field, and the occasional bit of foliage pokes up through the grey stones.</description>
    <position x="380" y="-71" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow path" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Basalt Isle, Field of Rubble">
    <description>A lone, roofless stone hut stands defiant against the continual assault of the inclement weather, sturdy and nearly intact despite its age.  Other ruins line the otherwise flat field, most of their stones blackened and reduced to their ruined foundations.  Scraggly trees poke through the edges of the field, though seems to grow here, only a few hardy plants continuing to valiantly make the attempt.</description>
    <position x="340" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Basalt Isle, Field of Rubble">
    <description>Ruined foundations surround what was once a town square, its paved cobblestone haphazardly shattered and broken.  A once-noble statue stands in the center of a fountain, completely missing its upper half and its historical plaque thoroughly defaced.  The fountain is long since dry and desiccated, though small marble benches next to it are largely intact.</description>
    <position x="320" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Basalt Isle, Field of Rubble">
    <description>Dead, skeletal trees jut here and there with their fingerlike branches intertwined in a nightmare embrace, indicating that the area was once a flourishing park.  However, all life has been violently scoured clean from the area, only a thick dusting of dark ash remaining of anything once living.  Small rocks cover the landscape almost completely, sown there with a determined maliciousness and preventing new life from taking root.</description>
    <position x="300" y="-11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Entrance">
    <description>The muddy path into the town is seldom used, as if few ever leave this small fishing village.  Wooden buildings line the streets, haphazardly nailed together without much care or concern, and over half of them looking quite abandoned.  Racks of half-preserved fish stand drying on hooks, the cloying odor ever pervasive in the air.</description>
    <description>The still of night blankets the quiet fishing village, and the fishy scent of smoke from burning oil lanterns drifts through the air.  Most of the wooden buildings stand completely dark and abandoned, although a few are lit from the interior with the muted sound of conversation coming from within.  Racks of half-preserved fish stand drying on hooks, the cloying odor mingling with the smell from the lanterns.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden gate" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Communion Circle" note="stairway of bone">
    <description>Barely functional and long past their prime, several haphazard shanties crowd each side of the street.  Simple burlap clothes hang out to slowly dry on fishing lines strung between several of the shanties, clearly repurposed for the task.  The smell of cooking fish fills the air, wafting on the salty ocean breeze.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go round hut" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" hidden="True" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Cobblestone Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>Cobblestone made from flat pieces of hexagonal basalt lines the modest path, giving this part of town a slightly more upscale look than the dirt path of the main village.  Mostly bare trees line both sides of the path, vying for what sunlight they can get, and wide patches of crag grass dot the landscape.  A wooden post driven into the ground marks the crossroads, indicating the path as Cobblestone Way.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Cobblestone Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>A wide wooden fence made mostly from repurposed fishing barrels surrounds each small house.  Each home has its own small yard, although the cobblestone road still seems somewhat crowded in.  The foliage is somewhat thicker here, allowed to flourish from frequent and careful watering.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="34" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Cobblestone Way" color="#00FFFF">
    <description>The small cobblestone path abruptly ends at a strange statue carved from a single block of obsidian.  Dark and somewhat macabre, the figure is rather abstract, though its eyes are piercing and have a drawing, otherworldly quality toward them.  Small wicker baskets of dried fish line the base of the statue, apparently left there as offerings.</description>
    <position x="280" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Communion Circle">
    <description>Open barrels half filled with dried and salted fish sit between the makeshift buildings, each one left incomplete and exposed to the dry salty air.  Huge stacks of shipping crates line both sides of the dirt road here, although some have been repurposed and broken down as building material.  An unguarded gap between huts leads directly to a small ledge over the ocean, serving as the village's dumping ground.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-31" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden hut" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Communion Circle">
    <description>The dirt road stops at a long wooden dock, very well kept in comparison to the rest of the run-down town.  A small boat is tied to this end of it, though it looks cracked and worn with age, barely seaworthy and staying afloat.  Quiet pervades the mood of the village here, the loudest ambient sound coming from the lapping of the ocean waves underneath the dock.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go basalt hut" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Communion Circle" note="zenriel">
    <description>The dirt road abruptly ends at a long wooden dock, built out over the ocean in a sturdy manner uncharacteristic to the rest of the village.  Long fishing lines drag out into the sea from poles anchored to the dock, left mostly unattended and uncared for.  The vast ocean stretches out to the horizon, broken only by the occasional rock jutting from the island's reef.</description>
    <position x="220" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stone building" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Communion Circle">
    <description>A dark hole in the ground serves as the town well, fed by a small stream that is one of the few places on the island to get fresh water.  The dirt road wends its way through the spaces between the wooden buildings, narrowing in an almost claustrophobic manner.  Every building seems dry and weather-worn, the old planks thoroughly cured by the salty wind.</description>
    <position x="260" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go general store" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Repair" note="repair|falistenal" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Standing in the center of this small wooden hut is a stone ironworking furnace, with a tapered chimney leading up through a hole in the roof.  Nearby a wooden table and stone counter lie ready, while several mostly repaired goods hang from pegs on the walls.  The tools spread out in the small shop are repurposed or crude, though together they are sufficient enough for the task.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Gem Shop" note="gem shop|gems" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Made entirely from the flat grey stone that gives the island its name, this small hut appears much older and sturdier than the rest of the town.  A small glass window in the western wall looks out toward the sea, and a long stone counter takes up most of the northern half of the room.  Built into the back wall is a tiny safe, clearly inadequate for the task of storing precious gems.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-11" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Furrier" note="furrier|bundles|arakand" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The long stone walls and floor appear to all be carved from a single piece of flat grey rock, making the building quite sturdy and able to withstand the ravages of time.  Several round porthole windows look out onto both the village and the sea.  In the center of the room is a large stone counter, piled up high with furs and leathers of varying quality.</description>
    <position x="200" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Bank" note="bank|teller" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Made mostly from squarish rocks spackled together and covered with a slanted wooden roof, the interior of this building is a bit larger than most of the others in the village.  Several iron boxes are set out on a wooden table along with several hand-written lists, indicating who has deposited or withdrawn what.  The building's interior exudes the faint smell of fish, coming from some unknown source.</description>
    <position x="220" y="29" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Exchange" note="exchange" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Tucked into this corner of the bank is the Exchange, consisting of three separate iron boxes laid out on a table for making change.  No light penetrates the roof of this windowless building, most of the illumiation coming from greasy oil lanterns hanging on the walls.  A small painting hangs on the eastern wall, depicting an enormous otherworldly monstrosity in the middle of devouring a ship.</description>
    <position x="230" y="29" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, General Store" note="general" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Several round makeshift tables are set out on the plain dirt floor of this modestly-sized building, selling both basic goods and slightly fancier items.  Hooks hanging from the walls display both simple and somewhat more elaborate clothing, both appearing imported.  Small windows let in light from outside, and a lantern of fish oil hanging from a rafter provides some extra illumination.</description>
    <position x="280" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go general store" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="General Store, Back Room" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Hard rations and a large number of fishing supplies are set up in this small room, bait filling up several barrels while fishing poles hang on hooks.  Lines are spread out on a long table made from wooden planks.  A wooden bench offers a place to sit, appearing to be often used by fishermen tying bait to their lines.  Tiny mice occasionally scurry among the bottom of the barrels, protected from persecution by the strong hand of ennui that blankets this town.</description>
    <position x="290" y="9" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Carousel" note="carousel|vaults">
    <description>The interior of this oddly round hut is cut neatly in half with a large wooden wall, dividing the Carousel's booths from the main entrance.  Gears, pulleys, and weights hang from the ceiling, forming the mechanism that drives the carousel.  An air of tension lingers in the air, as if no one in the building actually wants to be there.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="85" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go registration desk" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Carousel Desk" note="lost and found" color="#00FF00">
    <description>A long wooden desk spans the width of the western wall.  Crude oil lanterns hang from the ceiling, and the floor behind the desk is covered in an ornate carpet that looks rather out of place.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-61" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Basalt Isle, Decaying Dock" note="dock" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Originally made from sturdy wood, the dock here is splintered and ruined in places, and a large boulder has smashed through most of it near the bank.  Despite this, some of the structure appears somewhat useable, with a few sturdy pillars holding fast between the splintered boardwalk.  The water is relatively calm around the dock, providing a respite from the churning waves that plague the rest of the island.</description>
    <position x="140" y="109" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go desolate beach" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Basalt Isle, Shattered Cavern">
    <description>Huge and nearly pitch black, the vast majority of this cavern is filled with treacherous and unpassable water, the echoes from the waves resonating through the oversized hollow.  A narrow basalt ledge allows just enough room to sit or stand comfortably.  The underside of hexagonal basalt columns poke randomly through the darkness that shrouds the high ceiling, giving a glimpse of the island's massive weight above.</description>
    <position x="100" y="89" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go mouth" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Stairway of Bone">
    <description>Natural basalt columns form the strange hexagonal staircase, which curves up steeply toward the lonely cliff at the northwestern end of the island.  Fastened to the outer edge of the stairway is a grim railing, crafted almost entirely from the bleached bones of creatures both large and small.  Small hollows in the basalt cliff hold skulls, each one mounted on a miniature pedestal carved into the rock to ensure its permanent residence.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-62" z="1" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Stairway of Bone">
    <description>The basalt staircase closely follows the curve of the cliff, the bone railing made from femurs far too large to be from any of the mortal races.  Small skulls and teeth lie scattered along the side of the stairway, grinning with a macabre and fleshless intensity.  Ocean spray flies into the air from far below, tinging the air with salt.</description>
    <position x="260" y="-82" z="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Stairway of Bone">
    <description>Darkness shrouds the space between the vertical cliff walls, the macabre fleshless faces of skeletons grinning out from the darkness.  Pitch blackness otherwise pervades either side of the basalt stairway, dead-ending at a massive wrought iron gate that stands slightly open and is lit with deep red burning torches.  Clearly visible in the torchlight is the stylized symbol of a slashed double hex enclosed with a circle, the crest of the lich Jeihrem.</description>
    <description>Vertical cliff walls on either side are lined with whole skeletons, standing grimly at attention and staring forward with blind, fleshless grins.  The path on either side of the basalt stairway is somewhat narrow, dead-ending at a massive wrought iron gate that stands slightly open and shows a tall castle-like manor behind it.  Decorating the gate is a stylized symbol of a slashed double hex enclosed with a circle, the crest of the lich Jeihrem.</description>
    <position x="240" y="-102" z="1" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Entrance">
    <description>Wrought iron fences close off meticulously kept lawns on either side of the walkway leading to the huge manor, keeping visitors confined to a narrow path.  Large buttresses on its ramparts hold macabre statues of otherworldly creatures, reveling in the celebration of the profane.  A coppery tinge clings to the salty air, lending a sickening aspect to the confinement that is abated only the the open sky above.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-122" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron gate" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double door " destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hall of Blood">
    <description>The grand hall of the manor spares no expense in opulence, with each wall elegantly covered with paneling depicting images born from harrowing dreams.  Dark grey marble shot through with veins of red makes up the floor, softened somewhat by a blood-red rug that runs the length of the hallway.  A muted crimson glow comes from in the ceiling above, illuminating the sinister art.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-122" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double door " destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hall of Flesh">
    <description>Enormous leathern tapestries hang over the marble walls, reaching nearly to where the arched ceiling begins high overhead.  Each canvas is mostly blank, the paintings started but soon abandoned before much was completed.  An elaborate carpeted stairwell leads sharply downward, but is blocked by an impenetrable mass of seething darkness.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-142" z="1" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hall of Flesh">
    <description>Huge leathern tapestries hang on the walls of this arched-ceiling hallway, painted in vivid and unsparing detail.  Each one depicts a macabre scene, from a hoard of ravaging undead to a tall man tearing open a hole in reality itself.  Stairs leading upward are blocked off with a thick pane of glass marked with a crimson rune, denying passage to the upper parts of the manor.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-142" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hall of Blood">
    <description>Elaborate silver decorations on each wall depict a highly abstract form of artwork, forming vague patterns that play with the imagination.  The metallic decor is tinged a slight reddish color, stained with rusty markings from fluid that has dripped through holes in the ceiling.  A few of the dried droplets have reached the bare marble floor, which is streaked with veins of crimson that reach like branches through the expansive hall.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-122" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hall of Life">
    <description>Dozens of silver channels set in the grey marble walls and floors are capped with strips of clear glass, revealing a black, foul-looking ichor that occasionally pulsates as if vaguely alive.  The viscous solution flows from somewhere above and appears to be slowly oozing toward the east, disappearing into unknown channels deeper in the floor and walls.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-102" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hall of Life">
    <description>Potted plants and small trays of soil line the marble floor in a neat and orderly fashion, all of them blossoming with flowers or vines.  Small intendations in the walls hold clinging vinses that support other plants between them, forming an artistic tapestry of living greenery.  Many of the specimens exhibit an unnatural and unhealthy amount of growth, extra vines and branches extending through holes in the ceiling to the unseen room above.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-102" z="1" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="58" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Serene Garden">
    <description>Pallid night blooming flowers seem to almost glow in juxtaposition with the darkened foliage, their ghostly shapes visible in the dim light.  Crystalline panes form the ceiling overhead, letting in dim light from the night sky.  Lush and low groudcover carpets the floor, while the muted smell of flowers comes from raised beds of smooth rock.</description>
    <description>Entirely obscured by climbing vines, the walls here have become a living tapestry of clematis and honeysuckle.  Crystalline panes form the ceiling above, held fast within wrought iron frames.  Lush and low growing groundcover carpets the floor, leaving visible only a circular path of marble shot through with intersecting stony lines.  Raised beds carved from smooth, virid rock allow for a tiered series of plantings with exquisitely large blossoms overhanging their edges to form a cascade of color.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-82" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go archway" destination="59" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Chapel of Bone">
    <description>Hundreds of bleached white skulls strung into intricate designs rise up from each corner in fleshless grins.  Strands of skulls follow the vaulted arches of this small chapel and culminate at an enormous bone chandelier hanging from the ceiling.  The arrangement is lit with twelve skulls topped with a burning candles, illuminating the rows of understated pews below.  Carefully aligned arm bones on the front of a dark altar form an enormous and nearly solid crest, the mawlike double hex of the necromancer Jeihrem.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-82" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door " destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Jeihrem's Throne" note="gl necromancer" color="#FF8000">
    <description>Rising at the end of this long arched hallway is a dais, set with a throne made from pure obsidian and carved at sharp angles.  A huge circular window stained in murky tinges of purple and black rises behind the dais, allowing filtered daylight light to stream in from outside and shroud the throne in strange and eerie patterns.  Black iron-clad figures armed with halberds stand at attention on each side of the hall, silently guarding their master with the unmoving stillness that death brings.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-122" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Jeihrem's Manor, West Laboratory" note="w laboratory">
    <description>Brightly lit with mulitple gaethzen orbs set in each corner of the room, the laboratory is fully stocked with several metallic tables and counters.  Numerous tools are set out neatly and ready for use, while a glass cabinet is filled with powders, liquids, washcloths and other supplies.  A small stove rests against the northern wall, set up with glassware and ready to use for mixing chemicals.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-162" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go frost door" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Secluded Library" note="necromancer library|necro library">
    <description>Very little light enters the dusty library, the only source a dim lantern that sits on a narrow return desk.  Silhouettes of bookcases are visible in the darkness, each one lined with dark leather books.  It's quite apparent that the library is mostly neglected, although a few chairs and tables in the center of the room seem like they get at least some use.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-162" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Jeihrem's Manor, East Laboratory" note="e laboratory">
    <description>Harshly lit with mulitple gaethzen orbs set in each corner of the room, the laboratory is fully stocked with several metallic tables and counters.  Numerous tools are set out neatly and ready for use, while a glass cabinet is filled with powders, liquids, washcloths and other supplies.  A small stove rests against the northern wall, set up with glassware and ready to use for mixing chemicals.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-162" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go frost door" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway">
    <description>Cold and clinical, the hallway is lit with harsh gaethzen lights and is painted a plain, almost blinding white.  Not a speck of dust remains in the area, which is clean to the point of being sterile.  The air is extremely cold, though dry, and narrow vents in the walls constantly circulate it around.</description>
    <position x="200" y="-202" z="1" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="69" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="70" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway" note="kaitsen|risen supplies" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Cold and clinical, the hallway is lit with harsh gaethzen lights and is painted a plain, almost blinding white.  Not a speck of dust remains in the area, which is clean to the point of being sterile.  The air is extremely cold, though dry, and narrow vents in the walls constantly circulate it around.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-202" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="71" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="72" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Cold Laboratory, Hallway">
    <description>Cold and clinical, the hallway is lit with harsh gaethzen lights and is painted a plain, almost blinding white.  Not a speck of dust remains in the area, which is clean to the point of being sterile.  The air is extremely cold, though dry, and narrow vents in the walls constantly circulate it around.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-202" z="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open steel door" destination="73" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open iron door" destination="74" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="210" y="-217" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="70" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="190" y="-217" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="71" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="190" y="-187" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="72" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
    <position x="170" y="-187" z="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="73" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
   <position x="170" y="-217" z="1" />
   <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="74" name="Cold Laboratory, Work Station">
    <description>The air is quite chilly, cold enough to leave ice crystals with every breath.  A medium-sized and rather functional laboratory is set up, with a central marble table as the main feature.  Nearby, a row of cold lockers is designed to store specimens for later use, and a tray of very clean tools is set up near the table.</description>
   <position x="150" y="-217" z="1" />
   <arc exit="go" move="open door" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="75" name="Jeihrem's Manor, Hidden Glade" note="cre|necromancer depart" color="#400040">
    <description>Wire trellises arch upward to meet overhead and are twined with numerous climbing vines, creating a small patch of garden completely surrounded by foliage.  The ground is carpeted with a thick layer of grass, peppered with tiny yellow flowers that give off a strong and heady smell.  A small obsidian statue stands in the back of the tiny glade, stylized to resemble pitch black flames.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-82" z="1" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="60" />
  </node>
  <node id="76" name="Watcher's Cave, Entrance">
    <description>The stairwell exiting the cave winds between stalagmites and stalagtites, and a single shaft of sunlight pours through the dust and illuminates the far wall, revealing a bas relief.  Below the display against the wall rests a bleached ox's skull.  The tunnel branches to the east and west, bending into shadows deeper into the cave.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-131" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go stairwell" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="77" name="Watcher's Cave, Tunnel">
    <description>Loose gravel crunches underfoot, and the rough stone walls seem to absorb the available light.  Gaethzen shards line the stone walls, but shadows dominate here.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-151" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="78" />
  </node>
  <node id="78" name="Watcher's Cave, Open Cavern">
    <description>A western wall is vaguely visible, clustered with gaethzen shards softly illuminating a rough hewn tunnel entrance.  Loose gravel extends from the tunnel, scattered across the smooth ground.  The northern wall arcs gently backwards and extends upward into darkness above.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-151" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="77" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="79" name="Watcher's Cave, Open Cavern">
    <description>The northern and eastern walls are vaguely visible, clustered with gaethzen shards which softly illuminate the rough rock.  A few scattered rocks are sprawled over the otherwise smooth floor, minute hairline fractures extending from the south.  The walls arc gently backwards, and extend upward into the darkness above, a featureless and impenetrable gloom overhead.  Infrequent pinpoints of red flicker above and to the south, and a faint breeze stirs the area, carrying faint whispers which echo around the cavernous space.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-151" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="80" name="Watcher's Cave, Tunnel">
    <description>The carved tunnel is widely bored, the ground and walls nearly featureless and smooth.  Gaethzen shards spiral around the tunnel, looping from floor to wall to ceiling and back down again.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-111" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="76" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="81" />
  </node>
  <node id="81" name="Watcher's Cave, Open Cavern">
    <description>A western wall is vaguely visible, clustered with gaethzen shards softly illuminating a widely bored tunnel entrance.  The smooth stone ground is bare and featureless.  The southern wall arcs gently backwards and extends upward into the darkness above.</description>
    <position x="120" y="-111" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="80" />
  </node>
  <node id="82" name="Watcher's Cave, Open Cavern">
    <description>A southern wall is vaguely visible, clustered with gaethzen shards softly illuminating a narrow tunnel entrance to the southeast.  The stone floor ripples oddly, faint cracks spidering chaotically.  The cavern ceiling is blanketed in darkness, a featureless and impenetrable gloom overhead.  Occasional pinpoints of red flicker above, and faint whispers echo around the cavernous space.</description>
    <position x="140" y="-111" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="81" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="79" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="78" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="83" name="Watcher's Cave, Narrow Passage">
    <description>The walls are closer here, speckled with gaethzen shards, and though the ceiling remains out of view in the gloom above, the echoes of both subtle movements and the growing intensity of the whispers that now suffuse this space make it feel ever closer.  Periodic pinpoints of red flash above, lingering briefly before fading into the darkness, and a gentle breeze flows from the northeast.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-91" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="82" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="84" />
  </node>
  <node id="84" name="Watcher's Cave, Shattered Altar">
    <description>The ground seems to fall away in all directions save the southwest, and a heavy gloom blankets the area.  Disorienting threats and promises echo from every direction, and in the darkness, regular slits of red slowly open to reveal eyes with distorted pupils which linger a moment before blinking shut and vanishing.  A shattered altar rests at the center of the end of the pathway, gaethzen shards placed in a ring illuminating the centerpiece of the this space.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-111" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="83" />
  </node>
  <node id="85" name="Jeihrem's Barrow, Rundmolen Post Office" note="mail|post office" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Standing in the corner of this hut is a low stone counter made from cut stone blocks.  Vast, countless rows of differently sized shelves are behind the counter, and complex Dwarven mechanisms can be heard as they rearrange the package-covered storage.  Clerks shuffle endlessly back and forth between the counters and shelving as they assist patrons with their packaging and mailing needs.</description>
    <position x="220" y="-51" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <label text="salt golems">
    <position x="100" y="-21" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="banyakeas">
    <position x="30" y="79" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="banyakeas">
    <position x="350" y="-31" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="telga orek">
    <position x="150" y="-151" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Jeihrem's Barrow">
    <position x="245" y="23" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dock">
    <position x="150" y="109" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="to Ratha">
    <position x="-10" y="39" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Jeihrem's Manor">
    <position x="100" y="-70" z="1" />
  </label>
</zone>