<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="MT Prize Wings" id="599">
  <node id="1" name="Foyer" note="Foyer" color="#FF00FF">
    <description>Subdued lighting illuminates the tasteful wooden paneling of the room while a bevy of overstuffed furniture provides comfortable seating for those contemplating weighty choices.  Thick plush carpets in a myriad of hues cover the floor, almost totally obscuring the pale wooden planks of the flooring.  Around the walls, a number of colored archways contain magical portals that, when open, allow access to the prize rooms beyond.  A large set of double doors allows access to rooms devoted to dispenser activities while a round opening leads to the area devoted to workshops for alterations.</description>
    <description>Lighting illuminates the room which has carpets covering the floors.  A number of colored archways contain magic portals that, when open, allow access to the prize rooms beyond.  A set of double doors allows access to the dispensers while a round opening leads to the alteration area.</description>
    <position x="60" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go round opening" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go yellow portal" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green portal" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue-tiled entrance" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go return portal" destination="999" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go purple archway" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red archway" destination="1000" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Dispenser Hall" note="Dispenser Hall|raffles" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Centered in the middle of the floor, a luxurious carpet covers the polished wooden floor underneath a cut-crystal chandelier.  Oak paneling covers the walls while pale ecru plaster coats the spaces between the coffered ceiling.  A few leather armchairs provide seating for those needing time to contemplate their choices.</description>
    <description>A thick carpet covers the floor of the oak-paneled room.</description>
    <position x="40" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go double doors" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Alteration Suite, Lobby" note="Alteration Suite|alterations" color="#00FF00">
    <description>Elegantly carved and upholstered furniture adds the perfect touch to the sophisticated but understated luxury of this well-appointed waiting area.  A polished diamondwood buffet displaying a range of snacks is set against one wall while the chairs and sofas are grouped together to allow for quiet conversation between waiting patrons.</description>
    <description>A diamondwood buffet sets out snacks while chairs and sofas provide seating for the waiting patrons.</description>
    <position x="60" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go round opening" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glittery curtain" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ivy-colored curtain" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowy curtain" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Alteration suite, Garish Workroom" note="Garish Workroom">
    <description>Pale pastel pink walls provide a light contrast with the dark purple-tinged floor of gloomwood planks.  Against one wall, a purple-painted table provides ample working space for any project.</description>
    <description>Pale pink walls contrast with the gloomwood planks of the floor.  A purple-painted table provides working space.</description>
    <position x="40" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go glittery curtain" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Alteration Suite, Nemorous Workroom" note="Nemorous Workroom">
    <description>Painted murals depicting a forest scene cover the walls while a deeply plush carpet designed like fallen leaves covers the floor.  A worktable crafted with logs and rough-hewn planks provides a working surface.</description>
    <description>Murals of woodland scenes cover the walls while a table provides working space.</description>
    <position x="40" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ivy-colored curtain" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Alteration Suite, Tenebrous Workroom" note="Tenebrous Workroom">
    <description>Swathes of dark grey fabric cover the walls, mostly hiding the somber black paint and matching trim.  Wrought iron standing candleholders rest near the black table that serves as a working surface for projects.</description>
    <description>Swathes of somber fabric cover the walls and a black table serves as a work surface.</description>
    <position x="60" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go shadowy curtain" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Blue Suite, Royal-Blue Hall" note="Blue Suite|Royal-Blue Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a deep royal-blue hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <description>Royal-blue walls trimmed with white baseboards surround the displayed prizes in the room.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go blue-tiled entrance" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Blue Suite, Ocean-Blue Hall" note="Ocean-Blue Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a pale ocean-blue hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <description>Ocean-blue walls trimmed with white baseboards surround the displayed prizes in the room.</description>
    <position x="-60" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Blue Suite, Turquoise Hall" note="Turquoise Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a bright turquoise hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <description>Turquoise-hued walls trimmed with white baseboards surround the displayed prizes in the room.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Yellow Suite, Amber Hall" note="Yellow Suite|Amber Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plaster walls painted a rich amber hue enclose a spacious area designed to showcase the items on display.  Overhead lighting allows for the proper inspection of the various prizes on offer.</description>
    <description>Plaster walls painted amber enclose the area while lighting allows inspection of the prizes on offer.</description>
    <position x="60" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go yellow portal" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="22" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="16" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Yellow Suite, Buttercup Hall" note="Buttercup Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plaster walls painted a luscious buttercup hue enclose a spacious area designed to showcase the items on display.  Overhead lighting allows for the proper inspection of the various prizes on offer.</description>
    <description>Plaster walls painted buttercup-yellow enclose the area while lighting allows inspection of the prizes on offer.</description>
    <position x="60" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="23" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Yellow Suite, Jasmine Hall" note="Jasmine Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plaster walls painted a pale jasmine hue enclose a spacious area designed to showcase the items on display.  Overhead lighting allows for the proper inspection of the various prizes on offer.</description>
    <description>Plaster walls painted jasmine-yellow enclose the area while lighting allows inspection of the prizes on offer.</description>
    <position x="60" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Yellow Suite, Straw Hall" note="Straw Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plaster walls painted a faint straw hue enclose a spacious area designed to showcase the items on display.  Overhead lighting allows for the proper inspection of the various prizes on offer.</description>
    <description>Plaster walls painted straw-yellow enclose the area while lighting allows inspection of the prizes on offer.</description>
    <position x="60" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="19" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Yellow Suite, Lemon Hall" note="Lemon Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plaster walls painted a bright lemon hue enclose a spacious area designed to showcase the items on display.  Overhead lighting allows for the proper inspection of the various prizes on offer.</description>
    <description>Plaster walls painted lemon-yellow enclose the area while lighting allows inspection of the prizes on offer.</description>
    <position x="60" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Yellow Suite, Mustard Hall" note="Mustard Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plaster walls painted a muddy mustard hue enclose a spacious area designed to showcase the items on display.  Overhead lighting allows for the proper inspection of the various prizes on offer.</description>
    <description>Plaster walls painted mustard-yellow enclose the area while lighting allows inspection of the prizes on offer.</description>
    <position x="60" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="14" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Yellow Suite, Saffron Niche" note="Saffron Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>High overhead a gaezthen globe dangles from the ceiling and provides enough light to highlight the prize selections available.  The cozy niche is enclosed with plastered walls painted a vibrant saffron shade.</description>
    <description>A gaezthen globe provides lighting for the prizes set out in the saffron-painted niche.</description>
    <position x="40" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Yellow Suite, Golden Niche" note="Golden Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>High overhead a gaezthen globe dangles from the ceiling and provides enough light to highlight the prize selections available.  The cozy niche is enclosed with plastered walls painted a rich golden shade.</description>
    <description>A gaezthen globe provides lighting for the prizes set out in the golden-painted niche.</description>
    <position x="40" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Yellow Suite, Sunny Niche" note="Sunny Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>High overhead a gaezthen globe dangles from the ceiling and provides enough light to highlight the prize selections available.  The cozy niche is enclosed with plastered walls painted a sunny-yellow shade.</description>
    <description>A gaezthen globe provides lighting for the prizes set out in the sunny-yellow painted niche.</description>
    <position x="40" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Yellow Suite, Daffodil Niche" note="Daffodil Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>High overhead a gaezthen globe dangles from the ceiling and provides enough light to highlight the prize selections available.  The cozy niche is enclosed with plastered walls painted a pale daffodil-yellow shade.</description>
    <description>A gaezthen globe provides lighting for the prizes set out in the daffodil-yellow painted niche.</description>
    <position x="40" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Yellow Suite, Canary Niche" note="Canary Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>High overhead a gaezthen globe dangles from the ceiling and provides enough light to highlight the prize selections available.  The cozy niche is enclosed with plastered walls painted a bright canary-yellow shade.</description>
    <description>A gaezthen globe provides lighting for the prizes set out in the canary-yellow painted niche.</description>
    <position x="40" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Yellow Suite, Banana Niche" note="Banana Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>High overhead a gaezthen globe dangles from the ceiling and provides enough light to highlight the prize selections available.  The cozy niche is enclosed with plastered walls painted an intense banana-yellow shade.</description>
    <description>A gaezthen globe provides lighting for the prizes set out in the banana-yellow painted niche.</description>
    <position x="40" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Yellow Suite, Honey Alcove" note="Honey Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Walls plastered and painted the shade of honey enclose the small space set off from the main hallway.  Some gaezthen globes set onto sconces cast their light on the prizes displayed around the room.</description>
    <description>Walls the shade of honey enclose the space displaying prizes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Yellow Suite, Jonquil Alcove" note="Jonquil Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Walls plastered and painted the shade of jonquils enclose the small space set off from the main hallway.  Some gaezthen globes set onto sconces cast their light on the prizes displayed around the room.</description>
    <description>Walls the shade of jonquils enclose the space displaying prizes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Yellow Suite, Maize Alcove" note="Maize Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Walls plastered and painted the shade of maize enclose the small space set off from the main hallway.  Some gaezthen globes set onto sconces cast their light on the prizes displayed around the room.</description>
    <description>Walls the shade of maize enclose the space displaying prizes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Yellow Suite, Citrine Alcove" note="Citrine Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Walls plastered and painted the shade of citrine enclose the small space set off from the main hallway.  Some gaezthen globes set onto sconces cast their light on the prizes displayed around the room.</description>
    <description>Walls the shade of citrine enclose the space displaying prizes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Yellow Suite, Butter Alcove" note="Butter Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Walls plastered and painted the shade of butter enclose the small space set off from the main hallway.  Some gaezthen globes set onto sconces cast their light on the prizes displayed around the room.</description>
    <description>Walls the shade of butter enclose the space displaying prizes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Yellow Suite, Wheat Alcove" note="Wheat Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Walls plastered and painted the shade of wheat enclose the small space set off from the main hallway.  Some gaezthen globes set onto sconces cast their light on the prizes displayed around the room.</description>
    <description>Walls the shade of wheat enclose the space displaying prizes.</description>
    <position x="80" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="15" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Green Suite, Olive Hall" note="Green Suite|Olive Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of olive paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <description>Olive-colored plastered walls surround the prizes spread out for consideration in this area.</description>
    <position x="140" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go green portal" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Green Suite, Sea-Green Hall" note="Sea-Green Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of pale sea-green paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <description>Sea-colored plastered walls surround the prizes spread out for consideration in this area.</description>
    <position x="160" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Green Suite, Grass-Green Hall" note="Grass-Green Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of vibrant grass-green paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <description>Grass-colored plastered walls surround the prizes spread out for consideration in this area.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Green Suite, Viridian Hall" note="Viridian Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of deep viridian paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving a muted, calm feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <description>Viridian-colored plastered walls surround the prizes spread out for consideration in this area.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Green Suite, Lime Hall" note="Lime Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Coats of bright lime-green paint cover the plaster walls of this well-lit room, giving an upbeat feel to the area.  The hanging light fixtures allow for ample illumination of the prizes spread out for consideration.</description>
    <description>Lime-colored plastered walls surround the prizes spread out for consideration in this area.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="42" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Green Suite, Avocado Chamber" note="Avocado Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the rich avocado-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <description>Gaethzen spheres overhead cast warm light on the avocado-hued walls and the prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="160" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Green Suite, Malachite Niche" note="Malachite Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the rich malachite-hued plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <description>White trim accents the malachite-hued walls while overhead lights illuminate the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="140" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Green Suite, Pickle-Green Cubicle" note="Pickle-Green Cubicle" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the pickle-hued walls, the room is bare of adornment.  Simple gaethzen globes hanging from the ceiling provide light.  The lack of ornamentation focuses attention on the prizes on display.</description>
    <description>Unadorned except for the pickled-hued walls, the lack of ornamentation highlights the prizes on display.</description>
    <position x="180" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="33" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Green Suite, Sage Chamber" note="Sage Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the muted sage-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <description>Gaethzen spheres overhead cast warm light on the sage-hued walls and the prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="180" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Green Suite, Chartreuse Niche" note="Chartreuse Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the eye-searing chartreuse plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <description>White trim accents the chartreuse-hued walls while overhead lights illuminate the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Green Suite, Moss Cubicle" note="Moss Cubicle" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the moss-colored walls, the room is bare of adornment.  Simple gaethzen globes hanging from the ceiling provide light.  The lack of ornamentation focuses attention on the prizes on display.</description>
    <description>Unadorned except for the moss-hued walls, the lack of ornamentation highlights the prizes on display.</description>
    <position x="200" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Green Suite, Emerald Chamber" note="Emerald Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the brilliant emerald-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <description>Gaethzen spheres overhead cast warm light on the emerald-hued walls and the prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="220" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="40" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Green Suite, Pear Niche" note="Pear Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the pale pear-green plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <description>White trim accents the pear-hued walls while overhead lights illuminate the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="200" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Green Suite, Pine-Green Cubicle" note="Pine-Green Cubicle" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Except for the pine-colored walls, the room is bare of adornment.  Simple gaethzen globes hanging from the ceiling provide light.  The lack of ornamentation focuses attention on the prizes on display.</description>
    <description>Unadorned except for the pine-hued walls, the lack of ornamentation highlights the prizes on display.</description>
    <position x="240" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="39" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Green Suite, Pistachio Chamber" note="Pistachio Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Gaethzen spheres suspended overhead cast a warm light across the pastel pistachio-hued plaster walls.  The abundance of light spotlights the many prizes available for selection.</description>
    <description>Gaethzen spheres overhead cast warm light on the pistachio-hued walls and the prizes available for selection.</description>
    <position x="240" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Green Suite, Verdigris Niche" note="Verdigris Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Painted white trim accents the verdigris-colored plastered walls that form this secluded alcove.  Spread out under the overhead lights are all the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <description>White trim accents the verdigris-hued walls while overhead lights illuminate the prizes awaiting consideration.</description>
    <position x="220" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Blue Suite, Indigo Chamber" note="Indigo Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The spacious room has deep indigo-hued walls accented with a white wooden chair rail running across the plaster at waist-height.  The various prizes on offer are in the center of the room and are lit by a large gaethzen sphere suspended from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="-80" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Blue Suite, Cobalt Chamber" note="Cobalt Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The spacious room has rich cobalt-hued walls accented with a white wooden chair rail running across the plaster at waist-height.  The various prizes on offer are in the center of the room and are lit by a large gaethzen sphere suspended from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Blue Suite, Periwinkle Hall" note="Periwinkle Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a cheery periwinkle hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Blue Suite, Cyan Chamber" note="Cyan Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>The spacious room has vibrant cyan-hued walls accented with a white wooden chair rail running across the plaster at waist-height.  The various prizes on offer are in the center of the room and are lit by a large gaethzen sphere suspended from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="-40" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Blue Suite, Hyacinth Hall" note="Hyacinth Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Plain plastered walls have been painted a cheerful hyacinth hue and trimmed with narrow white baseboards.  Subtle indirect lighting of the displayed prizes is provided by gaezthen globes dangling from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="0" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Purple Suite, Wisteria Hall" note="Purple Suite|Wisteria Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Enclosed by wisteria-hued plaster walls, the airy spaciousness of the room allows for easy inspection of the prizes displayed.  All the items are well lit by gaethzen globes hung from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="50" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go purple archway" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Purple Suite, Grape Chamber" note="Grape Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set off from the hall, this chamber is devoted to displaying prizes in a more intimate setting.  The rich grape-colored walls give the area a feeling of ostentation and wealth.</description>
    <position x="200" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Purple Suite, Lavender Hall" note="Lavender Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Enclosed by lavender-hued plaster walls, the airy spaciousness of the room allows for easy inspection of the prizes displayed.  All the items are well lit by gaethzen globes hung from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="49" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Purple Suite, Plum Chamber" note="Plum Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set off from the hall, this chamber is devoted to displaying prizes in a more intimate setting.  The vibrant plum-colored walls give the area a feeling of ostentation and wealth.</description>
    <position x="160" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="54" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Purple Suite, Thistle Alcove" note="Thistle Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rough plastered walls are covered with a light thistle color that is highlighted by the white trim running around the floor.  A few wall sconces light the prizes arrayed around the small alcove.</description>
    <position x="140" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="52" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Purple Suite, Violet-red Niche" note="Violet-red Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rich violet-red colored walls enclose a small area well suited to highlighting the prizes exhibited around the room.  A large gaethzen sphere provides illumination for the area without being overwhelming.</description>
    <position x="140" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="53" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Purple Suite, Heliotrope Hall" note="Helitrope Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Enclosed by heliotrope-hued plaster walls, the airy spaciousness of the room allows for easy inspection of the prizes displayed.  All the items are well lit by gaethzen globes hung from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="64" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Purple Suite, Aubergine Hall" note="Aubergine Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Enclosed by aubergine-hued plaster walls, the airy spaciousness of the room allows for easy inspection of the prizes displayed.  All the items are well lit by gaethzen globes hung from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Purple Suite, Blue-violet Hall" note="Blue-Violet Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Enclosed by blue-violet plaster walls, the airy spaciousness of the room allows for easy inspection of the prizes displayed.  All the items are well lit by gaethzen globes hung from the coffered ceiling.</description>
    <position x="180" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Purple Suite, Puce Chamber" note="Puce Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set off from the hall, this chamber is devoted to displaying prizes in a more intimate setting.  The brilliant puce-colored walls give the area a feeling of excitement and activity.</description>
    <position x="200" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="57" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Purple Suite, Sangria Alcove" note="Sangria Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rough plastered walls are covered with a brilliant sangria-hued color that is highlighted by the white trim running around the floor.  A few wall sconces light the prizes arrayed around the small alcove.</description>
    <position x="220" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Purple Suite, Mulberry Niche" note="Mulberry Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Vibrant mulberry-hued walls enclose a small area well suited to highlighting the prizes exhibited around the room.  A large gaethzen sphere provides illumination for the area without being overwhelming.</description>
    <position x="220" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Purple Suite, Iris Chamber" note="Iris Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set off from the hall, this chamber is devoted to displaying prizes in a more intimate setting.  The vibrant iris-colored walls give the area a feeling of excitement and activity.</description>
    <position x="160" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="56" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="62" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Purple Suite, Magenta Alcove" note="Magenta Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rough plastered walls are covered with a vibrant magenta color that is highlighted by the white trim running around the floor.  A few wall sconces light the prizes arrayed around the small alcove.</description>
    <position x="140" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="63" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Purple Suite, Orchid Niche" note="Orchid Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pastel orchid-hued walls enclose a small area well suited to highlighting the prizes exhibited around the room.  A large gaethzen sphere provides illumination for the area without being overwhelming.</description>
    <position x="140" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Purple Suite, Phlox Chamber" note="Phlox Chamber" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Set off from the hall, this chamber is devoted to displaying prizes in a more intimate setting.  The pale phlox-colored walls give the area a feeling of peace and serenity.</description>
    <position x="200" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="55" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Purple Suite, Lilac Alcove" note="Lilac Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rough plastered walls are covered with a pale lilac color that is highlighted by the white trim running around the floor.  A few wall sconces light the prizes arrayed around the small alcove.</description>
    <position x="220" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Purple Suite, Dark Purple Niche" note="Dark Purple Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Deep dark purple colored walls enclose a small area well suited to highlighting the prizes exhibited around the room.  A large gaethzen sphere provides illumination for the area without being overwhelming.</description>
    <position x="220" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="65" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Purple Suite, Burgundy Alcove" note="Burgundy Alcove" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Rough plastered walls are covered with a rich burgundy color that is highlighted by the white trim running around the floor.  A few wall sconces light the prizes arrayed around the small alcove.</description>
    <position x="220" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="68" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Purple Suite, Amethyst Niche" note="Amethyst Niche" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Pale amethyst-hued walls enclose a small area well suited to highlighting the prizes exhibited around the room.  A large gaethzen sphere provides illumination for the area without being overwhelming.</description>
    <position x="220" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="50" />
  </node>
  <node id="999" name="A'baya Esplanade, Central Walkway" note="Taisidon_Mystery.xml|exit">
    <description>At the center of the busy shopping walkway, a beautiful ocean mosaic is pieced together with bits of shell and seaglass.  Festive gaethzen globes are hung from tall poles that are placed at even intervals along the macawood boardwalk.</description>
    <position x="40" y="180" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="1000" name="Red Suite, Coral Hall">
    <description>Smooth coral-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="120" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1001" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1002" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go red archway" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="1001" name="Red Suite, Blood-red Vault">
    <description>Suspended high above, a gleaming glass globe radiates ample light, casting a luminous glow upon the array of prizes.  Nestled within a snug alcove, the intimate space is enveloped by vibrant blood-toned plastered walls.</description>
    <position x="120" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1000" />
  </node>
  <node id="1002" name="Red Suite, Sanguine Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth sanguine-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="140" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1003" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1004" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1017" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1000" />
  </node>
  <node id="1003" name="Red Suite, Cardinal Vault" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Suspended high above, a gleaming glass globe radiates ample light, casting a luminous glow upon the array of prizes.  Nestled within a snug alcove, the intimate space is enveloped by rich cardinal-toned plastered walls.</description>
    <position x="140" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1002" />
  </node>
  <node id="1004" name="Red Suite, Amaranth Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth amaranth-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1005" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1006" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1016" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1002" />
  </node>
  <node id="1005" name="Red Suite, Maroon Vault" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Suspended high above, a gleaming glass globe radiates ample light, casting a luminous glow upon the array of prizes.  Nestled within a snug alcove, the intimate space is enveloped by deep maroon-toned plastered walls.</description>
    <position x="160" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1004" />
  </node>
  <node id="1006" name="Red Suite, Vermilion Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth vermilion-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="180" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1007" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1008" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1015" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1004" />
  </node>
  <node id="1007" name="Red Suite, Currant Vault" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Suspended high above, a gleaming glass globe radiates ample light, casting a luminous glow upon the array of prizes.  Nestled within a snug alcove, the intimate space is enveloped by brilliant currant-toned plastered walls.</description>
    <position x="180" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1006" />
  </node>
  <node id="1008" name="Red Suite, Cerise Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth cerise-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="200" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1009" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1010" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1014" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1006" />
  </node>
  <node id="1009" name="Red Suite, Crimson Vault" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Suspended high above, a gleaming glass globe radiates ample light, casting a luminous glow upon the array of prizes.  Nestled within a snug alcove, the intimate space is enveloped by crimson-toned plastered walls.</description>
    <position x="200" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1008" />
  </node>
  <node id="1010" name="Red Suite, Cinnabar Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth cinnabar-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="220" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1011" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1012" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1013" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1008" />
  </node>
  <node id="1011" name="Red Suite, Raspberry Vault" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Suspended high above, a gleaming glass globe radiates ample light, casting a luminous glow upon the array of prizes.  Nestled within a snug alcove, the intimate space is enveloped by raspberry-toned plastered walls.</description>
    <position x="220" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1010" />
  </node>
  <node id="1012" name="Red Suite, Merlot Hall" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Smooth merlot-hued plaster walls delineate the spacious room devoted to exhibiting prizes.  Overhead, glass globes suspended from the ceiling provide plenty of light for inspection of the items.</description>
    <position x="240" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1010" />
  </node>
  <node id="1013" name="Red Suite, Poppy-red Cell" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This cozy enclave is enclosed by poppy-red walls.  Mounted on sconces, several glass globes emit soft illumination, spotlighting the prizes arranged throughout the room for inspection.</description>
    <position x="220" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1010" />
  </node>
  <node id="1014" name="Red Suite, Ruby Cell" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This cozy enclave is enclosed by ruby-hued walls.  Mounted on sconces, several glass globes emit soft illumination, spotlighting the prizes arranged throughout the room for inspection.</description>
    <position x="200" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1008" />
  </node>
  <node id="1015" name="Red Suite, Wine Cell" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This cozy enclave is enclosed by wine-hued walls.  Mounted on sconces, several glass globes emit soft illumination, spotlighting the prizes arranged throughout the room for inspection.</description>
    <position x="180" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1006" />
  </node>
  <node id="1016" name="Red Suite, Strawberry Cell" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This cozy enclave is enclosed by strawberry-hued walls.  Mounted on sconces, several glass globes emit soft illumination, spotlighting the prizes arranged throughout the room for inspection.</description>
    <position x="160" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1004" />
  </node>
  <node id="1017" name="Red Suite, Scarlet Cell" color="#FF0000">
    <description>This cozy enclave is enclosed by scarlet walls.  Mounted on sconces, several glass globes emit soft illumination, spotlighting the prizes arranged throughout the room for inspection.</description>
    <position x="140" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1002" />
  </node>
  <label text="alterations">
    <position x="22" y="78" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="raffles">
    <position x="-4" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Blue Suite">
    <position x="-50" y="170" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Yellow Suite">
    <position x="24" y="350" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Green Suite">
    <position x="158" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Purple Suite">
    <position x="150" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Red Suite">
    <position x="150" y="0" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>