<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Temporal Pocket" id="516q">
  <node id="1" name="Temporal Pocket, Nexus">
    <description>Shifting colors pulse across the sky, oscillating in a fluctuating random pattern admidst the shattered shards of the sky.  More shards jumbled together comprise a floor drifting above the bottomless void.</description>
    <position x="160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="6" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go circular wall" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Temporal Pocket, Akigwe's Tower" note="Akigwe's Legacy|tower">
    <description>A layer of dust covers everything here.  High above, a crystal sits atop the tower before you and slowly flickers from one color to another, endlessly casting odd shadows throughout the cavern.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Temporal Pocket, Battered Grey Raven Prison" note="The Aftermath|Riot2">
    <description>The smells of death and decay are heavy in the air, and smoke rises from towers set at the corners of a wall high above you.  Guards have the small office here locked down behind a series of gates and barricades that lead further into the prison.</description>
    <position x="180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Temporal Pocket, Front Lawn" note="Dunshade|manor">
    <description>Nothing seems to be alive in this gloom-filled yard.  Large skeletal trees crowd the path which is covered with a detritus of their decaying leaves.  The walkway's paving stones are broken or missing in random spots, and occasionally a large flat stone protrudes upright, as if it had been heaved up out of the ground.</description>
    <position x="200" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Temporal Pocket, Wilderness Path" note="Beyond the Barrier|botb">
    <description>Enclosing the area, floating shards create a scenery that changes from forest green to fern to moss in hue all around you.  Beneath the fluctuating canopy are what appear to be suspended shards of pine-colored glass, creating a transparent boundary that divides the temporal zone from a bottomless void beneath.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Temporal Pocket, Outside the Manor" note="Kanton's Dagger|dagger">
    <description>Floating fragments of shattered glass create a backdrop of mysterious color that slowly shifts as each sliver rotates, separating the area from the void beyond.  A small road paved with mossy cobbles leads up to an imposing manor.</description>
    <position x="160" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Temporal Pocket, Grey Raven Prison" note="Quelling the Riot|riot1">
    <description>Fractured shards of floating glass-like crystal form high walls with rising towers, obscuring the roar of shouting and crashing objects from within the bustling prison.</description>
    <position x="140" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Temporal Pocket, Clearing" note="Morun Melgorehn|gnome">
    <description>A vast field spreads outwards, another anomalous area within the fractured pocket.  At the heart of the green clearing, a massive metal contraption lies curled up.  Glistening scales reveal themselves as exquisitely machined metal plates, and the great eyes of the crafted beast reflect light from their flat glass surfaces.  A giant mouth leads within.</description>
    <position x="120" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Temporal Pocket, Docks" note="ghost ship">
    <description>Fractured slivers of translucent crystal are frozen in place, creating the outlines of long docks reaching out into a complete void.  Ropes and nets litter the docks between crates and other cargo waiting to be loaded, blocking access to the piers waiting for ships.  An obvious path through the mess leads to a cobbled road.</description>
    <position x="140" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Temporal Pocket, Archives">
    <description>Coruscating reverse rainbows arc at various angles all around, casting madly flamboyant colors on every surface.  A fractured jumble of wood, stone, steel, dirt and bone form a shifting ground, a bottomless void stretching far below.  Encircling the area are a series of anomalies of distorted space sitting upon pedestals made of shifting crystal.  A short railing composed of coiled shadow is strung between the pedestals, preventing any ventures beyond the bizarre platform.</description>
    <position x="155" y="130" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go circular wall" destination="1" />
  </node>
  <label text="Akigwe's Legacy">
    <position x="120" y="80" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Prison Riot: The Aftermath">
    <position x="185" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dunshade: Echo of Tears">
    <position x="205" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Beyond the Barrier">
    <position x="185" y="155" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Kanton's Dagger">
    <position x="120" y="190" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Quelling the Riot">
    <position x="50" y="155" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Morun Melgorehn">
    <position x="25" y="130" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ghost Ship">
    <position x="75" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>