<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Stone Rotunda" id="509q">
  <node id="1" name="Stone Rotunda, Gathering Hall" color="#00FF00">
    <description>The circular room is massive and contains several tiered balconies reaching towards the dome overhead.  Here, on the ground level, the space is open with only a rectangular stone table at its heart -- a centerpiece viewable from the countless elevated seats in the galleries above.  Numerous tanks containing bioluminescent fish, corals and other sea-life line the walls, providing ample illumination for the chamber.</description>
    <position x="180" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go deep pool" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Stone Rotunda, Alcove">
    <description>Set in a back corner of the chamber, the alcove contains a solid ripplegate that gleams with the light from the tanks set along the walls.  The water spirals in an endless loop with the force of a waterfall.  The mist surrounding the portal conceals whatever lies beyond it.</description>
    <position x="200" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go substantial ripplegate" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ripplegate" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Escarpment, Dry Cavern">
    <description>A dried and long dead husk of staghorn coral grows from the center of the cavern, a crown of branching points jutting in all directions and topped with dozens of clean-burning candles.  The air has a salty tinge and dense mats of bladder wrack, rockweed, and dead coralline algae grow around the cavern floor.</description>
    <position x="240" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go substantial ripplegate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Escarpment, Cave Entrance" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Piles of broken rock, coral, and shell line the ground here, and crabs and other scuttling creatures hide in the crevices, competing for shelter and scraps.  Barrel sponges, exuding a constant stream of fine bubbles that billow upward, grow from the walls and shelter red and purple rippled cleaner shrimp.  Above, a small pocket of air betrays the flickering of a small lamp.</description>
    <description>Brilliantly luminescent fan worms, corals, and sponges provide sufficient visibility to note the boundaries of the cave walls.  The ghostly forms of scuttling crabs and other creatures can be seen scurrying around the shadows, hiding in crevices as they seek shelter and scraps.  Above, a small pocket of air betrays the flickering of a small lamp.</description>
    <position x="240" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Escarpment, Ledge" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Flickering shafts of light dance across the ledge's floor while the water's surface churns far above.  Rippled sand billows with the slightest disturbance, and vast schools of fish dart to and fro.  A tall escaparpment face, covered with coral and kelp outgrowths that sway in the currents, stretches far to the east and west.  A small opening in its cliff wall betrays nothing within.  A sharp drop to the south descends into inky blackness while a purple glow is visible to the east.</description>
    <description>The watery surface churns far above.  Rippled sand billows with the slightest movement, and vast schools of glowing jellyfish and plankton dart to and fro, leaving ghostly trails in their wake.  A tall escaparpment face, covered with bioluminescent coral and kelp outgrowths that sway in the currents, stretches far to the east and west.  A small opening in its cliff wall betrays nothing within.  A sharp drop to the south descends into inky blackness while a bright purple glow is visible to the east.</description>
    <description>The watery surface churns far above.  Rippled sand billows with the slightest movement, and vast schools of glowing jellyfish and plankton dart to and fro, leaving ghostly trails in their wake.  A tall escaparpment face, covered with bioluminescent coral and kelp outgrowths that sway in the currents, stretches far to the east and west.  A small opening in its cliff wall betrays nothing within.  A sharp drop to the south descends into inky blackness.</description>
    <position x="240" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Escarpment, Cliff Edge" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The ledge ends aburptly here, affording a vast view of the ocean void.  Fish swim tentatively out into the emptiness, darting back to the protection of the escarpment, diving deep into the darkness, or disappearing into the distance.  The cliff face only extends a short distance below before being enveloped by inky blackness, and colder water wafts upward, stirring fan corals and tube worms clinging to the edge.</description>
    <description>The ledge ends abruptly here, affording a vast view of the ocean void.  Firefly squid and luminescent jellyfish drift gracefully in the depths below, a flickering cosmos of shifting constellations.  Colder water wafts upward, stirring fan corals and tube worms clinging to the edge.</description>
    <position x="240" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Escarpment, New Growth" color="#0000FF">
    <description>A large ring marks the features here, and the silt is disturbed and sunken as if something buried has been removed.  Small starter patches of coral and an assortment of sea plants are worked around the ring's perimeter, and from time to time a curious dweller of the depths will venture forth and test the ring's boundary.  Few, however, linger within the perimeter for long before darting back out of sight.</description>
    <position x="260" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="5" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Tidal Flats, Rocky Overlook">
    <description>Crashing waves break against brecciated rock covered in chitons and barnacles, while gulls perch on nearby rocks, sleeping restlessly.  The pungent stench of rotting vegetation and scuttling creatures stranded outside of the safety of evaporating pools mingles with the sharp sea spray.  A sheer cliff face prevents southward travel, the ocean beckons to the north and a series of shallow pools stretch to the east.</description>
    <description>Crashing waves break against brecciated rock covered in chitons and barnacles, while gulls effortlessly soar above.  The pungent stench of rotting vegetation and scuttling creatures stranded outside of the safety of evaporating pools mingles with the sharp sea spray.  A sheer cliff face prevents southward travel, the ocean beckons to the north and a series of shallow pools stretch to the east.</description>
    <position x="220" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swm east" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go substantial ripplegate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Tidal Flats, Shallows" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The slippery and uneven rock here makes for risky footing in places, though the masses of barnacles underfoot provide a rough grip in others.  The waves break endlessly, following long and gradual risers, and the occasional startled stingray suddenly flutters away in a cloud of disturbed sand.  A few gulls bob comfortably in the waters nearby.  They eye everything that moves at a distance with a vague curiosity, ready to leap at a presented opportunity or flee to safety from a threat.</description>
    <position x="220" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Tidal Flats, Infralittoral Zone" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Visibility is extremely poor due to the gentle waves mixing clumps of hissing bubbles, fine sand, swaying algage and other debris into the water column.  Softly glowing sea stars migrate slowly in search of food while equally luminescent plankton contribute to the churning haze.  The terrain continues to decline, steeply descending into darker, deeper waters.  A soft purple glow can be seen to the northeast.</description>
    <description>Visibility is poor due to the gentle waves mixing clumps of hissing bubbles, fine sand, swaying algae and other debris into the water column.  Schools of tiny fish dart around the short plants and hide in the shifting rocks, and sea stars and urchins migrate slowly in search of food.  The terrain continues to decline, steeply descending into deeper waters.  A soft purple glow can be seen to the northeast.</description>
    <description>Visibility is poor due to the gentle waves mixing clumps of hissing bubbles, fine sand, swaying algae and other debris into the water column.  Schools of tiny fish dart around the short plants and hide in the shifting rocks, and sea stars and urchins migrate slowly in search of food.  The terrain continues to decline, steeply descending into deeper waters.</description>
    <position x="240" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Tidal Flats, Clearing" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Sunk about halfway into the rippled sands, an enormous black length of tomiek plating gives off a bizarre and unnatural purple glow.  The object is bright enough to illuminate the surroundings, revealing that an area a handful of yards around the sunken plating is strangely devoid of life -- no grasses or corals grow, no living fish swim or arthropods scuttle in its proximity -- yet there is the impression of movement within the plating.</description>
    <description>A long and narrow trench of disturbed sand stretches further into the inky darkness of the depths to the northeast.  The ripples of sand immediately surrounding the fissure are devoid of life, though new growths of coral and sea plants lie further out and show signs of fairly recently being transplanted.</description>
    <position x="260" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Tidal Flats, Vibrant Pools" color="#0000FF">
    <description>With each wave break the shallow pools fill with hissing, cold water.  Sheltering miniature worlds of life, the pools feature faintly glowing anemones casting gentle illumination that betrays nearby movement of shrimp and other grazers, while ghostly trails of flashing plankton reveal turbulence in the enclosures.  A herd of sea stars, glowing with gentle green lines down each arm, slowly travel towards the ocean.</description>
    <description>With each wave break the shallow pools fill with hissing, cold water.  Sheltering miniature worlds of life, the pools feature bright purple, red, and orange urchins clinging to crevices, needle point spines bristling outward, while small octopus flit between overhangs in search of prey.  Thick shelled snails slowly creep along as they graze on algae or probe at mussels while crabs busily pick at detritus.  They dart for safety at the slightest provocation, winding between anemones swaying in the slight currents of the enclosed pools.</description>
    <position x="240" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Kelp Forest, Air Pocket">
    <description>A perfect dome of water surrounds this space, the surface rippling, held back by a sphere of air.  Everything is slightly damp, the ground covered in a few inches of vibrating water, and a forest of kelp stretches into the darkness just beyond the wall of ocean.  A circle of rocks is stacked atop the base at the center of the sphere.  It supports a driftwood and dried kelp fire that warmly crackles, its acrid smoke disappearing as it winds to the watery ceiling.  The flickering firelight reflects strangely on the wall of water, and a gleaming eye of a passing fish shines momentarily before it darts back into the depths.  The kelp forest extends in every direction</description>
    <description>A perfect dome of water surrounds this space, the surface rippling, held back by a sphere of air.  Everything is slightly damp, the ground covered in a few inches of vibrating water, and a forest of kelp stretches into the darkness just beyond the wall of ocean.  A circle of rocks is stacked atop the base at the center of the sphere.  It supports a driftwood and dried kelp fire that warmly crackles, its acrid smoke disappearing as it winds to the watery ceiling.  The flickering firelight reflects strangely on the wall of water, and a gleaming eye of a passing fish shines momentarily before it darts back into the depths.  The kelp forest extends in every direction.</description>
    <position x="180" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ripplegate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Kelp Forest, Urchin Barrens" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The kelp thins here, bright purple urchins migrating along protective rocky pathways that provide shelter from prying otters and sheephead fish.  Most of the forest's stalks are nibbled and chewed to near oblivion, leaving only the thick and winding holdfasts in the wake of the sheltered urchin army.  A trail of sea stars pursues the urchins, all clearly visible in the brighter light here, as the turbulent surface far above churns.  A few otters wind playfully nearby, exuberantly spiraling in a trail of bubbles.</description>
    <description>The kelp thins here, bright purple urchins migrating along protective rocky pathways that provide shelter from prying otters and sheephead fish.  Most of the forest's stalks are nibbled and chewed to near oblivion, leaving only the thick and winding holdfasts in the wake of the sheltered urchin army.  A trail of luminescent sea stars pursues the urchins, providing the barest illumination in the dark waters.</description>
    <position x="160" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Kelp Forest, Swaying Thickets" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Schools of fish playfully dart in and out of the few unhindered shafts of light that manage to pierce the canopy of woven kelp fronds along the water's surface high above.  In the gloom, everything is green -- the water, the sunlight filtering through the kelp, and the flora and fauna of the depths.  The gentle current bends the towering forest at a slight angle, causing the structures to drag thick boulders covered in holdfasts slowly across the seafloor.  From time to time, otters dart down and snatch an urchin or clam before gleefully undulating away with their prize.</description>
    <description>Large squid gracefully soar between the shafts of kelp, brilliant lines of luminescence zigzagging down their long bodies and writhing tentacles as they search for prey.  Thick kelp fronds wind together far above, forming a thick roof along the surface, and the dark forest sways in the shadows, pushed by cold currents.  Visibility is poor, though luminescent plankton cast ghostly trails along the kelp that bends in the gentle current.  Flickers of movement and flashes of light signal the vibrant sea forms present.</description>
    <position x="200" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Kelp Forest, Sheltered Grove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The forest thins slightly, and large grouper gather in the safety of the rippling kelp strands.  Flickers of movement beneath the fronds betray the presence of sheltering creatures.  Swaying back and forth with the current, the kelp secures the sandy sea floor, leaving the water markedly clearer.  In the distance, reef sharks slowly circle, swimming with deadly purpose as they search for prey.  A steady purple glow can be seen to the northwest.</description>
    <description>The forest thins slightly, and large grouper gather in the safety of the rippling kelp strands.  Flickers of movement beneath the fronds betray the presence of sheltering creatures.  Swaying back and forth with the current, the kelp secures the sandy sea floor, leaving the water markedly clearer.  In the distance, reef sharks slowly circle, swimming with deadly purpose as they search for prey.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Kelp Forest, New Grove" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The sand is rocky, and even some larger boulder-sized chunks are strewn about.  Though the kelp forest is noticeably thinner here, several new growths show signs of recently being transplanted and secured to some of the larger stones nearby.  A gap remains in the sand, as if something that had been lodged was removed, and the transplants there appear noticeably unhealthy.</description>
    <position x="140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="21" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Abyssal Depths, Sheltered Cavern">
    <description>Carved into the rock wall, the barren cave is illuminated by a single brazier burning with a low yellow flame, consuming an oily jelly.  The sharp stench of sulfur mingles with the tang of salt, the air barely cleansed by the flora and fauna growing in the waters and along cave walls.  A small opening at one end of the cave plunges into nearly pitch-black waters, the barest of flashes of glowing light visible in the depths.</description>
    <position x="160" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="down" move="swim down" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ripplegate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Abyssal Depths, Beneath the Cliff" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Barely visible in the oppressive gloom, an upthrust sheet of rock looms overhead.  A narrow opening, the only evident gap, reveals a flickering yellow light beyond.  A wide sandy path stretches into the darkness between broken boulders.  Barnacles the size of a Gor'Tog flick ghostly white feathered claws into the water and draw inward, grasping for whatever tiny particles drift nearby.  Occasional flashes of light -- blues, greens, and reds -- hint at mysterious dramas of the depths far below.</description>
    <position x="160" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="swim southwest" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="up" move="swim up" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Abyssal Depths, Sulfur Plumes" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Brilliant jellyfish, squid, and deeplight fish school in the distance, shifting like fireworks against the inky black firmament.  Each grouping is outlined or wrung with lines of luminescence.  The area feels warmer as a double column of flowing stone belches a roaring deluge of billowing black water, superheated and shimmering against the otherwise stillness.  Composed of stacked and branching cakes of deposited material, the column is covered in white bodied tubeworms, dozens of feet tall, fanning feathery red gills into the scorching waters.  A soft purple glow can be seen to the northwest.</description>
    <description>Brilliant jellyfish, squid, and deeplight fish school in the distance, shifting like fireworks against the inky black firmament.  Each grouping is outlined or wrung with lines of luminescence.  The area feels warmer as a double column of flowing stone belches a roaring deluge of billowing black water, superheated and shimmering against the otherwise stillness.  Composed of stacked and branching cakes of deposited material, the column is covered in white bodied tubeworms, dozens of feet tall, fanning feathery red gills into the scorching waters.</description>
    <position x="140" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="swim northeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Abyssal Depths, Brine Pools" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The boulder trail thins to smaller rocks and expansive compacted sands.  Fields of scattered bulbous mushrooms spread wide, branching arms and glow with a weak blue light.  Albino crab and shrimp compete for scraps while schools of blind fish drift slowly in wait of prey.  A nearby natural depression appears strangely filled with slowly rippling water, an odd illusion of a watery pool beneath the depths.  A thick mussel bed rings the sight, and a steady purple glow can be seen to the south.</description>
    <description>The boulder trail thins to smaller rocks and expansive compacted sands.  Fields of scattered bulbous mushrooms spread wide, branching arms and glow with a weak blue light.  Albino crab and shrimp compete for scraps while schools of blind fish drift slowly in wait of prey.  A nearby natural depression appears strangely filled with slowly rippling water, an odd illusion of a watery pool beneath the depths.  A thick mussel bed rings the area.</description>
    <position x="120" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Abyssal Depths, Sandy Rings" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Buried in the sand and surrounded by concentric rings of silt, a massive tomiek spinneret rests on its side, and a long coil of black braided fiber drifts softly in the current behind it.  The spinneret gives off a bizarre and unnatural purple glow that's bright enough to illuminate its surroundings.  A wide area is strangely devoid of life -- no sessile creatures grasp at the water nor do scuttlers search in its proximity.  A strange impression of movement within comes from the spinneret.</description>
    <description>A large depression is visible in the sandy sea floor, and a trail leading away from the area indicates that whatever caused it was dragged elsewhere.  Concentric rings ripple outward from the impact point and seem undisturbed by the undersea tides.  From time to time, curious creatures of the depths probe into the area, but most quickly dart away again.</description>
    <position x="120" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Open Sea, Training Course">
    <description>The sites surrounding you change swiftly as your dolphin soars through the water -- docks, ships, rings, kelp forests and so much more just melt one into another.</description>
    <position x="160" y="180" z="0" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Leviathan's Rest, Air Pocket">
    <description>A perfect dome of water surrounds this space, the surface rippling, held back by a sphere of air.  Everything is slightly damp, the ground covered in a few inches of vibrating water, and just beyond the wall of ocean, glowing red lava hisses and steams in the depths.  At the center of the sphere, stacked above the waterline, a circle of porous rocks holds a brazier filled with burning tubeworm casings, a noxious stench roiling from the flames as they crackle with bizarre colors -- crimson, emerald, cobalt, and flashes of white, ombre and vermillion.  The multihued light reflects strangely on the wall of water, behind which pale, fingerlike fan corals sway in the hot waters.</description>
    <position x="200" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="siwim northwest" destination="30" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go riipplegate" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Leviathan's Rest, Blasted Plain" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Albino creatures scuttle around busily, competing for positioning atop boulders or crevices to take advantage of the sulfurous plumes of boiling hot water erupting from stacked geysers and cracks in the seafloor.  The heated fluid crashes into a wall of colder water pooling down from above and mixes chaotically in turbulent currents.  A few cautious flashes of luminescent light circle in the distance, seemingly not wanting to linger in the dangerous heat.</description>
    <position x="180" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="29" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Leviathan's Rest, Lava Sink" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The seabed suddenly drops precipitously, and churning hot water rushes upward from the cliff edge.  A wide, semi-circular hole, visible only by the menacing orange glow within, marks the otherwise inky darkness in all directions and serves as a gateway into a fiery cavern below.  Superheated water, filled with toxic gas bubbles, surges upward, the current pushing forward towards the sinkhole.  A thick colony of large, white-bodied tubeworms grow along the edge of the cliff, waving red fans into the boiling hot waters.  Sunk into the silt, an enormous spine with ribs as thick as tree trunks stretches to the east and south and is entirely covered in tiny writhing worms.</description>
    <position x="200" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Leviathan's Rest, Volcanic Valley" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The broken remains of a leviathan's skeleton lie buried in the sand and are surrounded by concentric rings of silt.  Splintered bone fragments from the vertebrae and ribs, clearly crushed by the impact of something large, litter the area.  None of the writhing worms consuming the leviathan's remains can be seen at the impact site's center, though some have begun to move inside the rings.</description>
    <position x="200" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="swim north" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Leviathan's Rest, Leviathan Skull" color="#0000FF">
    <description>An enormous leviathan's skull is partially sunk into the sediment and is bathed in the superheated toxic water bubbling up from a sinkhole.  The bones have long since been picked clean of organic material and are slowly being devoured by tiny crawling worms.  The deep red glow of nearby lava casts an eerie malevolence on the creature's skull, lighting it from within and giving it the appearance of staring out into the depths with unseeing eyes.</description>
    <position x="220" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <label text="Escarpment">
    <position x="260" y="220" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Tidal Flats">
    <position x="250" y="90" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Kelp Forest">
    <position x="90" y="90" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Abyssal Depths">
    <position x="50" y="200" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Leviathan's Rest">
    <position x="140" y="270" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="coral reef">
    <position x="170" y="290" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="deeplight fish">
    <position x="250" y="170" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="decomposing Merelew">
    <position x="270" y="180" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="deeplight fish">
    <position x="250" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="rockclaw lobster">
    <position x="250" y="120" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="deeplight fish">
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="nacre-plated Torbisan decapod">
    <position x="-10" y="110" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="deeplight fish">
    <position x="30" y="230" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="rockclaw lobster">
    <position x="20" y="240" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="nacre-plated Torbisan decapod">
    <position x="0" y="250" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="decomposing Merelew">
    <position x="10" y="260" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pool">
    <position x="130" y="170" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>