<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="The Tomiek Burrows" id="518q">
  <node id="1" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Underground Stream" note="Underground Stream|Stream">
    <description>The tunnel ends at an abrupt wall, and the ground gives way to large and fast-moving stream of water that appears from one side of the chamber and disappears deeper into complex.  The green fungus flourishes here, its glow almost blinding.  Water drips from the walls and ceilings, but the chamber shows no signs of collapse or erosion.</description>
    <position x="120" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Tunnel">
    <description>Winding lazily around a curve, the tunnel here loses its smoothness and congruity.  It seems more haphazardly excavated, but there are no signs of humanoid tools typical of mines and other underground spaces.  A subtle hum reverberates through the tunnel, although its source is elsewhere in the burrow.  Errant strands of cobwebs hang from the ceiling.</description>
    <position x="100" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Tunnel">
    <description>Phosphorescent fungus clinging to the walls casts a sickly green glow about this large oval-shaped tunnel, barely illuminating large lumps of silk that mar the otherwise smooth walls.  The occasional twitch reveals the last throes of life escaping some doomed, adventurer-sized prey encapsulated within the tightened fiber.  The smooth walls of the tunnel glisten with strands of errant silk and small pockmarks that appear at regular intervals, marking trails of creatures crawling over the face of the rock.  The air here is thick with a foul smell and stagnant from years of entombment.  The green fungus lights a crossroads, three paths splitting in different directions.</description>
    <position x="80" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="2" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Subterranean Grotto" note="Subterranean Grotto|Grotto|">
    <description>This underground cavern is illuminated by some kind of phosphorescent fungus which clings to the walls and ceilings.  Small spore-laden protrusions occasionally extend from the main masses, but the organisms resemble glowing green veins in the earth and stone.  Above, tree roots poke into the tunnel, worming through parts of the burrow, and water drips from the ceiling, dampening the walls and ground.  Threads of silk are strung from roots and stone alike, thick fresh coils interspersed with older fraying cobwebs.  Tunnels wind in several directions further into the complex.</description>
    <position x="80" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Tunnel">
    <description>This section of tunnel is remarkably straight and round, with smooth walls made of earth interspersed with veins of a black metal.  The oval shape of the tunnel makes walking slightly challenging unless one remains in the very center of the chamber.  Whatever creature or process created this tunnel churned through dirt, rock, and ore with perfect precision, leaving no trace of shoring or backfill.  The only blemish on the walls is the glowing green fungus which seems to thrive in this subterranean complex, providing ample light to marvel at the tunnel's excavation.</description>
    <position x="100" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Tunnel">
    <description>The tunnel here narrows significantly and the ceiling drops, lending the burrows a claustrophobic feel.  Several thick spiderwebs criss-cross the chamber, mildly hindering movement through the area.  Broken strands of silk, an articulated limb of black metal and disturbed earth on the ground and the walls ahead indicate that some kind of scuffle occurred, although there is no sign as to whether the melee occurred moments or years ago.</description>
    <position x="140" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Tunnel">
    <description>A barely perceptible hum fills this section, echoing from the silent darkness further down the curve of the tunnel.  The noise sounds like a complex of beehives as their inhabitants busily go about their work.  There are no signs of cobwebs here, and the tunnel is otherwise unremarkable.</description>
    <position x="140" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Funnel">
    <description>The ground suddenly drops here into a dark pit covered in cobwebs.  The silken mess resembles a whirlpool as it spirals down into the darkness.  The open cavity in the webbing -- several arm's lengths across -- could easily swallow a large horse and rider.  Flickers of motion in the darkness and the walls of the tunnel betray the movement of more than just an errant breeze.</description>
    <position x="160" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="9" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="7" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Pit" note="Pit">
    <description>A knee-high layer of organic muck, offal, bones, rusted armor and weapons, clothing, and carryalls fills this sullen pit deep within the cave complex.  You can discern several humanoids in various states of decay, as well as animals and other unidentifiable objects, long dead and rotted beyond recognition.  Far above, a massive funnel of cobwebs creates a scaffolding of sorts around the upper portions of the hole.  A dreadful stench assaults your nose, eyes, and lungs.  The miasma hangs in the air around and above you, refracting and distorting the ghastly green light from above into horrifying shapes and phantoms.</description>
    <position x="160" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Tunnel">
    <description>A faint green glow from some phosphorescent fungus on the earthen walls lights this remarkably smooth tunnel.  Growing narrower as it slopes gently downward, the tunnel is still spacious enough for a large Gor'Tog to stretch their arms and legs comfortably.  Articulated pieces of a black, chitinous metal, vaguely suggestive of limbs, lie scattered about the floor of the tunnel like unnatural skeletons.  The remains vary wildly in size, the smallest being several feet long and the largest spanning the entire length of the tunnel.  Each piece is jointed seven times and ends in a wickedly sharp point.  In spite of the green glow, shadows pool in the dark spaces before you.</description>
    <position x="80" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Underground Pool" note="Underground Pool|Pool">
    <description>A near-blinding green glow emanates from this large circular room.  Phosphorescent fungus covers nearly all of the ceiling, fully illuminating every inch of the space.  A stream of water from the far wall empties into a large pool in the center of the area.  Despite the fast-moving water, the pool is still and reflective as glass.  A noticeable humming noise pierces the silence, sporadically cycling in intensity as the source approaches and withdraws.</description>
    <position x="100" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Hatchery" note="Hatchery">
    <description>The ceiling opens here to a giant conical room.  Thousands of tiny crystals sway on the walls as if hung by cords and set upon by a gentle breeze, reflecting the green luminescence of the room's fungus.  Here is the source of the hum heard throughout the complex, a pronounced clinking noise, reminiscent of thousands of metal spoons being shaken in a drawer.  Upon closer inspection, you realize that the crystals are actually eyes, the eyes of thousands of spider hatchlings scurrying over themselves and the walls, ceiling, and floor.  Hundreds of eggs, fractured and whole, litter the floor and walls in clutches of a dozen or so.</description>
    <position x="100" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Large Chamber" note="Large Chamber|Chamber">
    <description>Spun sacks of spidersilk hang from the walls and ceiling and sit upon the floor of this large cavern.  Each sack overflows with trinkets, weapons, armor, and other adventuring necessities scattered about randomly.  Where some of the containers have spilled over or burst, additional threads of silk capture items that now dangle from their sacks like some hoarder's candelabra on a chandelier.</description>
    <position x="60" y="60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Cluttered Room" note="Cluttered Room">
    <description>Burrows and spidersilk containers hold bundles of hundreds of different materials, from leather straps and iron buckles to blades and armor plates.  Someone or something has disassembled thousands of items and tossed the parts haphazardly into the nearest containers.  The only sign of organization is a central platform made of black metal suspended from the ceiling with strong silken ropes.  Green fungus has been corralled on the ceiling around the platform, providing extra luminescence in that area.</description>
    <position x="80" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="The Tomiek Burrows, Shrine" note="Shrine">
    <description>Unlike the rest of the burrows, this room is small and angular, as if built for a humanoid rather than a spider.  A thick silk web dominates the space, only the entrance free from supporting threads.  In the center of the room a silken tapestry has been woven depicting a spider stealthily descending upon an unsuspecting dove.  Two wickedly curved tomiek blades are interwoven into the tapestry flanking the central image.  Hundreds of white stura atulave stones are suspended behind the tapestry, vibrating in the darkness.</description>
    <position x="60" y="80" z="0" />
  </node>
  <label text="Need Light -&gt;">
    <position x="-15" y="70" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="recently dug hole in the wall">
    <position x="30" y="210" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="The exit pops up in random places">
    <position x="10" y="200" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>