<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<zone name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins" id="519q">
  <node id="1" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Outer Ramp Remains" note="Zukir|Outer Ramp Remains">
    <description>Scattered granite rubble and shattered walls block all but a narrow portion of the ramp that leads to the former Keep of the Ughtensgard.  Large cracks spiderweb throughout the ramp that slants up from the ground, bypasses the first level and leads to the second level of the fortress, which is a shadow of its former self.  Much of the cobblestone that makes up the ramp is shattered, with some chunks having dropped away completely.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="2" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Outer Ramp Remains">
    <description>A large section of the wall has fallen, shattered into large chunks and leaving large obstacles to pick around on the way up the steep ramp.  Almost none of the ramparts remain, as if sundered from within by some immense force.  A massive iron and oak door lies on the ground bent and ruined, toppled downward and forming a makeshift tunnel that leads into the ruined castle.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="1" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go makeshift tunnel" destination="3" />
  </node>
  <node id="3" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Entry Hall" note="Entry Hall">
    <description>Broken strips of granite arches from the once vaulted ceiling lie on the ground, and patches of the sky are visible through massive holes in the ceiling.  Scattered pieces of worthless armor line the corridor, the best pieces long since scavenged or carried away.  Broken benches surround the ruins of a high fireplace, its chimney collapsed in on itself.</description>
    <position x="-20" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="4" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go makeshift tunnel" destination="2" />
  </node>
  <node id="4" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Great Hall" note="Great Hall">
    <description>All that remains of the once-mighty great hall is a large section of the outer wall, which is nearly fifteen feet thick and lined with perioic barrel slits.  Rubble from the ceiling litters the floor, although much of it is simply gone, dragged away by massive forces.  A broken flamewood table lies splintered on the floor, all four legs of it broken.</description>
    <position x="40" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="3" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebon-inlaid door" destination="6" />
  </node>
  <node id="5" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Long Corridor" note="Long Corridor">
    <description>Dim light filters in through massive holes in the ceiling, and treacherous cracks pepper the damp stone floor.  Empty iron sconces hang from thick bronze rings along the walls like eyeless sentinels, although several of them have been dashed to the ground by immense forces.</description>
    <position x="60" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="6" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Chapel of Meraud" note="Chapel of Meraud|Meraud">
    <description>The small chapel seems to have been spared the worst of the destruction, with only a bit of dust littering the floor.  Thick tallow candles impaled on spikes that extend from the granite walls have long burned out, though a bit of light streams in from tiny windows created by missing stones.  The altar bears no ornamentation save two crossed swords, held upright by an iron brace.</description>
    <position x="0" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ebon-inlaid door" destination="4" />
  </node>
  <node id="7" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway" note="Hallway">
    <description>Both walls have nearly completely crumbled on either side of the hall, blocking off all but a narrow passage through the least ruined portion of the hallway.  The high ceiling has also caved in, and bits of roof and tile pepper the sides of the corridor.  Traces of a ruined black and gold carpet can be seen poking through the rubble.</description>
    <position x="80" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="5" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go tunnel" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="8" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway">
    <description>Large sections of the wall have remained largely intact, although pieces of the ruined roof litter the floor.  Waterstains mar the carpet in the hallway, which stretches north from here toward an older segment of the keep while the passage south leads to what used to be the grand foyer.  The passage south is completely blocked off by a wall made from what used to be the castle roof.</description>
    <position x="80" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="9" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Broken Fountain" note="Broken Fountain|Fountain">
    <description>The eastern passage has collapsed, replaced by a of mound stone and tile.  Standing in the center of the room is the remnants of a once grand fountain, which is now bone dry.  Its top has broken off completely, having crushed one part of the rim, and a large waterstain has leaked from the broken side to the carpet below.</description>
    <position x="120" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="8" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding staircase" destination="20" />
  </node>
  <node id="10" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Receiving Area" note="Receiving Area">
    <description>Most of the polished walls are collapsed or are hanging precariously, the mosaic tile floor shattered and the pieces shifted to render its pattern unrecognizable.  A massive blast has carried the massive double doors inward, and they both lie on the floor to serve as a sort of scaffolding toward the audience chamber.  Several elegantly carved rosewood chairs sit along the wall, a few of them toppled but most remaining upright.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="11" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go cramped tunnel" destination="7" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb doors" destination="54" />
  </node>
  <node id="11" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Audience Chamber" note="Audience Chamber">
    <description>High vaulted ceilings are partially crumbled in places, with some of the timbers collapsed to the floor and the once-smooth granite blocks laying on the floor.  A long mahogany table in the center of the room is fully overturned in a way that seems deliberate and methodical.  Several smooth benches line the walls, though the ones near the table are also overturned.  A high-backed chair sits at the head of the table, defaced and ruined with weapon marks and covered with soot.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple door" destination="19" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slender panel" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="12" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway">
    <description>Large tapestries hang along the walls of the hallway, some of them missing and others burnt but a few surprisingly intact, hanging by braided ropes that loop over thick wooden pegs driven between the stones in the walls.  The hallway seems to have escaped some of the damage, only a few small piles of rubble lying here and there.  Low benches line the walls, made from carved marble.</description>
    <position x="100" y="-20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="13" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="10" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go walnut door" destination="49" />
  </node>
  <node id="13" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway">
    <description>Numerous pockmarks mar both the wall and the ceiling of the long hallway, indicating where small but powerful blasts went off.  Parts of the hallway are blocked by heaps of rubble, making the way treacherous.  Empty iron sconces line the walls, their torches long gone now.</description>
    <position x="100" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="12" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="14" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Dining Room" note="Dining Room1">
    <description>A massive oak table lies cracked down the center in the middle of the room, once commanding the center of the banquet area but now ruined and broken.  The center of the table is covered in soot, and sundered bricks from a nearby fireplace lay scattered on the once grand carpet.  Numerous ladder-backed chairs are piled up haphazardly in one corner of the room, and light patches on the walls indicate where paintings once hung.</description>
    <position x="100" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go oak door" destination="13" />
  </node>
  <node id="15" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Dining Room" note="Dining Room2">
    <description>A stone hearth seems to be the center for some sort of huge blast, only the bottom it remaining.  Simple wooden tables and chairs lie rotting and toppled, some of them broken beyond repair.  Short benches with thin, flat cushions line the stone walls, covered with soot and shattered glass from the nearby windows.</description>
    <position x="440" y="20" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="14" />
  </node>
  <node id="16" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Pantry" note="Pantry">
    <description>Tall shelves have been shaken off the shelves by some tremendous blast, and shards of glass combined with spilled spices cover the stone floor.  Sacks of flour lie ripped, covering everything with a thin film of white, and several empty baskets are overturned onto the floor, their contents long gone.  An overpowering smell of spice fills the air, combined with the smell of rotting food.</description>
    <position x="440" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="15" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="17" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Kitchen" note="Kitchen">
    <description>A scent of stale and moldy flour permeates the air, making the room decidedly unpleasant.  A huge stone hearth dominates the far wall, cracked heavily in two and covered in black soot that radiates out from where the fire used to be.  What used to be a long wooden cutting block is mostly burned away, lying on a counter that somehow manages to still remain smooth.</description>
    <position x="400" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="16" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="18" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brass door" destination="31" />
  </node>
  <node id="18" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Wash Room" note="Wash Room">
    <description>Bone-dry washtubs lie strewn all over the floor in a haphazard manner, along with numerous dipping ladles.  Several are burned and scorched, although it appears that the water inside them put out most of the flames.  A stone trough along the wall holds glistening black coal, which has long since gone cold.  Stacks of linens nearby remain bundled neatly on wooden pallets, covered in a layer of soot but remaining neat.</description>
    <position x="400" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="17" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="69" />
  </node>
  <node id="19" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Throne Room" note="Throne Room">
    <description>Ruined deep red carpet runs the length of the room, torn and blasted away in places but especially toward the steps leading to the dais.  An elegant crystal chandelier still hangs high in the vaulted ceiling, although its light has long gone out.  Tall stained glass windows have all the glass broken out, their patterns long gone.  The black marble floor is cracked in places, and a display case stands empty and its glass broken.</description>
    <position x="80" y="-80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go simple door" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="20" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Grand Staircase" note="Grand Staircase">
    <description>Broad stairways covered in waterstained velvety carpeting twine around each other, curving to meet the landing.  Shattered glass is littered everywhere, the domed ceiling nothing more than a skeletal framework of twisted metal with a few bits of glass remaining.  Pieces of the railing lie haphazardly on the steps.</description>
    <position x="140" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb winding staircase" destination="9" />
  </node>
  <node id="21" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway Remains" note="Hallway Remains">
    <description>Broken granite columns have collapsed along both sides of the hallway, the glossy semicircles crumpled and the milky marbling shattered.  A deep burgundy carpet cuts a wide swath down the center of the hallway, scrunched up and torn apart.  A door lies on the floor to the west, blasted clean off its hinges, while rubble blocks off what used to be two other doors.</description>
    <position x="140" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="20" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="22" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Rubble">
    <description>Large chunks of rubble and broken glass have rendered this room unrecognizable, although the splintered remains of a pine bed hint at it being a sleeping chamber once.  Several of the walls have caved in entirely, opening a way to the southeast.  The ceiling has caved in entirely, exposing this portion of the ruins almost completely to the elements.</description>
    <position x="100" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="21" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="23" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Rubble" note="Rubble">
    <description>Massive amounts of rubble have collapsed in from the ceiling and walls, leaving only a bit of navigable space.  The southern wall has collapsed entirely, leaving a sheer drop-off down the side of the castle.  Bits of splintered and battered furniture can be seen underneath some of the carelessly tossed stones.</description>
    <position x="140" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="24" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="22" />
  </node>
  <node id="24" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Rubble">
    <description>Few of the walls have remained intact in this room, and one pile is filled completely with rubble from the now nonexistent roof.  Sparse furnishings are crushed underneath the wreckage, including the splintered remains of a dark walnut wardrobe.  Dirty feathers litter the floor, having been scattered everywhere by a massive boulder that crushed the feather bed.</description>
    <position x="160" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="23" />
  </node>
  <node id="25" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Rubble">
    <description>Most of the north side of the room is intact, and a woven mat in the corner indicates that this was once a sleeping chamber.  A splintered rocking chair lies crushed underneath a fallen window ledge, its curved rockers lying prone on the floor like a pair of discarded shortbows.  Part of the northern wall has collapsed, leading into the next sleeping chamber.</description>
    <position x="160" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="26" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="24" />
  </node>
  <node id="26" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Sleeping Chamber" note="Sleeping Chamber">
    <description>Scattered and broken furniture lies about the floor, and a huge chunk of the wall is missing, exposing the once enclosed room to the outside air.  A low pallet lies underneath a scattering of broken glass, marking what was once a window in the side of the keep.  Rubble and debris is built up in the corners of the room, made of both wood and stone.</description>
    <position x="160" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="25" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go ironwood door" destination="27" />
  </node>
  <node id="27" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway">
    <description>A violent shift in the castle's foundation has left the hallway tilted at nearly a thirty-degree angle, making passage rather treacherous.  Most of the fluted granite columns lie broken and in sections, their ornamental long gone now.  A deep burgundy carpet lies bunched up against the western wall, leaving the bare marble flooring exposed.</description>
    <position x="160" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="26" />
  </node>
  <node id="28" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Prince's Chamber" note="Prince's Chamber">
    <description>Most of the southern wall of the chamber is gone, blasted apart into rubble.  What used to be a cherry four-poster bed lies broken in the center of the room.  A tall cherry wardrobe remains surprisingly intact, its sturdy bulk having weathered the chaos.  Shattered glass marks where a door once led to a balcony to the east.</description>
    <position x="160" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="29" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="27" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow crawlspace" destination="30" />
  </node>
  <node id="29" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Balcony Remains" note="Balcony Remains">
    <description>Although much of the balcony has been covered with rubble from the walls above, enough space remains to safely stand on the wide balcony, which offers a scenic view of the forested hills below.  Cracked railings line the platform's edge, and a torn canvas lies draped over them.  Most of the wall to the west is gone, and shattered glass is scattered across the floor.</description>
    <position x="420" y="40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="28" />
  </node>
  <node id="30" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Narrow Passage" note="Narrow Passage">
    <description>Lit only by the faint light that leaks through a crack in the wall, the cramped passageway leads up some dark, slick steps.  The air is thick and musty, and cobwebs hang from the low ceiling, floating hauntingly in the stillness.</description>
    <position x="160" y="-40" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="28" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go slender panel" destination="11" />
  </node>
  <node id="31" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway">
    <description>Black soot stains mar the dark stone walls and head-sized stones are missing in places, some of them lying haphazardly on the floor.  A small room sits at one end of this passage, although most of it is blocked by yet more rubble.  Most of the flagstones that make up the floor are broken, especially those that have been subjected to falling rocks.</description>
    <position x="340" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southwest" move="southwest" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go brass door" destination="17" />
  </node>
  <node id="32" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Grand Foyer" note="Grand Foyer|Foyer">
    <description>Numerous massive timbers have fallen from the vaulted ceiling and lie scattered about the grand foyer in broken splinters.  Polished granite stones are shaken to their core, leaving huge holes in the walls and ruining the carpet, which is burned in places and water damaged in others.  Brass wall sconces lie dormant, their fires long extinguished and perhaps the source of the carpet's ruin.</description>
    <position x="320" y="360" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northeast" move="northeast" destination="31" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="33" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="northwest" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="33" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Entry Stair" note="Entry Stair">
    <description>Thick limestone balustrades lie broken on both sides of the stairway, which curves inward as the steps becomes narrower at the peak.  Enormous walnut doors that span the width of the stairway lie splintered and useless beneath the ornately carved keystone, completely blocking any exit from the front of the Keep.  Slender windows with pointed arches are shattered, leaving broken glass everywhere.</description>
    <position x="320" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="32" />
  </node>
  <node id="34" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Hallway">
    <description>A thin crimson floor runner is bunched up against the wall, the wide hallway partially filled with mounds of rubble from the ceiling.  Part of the northern wall is also collapsed, although not quite enough to block passage.  Shards of glass cover the floor where windows were simply blown away.</description>
    <position x="300" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="southeast" destination="32" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="35" />
  </node>
  <node id="35" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Library" note="Library">
    <description>A large portion of the expansive room's ceiling has collapsed in on itself, the stone piled up in the southwest corner and covering most of the windows.  Deep blue carpet is marred by burn spots in some places and water stains in others, and nearly all the bookshelves are toppled down, the books either gone or ruined by inclement weather.  A single claw-foot chair remains undamaged, with a low table resting nearby.</description>
    <position x="280" y="340" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="36" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="34" />
  </node>
  <node id="36" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Study" note="Study">
    <description>Very little remains of the Prince's study, its contents destroyed in a massive blast.  Even the carpet has burned away, leaving a cracked and spiderwebbed pattern on the bare floor, and whatever furniture used to be housed here is long gone.  Whatever wrath was subjected on the room was very complete with its annihilation.</description>
    <position x="280" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="35" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go massive hole" destination="37" />
  </node>
  <node id="37" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Armory" note="Armory">
    <description>The walls here are lined with burlap, most of it torn and some of it burned.  Covering the floor is a thin layer of straw and sawdust, most of it having molded over.  Boxes for weapons are stacked haphazardly along the walls with markings and numbers burned into the side panels.  Most of them are broken open, their contents having been pilfered long ago.</description>
    <position x="280" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go massive hole" destination="36" />
  </node>
  <node id="38" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Damp Corridor" note="Damp Corridor">
    <description>The chamber here lies at the end of a corridor, and is almost circular, with scorch marks radiating out from the north.  Water drips from the summit of the roof, and moss and lichen cling to the walls and the floor, making the path treacherously slippery.  Muddy boot prints are trampled through the floor, most of them looking quite old.</description>
    <position x="240" y="300" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="37" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble door" destination="51" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go high arch" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="39" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Blasted Corridor">
    <description>The thick stone walls have crumbled in places, but remain rather sturdy despite the repeated blasts to them.  Everything is covered in a thin layer of grimy soot, concentrated more toward the north.  Bits of debris lay scattered on the corridor floor, most of them parts of the wall or ceiling.</description>
    <position x="240" y="280" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="40" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Blasted Corridor" note="Blasted Corridor">
    <description>An enormous crater in the walls, ceiling, and floor of this end of the corridor incidates where an enormous blast went off, blackening the walls and shattering the stone walls.  Spiderwebbing cracks sprawl out from every crater, revealing deep rusty orange bands in the square-cut blocks of stone.  An open stairway spirals downward, the top stair missing but still easily navigable.</description>
    <position x="240" y="260" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="39" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="41" />
  </node>
  <node id="41" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Twisting Stair" note="Twisting Stair1">
    <description>Empty iron sconces still cling precariously to the walls, blackened by soot from an immense blast from the corridor above.  A large chunk of the ceiling has fallen in, allowing just barely enough light to see by.  Each step is a wedge of thick granite, strong enough to weather most of the assault's blasts.  The severe curve of the stairway and meager lighting combine to hamper visibility, making this an ideal spot for an ambush.</description>
    <position x="260" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="40" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="42" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Twisting Stair" note="Twisting Stair2">
    <description>Runnels of stale, sooty water follow the curve of the stairway as it spirals downward, trickling audibly from step to step and slicking the stone surfaces.  Dead torches lie dormant in their sconces, although sooty black stains still remain above them.  The severe curve of the stairway and meager lighting from further up combine to hamper the visible area, making this an ideal spot for an ambush.</description>
    <position x="220" y="240" z="0" />
    <arc exit="up" move="up" destination="41" />
    <arc exit="down" move="down" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="43" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Guard Post" note="Guard Post">
    <description>Cheerlessly devoid of any ornamentation or decoration, the squarish chamber is built for function rather than comfort, and has been mostly spared any destruction.  The low ceiling of lightly glowing lichen-covered stone presses down with weight of the ruined Keep above, and rotten piles of what used to be hay are swept into the corners.  A dusty rough-hewn table and a pair of blocky chairs are the only furnishings in the room, and an open stairway leads up into darkness.</description>
    <position x="220" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="44" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb stairway" destination="42" />
  </node>
  <node id="44" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Guard Barracks" note="Guard Barracks">
    <description>Hanging from thick wooden pegs driven between heavy stones of the walls, long shelves line the barracks from end to end, though they have mostly been picked clean by looters.  Unmade cots with rotted straw mattresses and pillows form rows to either side of the room, leaving a wide walking area in the center.  A wide weapons cabinet on the far wall is smashed open, its contents pillaged.</description>
    <position x="200" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="43" />
  </node>
  <node id="45" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Hallway">
    <description>Faint light leaks through the slatted grille of a heavy wooden door, mainly coming from lightly glowing red lichen that covers damp stone ceiling and disappear into the surrounding darkness.  Narrow runnels of murky water trickle through the area, echoing hollowly through the stone and steel corridor.</description>
    <position x="240" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="43" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="55" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="56" />
  </node>
  <node id="46" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Hallway">
    <description>Narrow runnels of murky water trickle through the area, echoing hollowly through the stone and steel corridor.  Very little light remains in this area, coming mainly from slightly glowing red lichen that seems to have infested the corridor, perhaps from the sewers below.  A fine layer of soot covers everything.</description>
    <position x="240" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="north" move="north" destination="47" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="45" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="57" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="58" />
  </node>
  <node id="47" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Hallway">
    <description>Faint light leaks through the slatted grille of a heavy wooden door, mainly coming from lightly glowing red lichen that covers damp stone ceiling and disappear into the surrounding darkness.  Narrow runnels of murky water trickle through the area, leading into a rusted grate thickly covered in glowing red lichen.  The smell of must and mold covers everything.</description>
    <position x="240" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="south" destination="46" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="48" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go iron door" destination="59" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go steel door" destination="60" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rusted grate" destination="66" />
  </node>
  <node id="48" name="Old Sewers, Dimly Lit Passage" note="Old Sewers|Sewers" color="#0000FF">
    <description>The intermittent sound of thrumming echoes down the passage as water moving swiftly east slices between the bars of a massive steel gate.  The collision of water sends a spray of clammy mist into the air, soaking the walls with dirty muck and assaulting the nostrils with a foul smelling fog.</description>
    <position x="260" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="south" move="swim south" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb ladder" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="49" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Ballroom" note="Ballroom">
    <description>Glass and pieces of crystal are scattered all over the floor, with the occasional burned-out tallow candle visible through the razor-sharp shards.  Darkly stained hardwood makes up the floor, though the western half of the room is collapsed and impossible to nagivate.  A large missing space in the middle indicates where a crest of Tirof-Sorvendig once laid, now missing.  A tiered platform makes a makeshift orchestra stand that is partially covered with muck.</description>
    <position x="120" y="0" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go eastern doors" destination="12" />
  </node>
  <node id="50" name="Supply Wagon, Cache" color="#FF0000">
    <description>Stacked neatly around the walls are sets of treasures sorted into tidy piles.  Each mound is placed under a sign hanging from the ceiling identifying its contents.  Further baskets, coffers, and crates litter the ground, identically labeled with precise care.</description>
    <position x="180" y="-120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="painted door" />
  </node>
  <node id="51" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Larder" note="Larder">
    <description>This white marble room is cool and surprisingly dry, having been overlooked in the Keep's destruction.  Barrels and kegs are piled up in corners, hogsheads of grain and flour are stacked on wooden pallets, and crocks of preserved fruits and vegetables line sturdy shelves.  From the ceiling rafters are slung rashers of bacon, smoked partridges and geese, links of sausage and haunches of mutton and beef.</description>
    <position x="220" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go marble door" destination="38" />
  </node>
  <node id="52" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Arched Chamber" note="Arched Chamber">
    <description>The room is poorly lit, and the debris scattered over the floor seems unrelated to the destruction above.  Overall disrepair and neglect reign in this chamber, and small alcoves are packed with forgotten supplies.  The dissassembled remains of a decrepit catapult lie in one corner, with cobweb-covered balls of iron surrounding it.</description>
    <position x="240" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="38" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trapdoor" destination="53" />
  </node>
  <node id="53" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Catacombs" note="Catacombs">
    <description>Row after row of long, narrow niches are carved deep into the granite foundations of the Keep.  Each niche holds the mummified body of a long-dead hero, perfectly preserved in the dry air.  The catacombs are undisturbed and eerily silent, seeming to have escaped the destruction that befell the rest of the Keep.</description>
    <position x="260" y="320" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go trapdoor" destination="52" />
  </node>
  <node id="54" name="Throne Room, Seating Area" note="Seating Area">
    <description>Plush velvet cushions lie scattered all over the floor, tossed and strewn about from the splintered mahogany benches.  Water damage has leaked into the burgundy carpet, marring the gladioluses that are worked in silver thread.  The broken throne is clearly visible from the seating area, having suffered heavy damage.</description>
    <position x="60" y="-60" z="0" />
    <arc exit="out" move="out" destination="10" />
  </node>
  <node id="55" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Cell">
    <description>Crumbled bits of mortar litter the floor of the cramped cell, fallen from between the massive blocks of stone that form the damp prison.  Scratch marks and red-brown stains cover the faces of the giant slabs where iron shackles are fastened securely to the walls.</description>
    <position x="260" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="56" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Cell">
    <description>Crumbled bits of mortar litter the floor of the cramped cell, fallen from between the massive blocks of stone that form the damp prison.  Scratch marks and red-brown stains cover the faces of the giant slabs where iron shackles are fastened securely to the walls.</description>
    <position x="260" y="220" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="45" />
  </node>
  <node id="57" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Cell">
    <description>Crumbled bits of mortar litter the floor of the cramped cell, fallen from between the massive blocks of stone that form the damp prison.  Scratch marks and red-brown stains cover the faces of the giant slabs where iron shackles are fastened securely to the walls.</description>
    <position x="220" y="180" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="58" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Cell">
    <description>Crumbled bits of mortar litter the floor of the cramped cell, fallen from between the massive blocks of stone that form the damp prison.  Scratch marks and red-brown stains cover the faces of the giant slabs where iron shackles are fastened securely to the walls.</description>
    <position x="220" y="200" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="46" />
  </node>
  <node id="59" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Cell">
    <description>Crumbled bits of mortar litter the floor of the cramped cell, fallen from between the massive blocks of stone that form the damp prison.  Scratch marks and red-brown stains cover the faces of the giant slabs where iron shackles are fastened securely to the walls.</description>
    <position x="220" y="160" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="60" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Cell">
    <description>Crumbled bits of mortar litter the floor of the cramped cell, fallen from between the massive blocks of stone that form the damp prison.  Scratch marks and red-brown stains cover the faces of the giant slabs where iron shackles are fastened securely to the walls.</description>
    <position x="220" y="140" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go door" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="61" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Questioning Chamber" note="Questioning Chamber">
    <description>Dark, ruddy stains coating the walls and floor can be seen behind the collection of strange, twisted metal devices hung inside the chamber.  A wheeled cart, covered by a sodden blanket, bears an array of rusted instruments, and despite the muck and decay clinging to each one, they look extraordinarily sharp.  The tangy smell of blood lingers in the dank air.</description>
    <position x="240" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="63" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go wooden door" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="62" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Above Pit" note="Above Pit">
    <description>Glowing red lichen sends a harsh glow over the circular chamber, illuminating the soot that still covers the stone floor.  The odor of decay drifts from a wide, gaping cavity that consumes the center of the room and drops away into the depths of the Keep's foundation.  Driven into the bedrock near the edge of the precipice, a heavy steel bar anchors a length of braided vine rope that trails into the pit.</description>
    <position x="260" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="west" move="west" destination="61" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb braided rope" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="63" name="Ulf'Hara Dunegon, Machine Room" note="Machine Room">
    <description>Heavy timbers angle along the walls and across the ceiling, supporting the weight of the ruined Keep above.  A collection of rusted gears and pullies clutter the perimeter of the squarish chamber, encircling a massive winch that squats darkly in the center of the room.  Thick cables run over the top of the winch, nestled within the groove of a large wheel, and disappear into holes bored into the floor.</description>
    <position x="220" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="east" destination="61" />
  </node>
  <node id="64" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Deep Pit" note="Deep Pit">
    <description>Bone fragments and skeletal animal remains litter the jagged sections of broken rock that jut forth from the bottom of the chasm.  Faint torchlight leaks into the depths of the pit from high above, reflecting dimly against the wet-slicked walls that stretch upward to dizzying heights.  Meandering rivulets of ground water trickle through piles of loose stone and disappear into a long depression in the floor.</description>
    <position x="260" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="climb" move="climb braided rope" destination="62" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go portcullis" destination="65" />
  </node>
  <node id="65" name="Ulf'Hara Dungeon, Moradu's Lair" note="Moradu's Lair">
    <description>Carved from the very rock of the Keep's foundation, reddish-brown stains cover the walls and floor of the hollow chamber.  Burning logs jammed into cracks in the jagged stone faces throw wavering light across the expanse of the area, illuminating a large nest of splintered trees, saplings, and bark that occupies the side of the room directly across from a solid portullis.</description>
    <position x="280" y="80" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go portcullis" destination="64" />
  </node>
  <node id="66" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Drain Pipe" note="Drain Pipe" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thick layers of muck and slime coat the walls of this stone drain pipe, which carries putrid dark waste water away from the Keep.</description>
    <position x="220" y="120" z="0" />
    <arc exit="northwest" move="swim northwest" destination="67" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go rusted grate" destination="47" />
  </node>
  <node id="67" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Drain Pipe" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thick layers of muck and slime coat the walls of this stone drain pipe, which carries putrid, dark waste-water away from the Keep.</description>
    <position x="200" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="southeast" move="swim southeast" destination="66" />
    <arc exit="west" move="swim west" destination="68" />
  </node>
  <node id="68" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Drain Pipe" color="#0000FF">
    <description>Thick layers of muck and slime coat the walls of this stone drain pipe, which carries putrid, dark waste-water away from the Keep.  Dim light filters through a filth-covered opening at the end of the tunnel.</description>
    <position x="180" y="100" z="0" />
    <arc exit="east" move="swim east" destination="67" />
  </node>
  <node id="69" name="Ulf'Hara Keep Ruins, Stone Well">
    <description>A well-worn path from the wash room door leads to a functional stone well.  Spared from the blasts mostly by its unimportance, the small room housing the well is otherwise bare, its walls made from fully intact stone.  Thin tendrils of vines grow around the well's base while the protective peaked roof remains unmolested.</description>
    <position x="400" y="380" z="0" />
    <arc exit="go" move="go narrow door" destination="18" />
  </node>
  <label text="Old Sewers">
    <position x="264" y="133" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Kitchen">
    <position x="380" y="320" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Chapel of Meraud">
    <position x="-40" y="50" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="prize room">
    <position x="154" y="-140" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Zukir">
    <position x="-16" y="-147" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Ballroom">
    <position x="114" y="-20" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Fountain">
    <position x="94" y="281" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Armory">
    <position x="284" y="293" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Study">
    <position x="283" y="312" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Library">
    <position x="239" y="333" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Foyer">
    <position x="284" y="352" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Barracks">
    <position x="169" y="200" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Pantry">
    <position x="422" y="345" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Wash Room">
    <position x="366" y="365" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dining Room">
    <position x="384" y="-1" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Prince's Chamber">
    <position x="160" y="45" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Balcony Remains">
    <position x="354" y="44" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Throne Room">
    <position x="43" y="-98" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Audience Chamber">
    <position x="83" y="-73" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Receiving">
    <position x="22" y="-48" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Sleeping">
    <position x="163" y="291" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Larder">
    <position x="180" y="312" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Entry Stair">
    <position x="293" y="384" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Rubble">
    <position x="117" y="327" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Moradu's Lair">
    <position x="283" y="72" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Drain Pipe">
    <position x="160" y="107" z="0" />
  </label>
  <label text="Dungeon and cells">
    <position x="244" y="169" z="0" />
  </label>
</zone>